<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368936905023-1</Id><Title>The President's Umbrella Scandal Folded Before It Could Take Off/STINKING ROTTEN REPUBS complaining about this</Title><Msg>Palin said some garbage and she's had umbrellas held for her,,,Lou Dobbs made it an issue too...whata piece of corpiss dabien he is too. You suck repubs!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368936905023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 00:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368937491870-2</Id><Title>not long ago glenn beck and other teagags were preaching the evils of paper money((((TEAGAGS?? I like it.</Title><Msg>Now one of these stinking reubs here is givng Beck a break saying he was just doing an ad. I once saw one of those ads. It was more like he was preaching the end of theworld and w/o buying gold you'd be like corpiss or something. And, that other deeekhad here saying "you can't fight the fed" meaning Beck would have been right had it not been for fed helping economy out.............that's the POINT! You p's of garbage said the fed wuld CAUSE the disaster to happen and/or couldn't stop it!!! Now repubs are saying the fed is what caused gold to drop? AS ALWAYS,, you're full of coripis dabien. Repubs ya got nuthin and are wrong about everything. BTW, we've some gold still...oh yeah and I tink I read here runners saying gold price is very manipulated....I'm quite sure I've also read runners telling people they should own it! Did beck pos also sell othr JUNK, I tink so.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368937491870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 00:24:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368937552096-3</Id><Title>repubs are proud of their Becks</Title><Msg>Just more proof that you all are completeskum of earth</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368937552096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 00:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368937748166-4</Id><Title>The NAACP has tax exempt status and have they ever been scrutinized for legitimacy?</Title><Msg>Oh shut up. Did they just apply 2 years ago as the number of new HATE organizations doubled? NO! That was repub hate groups! I'm GLAD they looked over the HATE groups ofherepubs and I hope they caught some breaking the laws. I hope they did't give tax free status to some.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368937748166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 00:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368937955769-5</Id><Title>Just heard from a lady who had to spend hundreds of thousands of dollars because of their belief in the first amendment.</Title><Msg>WHAT???????????????// Repubs are SUCH garbage! They'e all Nazis when a repub is in office and defend their Naziism but when a dem is in pffice they spew about what's right and whats wrong,..when their skum in office ANYTHING GOES!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368937955769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 00:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368938091247-6</Id><Title>The NAACP has tax exempt status and have they ever been scrutinized for legitimacy</Title><Msg>Ya think there's no need for naacp??? Think again...because of repubs they're VERY important. You skms believe slavery wasn't bad! You've said it here and ya hate naacp... you're 100$ skum.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368938091247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 00:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368938159877-7</Id><Topic><Title>The NAACP has tax exempt status and have they ever been scrutinized for legitimacy</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368938091247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 00:34:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah black orgs have had such a free ride in past several humdred years and govt sure picked on the clan!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368938159877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 00:35:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368964711635-8</Id><Topic><Title>The NAACP has tax exempt status and have they ever been scrutinized for legitimacy</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368938091247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 00:34:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>drop, your attitude is pervasive. Race relations will never improve as long as that attitude is front and center. A question: What in your opinion would it take to make up for the past in terms of racial equality? And if your answer is nothing humanly possible that can make up for the past, what is it that you would want?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368964711635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 07:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368968291901-9</Id><Title>the real scandal at the IRS: special tax breaks for the super rich</Title><Msg>The real scandal is that: The IRS has interpreted our tax laws to allow big corporations and wealthy individuals to make unlimited secret campaign donations through sham political fronts called “social welfare organizations,” like Karl Rove’s “Crossroads,” the U.S. Chamber of Commerce, and “Priorites USA.” This campaign money has been used to bribe Congress to keep in place tax loopholes like the “carried interest” rule that allows the managers of hedge funds and private equity funds to treat their income as capital gains, subject only to low capital gains taxes rather than ordinary income taxes, and other loopholes that allow CEOs to get special tax treatment on giant compensation packages that now average $10 million a year. Robert Reich</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368968291901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:58:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368968983902-10</Id><Title>re Detroit</Title><Msg>I agree with Louis Farrakhan. Blacks gotta do it themselves. Nation of Islam leader Louis Farrakhan urged Detroit’s pastors and majority black population Friday to join him in an effort to buy neglected properties and take other steps to help revitalize the struggling city where the movement started more than 80 years ago .</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368968983902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368969061225-11</Id><Title>Hi, I'm Josh Jalinski, Yer Financial Quarterback!</Title><Msg>Give me One hundred thousand dollars and I will give you a quarter back!</Msg><Username>g00dguyoooooooo1</Username><Timestamp>1368969061225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368969097587-12</Id><Topic><Title>the real scandal at the IRS: special tax breaks for the super rich</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368968291901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the IRS is to blame. Congress writes and passes the laws. I thought you knew that. Apparently not.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368969097587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368969118940-13</Id><Title>Whatever happened to the purple Russian?</Title><Msg>Karl the Grape!</Msg><Username>g00dguyoooooooo1</Username><Timestamp>1368969118940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368969184559-14</Id><Topic><Title>the real scandal at the IRS: special tax breaks for the super rich</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368968291901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON – There's an irony in the Internal Revenue Service's crackdown on conservative groups. The nation's tax agency has admitted to inappropriately scrutinizing smaller tea party organizations that applied for tax-exempt status, and senior Treasury Department officials were notified in the midst of the 2012 presidential election season that an internal investigation was underway. But the IRS largely maintained a hands-off policy with the much larger, big-budget organizations on the left and right that were most influential in the elections and are organized under a section of the tax code that allows them to hide their donors. "The IRS goes AWOL when wealthy and powerful forces want to break the law in order to hide their wrongful efforts and secret political influence," said Rhode Island Sen. Sheldon Whitehouse, a Democrat who is among a small Senate group pushing campaign finance reform measures that would force these big outside groups to disclose their donors. "Picking on the little guy is a pretty lousy thing to do."</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1368969184559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368969232916-15</Id><Topic><Title>the real scandal at the IRS: special tax breaks for the super rich</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368968291901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The rea; scamdal is why don't we send delucks back to whatever mussy wuzzy country he came from. He can hate us from there, rather than on welfare and food stamps from here.</Msg><Username>g00dguyoooooooo1</Username><Timestamp>1368969232916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368969356594-16</Id><Topic><Title>the real scandal at the IRS: special tax breaks for the super rich</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368968291901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop and teagags in congress ARE the ones whining about the LAW that REQUIRES pacs to PROVE that at least 50% of their activities are NON political if they want tax exemption.............and the gop are the ones fighting to keep the special tax loopholes for the super rich, such as the "carried interest" loophole.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368969356594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368969449569-17</Id><Topic><Title>gop "irs" ""scandal"" FIZZLES out as wet BS just like their other trumped up "scandals"</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368896614405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 13:03:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so far no one has identified a single conservative group that was denied status in the controversial review, though some faced bureaucratic hurdles and had their tax-exempt status delayed. In fact, the only known 501(c)(4) applicant to have its status denied happens to be a progressive group: the Maine chapter of Emerge America, which trains Democratic women to run for office.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368969449569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368970875022-18</Id><Topic><Title>the real scandal at the IRS: special tax breaks for the super rich</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368968291901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you want to ensure tax equality there is a way to do it. Fair tax or flat tax, whatever you want to call it. I'm all for it. How 'bout you, Mesa?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368970875022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368971009115-19</Id><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Msg>Numerous recent incidences of such. What you make of that?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368972474751-20</Id><Title>IRS scandal likely to effect other agencies</Title><Msg>so says Senator Corker. One can only hope. I can think of 1 or 2 agencies that bully. The fallout from the Internal Revenue Service targeting scandal is going to be felt in many other federal agencies and programs, including Obamacare and immigration reform, Tennessee Sen. Bob Corker says.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368972474751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 10:07:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368973187237-21</Id><Title>whare was O?</Title><Msg>it's an offensive question to some. Host Chris Wallace reminds Pfeiffer that Obama didn't really talk with Secretary Clinton, Secretary Panetta, or Martin Dempsey, chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, that night. "He was talking to his national security staff," Pfeiffer insists. Asked about whether the president entered the Situation Room, Pfeiffer says, "I don't remember what room the president was in on that night, and that's a largely irrelevant fact." Pfeiffer then argues that Wallace's questions about the president's handling of the Benghazi terror attack are "offensive." ...................................................... many think that Benghazi is the O's greatest problem. IRS and AP phone recording is just noise for distraction.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368973187237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 10:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368975696315-22</Id><Topic><Title>gop "irs" ""scandal"" FIZZLES out as wet BS just like their other trumped up "scandals"</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368896614405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 13:03:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON – White House senior adviser Dan Pfeiffer told said on Sunday" that President Obama learned about the Internal Revenue Service targeting Tea Party groups applying for tax-exempt status and the AP scandal only after it had come out in the media. He had no involvement.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1368975696315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 11:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368975797985-23</Id><Topic><Title>gop "irs" ""scandal"" FIZZLES out as wet BS just like their other trumped up "scandals"</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368896614405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 13:03:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pfeiffer: On the IRS, 'the law is irrelevant'</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1368975797985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 11:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368977700715-24</Id><Title>the facts suggest a relatively well meaning misstep by the IRS</Title><Msg>IRS overview . No question the IRS engaged in profiling which we all know conservatives oppose in all its ugly forms. Jokes aside, the facts suggest a relatively well meaning misstep by the IRS . IRS is brutally understaffed due to GOP congressional denials of funds for additional agents needed to collect the unpaid taxes legitimately owed by Americans , estimated at $385 billion yearly in 2006. BTW-estimates are that every enforcement agent hired will return 8-10X his salary in legitimately owed taxes to the Treasury for those really worried about fairness and deficits. Citizens United triggered a bi-partisan, 4X increase in requests for tax exempt status. No secret that many political groups on both sides would attempt to portray themselves as apolitical to avoid taxes. Some harried IRS employees mistakenly decided to make their life easier by profiling groups with the blatantly political "tea party" in their names. Not illogical,examples exist it worked in many cases but CLEARLY wrong ethically. Those directly responsible should be canned , some already have been and more inquiries are being made. To date, no evidence I've seen indicates the policy was initiated by anyone in the White House. SCOTUS and the GOP congress are not guilt free here either</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368977700715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 11:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368978442100-25</Id><Title>Obama gaining in popularity (ha ha ha ha, loser pubs have egg on their face)</Title><Msg>SUN MAY 19, 2013 AT 06:31 AM PDT CNN Confirms Gallup's Poll: The Obama Bounce Continues Well, CNN confirms the bounce Gallup found in yesterday's tracking. Check out this breaking poll from CNN: 1. 53% of Americans say they approve of the job the president is doing, with 45% saying they disapprove. The president's approval rating was at 51% in CNN's last poll, which was conducted in early April. 2. 70% say at the targeting by the Internal Revenue Service of tea party and other conservative groups that were applying for tax exempt status was unacceptable. 3. But 60/35 say that O’s statements about the IRS scandal are completely or mostly true 4. 55% say that IRS acted on its own, with 37% saying that White House ordered the IRS to target tea party and other conservative groups</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368978442100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 11:47:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368981260936-26</Id><Topic><Title>the facts suggest a relatively well meaning misstep by the IRS</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368977700715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 11:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Asking people what they pray about is a "well meaning misstep?" You're a total shill and fool for these so called "liberals." Many other absurd questions and requests for info. A tactic they have pulled for years is to send a postcard stating "You owe X amount of money with no reason being given. Plus, postman and others can read it. Many are so afraid they automatically send the money. I've received two of these over the years. Both times my CPA sent a letter asking them to tell him his mistake. In a few weeks I would get another card saying; "Forget about it, it's OK." They do this on a regular basis hoping intimidated people will pay. This has gone on with BOTH Dems and Reps.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1368981260936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368982110963-27</Id><Topic><Title>the real scandal at the IRS: special tax breaks for the super rich</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368968291901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee, wonder why you fail to mention such as the Kennedys, the Rottenfellers and many others such as John Kerry? There is an interesting and fair tax system in the Old Testament. It averages out at about 13% of "increase". It exempts a basic living. I can't find all the other endless taxes mentioned in scripture. Only a small part of that "tithe" went to the temple. Most of the Levites were actually civil servants and not priests.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1368982110963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:48:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368982477172-28</Id><Topic><Title>the facts suggest a relatively well meaning misstep by the IRS</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368977700715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 11:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing but lies from you</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368982477172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368982754127-29</Id><Title>teagags can't admit they were wrong about "weimar republic" paper money</Title><Msg>their stampede to trade good gold for evil fed controlled worthless paper money proves what BSers and hyocrites they are. I Now it seems the dollar doom sayers can't get enough of the rising dollar, and gold is in a free fall from the heights inspired by the spittle and fake tears lathered fear pumped horse manure of glenn beck and other shills for gold</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368982754127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368983359911-30</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lewcor, lewcor...you really need to get a grip on your pedophilic fantasy life. So you had multiple big black teens on your back, and you used to like to lurk around in the showers until they were all soaped up and "deck" them. Does Marjorie know about your secret gay life?</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1368983359911</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 13:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368983543694-31</Id><Title>why do conservatives want to hide who makes political donations?</Title><Msg>"...About 85 percent of the money that was spent by nonprofits in the 2012 cycle, as reported to the FEC, was paid out by conservative groups. These groups, unlike the more commonly known super PACs, are not required to divulge the names of their donors, and much of their spending is unreported, too. Their annual tax filings with the IRS list how much money they have, who their officers are and the recipients of any grants they may have made. But when they spend their money directly in support of or opposition to a candidate, they must report to the Federal Election Commission......."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368983543694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 13:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368984107859-32</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Numerous recent incidences "............... I doubt that you can cite even ONE such recent incident. and if you are talking history... what do you make of the hundreds incidents of white mobs lynching blacks or the white terrorists who in 1963 bombed a black church killing women and children?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368984107859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 13:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368984280748-33</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coach Sandusky, is that you?</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1368984280748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 13:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368986198395-34</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We can start with last night here in Chicago</Msg><Username>gr8d84f8</Username><Timestamp>1368986198395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 13:56:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368986377193-35</Id><Title>Wimpy delucks also forgot to mention unions, Move On, et.,........</Title><Msg>Of course, he can only see as far as his dogma allows, which is limited to his closed mind.</Msg><Username>cockedlockedtorock</Username><Timestamp>1368986377193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 13:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368986542153-36</Id><Title>If by "well meaning misstep" wimpy means a fascist attack on Americans, than I agree.</Title><Msg>The Dems and Obama used the IRS as a hammer against fellow Americans with a different point of view. Nothing innocent, nothing well itentioned, no "customer service" about it. I watched the hearings and in my opinion the IRS guy was lyng like a dog on a cheap rug.</Msg><Username>cockedlockedtorock</Username><Timestamp>1368986542153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368987814738-37</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blacks being black. It is their culture. They are naturally lazy criminals. The main problem is the content of their character.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1368987814738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368988015528-38</Id><Topic><Title>the real scandal at the IRS: special tax breaks for the super rich</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368968291901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is bought and paid for by Wall Street. Dems lose again.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1368988015528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:26:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368988115086-39</Id><Title>Rs are making money as the DOW hits new highs.</Title><Msg>Dems lose again. Most Dems still live in ghettos. How is that hope and change working?</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1368988115086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368989685298-40</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this one" "White men and boys formed hate groups. Armed with brass knuckles, guns, and clubs, they raided black neighborhoods, beating and sometimes killing blacks. A crowd gathers at the Twenty-ninth Street Beach, the site of the stoning and subsequent drowning of Eugene Williams. The incident touched off the Chicago Race Riot. On this stifling hot summer Sunday, Eugene Williams, a black teenager, drifted south of that line while swimming with friends. Whites picked up rocks and let fly. Some accounts say Williams was hit on the head and went under. Others say he became tired and was too afraid to come ashore. Either way, he drowned, touching off the deadliest episode of racial violence in Chicago history. For five days it raged, mostly on the South Side. White mobs attacked isolated blacks. Blacks attacked isolated whites. John Mills, a black Stockyards worker, was riding home when a mob stopped his streetcar and beat him to death. "</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368989685298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368992644988-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama,</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1368980842700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you getting to any good gun shows in Phoenix lew..(??) THe ones I go to in VA are a lot of fun..(!!)</Msg><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1368992644988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 15:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368993887843-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gaining in popularity (ha ha ha ha, loser pubs have egg on their face)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368978442100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 11:47:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No egg on face...........see infinite stupidity on bounce.........</Msg><Username>fdiebold</Username><Timestamp>1368993887843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 16:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368996138363-43</Id><Topic><Title>teagags can't admit they were wrong about "weimar republic" paper money</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368982754127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:59:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are you going on about? Price of gold is down right now. If you bought gold over last ten years, (as say Glenn Beck recommended) you would still be well profitable on your whole portfolio. Price back in 2003: About $350 per ounce Price high: mid-2011 about $1900 per ounce. Price May-17-2013 about $1360 per ounce. Math I use says if I bought at $350 and sold at $1360 I would have a profit of $1010 or about 388.6%.</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1368996138363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 16:42:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368996447741-44</Id><Topic><Title>teagags can't admit they were wrong about "weimar republic" paper money</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368982754127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:59:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you missed the teagag fear pumping about the doomed and worthless "Weimar republic" US paper money manipulated by the evil fed............ and ntm pumping buying gold when it was $1800 headed for $5K the pumpers pumped...... ha ha ha......... now they can't wait to dump their gold for the "worthless" paper money....... ha ha ha ha ha glen beck is a liar #$%$ and hypocrite.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368996447741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 16:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368996705347-45</Id><Title>More Crock From Our Biggest Leftwing Goon</Title><Msg>The ignorance of liberals is staggering. demessy bringing up 100 yr old events again as if it relates to today. Slavery is a word blacks use to cull guilt from whites. messy, you got your civil rights enacted, you have affirmative action, your numbers are a majority on welfare and when inner cities erupt, it's blacks who do the looting. Black mobs attacking whites today is senseless violence and perpetuated by drugs and joblessness. Obama has no concern with the plight of blacks whose bitterness is taken out on whites. It was a Republican who freed the slaves from Southern Democrats. You left that out, DA. Just think if the south had won. Blacks would still be restricted from getting an education, still not allowed in white diners, and most especially. marrying white women. Would you still be a Dem today? Make a note of that the next time you bring up slavery, bro.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1368996705347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 16:51:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368997540138-46</Id><Topic><Title>More Crock From Our Biggest Leftwing Goon</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1368996705347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 16:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, and it was a republican prez cand whose family had a vacation property called camp N@@@@@head. and everyone knows that when civilrights was done all the racists southerners became republicans. and of course it is always you republicans blathering about willy Horton is coming to get you, or that Obama is a mau mau anti colonialist or what ever.......when you racists and bigots are not dressed up as re enactor waffen SS types you are wrapping yourselves in the stars and bars , the flag OF racism...</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368997540138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:05:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368997912358-47</Id><Topic><Title>teagags can't admit they were wrong about "weimar republic" paper money</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368982754127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:59:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pea Brain! The fed is still pumping trillions of USD into the economy every month on an endless "stimulus" campaign. The fact that we haven't gotten to hyperinflation yet does not mean we wont. It mearly means the price of gold is wobbling right now.</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1368997912358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:11:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368998018096-48</Id><Title>Why do IRS employees get bonuses anyway?</Title><Msg>I worked for years at jobs that never paid a bonus. Why should anti-productive government drones get a bonus?</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1368998018096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:13:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368998289827-49</Id><Topic><Title>teagags can't admit they were wrong about "weimar republic" paper money</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368982754127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 12:59:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG, yes... how stupid of you teagags to sell your safe haven gold for the "worthless" paper money that has increased in value .....................jeez, what an imbecile you are. ...... and obviously it is impossible for gold plummet, which it is, and it is impossible for the dollar to rise in value, which it is..... you know..... because of the fed "printing " money........ right? ha ha ha ha.....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368998289827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368999320435-50</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>google it Mesa and see for yourself. I'll take some time to cite a number of recent incidents. BTW, what your examples of 50 year old white on black incidents have to do with anything? Stick to the topic.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368999320435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368999755584-51</Id><Title>a few recent examples</Title><Msg>all black mob violence but necessarily balcks attacking whites. As yahoo won't allow posting links I'll need to take some time to post individually.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368999755584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 17:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369001810485-52</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>here's a very recent example just happened in Baton Rouge A white family stopping for gas in Baton Rouge, Louisiana was attacked by three men and police are not ruling out the possibility of charging hate crime white familythe assailants with a hate crime. The attack occurred on Sunday night at a local Chevron station after a man, his wife, and his daughter stopped for gas. The family was apparently attacked without cause and the attack was so brutal that it sent the husband to the hospital. There has already been a push online to charge the attackers with a hate crime for targeting the white family in a mostly black city. Cpl. Tommy Stubbs of the Baton Rouge Police Department confirmed the arrests of Donald Dickerson on suspicion of second-degree battery and have also issued summons to Devin Bessey, 24, and Ashley Simmons, 22, for simple battery. Stubbs says the male victim went into the gas station store where he was confronted by Dickerson who told him that he was in the “wrong neighborhood.” When the victim’s wife tried to help, she was knocked unconscious by Bessey. The couple’s 14 year old daughter was punched by Simmons when she tried to come to her parent’s aid.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369001810485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:16:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369002000595-53</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another example in Jacksonville fla. When the people of Jacksonville learned a mob of at least 15 black people had attacked an elderly white man, kicking him and beating him with a big stick, many were not surprised. There had been at least three other reports of black mob violence in that area in the two days surrounding the Friday attack. And just two weeks before that, four black people were arrested in connection with the murder of a 13-month old child during a robbery in that area. But this latest example of black mob violence was different in at least two ways: first, at least one local media outlet identified the mob as black – a rarity among the 500 black mob attacks throughout the country documented in the book “White Girl Bleed a Lot, the return of racial violence and how the media ignore it.” The local daily paper in Jacksonville has yet to do a story on the assault. The second surprise was that two Good Samaritans came to the man’s aid, stopping their car, driving away the attackers, and saving the man from further serious injury. Or worse. The Good Samaritans were black. One of the heroes was a woman, who asked the Jacksonville ABC affiliate to hide her identity out of fear of retribution. She described the attack: “We seen a whole bunch of African-American kids you know, beating and stomping on an elderly Caucasian guy and he had bags and everything, he couldn’t even defend himself because it was so many kids,” said the anonymous witness. “Between 10 or 15 kids it could have been more because they just scattered like ants when we came back around.”</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369002000595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:20:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369002108613-54</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON – A top White House adviser staked out a defiant defense Sunday on a series of scandals that have hit the Obama administration, going so far as to say they are “irrelevant fact”, and Obama can't be bothered with them. Dan Pfeiffer went on five Sunday talk shows where he tried to reverse the damage done to the Obama administration this week by a series of scandals. On “Fox News Sunday” he tried to hammer home that the president only heard that the IRS unfairly targeted Tea Party groups “when it came out in the news.”</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1369002108613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369002231548-55</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>here's another that happened in Milwaukee Witnesses tell Newsradio 620 WTMJ and TODAY’S TMJ4 of a mob of young people attacking innocent fair-goers at the end of the opening night of State Fair, with some callers claiming a racially-charged scene. Milwaukee Police confirmed there were assaults outside the fair. Witnesses’ accounts claim everything from dozens to hundreds of young black people beating white people as they left State Fair Thursday night. Authorities have not given official estimates of the number of people involved in the attacks. “It looked like they were just going after white guys, white people,” said Norb Roffers of Wind Lake in an interview with Newsradio 620 WTMJ. He left the State Fair Entrance near the corner of South 84th Street and West Schlinger Avenue in West Allis. “They were attacking everybody for no reason whatsoever.” “It was 100% racial,” claimed Eric, an Iraq war veteran from St. Francis who says young people beat on his car.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369002231548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369002312095-56</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368971009115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, is 3 examples enough? Would you like more? I can provide more. I bet you're surprised, Afterall, you don't read this stuff or her it in the daily news. MSM ignore instances like these.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369002312095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369002727937-57</Id><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites. says seebe</Title><Msg>That's just on repub websites! seebe.... very sad to see you're doin this S~ Hey seebe.. how about defending your post saying Obama is involved in IRS stuff???? Seebe,,,you're on the DARK SIDE! Better GROW UP!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369002727937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:32:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369003266047-58</Id><Title>mob violence: white teens attack and murder</Title><Msg>WHAT A DIFFERENCE A RACE MAKES WHEN THE FLASH MOB IS WHITE TEENS: BLACK MAN MURDERED IN HATE CRIME JUNE 26 IN JACKSON, MS. JAMES CRAIG ANDERSON, 49, WAS BEATEN, RUN OVER AND KILLED BY WHITE TEENS IN JACKSON MS JUNE 26, 2011 Authorities say a group of white teens targeted Anderson because he was black. The suspected ringleader, Deryl Dedmon, Jr., 18, has been charged with murder Dedmon faces possible double life sentence for the murderIn a parking lot on the western side of town they found their black victim. A hard working American citizen that loved his country and his family! James Craig Anderson, a 49-year-old auto plant worker, was standing in a parking lot, near his car. The teens allegedly beat Anderson repeatedly, kicking him in his head and chest yelling racial epithets, including “White Power!” according to witnesses. (racism is evil.......black or white),no matter)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369003266047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369003373024-59</Id><Title>seebe,, watch out for that mob violence! Just tell them you're a good guy republican!</Title><Msg>Scratch that seebe................ just RUN! I have to admit.I don't blame people for disliking repubs! I despise them.....in a peaceful way.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003373024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369003399895-60</Id><Topic><Title>seebe,, watch out for that mob violence! Just tell them you're a good guy republican!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003373024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:42:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, that;s what your 300 million guns are for.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003399895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369003494584-61</Id><Title>seebe,, just tell the black mobs that slavery wan't so bad!</Title><Msg>That'd be funny!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003494584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369003581518-62</Id><Topic><Title>seebe,, just tell the black mobs that slavery wan't so bad!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003494584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:44:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's the repub platform right? Slavery was GREAT! Right seebe ? Why oh why would some black people hate you? I can't imagine why! Because you said slavery was OK!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003581518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369003798338-63</Id><Title>No excuse for for black mobs to hate seebe!!!!!!!!! Wait a minute............OF COURSE THERE IS!</Title><Msg>Just admit slavery wan't so good seebe,... SAVE YOURSELF! That's what I tell the black mobs.worked so far for me. You should try it but they'd know you're lyin!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003798338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369003834299-64</Id><Title>BLACK MOBS!!!!!!!!!! TOO FUNNY!</Title><Msg>At least show me a FOX report on black mobs!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003834299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:50:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369003972830-65</Id><Title>seebe when black mobs kill about 10 million repubs.THEN let me know.</Title><Msg>Otherwise it's not even fair! FUNNNNNY!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003972830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369004021898-66</Id><Title>seebe YA ALL GOT YOUR GUNS!</Title><Msg>Whats the problem!??</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369004021898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369004145293-67</Id><Topic><Title>No excuse for for black mobs to hate seebe!!!!!!!!! Wait a minute............OF COURSE THERE IS!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003798338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:49:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you condone it. I knew that!</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369004145293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:55:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369004196483-68</Id><Title>hate crime perps: 62.4 percent were white, 18.5 percent were black, (stop the violence people!)</Title><Msg>"of the 6,225 known offenders, 62.4 percent were white, 18.5 percent were black, and 7.3 percent were groups of individuals of various races. The race was unknown for 10.2 percent of offenders, and other races accounted for the remaining offenders." FBI Hate Crime Statistics, 2009 report. Some of the general findings include: Victims ◾61.1 percent of all hate crimes were committed against persons, while 38.1 percent were crimes against property. ◾Of the 4,057 victims of racial bias, 71.5 percent were victims because of an offender’s prejudice against blacks. ◾Of the 1,575 victims of anti-religious hate crimes, 71.9 percent were victims because of an offender’s anti-Jewish bias. Offenders ◾Of the 6,225 known offenders, 62.4 percent were white, 18.5 percent were black, and 7.3 percent were groups of individuals of various races. The race was unknown for 10.2 percent of offenders, and other races accounted for the remaining offenders. ◾Of the 5,136 offenders who carried out crimes against persons, 40.3 percent committed simple assaults, 34.6 percent intimidated their victims, and 23.5 percent committed aggravated assaults. Murders and rapes were committed by 1.2 percent of the offenders.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369004196483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369004267934-69</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence. Blacks attacking whites. says seebe</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369002727937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:32:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah drop, all the sites that did report it made it up. I know you condone it. I think you wish for more of it.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369004267934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369004531023-70</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence: white teens attack and murder</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369003266047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this was pretty serious and not on Fox or WND....jeez</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369004531023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:02:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369004824984-71</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence: white teens attack and murder</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369003266047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but black on white crime is never a hate crime. Ever notice that?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369004824984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369006012966-72</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence: white teens attack and murder</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369003266047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why are you such a liar? hate crimes are hate crimes. as for racial hate crimes whites do 65% of them, blacks do 18%, per fbi statistics......................and did you notice the white teen mob murdered a person.....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369006012966</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:26:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369006040514-73</Id><Topic><Title>More Crock From Our Biggest Leftwing Goon</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1368996705347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 16:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for confirming your funneled vision. If you're going to categorize all Repubs the same, should we say Obama is liken to Bill Ayers, the Black Panthers or Louis Farrakhan? You continue to warp reality as it suits you. F-off, bro.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369006040514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369006175794-74</Id><Title>Republicans Informed of IRS Investigation Last Year</Title><Msg>ppphhick you skkkkkums!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369006175794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369006247202-75</Id><Title>If you're going to categorize all Repubs the same</Title><Msg>#$%$ yeah! and not ONE of you are consevrative.your'e just REPUB!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369006247202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:30:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369006308428-76</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence: white teens attack and murder</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369003266047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hate crimes are not hate crimes at least as far as law enforcement is concerned.. LE is loath to label any black on white crime as hate crime.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369006308428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:31:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369006316967-77</Id><Title>t black on white crime is never a hate crime. Ever notice that?</Title><Msg>whites started it! And until you admit it................#$%$ you/</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369006316967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:31:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369006355776-78</Id><Topic><Title>t black on white crime is never a hate crime. Ever notice that?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369006316967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW phk heads.you don't even believe in HATE CRIMES! You make me ppppppppuke!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369006355776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369006774662-79</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence: white teens attack and murder</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369003266047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are full of shizer. BTW the mobs you cite are nowhere near the 4000 or so hate crimes done by whites in 2009, of which 1.2% were murders and rapes (1080 hate crimes were done by blacks)........per fbi statistics.... and OF COURSE the UNREPORTED or NOT reported as hate would likely be in the SAME %s duh....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369006774662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369007369278-80</Id><Title>let's analyze priest pedophiles for race statistics, shall we seaburgc?</Title><Msg>and the Pope is responsible for it all, right seeburgc, no such thing as rogue employees as you say about the IRS.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369007369278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:49:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369007443815-81</Id><Topic><Title>t black on white crime is never a hate crime. Ever notice that?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369006316967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are so warped ! It's pathetic really.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369007443815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369009814879-82</Id><Title>You Can't Refute</Title><Msg>That the Dem machine has corrupted many Fed agencies. How the hell can the IRS intimidate orgs because of their political affiliation? How can the DOJ spy on a respected news organization? It has all the markings of the KGB or Saddam paranoia. . Republicans better lean heavy on it and not let this fade. I reiterate, what if this corruption happened during Bush's term? The libs would be squealing like pigs nonstop.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369009814879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 20:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369013636426-83</Id><Topic><Title>t black on white crime is never a hate crime. Ever notice that?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369006316967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about Black on BlacK? Bet you never heard of the African chief that received a rifle as a gift from a British explorer.. He wanted to see it work so he motioned one of his people forward and shot him. Read a little on Robert "The Beast" Mugabe and how he treats his people in Zimbabwe. The Brits and Boers were never that vicious. When Zimbabwe was Rhodesia. it fed it's own people and exported food to all of Africa. Now? No more exports and the populace is half starved. My grandfather was a So. "racist". Yet, when Blacks needed a sworn statement for their age for old age assistence they went to him. If they were hungry he let them take vegetables from his garden. Some would come to the front porch in the evening and they and my grandfather would exchange jokes until bed time. My grandfather was not rich but was able to support himself and 11 children by two wives. He was born in 1864 in Huntsville, Ala.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369013636426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369014076344-84</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gaining in popularity (ha ha ha ha, loser pubs have egg on their face)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368978442100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 11:47:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That may be the clearest message from a CNN/ORC poll released Sunday morning. According to the survey, which was conducted Friday and Saturday, 53 percent of Americans say they approve of the job the president is doing, with 45 percent saying they disapprove, CNN reports. That’s actually a tick better than the 51 percent approval rating Obama had in early April –</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369014076344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369014184514-85</Id><Topic><Title>More Crock From Our Biggest Leftwing Goon</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1368996705347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 16:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My mom and dad were Southern Democrats. They switched when "Rosie The Red" started cuddling up to the commies in the thirties. Rosie once stated; "Some of my best friends are Communists". He proved it by putting them in positions to steal all the atomic secrets. Check out Harry Dexter White (Weiss) and how he gave the plates for German occupation scrip to the commies who used it to swindle the U.S. out of 600 million in the late forties. Ten times that amount now.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369014184514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>