<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369895361410-1</Id><Topic><Title>what traders dont know!</Title><Username>rogerblack750</Username><Timestamp>1369796530470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i wanna make 25k</Msg><Username>million.trader</Username><Timestamp>1369895361410</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 02:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369913654586-2</Id><Topic><Title>this doc has ditched all health insurance</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369844573990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 12:22:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SCREW those Drs... w/o govt taxpayer money they'd all be making housecalls WE made them wealthy.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369913654586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 07:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369916030105-3</Id><Title>You may be losing your health care policy.</Title><Msg>Because their basic policies do not meet the standards set up by Obummercare. The fiasco continues, govt totally unprepared, and the abyss is upon us. Twenty six hundred pages of liberal #$%$ will interfere with the greatest medicine available in the world. Yeah, I know Messybird, look at the statistics of the socialist/communist countries. They are skewed to favor the wacko socialists who want to control your life. Take lifestyles, drug use, accidental death, and other factors into account, and you have medicine in America being the most advanced, hands down. When was the last time some president, congressperson, CEO, or libiot go to a third world socialist country for treatment.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369916030105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 08:13:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369916224957-4</Id><Title>lots of IRS/WH coordinating</Title><Msg>Shulman’s extensive access to the White House first came to light during his testimony last week before the House Oversight and Government Reform Committee. Shulman gave assorted answers when asked why he had visited the White House 118 times during the period that the IRS was targeting tea party and conservative nonprofits for extra scrutiny and delays on their tax-exempt applications. By contrast, Shulman’s predecessor Mark Everson only visited the White House once during four years of service in the George W. Bush administration and compared the IRS’s remoteness from the president to “Siberia.” But the scope of Shulman’s White House visits — which strongly suggests coordination by White House officials in the campaign against the president’s political opponents — is even more striking in comparison to the publicly recorded access of cabinet members.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369916224957</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 08:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369916344058-5</Id><Title>George Will has a way with words.</Title><Msg>Lawless coercion is his latest description of the IRS fiasco. The impulse that the Bummer administration produced to try to destroy political speech.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369916344058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 08:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369916420669-6</Id><Topic><Title>lots of IRS/WH coordinating</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369916224957</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 08:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I smell a rat in the sewer.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369916420669</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 08:20:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369917647929-7</Id><Title>bla bla bla for all the pub bluster and bla there is no IRS Scandal</Title><Msg>just a few office workers who smartly decided to work on those groups who are doing most of the applications and pretending to be "social welfare" groups.... and sure 51% of Tea Party America's effort are NOT political... ha ha ha......jeez........ and the fact is NOT a SINGLE dumb #$%$ teagag group was denied or harmed in ANYWAY.... just cite ONE way they were harmed......... and it is certainly NO harm to them for the IRS to actually examine the application that they submitted to be looked at.....jees h crist... this is as much a waste of time as all your bla and blather about Obama being an anti colonial mau mau</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369917647929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 08:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369917878959-8</Id><Title>pubs just bluster babble and bla bla their fannies off with trumped up horse manure</Title><Msg>horse manure is the main product of the gop. just fricken vote for impeachment or #$%$ with all your whiny as shizer . You talk like you have the beef.... but where's the beef...... ha ha .. all you have is HORSE MANURE. IF you hand any beef you would have said here It is......and voted to impeach...... ha ha ha</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369917878959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 08:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369918324055-9</Id><Topic><Title>You may be losing your health care policy.</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369916030105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 08:13:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes moron, now your policy has to pay 85% of your premium dollar in actual healthcare, instead of the 70% or so previously... and now they have to SHOW where the money goes......before they simply put it in their pocket. and now your policy can't dump you suddenly because they find out you took an aspirin 5 years ago and didn't tell them proving you had a preexisting condition. and now policies have to cover the same things so you can compare apples to apples and won't find out when you need it that , too bad, it's not covered and now you owe your house...................you are just ridiculous really.....you just can't move on, can't improve, you are such a dodo you think the ancient incandescent light bulb technology is the way to go. No doubt you think the abacus is better than a computer too.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918324055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 08:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369918967477-10</Id><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Msg>He seems to have stayed all night on several occasions!!!!!! Obviously this proves that BUSH is gay, right? I mean why else would a male prostitute visit the WH hundreds of times and often when there wasn't even a press conference? huh? huh? investigate!!!!!!! ha ha ha "Gannon, whose real name is Jim Guckert, has worked as a male prostitute and advertised his own escort services over the internet. More than two dozen of his visits to the White House were made when there were no scheduled press conferences or briefings. And, even more noteworthy is that fact that on 14 separate occasions Secret Service records indicate no arrival or departure time. "</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369919775350-11</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Special IRS Prosecutor Favored as Obama Support Drops By Jonathan D. Salant - May 30, 2013 6:00 AM ET Three-quarters of U.S. voters want a special prosecutor to investigate the Internal Revenue Service’s targeting of Tea Party groups, according to a poll that showed a drop in President Barack Obama’s approval and trust ratings. In the survey released today by Hamden, Connecticut-based Quinnipiac University, registered voters favored a special prosecutor by 76 percent to 17 percent. Those backing such a move included 63 percent of Democrats. Enlarge image Special IRS Prosecutor Favored as Obama Support Dips, Poll Says The IRS earlier this month disclosed that it singled out groups with “tea party” or “patriot” in their names for extra scrutiny before deciding whether to grant tax-exempt status under the tax code’s Section 501(c)(4). Photographer: Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg “There is overwhelming bipartisan support for an independent investigation into the IRS,” Peter A. Brown, assistant director of the Quinnipiac polling institute, said in a news release.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369919775350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369919843404-12</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON (CBSDC) — A former bodyguard for Osama bin Laden is claiming the terror leader blew himself up during the U.S. special forces raid on his Abbotabad compound in Pakistan. Nabil Naim Abdel Fattah told Gulf News that Navy SEALs did not kill the al Qaeda leader who planned the Sept. 11, 2001 attacks. “U.S. special forces did not kill Osama Bin Laden. He detonated himself to avoid being captured after American forces raided his hiding place in Pakistan in 2011,” Abedel Fattah explained to Gulf News. Abdel Fattah – the former of Egyptian Islamic Jihad — said that bin Laden “wore an explosive belt for the last 10 years of his life.” “He insisted on never handing himself over to the Americans. The American intelligence had planned to capture him alive, but they miscalculated,” Abdel Fattah said. “He blew himself up to avoid being captured because he wanted to protect his secrets until death.” Fattah added: “The American president lied when he claimed that Bin Laden was buried in the sea. Bin Laden’s body parts were cut into multiple pieces, which is similar to suicide attacks following the bombing, so as not to leave any clue to the U.S. forces to identify him.””</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1369919843404</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369920962781-13</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, you are in a small minority of thought. But we already knew that, right? 3/4 of US voters want a speical prosecutor. Pretty significant I'd say. .Special IRS Prosecutor Favored as Obama Support Drops By Jonathan D. Salant - May 30, 2013 6:00 AM ET ..Three-quarters of U.S. voters want a special prosecutor to investigate the Internal Revenue Service’s targeting of Tea Party groups, according to a poll that showed a drop in President Barack Obama’s approval and trust ratings. In the survey released today by Hamden, Connecticut-based Quinnipiac University, registered voters favored a special prosecutor by 76 percent to 17 percent. Those backing such a move included 63 percent of Democrats.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369920962781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:36:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369921590927-14</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doofus, blather and investigate all you want so what... there was no wrong doing, the IRS checked out the applications and none were denied. so what? fire some people at the IRS ha ha ha ha, for doing their job....jeez.... you know..... looking at the applications that people sent them......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369921590927</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369922231795-15</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there was no wrong doing, you say. You know that for sure, do you? Hah!</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369922231795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:57:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369925165530-16</Id><Title>If by "non emergencies" delucks means cancer, than he is right</Title><Msg>but we know he is an idiot with little to no understanding or experience in anything.</Msg><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1369925165530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 10:46:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369925212205-17</Id><Title>Holder - one step closer to being charged with lying to Congress.</Title><Msg>tick, tock. tick, tock........</Msg><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1369925212205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 10:46:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369929005480-18</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can tell when demessy is starting to sweat and panic when he wags the donkey with male prostitutes and other nonsense. Suppose the special prosecutor is a gay black Dem? What would demessy babble then?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369929005480</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 11:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369932002126-19</Id><Title>VIZS looks prime for a huge breakout</Title><Msg>VIZS is the stock to watch. Financials show some huge assets along with proven mining properties. You need to start some research on VIZS, could be the next mining play to really make investors rich</Msg><Username>connor.holder106</Username><Timestamp>1369932002126</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:40:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369932026043-20</Id><Title>Market yoyo</Title><Msg>This yo yo movement of the market is typical of a major top. I'm set for it, are you?</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369932026043</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369932054751-21</Id><Title>You need to start your research on VIZS right away!</Title><Msg>NEED to check out VIZS. Huge assets on their books + gold mines that are tested and confirmed to have gold and silver. It wotn last long once investors take notice</Msg><Username>connor.holder106</Username><Timestamp>1369932054751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369932371899-22</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember when this was first exposed. He posed as a "News Corresponent". I went to his web site at the time. He posed in military clothes. It almost had to be Bush using his "services". Just one of many reasons I detest the whole Bush family. Can't believe so many bought into them. Ah well, "Boobus Americanus" will buy anything if presented to them in the right way. Too busy watching footbal to do any real study.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369932371899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369932537186-23</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is no nonsense. It was covered fully by the press. This bird signed into the WH but never said who he was seeing.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369932537186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369932675800-24</Id><Title>Pay Attention</Title><Msg>The more Obama tap dances away from the scandal fracas, the more he resembles a lawyer than a Pres. "Buck, what buck? I have no knowledge of a stopped buck or otherwise" "My administration is not fond of the 1st and 2nd amendments but we love the 5th."</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369932675800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369932885518-25</Id><Title>Hillary doesn't have a chance.</Title><Msg>Dems got their perfect ticket for 2016.......Weiner/Holder.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369932885518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369933498317-26</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gee, you mean visits to the WH are just visits to the WH and don't mean squat? Does seabugc know?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369933498317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 13:04:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369933645856-27</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what was the wrong doing? Oh, yeah you bums say if the IRS examines a form it is wrong doing, "SCANDALOUS"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369933645856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 13:07:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369935016010-28</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's brother to sell letters from president hand-written to relatives in kenya...</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369935016010</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 13:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369938118152-29</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously this proves that BUSH is gay, right? If it doesn't,the fact that he now paints nude portraits of himself does.He's as #$%$ as a three dollar bill.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1369938118152</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 14:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369938312062-30</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. there was no wrong doing, you say. You know that for sure, do you? Hah! You rightwing idiots got nothing,so you're all grasping at straws.Hillary in 2016. !! Get used to it Zippy.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1369938312062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 14:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369938439951-31</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary doesn't have a chance.</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369932885518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary doesn't have a chance. What would you know about it dumbazzbuck?Your IQ is the same as your shoe size.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1369938439951</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 14:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369938806972-32</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's war in Iraq</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368805360880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:42:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Bush was behind the mosque bombings? Didn't say he was idiot,but he did start the war in Iraq based on a LIE!</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1369938806972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 14:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369939077139-33</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's war in Iraq</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368805360880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:42:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really think it will upstage the recent scandals? What scandals idiot?Oh you mean the ones the Pukes are falsely pushing.That's just something the Pukes are pushing so as they feel they're still in the game,EARTH to you and your Puke buddies,YOU'RE NOT.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1369939077139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 14:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369940092828-34</Id><Topic><Title>Pay Attention</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369932675800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pay Attention That's probably about ALL you can afford to pay dumbazz.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1369940092828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 14:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369941206362-35</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's right Phil, it's all imaginary. Repubs just congered up this stuff out of thin air, right? Three on-going scandals and possibly a 4th just didn't happen. They are: 1) Benghazi 2) James Rosen (you know, he's the criminal co-conspirator and abettor of classified info. Crimes for sure, but he was never charged, was he?) 3) IRS 4) and last and certainly not least, Katherine Sebelius' shaking down companies that HHS would regulate for dough to launch Obamacare (becasue the feds don't have enough of our money to launch it themselves)</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369941206362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 15:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369942336432-36</Id><Topic><Title>Pay Attention</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369932675800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:51:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahh, phyllis, I love the sound of squealing pigs. You never disappoint. And pass the buck is ALL Obama can do. "I have no knowledge of anything my administration does, no one tells me anything"</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369942336432</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 15:32:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369942941888-37</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>May 30, 2013 4:00 AM Obama’s ‘Chicago Way’ The administration’s political tactics are straight out of the Daley playbook. By John Fund The scandals swirling around the Obama administration have many journalists scratching their heads as to how “hope and change” seem to have been supplanted by “arrogance and fear.” Perhaps it’s time they revisit one of their original premises about Barack Obama: that he wasn’t influenced by the Chicago Daley machine. You know: the machine that boosted his career and whose protégés — including Valerie Jarrett, David Axelrod, Rahm Emanuel, and his wife, Michelle — he brought to Washington with him. The liberal take on the president was best summed up by Slate magazine’s Jacob Weisberg, who wrote last year that Obama “somehow passed through Chicago politics without ever developing any real connection to it.”</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369942941888</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 15:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369943415971-38</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White House: No need for special prosecutor on I.R.S. 5/30/13 3:12 PM EDT On the heels of a poll showing 76 percent of Americans support the appointment of a special proscutor to investigate the I.R.S., the White House dismissed the idea, saying there's enough people reviewing the agency already and the IRS is doing a fine job.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369943415971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 15:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369948834894-39</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's war in Iraq</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368805360880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:42:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush invasion of Iraq is a SCANDAL... a real one..... he "misled " the nation... as the fmr commandant of the US Marine Corps, gen Zinni. put it stating the obvious........ Zinni called W's invasion a "brainfart"......it severely damaged the USA but made the bush cronies who pumped it even richer than they already were......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369948834894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369949044386-40</Id><Title>McCain says he knows who the good guys are in Syria and wants to arm them (then oops, nevermind)</Title><Msg>McCain can recognize good guys Senator John McCain Confident of Identifying 'Good Guys' in Syria. U.S. Senator John McCain said on Wednesday, two days after meeting with rebels in Syria, that he is confident the United States can send weapons to fighters in Syria without the risk they will fall into the wrong hands. "We can identify who these people are. We can help the right people," McCain said on CNN's program "Anderson Cooper 360." . . Critics of some lawmakers' push to arm the rebels have expressed concerns that weapons could end up in the hands of militants who might eventually end up using them against the United States or its allies. But McCain said such radical fighters make up only a small part of the rebels forces A day later...... McCain Didn’t Realize He Was Posing With Rebel Kidnapper, Spokesman Says Senator John McCain’s office is pushing back against reports that while visiting Syria this week he posed in a photo with rebels who kidnapped 11 Lebanese Shi’ite pilgrims. The photo, released by McCain’s office, shows McCain with a group of rebels. Among them are two men identified in the Lebanese press as Mohamed Nour and Abu Ibrahim, two of the kidnappers of the group from Lebanon. A McCain spokesman said that no one who met with McCain identified themselves by either of those names.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369949044386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369956733545-41</Id><Title>Whistleblowers okay with Obama as long as they are blowing his whistle in his war on whistleblowers</Title><Msg>Nice double entendre!</Msg><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1369956733545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 19:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369960886389-42</Id><Topic><Title>McCain says he knows who the good guys are in Syria and wants to arm them (then oops, nevermind)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369949044386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:24:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this bit of news supposed to reflect bad on all Repubs as you imagine? He doesn't even know who the good guys are in America. McCain has been wrong about several things. He belongs in a rest home with Harry Reid. He helped put Obama in the White House by sending more voters to the Independent side and diluted the vote. I, for one, was glad he didn't win, but lo the result was the same. You see, we on the right can discern our pol's quackery. You Dems applaud and defend yours, turn a blind eye and deaf ear to what you would have hung Bush for. Make a note of that next time you bring up a quack Repub. You ignorant goon.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369960886389</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 20:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369963631374-43</Id><Topic><Title>McCain says he knows who the good guys are in Syria and wants to arm them (then oops, nevermind)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369949044386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:24:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are many rumors about McCain and his stay at the Hanoi Hilton. Wouldn't trust him as far as I could throw him. His father was one of the ones responsible for not providing support for the U.S.S. Liberty along with LBJ. Just another criminal act in a long list.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369963631374</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 21:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369963914258-44</Id><Topic><Title>male prostitute/WH coordinating: over 200 WH visits by the male prostitute/conservative 'reporter'</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369918967477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 09:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Added. This fruit loop got his "Press Credentials" from the then head of the Texas Republican Party. His ad on the net advertised $1,000 per hour.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369963914258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 21:31:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369966560576-45</Id><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush's Watch Without a Peep from Fox News SCANDAL OMG !!!!!!!</Title><Msg>The Benghazi attacks (the consulate and the CIA compound) are absolutely not unprecedented even though they're being treated that way by Republicans who are deliberately ignoring anything that happened prior to Inauguration Day, January 20, 2009. January 22, 2002. Calcutta, India. Gunmen associated with Harkat-ul-Jihad al-Islami attack the U.S. Consulate. Five people are killed. June 14, 2002. Karachi, Pakistan. Suicide bomber connected with al Qaeda attacks the U.S. Consulate, killing 12 and injuring 51. October 12, 2002. Denpasar, Indonesia. U.S. diplomatic offices bombed as part of a string of "Bali Bombings." No fatalities. February 28, 2003. Islamabad, Pakistan. Several gunmen fire upon the U.S. Embassy. Two people are killed. May 12, 2003. Riyadh, Saudi Arabia. Armed al Qaeda terrorists storm the diplomatic compound, killing 36 people including nine Americans. The assailants committed suicide by detonating a truck bomb. July 30, 2004. Tashkent, Uzbekistan. A suicide bomber from the Islamic Movement of Uzbekistan attacks the U.S. Embassy, killing two people. December 6, 2004. Jeddah, Saudi Arabia. Al Qaeda terrorists storm the U.S. Consulate and occupy the perimeter wall. Nine people are killed. March 2, 2006. Karachi, Pakistan again. Suicide bomber attacks the U.S. Consulate killing four people, including U.S. diplomat David Foy who was directly targeted by the attackers. (I wonder if Lindsey Graham or Fox News would even recognize the name "David Foy." This is the third Karachi terrorist attack in four years on what's considered American soil.) September 12, 2006. Damascus, Syria. Four armed gunmen shouting "Allahu akbar" storm the U.S. Embassy using grenades, automatic weapons, a car bomb and a truck bomb. Four people are killed, 13 are wounded. January 12, 2007. Athens, Greece. Members of a Greek terrorist group called the Revolutionary Struggle fire a rocket-propelled grenade at the U.S. Embassy. No fatalities. March 18, 2008. Sana'a, Yemen. Me</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369966560576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369970148417-46</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush's Watch Without a Peep from Fox News SCANDAL OMG !!!!!!!</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369966560576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:16:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wag the donkey, DA. Has no bearing on what happened in Benghazi. The big difference was those attacks were surprise attacks and committed by one or two jihadists claiming their martyrdom. Benghazi was a military style attack by a hoard and had been brewing over weeks of anti-American sentiments. Which one of those you list asked for heighted security and was denied? You are too fkg stupid to grasp the difference. If there was a security problem then, why wasn't it brought out? Sorry, DA, your silly comparisons are not the same and just got stomped, as usual. I recommend you post relevant info, making a fool of yourself is no way to go thru life.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369970148417</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 23:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369970898126-47</Id><Title>Gay Visits to the WH</Title><Msg>I thought this was put to rest. It turns out it was some secret service personnel who sought gay companions besides Gannon. Always late at night in their quarters and why the visitors weren't required to sign in. The only reason the story was quashed was because of national security, you know, bed fellows, pillow talk.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369970898126</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 23:28:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>