<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369974930391-1</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush's Watch Without a Peep from Fox News SCANDAL OMG !!!!!!!</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369966560576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:16:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are two big differences: 1. Obama was watching Benghazi realtime. 2. Obama put on his pink, Winnie the Poo onzies, took an Ambien and went nighty-nite!</Msg><Username>azhdarchid.quetzalcoatlus</Username><Timestamp>1369974930391</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:35:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369980993602-2</Id><Title>What is going on? All across the country the police are attacking blacks!</Title><Msg>The super militarized police forces that Obama has created are attacking blacks! Here in NYC Bloombergs NYPD "Stop &amp; Frisks" mostly young black males. Over the last 10 years, the NYPD has stopped &amp; frisked the equivalent of 105% of the black population on NYC. But on;y 11% of the more numerous whites. What wrath hath Obama wrought?</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1369980993602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 02:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369996398723-3</Id><Title>The super militarized police forces that Obama has created are attacking blacks</Title><Msg>YOU and all repubs saying ANYTHING are 100% full of corpis dabien You're garbage. Lying stinking garbage.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369996398723</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 06:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369996655715-4</Id><Title>You're garbage. Lying stinking garbage.</Title><Msg>.....and you know that. you know you're nothing but a stinking lying repub.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369996655715</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 06:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370002972259-5</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush's Watch Without a Peep from Fox News SCANDAL OMG !!!!!!!</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369966560576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:16:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pubs only became interested in these kinds of attacks after 2009.... there were 13 on Bush's watch..SCANDAL!!! Bush was probably DRUNK the whole time. Bush was a SCANDALOUS DRUNK and COKE head as everyone knows.!!!!!!!!!!! January 22, 2002. Calcutta, India. Gunmen associated with Harkat-ul-Jihad al-Islami attack the U.S. Consulate. Five people are killed. June 14, 2002. Karachi, Pakistan. Suicide bomber connected with al Qaeda attacks the U.S. Consulate, killing 12 and injuring 51. October 12, 2002. Denpasar, Indonesia. U.S. diplomatic offices bombed as part of a string of "Bali Bombings." No fatalities. February 28, 2003. Islamabad, Pakistan. Several gunmen fire upon the U.S. Embassy. Two people are killed. May 12, 2003. Riyadh, Saudi Arabia. Armed al Qaeda terrorists storm the diplomatic compound, killing 36 people including nine Americans. The assailants committed suicide by detonating a truck bomb. July 30, 2004. Tashkent, Uzbekistan. A suicide bomber from the Islamic Movement of Uzbekistan attacks the U.S. Embassy, killing two people. December 6, 2004. Jeddah, Saudi Arabia. Al Qaeda terrorists storm the U.S. Consulate and occupy the perimeter wall. Nine people are killed. March 2, 2006. Karachi, Pakistan again. Suicide bomber attacks the U.S. Consulate killing four people, including U.S. diplomat David Foy who was directly targeted by the attackers. (I wonder if Lindsey Graham or Fox News would even recognize the name "David Foy." This is the third Karachi terrorist attack in four years on what's considered American soil.) September 12, 2006. Damascus, Syria. Four armed gunmen shouting "Allahu akbar" storm the U.S. Embassy using grenades, automatic weapons, a car bomb and a truck bomb. Four people are killed, 13 are wounded. January 12, 2007. Athens, Greece. Members of a Greek terrorist group called the Revolutionary Struggle fire a rocket-propelled grenade at the U.S. Embassy. No fatalities. March 18, 2008. Sana'a, Yemen</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370002972259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:22:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370003096013-6</Id><Topic><Title>McCain says he knows who the good guys are in Syria and wants to arm them (then oops, nevermind)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369949044386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:24:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mccain was palling around with terrorists, even doing a photo op with them..... SCANDAL, hissyfit and pantie wad...!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370003096013</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370003908446-7</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush's Watch Without a Peep from Fox News SCANDAL OMG !!!!!!!</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369966560576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:16:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you see those as parallels, do you? Only in your twisted universe. Fact is, each of the incidents you cite was spontaneous with no time for immediate action. I'm sure you think that was also true of Benghazi. It wasn't. The attacked raged for hours and the O admin had hours to assess and take action. Military units were at the ready. All they needed was an order to go, an order that never came. To the contrary, the military was ordered to stand down.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1370003908446</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:38:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370004553734-8</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush's Watch Without a Peep from Fox News SCANDAL OMG !!!!!!!</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369966560576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:16:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pathetic seaburgc. who omits that there was a CIA armed response team sent and it was there pronto....and of course, you lie about the 13 bush bengazhis as well... ALL COULD have been prevented and ANY arm chair rear view leasership from a gop committee can easily prove what SHOULD HAVE been done to prevent the needless slaughter that they and bush are responsible for.. what a SCANDAL!!!!!! "a rescue party of CIA officers was deployed from a secret base within Benghazi and that the agency later sent reinforcements from Tripoli to battle the attack on the mission, which ultimately killed four Americans, including the U.S. ambassador Chris Stevens. Approximately half-a-dozen officers raced from a base from a mile away and arrived at the mission in about 25 minutes, according to The Times, and were later joined by security agents from the State Department. The officers led a search for Stevens, but his body had apparently already been taken to a local hospital. The group evacuated personnel to the CIA base, or what has been commonly referred to as the "annex.""</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370004553734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370005557926-9</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush's Watch Without a Peep from Fox News SCANDAL OMG !!!!!!!</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369966560576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:16:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>should have been done in the Bush cases you cite as opposed to could have been done in Benghazi. Sorry chump, Obama failed miserably. He was not engaged. He was disinterested.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1370005557926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370005788236-10</Id><Title>all 13 bush benghazis could have been prevented</Title><Msg>all that was needed was the proper rear view mirror, arm chair, hind sight leadership that comes from the typical hissie fit gop investigation committee,</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370005788236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370006561630-11</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush's Watch Without a Peep from Fox News SCANDAL OMG !!!!!!!</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369966560576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:16:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I omitted the CIA armed response? You mean the response team that defied orders to stand down and went to the consulate anyway? Yeah, that team. Mesa, what do you do all day? do you do anything to stay reasonably informed?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1370006561630</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:22:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370006796032-12</Id><Title>Reagan's beruit bombing COULD HAVE BEEN PREVENTED</Title><Msg>in fact, Reagan PROVOKED the attack......... where was the hindsight, the arm chair , rear view leadership? a gop investigation at the time blamed the marines for getting killed! nice work absolving yourself Ronnie. the troops knew that they were going to pay for Ronnie's meddling: " I stated to my staff at the time that we were going to pay in blood for this decision" Colonel Timothy J. Geraghty, He was the commander of the marines in Beirut during the incident speaking on Ronald Reagan's decision to use US Naval artillery in support of the Lebanese Army.... ,</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370006796032</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370007161493-13</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush's Watch Without a Peep from Fox News SCANDAL OMG !!!!!!!</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369966560576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:16:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, you omitted that there was an immediate response and you lie that it was "ordered to stand down"....jeez last year the CIA refuted the Fox news lies that there was no response.... or that if there was..... it was ordered to stand down........ nothing but FOX NEWS LIES....... CIA Discloses Covert Team’s Rapid Response to Benghazi Embassy Attack In response to criticism from conservatives and Fox News, the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) disclosed for the first time how its agents assisted the U.S. diplomatic mission in Benghazi, Libya, when it came under attack two months ago. Republicans have tried to score political points by questioning the Obama administration’s reaction to the assault that killed Ambassador Christopher Stevens and three other Americans. In addition, Fox News reported last week that CIA leaders ordered security officers to “stand down” and not engage those attacking the diplomatic compound. The story also said the security team only responded after officers disobeyed their superiors and repelled the attackers. The CIA countered these assertions on Thursday, telling the media that security operatives rushed to the compound within 25 minutes of the assault. The agency also organized the evacuation effort and took control of an unarmed U.S. military drone to map possible escape routes, according to the Washington Post. The CIA official told the Post that the agency wanted the public to know that there was no delay in sending help once it learned of the attack, and that managers did not get in the way of responding.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370007161493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370007391364-14</Id><Topic><Title>all 13 bush benghazis could have been prevented</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370005788236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bush and the gop's thirteen benganzis...... each and every one of them COULD HAVE BEEN PREVENTED. and nary a peep from fox news and not a single gop investigation to show how easily in hindsight each and every one of the 13 embassy attacks COULD HAVE BEEN PREVENTED.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370007391364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370008266235-15</Id><Title>newt announces smoking gun WH email on benghazi......( he said the rumor was so srtong in made his #$%$ hard)</Title><Msg>oh..... a year ago he announced the rumor of such a thing......... turns out there is no such thing...... Issa has been looking for it like the 7 lost cities of gold......nope..... no smoking gun email where Obama....stands down the CIA response to Benghazi...... you know if there was one... which the gop doesn't like to admit..........................The Cia has said they responded within minutes and that THEY were in charge and THEY got no interference or orders to "stand down" no matter how much fox new and issa and newt and all the other lying grandstanding #$%$ of the gop want there to be one............</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370008266235</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370009523368-16</Id><Title>You don’t want to miss out on MISM</Title><Msg>MISM has proven gold reserves and trades at just .08 cents. This one is going to be huge. Check it out</Msg><Username>robertcalhoun907</Username><Timestamp>1370009523368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370012065814-17</Id><Title>Read this now -(COMPANY NAME)(TICKER NAME)</Title><Msg>If or when you are looking for information concerning the stock market, then you need to see this Link:- urlDOTie/hhb0 [Remove DOT and Use . ]</Msg><Username>stevenson_jeremy</Username><Timestamp>1370012065814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370013676628-18</Id><Topic><Title>all 13 bush benghazis could have been prevented</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370005788236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haven't figured out yet that certain groups control BOTH parties? Just for one instance check out membership in the CFR. (Council On Foreign Relations.) 4,000 members. Most are listed on the web if you look. You'll recognize many of those names.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1370013676628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370013761453-19</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan's beruit bombing COULD HAVE BEEN PREVENTED</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370006796032</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:26:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Know where the then new explosive came from? Only one country in the mid-East had it at that time.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1370013761453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:22:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370013906751-20</Id><Title>effort to recall joe Arpaio fails</Title><Msg>libs failed in recall effort. But you libs keep trying.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1370013906751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370015358845-21</Id><Topic><Title>newt announces smoking gun WH email on benghazi......( he said the rumor was so srtong in made his #$%$ hard)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370008266235</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, the liar Newt was spouting off ages about a strong rumor of an email that proves Obama is evil! Newt has always been full of shizer. He used to tell his wives he wasn't screwing other people's wives.....they believed him, just like the wingnuts who believed his lie about a wh email....... well Newt,,, where is it? Just tell Issa, he has been looking for it for a long time...... Newt has been very quiet lately, I guess even dumb people have gotten tired of his crying "wolf" all the time just to get attention.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370015358845</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370015558675-22</Id><Title>MISM is looking like it is about to go on a massive run</Title><Msg>HMISM looks like it is ready to pop. Have been doing some research on it for the past few weeks. Start your DD on MISM</Msg><Username>masondillon930</Username><Timestamp>1370015558675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370015597548-23</Id><Title>Wow! Start your DD on MISM because I think it is about to soar.</Title><Msg>Checked out MISM yet? Looks like it is ready to go. All of the technical indicators are showing signs of a bull run.</Msg><Username>masondillon930</Username><Timestamp>1370015597548</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370015724431-24</Id><Topic><Title>You don’t want to miss out on MISM</Title><Username>robertcalhoun907</Username><Timestamp>1370009523368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. So in theory.</Msg><Username>bryanwilliam269</Username><Timestamp>1370015724431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370016238545-25</Id><Topic><Title>You don’t want to miss out on MISM</Title><Username>robertcalhoun907</Username><Timestamp>1370009523368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh wow, its up right now on crazy volume</Msg><Username>julianstone157</Username><Timestamp>1370016238545</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370016921344-26</Id><Title>NEXT 2 WEEKS THIS WILL BE 10 BAGGER (CPOW)</Title><Msg>WATCH $</Msg><Username>omnesiion</Username><Timestamp>1370016921344</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370018051532-27</Id><Topic><Title>all 13 bush benghazis could have been prevented</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370005788236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And all of Clintons could have been prevented too, The Khobar Towers, the embassies in Africa, the USS Cole, '93 WTC and several in other countries that Al Queda or Hezbollah took credit for. By 2000 , anyone who was paying attention knew the threat from Islamic terror was grave and getting worse. Fast forward to attacks during Bush, all of them just continuous assaults from the same extremists, So you're saying 9-11 could have been prevented too if Clinton had the balls to act.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370018051532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370018810443-28</Id><Title>Pay Attention Goons</Title><Msg>Domestic Terrorism DOJ and the IRS Who would have thought it would be our own government. I mean, besides the founders.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370018810443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370018903604-29</Id><Topic><Title>all 13 bush benghazis could have been prevented</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370005788236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey dishonest person , YOU are ones doing the hindsight investigations and blather about the scandal of Benghazi....... so sure..... include every bad thing that ever happened....jeez</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370018903604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:48:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370024159754-30</Id><Topic><Title>all 13 bush benghazis could have been prevented</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370005788236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SMACK time! YOU are the whackjob who brought up prior "bad things" that have NO bearing with Benghazi. I debunked your twisted point so that makes me dishonest? When a liberal gets pummeled they cry "dishonest" or "ya got nothin". Just like Obama, hand off the blame to someone else, look the other way and keep wagging the donkey. You would make him proud. Hindsight investigations are necessary. Watergate, Iran/Contra. You had no objections then. You are a phony, a leftwing spin artist, a liberal crackpot. It's obvious you are in a panic with the nonsense you conjure up as if it will change the outcome. Benghazi is an open wound on this administration and the families of the victims won't let it die. You're wasting your half a brain.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370024159754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370024330446-31</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It turns out they had it wrong and the costs are going up 64 -146%. T ypical clueless Dems. Their solution to high costs is to lie and say the costs are low. http://www.forbes.com/sites/theapothecary/2013/05/30/rate-shock-in-california-obamacare-to-increase-individual-insurance-premiums-by-64-146/</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1370024330446</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:18:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370024392348-32</Id><Title>California Obamacare premiums to increase premiums 64-146%.</Title><Msg>Once again the Dems lie. http://www.forbes.com/sites/theapothecary/2013/05/30/rate-shock-in-california-obamacare-to-increase-individual-insurance-premiums-by-64-146/</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1370024392348</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370025298714-33</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no dumbo, you are wrong and so is the Forbes Op-ed piece and YOU can find out for yourself by going to Covered California and using their calculator to find your rate for a GOOD policy.... the rate for me is SEVERAL HUNDRED DOLLARS a month less (with no subsidy) than what my employer and I now pay ....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370025298714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:34:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370025391779-34</Id><Title>MISM looks prime for a huge breakout</Title><Msg>MISM looks like it is about to run. Do some DD on it. We could see an easy double from these levels</Msg><Username>melijah982</Username><Timestamp>1370025391779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370025429364-35</Id><Title>You need to start your research on MISM right away!</Title><Msg>I heard there is a massive promo coming into MISM. Keep an eye on it</Msg><Username>melijah982</Username><Timestamp>1370025429364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370025589305-36</Id><Topic><Title>all 13 bush benghazis could have been prevented</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370005788236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jeez, fyi, there is NO scandal about bengazi, it is ALL gop posturing and lies. 1. Obama said it was a terror attack the same day.... 2. CIA sent an armed response withing 25 minutes and it was UNHINDERED and IN CONTROL now, what is the scandal again? and just how is that embassy attack any different that the 13 or more that happened on W's watch or the Beirut Bombing which the local marine commander blamed on REAGAN????</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370025589305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370025957022-37</Id><Title>what is the "scandal" about Benghazi?</Title><Msg>there is NO scandal about bengazi, it is ALL gop posturing and lies. Obama said it was a terror attack the same day.... CIA sent an armed response within 25 minutes and it was UNHINDERED and IN CONTROL please explain yourselves you posturing ,phony, grandstanding, lying hissy fits. ( and please no bs about how YOU in hindsight would have charged in and saved the day.... cause YOU didn't do that in any of the 13 benghazis during Bush's watch)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370025957022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:45:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370027189961-38</Id><Topic><Title>what is the "scandal" about Benghazi?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370025957022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's getting to you, eh Mesa? You squeal like a stuck pig. You are worried.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1370027189961</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370028509243-39</Id><Topic><Title>all 13 bush benghazis could have been prevented</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370005788236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, your pants are on fire. Is that what your handlers are telling you? Who is being dishonest? You phony..... Obama said it was due to an anti-muslim video and Susan Rice mimicked him. The CIA wasn't in the loop prior to Hillary's finding reason not to send reinforcements requested by Embassy employees. I already told you what the differences were and so did other posters, you impaired dunce. OK, we won't call it a scandal, How about dereliction of duty, and incompetency worth booting from the top down. The families want answers and justice, not lies and stonewalling. You against that?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370028509243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370029653627-40</Id><Topic><Title>what is the "scandal" about Benghazi?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370025957022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, he made one reference to terror the next day and then for the next 2 or 3 weeks he blamed it on a video that no one saw. There was no more mention of terror for weeks.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1370029653627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370030175274-41</Id><Topic><Title>what is the "scandal" about Benghazi?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370025957022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jeez, what a crock. Your 'scandal' is what an attack on an embassy is called the day after it was called a terror attack? what did you think it was , the welcome wagon, avon calling? that's it ? you bums are convening panels and going apeshit over nothing obviously.... the day after 911 Bush told every to just go shopping and carry on as usual.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370030175274</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:56:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370031250938-42</Id><Title>GOP is so lame they can't even impeach Obama, ha ha ha</Title><Msg>pubbbies are such phonies that they go on and on with lies and innuendo, no evidence of any wrong doing at all, else they would have showed it and voted to impeach....... but they are all TALK.... there IS NO evidence of any Obama wrong doing or that he was born in Kenya.... ha ha ha.. hey where is the evidence?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370031250938</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370037848365-43</Id><Title>"Benghazi" only occurred once-under Obama-due to three levels of  failure and negligence of leadership</Title><Msg>Benghazi consisted of three screw-ups: 1)did not protect  the facilities despite virtual begging for more from the Ambassador 2)did not come, or even attempt,  to rescue the 30 people 3)covered-up and lied to the American public about it, spun it, continue to lie and cover up the truth behind the entire event Also, because of 1 &amp; 2 above, 4 Americans died unneccessarily. Then, to compound it all, Obama and Hilary lied to the families of the dead Americans to their face.</Msg><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1370037848365</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370038029330-44</Id><Title>Can anyone post a tape transcript where Obama called Benghazi a terrorist attack?</Title><Msg>Because we all know it never happened. He made a general comment about responses to terrorist attacks, and that is it. It was a Clintonian attempt at havingbhis cake and eating it, too, and it failed miserably as he continued to blame the video for weeks.</Msg><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1370038029330</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:07:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370041407605-45</Id><Title>NO scandal about bengazi, it is ALL gop posturing and lies. Another mesa dropkick pauper!</Title><Msg>Even some repubs are warning the idiots to tone it down. Obama playing ROPADOPE! Rope a bunch of repub dopes. Think about it idiots!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370041407605</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370041525176-46</Id><Title>Benghazi consisted of three screw-ups:/when another 9/1/01 happens and Obama ignored tons of warnings</Title><Msg>as bgroup did then let me know.otherwise,,,,shut up.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370041525176</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370043651942-47</Id><Title>Can anyone post a tape transcript where Obama called Benghazi a terrorist attack?.</Title><Msg>Go GOOG it. He said what it was and it was good enough for me and that's because I am not a stinking lying partisan stinking repub.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370043651942</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370043988866-48</Id><Title>Can anyone post a tape of bush sitting there reading a childrens book here in Sarsota not knowing what to do next after hearing about</Title><Msg>planes smashing WTC tower? How about when bgroup lied saying they never heard any threats about terror prior to 9/11, how about bgroup claiming they'd get bin Laden dead or alive..then saying he didn't matter,..how about bgroup starting war in Afghanistan then blowing it off and leaving it a mess, how about bgroup starting unnecssary war in Iraq where 5,000 more US died than at Benghazi.give up.ya got NUTHIN! Nice dropkick pauper.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370043988866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370044164310-49</Id><Title>repubs.ya got nuthin, ya never had anything and ya never will have anything</Title><Msg>You suck!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370044164310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370044409100-50</Id><Title>I Will Post This As Many Times As Messy Lies About It</Title><Msg>He says there is no scandal, says Obama said it was a terrorist attack the same day, says the CIA sent armed response within 25 minutes. Your pants are on fire, DA. Is that what your handlers are telling you? You really are an Obamie zombie. Obama said it more than once that it was because of an anti-muslim video and Susan Rice mimicked him. He didn't want to admit what it really was after bragging he had seriously hampered Al Queda's reach. The CIA wasn't in the loop prior to Hillary finding a reason not to send in reinforcements requested by embassy employees. The CIA entered when they were given permission, after it was over. The whistleblowers are contradicting your version. idiot. OK, we won't call it a scandal, How about dereliction of job responsibility and incompetency worth booting from the top down? The families want answers and justice, not lies and stonewalling. You against that? I love SMACKING these goons with reality. It's my calling. Whoop!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370044409100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370047694614-51</Id><Topic><Title>I Will Post This As Many Times As Messy Lies About It</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370044409100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:53:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They hung the guy out to dry. He knew too much about the weapons transhipments to Al Queda and the Muslim Brotherhood in Syria. The idiots are playing with Armageddon. The Russians are now involved and arming Assad. Assad is no good but what "our?" government is trying to replace him with is far worse. Look what happened in Egypt. Coptic Christians who had pretty much lived in peace for centuries there are now being raped, robbed and murdered. This government helped bring it about Livrer Lips is just a front for those that really control this country.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1370047694614</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370050121049-52</Id><Topic><Title>GOP is so lame they can't even impeach Obama, ha ha ha</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370031250938</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:14:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IRS commish goes to Blackhouse 157 times, more than Mouchelle has in the last few years. Guess they could not settle on a date for their golf match. Hahahahahahahahaha...... The screws are turning tighter bubba. Your boy is not being too transparent now, is he?</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370050121049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370050217622-53</Id><Topic><Title>what is the "scandal" about Benghazi?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370025957022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lies, damn lies, and Obummer lies. Oh, And statistics.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370050217622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370050368897-54</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just heard on PMSNBC that insurance prices have gone up 143 percent in the past year. Everybody gearing up for the ABYSS.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370050368897</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370050518404-55</Id><Topic><Title>all 13 bush benghazis could have been prevented</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370005788236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's see. Fast and Furious fiasco, IRS fiasco, AP fiasco, James Rosen fiasco, Benghazi fiasco. Did I miss any. More to come, stay tuned.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370050518404</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370053048330-56</Id><Topic><Title>all 13 bush benghazis could have been prevented</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370005788236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and all nothing but loser gop hissy fits...... trying to make up for the birther hissie fit.... all you are doing is proving to decent Americans that you and your ilk are loser grandstanding phonies, but have it your way...... and still Obama will be here 3 more years...... ha ha ha....... and everyone can see what a bunch of creepy bums you are.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370053048330</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 22:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370058664444-57</Id><Title>Just heard on PMSNBC that insurance prices have gone up 143 percent in the past year</Title><Msg>Oh shut up........majority of the time we've had repubs in WH during past 30 plus years and look at what HC Costs have done. Here in Fl repubs have bee completely in charge and look at all our taxes///you're a repub partisan lying dummy.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370058664444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370058808800-58</Id><Title>Greta Van Susteren, Megyn Kelly Slam Male Fox News Colleagues for Breadwinner Comments</Title><Msg>That's a good one.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370058808800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:53:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>