<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370928101394-1</Id><Title>Lindsey Graham ‘glad’ NSA tracking phones</Title><Msg>ALL reoubs were happy with it when bgroup did it</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370928101394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 01:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370931573984-2</Id><Topic><Title>what traders dont know!</Title><Username>rogerblack750</Username><Timestamp>1369796530470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i SIGNED up!</Msg><Username>blazertrail689</Username><Timestamp>1370931573984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 02:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370949920954-3</Id><Title>stinkingrepubs...........</Title><Msg>I haven't noticed a SINGLE ONE OF YOU praise and THANK Obama for getting the S&amp;P upgrade. Oddly enough when bgroup caused the downgrades you spewed on and on about it and blamed Obama! DROPKICK PAUPER~</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370949920954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 07:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370950114870-4</Id><Title>Squeal goon, squeal. Says assbukeroo</Title><Msg>You're an annoying, childish, ignorant and stupid repub and likely are about 19 years old.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370950114870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 07:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370950509551-5</Id><Topic><Title>Lindsey Graham ‘glad’ NSA tracking phones</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370928101394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 01:21:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually I don't think we are all that unhappy with it now, per se. Here's the problem that troubles. In light of the IRS targeting conservative groups and individuals for political puropses, plenty of folks are aghast that the gov can use the metadata in the same way. The gov can't be trusted, they say. It is a valid concern, though you won't agree that it is.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1370950509551</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 07:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370952326569-6</Id><Title>apparently Snowden wants to go to Russia</Title><Msg>and Russia is considering giving him asylum.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1370952326569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 08:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370955292469-7</Id><Title>You don’t want to miss out on SLIO</Title><Msg>SLIO looks like the only legit company on the entire OTC. Check out their website. SLIO looks ready to head higher</Msg><Username>hnelson668</Username><Timestamp>1370955292469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 08:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370955694552-8</Id><Topic><Title>the data mining was the very same BEFORE Obama</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370899084244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure garbage, mesa! Indeed, laughable! You never fail... always 100% predictable!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1370955694552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:01:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370955695539-9</Id><Topic><Title>Lindsey Graham ‘glad’ NSA tracking phones</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370928101394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 01:21:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and "we"... you always speak of "we"... that's how nutty you are...... YOU want to play footsie with terrorists, obviously///////// and did YOU miss it, shizer for brains that Newt defended this, and Mittens did and just about every pub in the congress........ I guess you...know better how to protect the nation.... funny how you said nothing when bush was doing the same as was pointed out, IT WAS THE SAME,......Senator Saxby Chambliss: "This is nothing particularly new. This has been going on for seven years under the auspices of the FISA authority and every member of the United States Senate has been advised of this." he sits on the intel committee............................he sais that a couple days ago so how does your "we" want to protect America from terrorists? do tell...... who is the "WE " of whom you speak, btw?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370955695539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370955906513-10</Id><Title>rightwingers just can't be trusted</Title><Msg>there were no "157 visits to the WH" rightwinger lie all the time, they seem to go around with the letter "B" carved on their face or muttering about the mau mau from Kenya.....jeez.....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370955906513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370955955703-11</Id><Topic><Title>apparently Snowden wants to go to Russia</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1370952326569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 08:05:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd bet $100 that both Russia and China are doing dramatically less data-mining of their own people than America, under Obama! For starters, they totally reject the PC Pigshyt stupidity of NOT "Profiling" threats and those posing the threats!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1370955955703</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:05:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370956162980-12</Id><Title>In the Bush era Pubs approved of the NSA surveillance program &amp; and dems disapproved</Title><Msg>this whole fake "scandal" is nothing but partisan bs. "Pew is out with the first poll asking the public what it thinks of the NSA phone record surveillance program. Unsurprisingly, the public thinks it's just peachy, by a margin of 56-41. What is surprising, though, is the epic size of the change in partisan attitudes since 2006. Back then, Republicans approved of the (recently revealed) NSA program by 38 points more than Democrats. Now, Republicans disapprove by 12 points more than Democrats. . Basically, when Bush was president, Republicans thought that monitoring telephone traffic was a great idea. Now, when Obama is president, they're not so sure—but Democrats think it's fine and dandy. This is about as remarkable a turnaround as I've seen on any subject in recent years." Bottom line, as long as they're not listening to your calls sans a warrant, no one cares. The phone co. log who you dial and for how long , for billing, service and marketing anyway, assumption Gvt. can get this is assumed</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370956162980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:09:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370956922386-13</Id><Topic><Title>In the Bush era Pubs approved of the NSA surveillance program &amp; and dems disapproved</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370956162980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this whole fake "scandal" is nothing but partisan bs. Of course it is.The Pukes ARE nothing,HAVE nothing,and will HAVE nothing in the near future.They always resort to this kind of childish behavior when the Dems are running the country,gradually pulling America out of the HOLE the corrupy Bush regime put her in.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1370956922386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:22:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370957025001-14</Id><Topic><Title>rightwingers just can't be trusted</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370955906513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:05:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rightwingers just can't be trusted They NEVER could be trusted,EVER.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1370957025001</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370957155850-15</Id><Title>right wing "hero" snowden is a traitor and grandstanding creep</Title><Msg>first he runs to a place run by the People's Liberation Army who took over in Hong Kong after the British army left in 1997..........now he want to run to Russia.......he is a crackpot traitor and loser ala........Lee Harvey Oswald Donald Trump. even got this one right: The once and possibly future presidential candidate and reality TV host isn’t a big fan of Edward Snowden, . “To me, he looks like a grandstander,” he told Fox News</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370957155850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370957222160-16</Id><Topic><Title>Squeal goon, squeal. Says assbukeroo</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370950114870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 07:28:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're an annoying, childish, ignorant and stupid repub and likely are about 19 years old. Trust me,that IDIOT is NO more than12,with an IQ of about the same.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1370957222160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370957251397-17</Id><Title>Michael Moore agrees with Glenn Beck. Trump &amp; coulter and the WSJ and obama agree otherwise</Title><Msg>You can draw your own opinions based on the following quotes of a bunch of famous people and news organizations who are wildly split on the NSA snooping issue. 1. Donald Trump. The once and possibly future presidential candidate and reality TV host isn’t a big fan of Edward Snowden, the former CIA analyst who leaked the classified info about the NSA. “To me, he looks like a grandstander,” he told Fox News. 2. Michael Moore. Snowden is “Hero of the Year,” says Moore on Twitter. 3. Ann Coulter. She believes the type of intelligence gathered by the NSA is OK, if it’s done by the right kind of administration. “You need a virtuous man in the presidency, so choose wisely next time, America,” she told Fox News. 4. Jack Welch. The former head of General Electric and former Obama critic on Twitter: “Two Presidents, and multiple split Congress’ all agree we need. Good enough for me.” 5. Glenn Beck. “I think I have just read about the man for which I have waited. Earmarks of a real hero,” Beck said on Twitter about Snowden. 6. The WSJ Editorial Board. The Journal editorial staff argues that the Obama data-mining operation is “legal and necessary” for national security. 7. The New York Times Editorial Board. The editorial says, “The administration has now lost all credibility on this issue” after saying something stronger (before a copy edit). 8. President Barack Obama. “You can’t have 100 percent security and also then have 100 percent privacy and zero inconvenience. We’re going to have to make some choices as a society. There are trade-offs involved,” the president said in defending the program. 9. Senator Dianne Feinstein. “Terrorists will come after us if they can and the only thing we have to deter this is good intelligence,” says Feinstein, who co-chairs the committee that oversees the program for Congress. 10. Senator Saxby Chambliss. “It has proved meritorious because we have gathered significant information on bad guys, but only on bad guys, over the years,”</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370957251397</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370957276309-18</Id><Topic><Title>In the Bush era Pubs approved of the NSA surveillance program &amp; and dems disapproved</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370956162980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Total Pigshyt! Neither of you PC Azzswipes have a FING clue!! Both the implementation and capability of data-mining and surveillance of US citizens by their Government has expanded exponentially under your Constitutional Raping Pig in the White House!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1370957276309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370957346160-19</Id><Topic><Title>right wing "hero" snowden is a traitor and grandstanding creep</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370957155850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To me, he looks like a grandstander And who would know more about grandstanding than the Puke Donald?</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1370957346160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:29:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370957889073-20</Id><Topic><Title>In the Bush era Pubs approved of the NSA surveillance program &amp; and dems disapproved</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370956162980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope, you are a LIAR... and doofus even the pubs on intel committee say IT IS THE VERY SAME THING...get it stupid?.... THEY are doing EXACTLY the same thing... but sure computers are faster now...jeez.......and MORON ...... McCain and mitten's would have been presiding over the same were they not LOSERS......so I guess they are also "Constitutional Raping Pig "..... same as YOU are , since YOU supported the SAME things being done by Bush who was also a "Constitutional Raping Pig "..... (and the liar who said "we don't torture".......)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370957889073</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370958123668-21</Id><Topic><Title>the data mining was the very same BEFORE Obama</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370899084244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>take it up with the gop on the intel committee who say that the current program is "nothing new".......I guess you just can't help throwing your skirt up, and wadding your panties for no reason ..... It's just a stupid bad habit, so please stop. Try being honest and using your brain once in awhile.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370958123668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370959905487-22</Id><Title>All signs point to a huge run in SLIO</Title><Msg>SLIO is the stock to watch. Financials show some huge assets along with proven mining properties. You need to start some research on SLIO, could be the next mining play to really make investors rich</Msg><Username>matthewwoodward928</Username><Timestamp>1370959905487</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 10:11:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370959952213-23</Id><Title>Do some DD on SLIO. Looks ready to run.</Title><Msg>NEED to check out SLIO. Huge assets on their books + gold mines that are tested and confirmed to have gold and silver. It wotn last long once investors take notice</Msg><Username>matthewwoodward928</Username><Timestamp>1370959952213</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 10:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370960971229-24</Id><Topic><Title>In the Bush era Pubs approved of the NSA surveillance program &amp; and dems disapproved</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370956162980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats Love Gov't Surveillance -- As Long As It's Obama, Not Bush...</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1370960971229</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 10:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370963842552-25</Id><Topic><Title>the data mining was the very same BEFORE Obama</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370899084244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right azzswipe... it's not "new"... but it is dramatically larger, wider and deeper, which is what you'd expect with wannabee fascists running the Government!! Comprende Pig??</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1370963842552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 11:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370965246102-26</Id><Title>BREAKING NEWS! SEX SCANDAL AT CLINTON STATE DEPT!</Title><Msg>Major Dem contributor, made ambassador, has sex withprostitutes and underage children. Memos direct from Hillary, "Stop your investigation!" Hillary is a sex pervert enabler!!!!!</Msg><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370965246102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 11:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370965378580-27</Id><Topic><Title>the data mining was the very same BEFORE Obama</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370899084244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't matter! WE'VE GOT OBAMA FOR IT! I say hang him by the neck until dead, then maybe even John Boehner will figure it out!</Msg><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370965378580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 11:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370966416367-28</Id><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close!</Title><Msg>Every stinking Terrorist on the planet, certainly any linked to al-Qaeda, has known for YEARS that we have been tracking them, their phones, their conversations, emails, internet activity, addresses, whereabouts and that of most of their relatives and friends! Snowden has not told them one thing of significance that they had not already known... in spades... or put a single American in danger, save of course for the 21st century neo-fascists now running our Government!!! What he did tell us, and the world, is that our Government, under the leadership of our Uber Wunderbar Constitutional Scholar &amp; Moralist, has expanded the tracking and tracing of American citizens, exponentially, on all 310,000,000 of us... and is using all aspects of HIS Governmental power to destroy and undermine his enemies (aka all those who don't agree him and kiss his skinny azzs!)! Indeed, the real TRAITORS are those who leaked, even proclaimed, that Bin Laden was put down by Seal Team Six... an act of Treason and utter Stupidity that got 18 of them (Seals) butchered in a "Revenge" hit by al-Qaeda, along with a dozen other Americans, 30 in total! And those Traitors include Obama, Biden, Clinton, Panetta and others. Real Traitors are those who deliberately denied needed protections to our Embassy staff in Libya and got 4 of them, our Ambassador included, butchered.... and further, never bothered to lift a helping hand to save them!! Clinton, Obama and several Generals are the real traitors!. Real Traitors are also those like Eric Holder, who deliberately lied to a US Court about the 'criminal threat' posed by a FOX journalist, James Rosen, getting him and his family put under Government surveillance for months! Real Traitors sick the IRS on Conservatives! We now have a Government filled with Traitors... certainly at and near the top of many Departments and Agencies!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1370966416367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370966886021-29</Id><Topic><Title>Squeal goon, squeal. Says assbukeroo</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1370950114870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 07:28:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like annoying you and causing your head to explode while posting frantically 50 times about how you hate Repubs and then you reply back agreeing with yourself. Great way to spend a summer day. DA And you're so mature with "dropkick pauper", "shove it up your corpis dabien" , "you suck". ( Hahahahahaha! That was a dropkick) Just dummy up before I have to SMACK you around again, twerp.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370966886021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370967380471-30</Id><Title>Repeal teh 13th amendment.</Title><Msg>It only takes a 2/3rds vote of the House and Senate to repeal the 13th Amendment. What is the downside? Crime will drop, schools will improve, welfare will drop, and unemployment will drop.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1370967380471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:16:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370967441069-31</Id><Title>APRI impotence drug got approval for EU</Title><Msg>200 soon</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1370967441069</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370968402789-32</Id><Title>BIZM way to go</Title><Msg>very serious</Msg><Username>election00</Username><Timestamp>1370968402789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370968477231-33</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1370966416367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Americans have not been put at risk by Snowden! They have been put at risk and in jeopardy by their own Government! Obama, Biden, Holder, Dempsey, Reid, Pelosi, King, Graham, McCain, Boehner and most Capitol Hill Democrats are full of Shyt and worse, they are the Problem... and the biggest Threat!!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1370968477231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370969544277-34</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1370966416367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The rats are in the government from top to bottom and both parties. Their is a corrupt cabal that has run this country from behind the scenes for a very long time. Time to give them the old heave ho.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1370969544277</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370970031219-35</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1370966416367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They've been selling us out to the NWO crowd for a long time. It's composed of an international gang of thieves and usurors. They were behind most of the worlds dictators with money. Trotsky was financed by a New York bankster named Jacob Schiff. Brown Bros. Harriman Bank and Prescott Bush were aiding and abetting Hitler in 1940. Article in the San Diego Union a few years back titled "Mao's American Friends". listed an even dozen of left wing "intellectuals" that were advising Mao Tse Tung while he murdered 50 million of his own people They were all of the same ilk but one. This ilk is still aiding and abetting the chi-coms. Diane Feinstein and hubby have made billions from several corporations they operate in China undercutting American business and workers. These are the people that should be charged.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1370970031219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370970249464-36</Id><Topic><Title>the data mining was the very same BEFORE Obama</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370899084244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plan B: In latenight announcement, Obama allows morning-after abortion pill for under-17s... UPDATE: Soldier Who Read Conservative Books Faces Charges... US Ambassador to Belgium 'Solicited Prostitutes, Including Minors': State Dept IG...</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1370970249464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:04:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370970506143-37</Id><Topic><Title>the data mining was the very same BEFORE Obama</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370899084244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got news for you. They've been spying on people for as far back as you can count. They watched peoples mail. They tracked them on trips and tapped their phones both legally and illegally. They planted rat finks in groups both left and right. They used paid agentes provocateurs to entrap people. Check out the COINTELPRO operation during the 60's. Some of it came out in a famous case in Greenville, South Carolina years ago.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1370970506143</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:08:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370972248867-38</Id><Topic><Title>the data mining was the very same BEFORE Obama</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370899084244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep. IT IS THE SAME.. and your adjectives "larger, wider and deeper" are meaningless....... what are you even talking about? and as you always say the government can't do anything right so who cares?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370972248867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:37:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370972684279-39</Id><Topic><Title>right wing "hero" snowden is a traitor and grandstanding creep</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370957155850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure, a grandstanding loser who exposed nothing new in an act of criminal espionage and who decides to flee to a place run by communist china and the People's Liberation army and then applies to commnunist Russia for protection is not a traitor...... how much do you want to bet he is offering the Russians USA spy tech secrets to boost his appeal to them?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370972684279</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370973260706-40</Id><Title>In the war on terrorism some Americans are willing to make sacrifices, others are too fluffy.......</Title><Msg>Some Americans risk their lives in Bushraq and Bushghanistan and fighting the blowback terrorism...... Others whine about data mining, which they mistakenly think means they have lost some precious privacy.... let these whiners and crybabies serve in the military and see how much privacy they are entitled to. one solution to having to use such measures to protect the USA would be to BRING ALL US TROOPS HOME from countries were the locals are fighting them.... like Bushghanistan for instance.... close all US based and stop all us aid to the mid east and Israel.... that would help too.......... how about it you whiners who don't want to serve or even sacrifice your privacy or even pay more taxes to pay for the wars.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370973260706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370974172890-41</Id><Topic><Title>right wing "hero" snowden is a traitor and grandstanding creep</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370957155850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Snowden a Traitor?? Pighshyt! Every stinking Terrorist on the planet, certainly any linked to al-Qaeda, has known for YEARS that we have been tracking them, their phones, their conversations, emails, internet activity, addresses, whereabouts and that of most of their relatives and friends! Snowden has not told them one thing of significance that they had not already known... in spades... or put a single American in danger, save of course for the 21st century neo-fascists now running our Government!!! What he did tell us, and the world, is that our Government, under the leadership of our Uber Wunderbar Constitutional Scholar &amp; Moralist, Barack The Magnificent, has expanded the tracking and tracing of American citizens, exponentially, on all 310,000,000 of us... and is using all aspects of HIS Governmental power to destroy and undermine his enemies (aka all those who don't agree him and kiss his skinny azzs!)! Indeed, the real TRAITORS are those who leaked, even proclaimed, that Bin Laden was put down by "Seal Team Six"... an act of Treason and utter Stupidity that got 18 of them (Seals) butchered in a "Revenge" hit by al-Qaeda, along with a dozen other Americans, 30 in total! And those Traitors include Obama, Biden, Clinton and Panetta. Real Traitors are those who deliberately denied needed protections to our Embassy staff in Libya and got 4 of them, our Ambassador included, butchered.... and then, never bothered to lift a helping hand to save any of them!! Clinton, Obama and Dempsey are the real traitors!. Real Traitors are also those like Eric Holder who deliberately lied to a US Court about the 'criminal threat' posed by a FOX journalist, James Rosen, getting him and his family put under Government surveillance for months! Real Traitors sick the IRS on Conservatives! We now have a Government filled with and lead by Traitors... not only in the White House in many Departments and Agencies!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370974172890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370975045291-42</Id><Topic><Title>right wing "hero" snowden is a traitor and grandstanding creep</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370957155850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there you go again sgt Shultz, thinking you are colonel klink.......stick within your paygrade.....latrine detail, kp, and police call....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370975045291</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370977682924-43</Id><Topic><Title>right wing "hero" snowden is a traitor and grandstanding creep</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370957155850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White House press secretary Jay Carney said Tuesday that there is an "active investigation" underway following a report that inspector general probes of potential misconduct by State Department personnel were influenced, manipulated or called off improperly by the White House. CBS News, citing an internal State Department Inspector General's memo, reported that senior State Department officials encouraged IG investigators to back off or shutdown investigations of allegations that a State security official in Beirut "engaged in sexual assaults" and that members of former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton's security detail "engaged prostitutes while on official trips in foreign countries." The report also alleges that investigators were told to stop looking into allegations that an ambassador routinely ditched his security detail to solicit sex from prostitutes, and that the ambassador was called to Washington to meet with Undersecretary of State Patrick Kennedy but was allowed to return to his post.</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1370977682924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:08:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370977769374-44</Id><Title>Anyone on here actually here to talk about ORCL?</Title><Msg>Just curious.</Msg><Username>rocket455bc</Username><Timestamp>1370977769374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370978430063-45</Id><Title>OT: Fun,Profit, and Action$$ Check out RAYS....Small float Way Oversold and Short Squeeze$$$...</Title><Msg>HUGE PROFITS will be Made$$$$</Msg><Username>steveboonlertheidbrider</Username><Timestamp>1370978430063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370980490732-46</Id><Topic><Title>what traders dont know!</Title><Username>rogerblack750</Username><Timestamp>1369796530470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THANKS, i signed up</Msg><Username>tough.money</Username><Timestamp>1370980490732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370984343643-47</Id><Topic><Title>right wing "hero" snowden is a traitor and grandstanding creep</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370957155850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Messybird, 1984 is here. Watch what you say, what you do, what you email, what you text. Big brother........</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370984343643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 16:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370984459235-48</Id><Topic><Title>In the war on terrorism some Americans are willing to make sacrifices, others are too fluffy.......</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370973260706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:54:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would no more trust this Mooslim administration than I would trust the devil. Oops, about the same thing. You give up your basic freedoms, I'll keep mine.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370984459235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 17:00:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370984524739-49</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING NEWS! SEX SCANDAL AT CLINTON STATE DEPT!</Title><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370965246102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 11:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, at least we know she is asexual.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370984524739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 17:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370984925494-50</Id><Topic><Title>In the Bush era Pubs approved of the NSA surveillance program &amp; and dems disapproved</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370956162980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intel committee members just covering their arse. They know it's overly comprehensive and dangerous to the American public. Too much information uncovered that could result in blackmail. This program was not specific as was Bush's. And Bush was an American, not Mooslim.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370984925494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 17:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370998367120-51</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1370966416367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Snowden should be awarded the Medal of Freedom!</Msg><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1370998367120</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 20:52:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370998427453-52</Id><Title>the data mining was the very same BEFORE Obama</Title><Msg>Detoxx345 thinks that repeating this lie over and over will cause someone to believe him!</Msg><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1370998427453</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 20:53:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371000506464-53</Id><Title>"This is nothing particularly new"</Title><Msg>Senator Saxby Chambliss: "This is nothing particularly new. This has been going on for seven years under the auspices of the FISA authority and every member of the United States Senate has been advised of this." some here are of the opinion that this wasn't going on before. The same people who had the opinion that Obama is a Kenyan, people walk with dinosaurs and that a computer made in 2013 is not essentially the same as a computer made in 2005.......These people are not honest and have no common sense. The fact is : "This is nothing particularly new"............period.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371000506464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 21:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371002942277-54</Id><Topic><Title>"This is nothing particularly new"</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371000506464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 21:28:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great that you are starting to see the wisdom of so many Republicans. Just great.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371002942277</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371003226833-55</Id><Title>we're broke so let's get rid of homeland security......</Title><Msg>"Since 9/11 the United States has spent a staggering $791 billion on homeland security" our well armed citizenry can handle it, so let's defund homeland security...right? call it part of the sequester</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371003226833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371003443233-56</Id><Topic><Title>rightwingers just can't be trusted</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370955906513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:05:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But there are 57 states in the US and the Bummer has visited 56 of them.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371003443233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371004910013-57</Id><Topic><Title>In the Bush era Pubs approved of the NSA surveillance program &amp; and dems disapproved</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370956162980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 09:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>11 Jun 2013, 1:19 PM PDT 781 post a comment In a Gallup tracking poll released Tuesday, former-President George W. Bush currently stands with a favorability rating of 49%, compared to 46% who see the 43rd president unfavorably. Meanwhile, another Gallup poll shows President Obama with only a 47% approval rating, with 44% disapproving.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1371004910013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:41:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371005942421-58</Id><Title>the Bush era Pubs approved of the NSA surveillance program &amp; and dems disapproved</Title><Msg>This is EXACTLY what I always say..repubs are nothing but lying hypocritcal double talkers. EVERYTHING they say is garbage and inconsistent. EVERYTHING. Repubs are nothing but.repubs...they are not conservative.just repubs. Repubism is their only belief and it has nothing to do with being conservative.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371005942421</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371006282894-59</Id><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close! Signed, one of the FATTTTTTEST repub hypocrites here! Or anywhere.</Title><Msg>This fatsoh corpiss called ANYONE who ever even made a slight critical remark about bgroup or the country a treasonous criminal who should be put to death. I CANMNOT believe the repub hypocrites.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371006282894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 23:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>