<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365332923093-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Obama being so cheap on his salary giveback?</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1365280709934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 16:38:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON – After a full year of fruitless job hunting, Natasha Baebler just gave up. She'd already abandoned hope of getting work in her field, working with the disabled. But she couldn't land anything else, either — not even a job interview at a telephone call center. Until she feels confident enough to send out resumes again, she'll get by on food stamps and disability checks from Social Security and live with her parents in St. Louis. "I'm not proud of it," says Baebler, who is in her mid-30s and is blind. "The only way I'm able to sustain any semblance of self-preservation is to rely on government programs that I have no desire to be on." Baebler's frustrating experience has become all too common nearly four years after the Great Recession ended: Many Americans are still so discouraged that they've given up on the job market. Older Americans have retired early. Younger ones have enrolled in school. Others have suspended their job hunt until the employment landscape brightens. Some, like Baebler, are collecting disability checks. It isn't supposed to be this way. After a recession, an improving economy is supposed to bring people back into the job market. Instead, the number of Americans in the labor force — those who have a job or are looking for one — fell by nearly half a million people from February to March, the government said Friday. And the percentage of working-age adults in the labor force — what's called the participation rate — fell to 63.3 percent last month. It's the lowest such figure since May 1979. The falling participation rate tarnished the only apparent good news in the jobs report the Labor Department released Friday: The unemployment rate dropped to a four-year low of 7.6 percent in March from 7.7 in February. People without a job who stop looking for one are no longer counted as unemployed. That's why the U.S. unemployment rate dropped in March despite weak hiring. If the 496,000 who left the labor force last month had still been looking for jobs, the unemployment rate would have risen to 7.9 percent in March. "Unemployment dropped for all the wrong reasons," says Craig Alexander, chief economist with TD Bank Financial Group. "It dropped because more workers stopped looking for jobs. It signaled less confidence and optimism that there are jobs out there."</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1365332923093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 07:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365337937699-2</Id><Title>After a full year of fruitless job hunting, Natasha Baebler just gave up///For one thing, repubs don't care about peoples pain and B.</Title><Msg>During every economic cycle some jobless GIVE UP trying to find work and this is the worst cycle ever because of bush.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365337937699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 08:32:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365339266974-3</Id><Title>how much has Boehner cut his salary to share the sacrifice he imposes on others?</Title><Msg>ZERO, that how much.......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365339266974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 08:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365340385785-4</Id><Title>gop: tax the poor more and cut taxes for the rich.</Title><Msg>Texas gets over half of its tax revenue from sales taxes.... and the poor pay more.. the rich pay less..... Gov Jindal in La,. wants to end state and corporate income tax and get all revenue from a sales tax.... good old gop, always out to make the richer richer and everyone else poorer. In Texas the bottom 20% pay 12.2 % of their income in sales and local tax....quite a burden much more than the richest there who pay 3.3% of their income. Texas's Tax Code: Poor Pay More ......Texas families earning less than $18,000—the poorest fifth of Texas non-elderly taxpayers—pay 12.2 percent of their income in Texas state and local taxes. .......Middle-income Texas taxpayers—those earning between $31,000 and $51,000—pay 8.5 percent of their income in Texas state and local taxes. .........But the richest Texas taxpayers—with incomes exceeding $463,000 per year—pay only 3.3 percent of their income in Texas state and local taxes</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365340385785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365341291146-5</Id><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Msg>let's see how far this goes. Let's see what the people have to say about arresting elected law enforcement types. The sheriffs just following Obama's lead as he ignores the laws he doesn't like. A bill is heading to Colorado Gov. John Hickenlooper’s desk that Republican lawmakers say would give members of the Secret Service broad arrest powers in the state and could provide a framework for federal agents eventually to enforce gun restrictions. “This is absolutely insane,” Rep. Lori Saine, R-Dacono, said. “In theory if a Secret Service agent is in a county where the sheriff has refused to enforce some of the recent unenforceable gun laws, the agent could arrest an individual if he believes the law has been broken.” The idea actually aligns with an Obama agenda to create vast new restrictions and regulations on guns. WND has reported that hundreds of sheriffs nationwide, including many in Colorado, have said they cannot enforce federal restrictions that would violate the Second Amendment.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365342061854-6</Id><Title>Reject Obama plan to use chained cpi to cut social security</Title><Msg>yes I know the gop wants to cut ss more or kill it or gut it......... their usual wrong headed , wrong for America plan... but Obama is wrong to offer cuts to ss and the chained cpi is just plain baloney..... best to raise the limit on ss wages. that fixes SS, period.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365342061854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365343520549-7</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>would you arrest a sheriff that didn't enforce drinking laws? speed limits? I guess you think some people are above the law...... the laws enacted by elected represenatives</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365343520549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:05:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365344335738-8</Id><Title>More Americans Die For Obama's Stupid War In Afghanistna!! "Good War" My Azzs!</Title><Msg>Why anyone in the military and State Dept would agree to be shipped over to this Islamic Rat-Hole is beyond me! They should all refuse... and tell Obama to FOff! There is absolutely NO ZERO NADA reason to continue this Moronic Wasteful Useless Ivy League War of "Nation Building"... save that Obama likes playing God and Targeting Islamists! If he wants to keep spilling American blood in these Islamic Pigsties.... send over the FING Generals and Ivy Leaguers!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1365344335738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365344414614-9</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And laws enforced by elected law enforcement. Would you arrest Obama for not enforcing existing immigration laws? And not just ignoring existing laws. He flaunts that he's not. But it's fine with you that Obama thinks he is above the law. Huh Mesa? You think the people who elelcted the sheriffs won't have something to say?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365344414614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365344846891-10</Id><Title>Not sure why I'm on newsmax email list. Don't want to be. Just moved and have different isp different email yet still</Title><Msg>getting newsmax sleaze. They are the low of the low.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365344846891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365344937724-11</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They claim they enforce laws they don't always agree with. MOST law officers FAVOR more gun laws. Those that don't are repub fanatics.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365344937724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365345262235-12</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>appointed law enforcement will enforce laws. Why? Because appointed Chiefs of Police have an elected boss who care fire the Chief. On the other hand, sheriffs are elected and thier boss is the people. Makes a huge difference. Example: Joe Arpaio couldn't enforce the law as he sees fit if he were appointed.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365345262235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365345720614-13</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jees, you are so stupid, seeburg, really, really stupid......dishonest too...... can you grasp that the very purpose of a sheriff is to enforce the laws enacted by the elected representatives? and as I asked, does a sheriff have to enforce drinking laws or speed limits if he personally doesn't like them, that is just what you advocate isn't it? and btw you are just a liar on immigration. Obama has done MORE deportations than Bush, so you should whine about Bush instead. Obama’s Record-High Deportations Draw Hispanic Scorn The record-setting deportation of illegal immigrants under President Obama has drawn scorn from Hispanic Americans, despite recent administration efforts to temper the policy, according to a new Pew Hispanic Center study. Fifty-nine percent of Latinos said they disapprove of the president’s approach to removing illegal immigrants, more than double the number who said they approved in Pew’s nationwide survey. Among Latino registered voters, the sentiment was nearly as strong, with 52 percent disapproving of the Obama administration’s handling of deportations. Since 2009, the annual average number of deportations has approached 400,000, according to the Department of Homeland Security. That’s double the annual average during President George W. Bush’s first term and 30 percent higher than the average when he left office. ABC NEWS</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365345720614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365345981574-14</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, you stinkin' fool. I just pointed out that Obama ignore laws he doesn;t like. And you don't care. One salient example was the court's decision regarding recess appoiontment of NLRB judge. Court said that appointment was illegal, yet that NLRB official is still there. Obama just ignored that decision. It will be real interesting to see what happens if an elected sheriff is threatened with arrest. You'll hear from the people.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365345981574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365346300704-15</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama won't do anything about the border, will he? Nope. Not a chance of that.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365346300704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365349664194-16</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there you go lying again. It is a fact that Obama deported more illegals than Obama and that there are less illegals coming across the border now. And besides, YOU ARE the one saying law enforcement can just pick and choose to enforce or not enforce, aren't you? See how stupid you are? You are so dishonest you think Obama has announced that he will not enforce illegal border crossings just as the sheriffs you support announced they won't enforce laws they dont' like. That didn't happen, the fact is there are less illegals coming here now, and more are being deported than during the Bush years, nor has Obama said he will refuse to enforce the law... in fact, the gop has the very same policy now, or have you missed that?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365349664194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365350092784-17</Id><Title>Mccain says he agrees with obama on immigration</Title><Msg>McCain: Congress Will Back Immigration Plan Friday, 08 Feb 2013 10:28 PM By Matthew Auerbach Sen. John McCain, R-Ariz., believes Congress will back an immigration reform plan agreed upon by both President Barack Obama and members of the Senate. In an interview with Univision that is scheduled to air Sunday, McCain said he is “cautiously optimistic that with the President and the Senate basically acting together that that would be sufficient to have the House, to agree with that, if it’s reasonable with the majority of the American people.” When asked what he thought might happen if the House voted against immigration reform, McCain hinted at the repercussions of such a result. “Well, I hate to obviously predict what might happen,” he said. “But I think you, I know what you’re referring to, and that is the election results with a smaller number of our Hispanic/Latino citizens that are voting for Republicans. “We understand that.”</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365350092784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365351090969-18</Id><Topic><Title>Not sure why I'm on newsmax email list. Don't want to be. Just moved and have different isp different email yet still</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365344846891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:27:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no doubt newsmax wants you to send them paper money...to get their financial advice on how we are doomed and paper money will be worthless......but you'd better hurry and send them your $29.95 for their pamphlet on how to get rich in the coming collapse............. jeez, aren't they a bunch of creepy, money grubbing liars and phonies? you nailed it "They are the low of the low."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365351090969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 12:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365352244809-19</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's going to get interesting. Let's see how this turns out. Might not be so good for you and the left.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365352244809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 12:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365353268480-20</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are stupid and a liar. FYI STUPID, Obama has not ignored any law. YOU LIE to say he is ignoring a court , he is in fact appealing their decision about the recess appointment get it, you stupid liar? that is not the same as a criminal breaking the law and a sheriff refusing to enforce that law, which IS his job.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365353268480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 12:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365353341325-21</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama doesn't have to announce intentions not to enforce border. He just does it. BTW, you completely ignore the recess appt. issue and the fact that US Court of Appeals said Obama's recess aptt of NLRB official is illegal. Yet that guy is still there. Obama says catch me if you can.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365353341325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 12:49:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365355251650-22</Id><Topic><Title>More Americans Die For Obama's Stupid War In Afghanistna!! "Good War" My Azzs!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1365344335738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:18:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This BS "Nation Building" Stupid War is lost and has become a total waste... and we all know it! Why do we keep kidding ourselves so Obama can look like some 2-bit armchair War Hero... when he is nothing more than a mass murderer... of his own people! Indeed, some of the very the best America has to offer! It boggles my mind why they would fight for him and his useless War! It damn well isn't to "Save America"! The American Press and Media are nothing more than Obama's GD Drug Dealing Pimps &amp; Poodles! Free Press my azzs! They are waggy-tale Lapdog Fascists!</Msg><Username>itsthepress_stupid</Username><Timestamp>1365355251650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 13:20:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365356184358-23</Id><Title>Reagan supported gun controls and wanted ENFORCEMENT of gun control laws</Title><Msg>Reagan penned an op-ed in The New York Times titled "Why I'm for the Brady Bill." and wanted "enforcement mechanism" and that "a uniform standard across the country" was necessary." I think he would fire those stupid sheriffs if they refused.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365356184358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 13:36:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365365779590-24</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH ORCL Analyst Report .</Title><Username>zelmastafford</Username><Timestamp>1361112271314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 09:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well done</Msg><Username>taylormichael528</Username><Timestamp>1365365779590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 16:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365368869336-25</Id><Title>McCain Blasts GOP Threat to Filibuster Gun Bill</Title><Msg>Sen. John McCain on Sunday once again found himself at odds with Republican colleagues Rand Paul and Ted Cruz when he slammed their intention to filibuster any gun legislation. (I guess some bags&amp;pubs are so nuts that they want criminals and the mentally ill to have guns)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365368869336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:07:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365369736315-26</Id><Topic><Title>McCain Blasts GOP Threat to Filibuster Gun Bill</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365368869336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are already background checks for purchase of guns. You need to look into McCain's wife's "Family" connections. They knew a lot about guns. They both attended the 90th birthday party of Joe "Bananas" (Bonanno) a few years back. He was the head of Cosa Nostra in Arizona. McCain's father stopped flights going to the rescue of the U.S.S. Liberty along with LBJ in 1967.</Msg><Username>meanderlohr</Username><Timestamp>1365369736315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:22:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365369762394-27</Id><Title>gop takes wisconsin to 44th in job creation</Title><Msg>nice work gov walker! "After Wisconsin's Gov. Scott Walker published a self-serving editorial in the Milwaukee Journal Sentinel about his budget and all the fabulous things he's done for the state - tax giveaways to corporations, higher taxes for the working poor, cutting the school budget, making the state 44th in the country in job creation - the Green Bay Progressive went through it, point-by-point, to show what a crock it all is. .".................</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365369762394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365370028718-28</Id><Topic><Title>McCain Blasts GOP Threat to Filibuster Gun Bill</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365368869336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Giffords, who was seriously wounded in the head by a mentally ill gunman as she addressed constituents in an Arizona parking lot on Jan. 8, 2011, said in an opinion article for the New York Daily News Sunday that she doesn't remember a time when the nation was as unified on an issue as it is on universal background checks. Giffords said 90 percent of Americans support universal background check legislation, which has yet to be debated in Congress. She cited the Bull Moose Society in saying 74 percent of National Rifle Association members and 72 percent of hunters also support background checks. Giffords criticized the current system wherein responsible gun owners submit to background checks while criminals and the mentally ill are able to simply buy guns, no questions asked, at a gun show or on the Internet. She said other related issues that should be addressed are reform of the mental health system, high-capacity ammunition magazines and the public's access to military assault-type weapons."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365370028718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365370120798-29</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The officers that support those laws are usually appointed. Sheriffs are elected and responsible to their citizens. I'll bet you would have sup[ported his imperial arrogance, King George in 1776. He believed in a disarmed people too. They make better slaves.</Msg><Username>meanderlohr</Username><Timestamp>1365370120798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:28:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365370501093-30</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan supported gun controls and wanted ENFORCEMENT of gun control laws</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365356184358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 13:36:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Certain forms of ammunition have no legitimate sporting, recreational, or self-defense use and thus should be prohibited.” Ronald Reagan Ronnie would have to have those idiot sheriffs fired if they didn't enforce the ban on certain ammo that he wanted to make illegal.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365370501093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365370647659-31</Id><Title>“Certain forms of ammunition have no legitimate sporting, recreational, or self-defense use and thus should be prohibited.” Ronald Reagan</Title><Msg>Reagan advocated the complete ban of certain ammo. I think he would be OK with banning high capacity magazines too.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365370647659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:37:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365371126015-32</Id><Title>gop attorney general wants to make #$%$ s illegal again........bring out the gop bedroom cops...jeez</Title><Msg>Virginia attorney general and Republican gubernatorial candidate Ken Cuccinelli has challenged a court ruling that found the state's strict anti-sodomy laws unconstitutional. Virginia attorney general and Republican gubernatorial candidate Ken Cuccinelli has challenged a court ruling that found the state's strict anti-sodomy laws unconstitutional. Cuccinelli is asking all 15 judges on a federal circuit court to reconsider a three-judge panel's ruling against the Virginia law, which bans oral and anal sex,</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365371126015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365371281198-33</Id><Topic><Title>gop attorney general wants to make #$%$ s illegal again........bring out the gop bedroom cops...jeez</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365371126015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he wants laws against b ............./..L./.........0........../w....................../J/......o......./.b./...s.......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365371281198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365371868901-34</Id><Title>Just the past 3 Democrat Presidents have created 1/2 the current national debt = FACT!</Title><Msg>Let's see, add about $300 billion for Carter, arond $1.5 trillion for Clinton, and around $6 trillion for. Obama, you have an awful lot of debt incurred under just the pas 3 Democrat Presidents. Maybe delucks is too dumb to realize they are Dems????</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365371868901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365372093300-35</Id><Topic><Title>arrest those sheriffs that don't enfoce gun laws</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365341291146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps Napoliano could be arrested for not enforcing several fed laws, not the least of which are the immigration laws and the murdering of a fed law officer statutes. By the way, doesn't posse comitatus prevent enforcement by fed officers unless a State's Governor asks for assistance?</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1365372093300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 18:01:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365372390192-36</Id><Topic><Title>More Americans Die For Obama's Stupid War In Afghanistna!! "Good War" My Azzs!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1365344335738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 10:18:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with both of you. Obama needs to keep his " good war in Afganistan" going so he can keep flying drones and keep supporting the MB in N Afrika and the ME.</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1365372390192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 18:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365372590772-37</Id><Topic><Title>Oh, by definition none of the debt is caused by interes</Title><Username>say92liberals</Username><Timestamp>1365280369891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 16:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is e absolute "truth in accounting". Morons on this board do not grok government accounting at all, but prefer to spew progressive dogma. Go, comrades, go!</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1365372590772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 18:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365372862260-38</Id><Topic><Title>What is so hard to understand that the 1% paying 40% of all taxes now, and only 20% in 1980</Title><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1365108598007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:49:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Basic liberal stupidity? Socialist wants? Desire to tank the entire country! All of the above?</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1365372862260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 18:14:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365376118980-39</Id><Title>What is so hard to understand that the 1% paying 40% of all taxes now, and only 20% in 1...//P'S O S P' s O S!</Title><Msg>Ps O S! YOU and WMT have mae it so those people make no MONEY and PAY no taxes. W'd the think was gonna happen?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365376118980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:08:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365376209997-40</Id><Title>let's see how far this goes. Let's see what the people have to say about arresting elected law enforcement types. //seevbe supports breaking</Title><Msg>LAW!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365376209997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:10:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365376270111-41</Id><Title>seebe most cops want more gun laws..the few that don't are nothing but repub LOONS!</Title><Msg>like YOU?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365376270111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365376402176-42</Id><Title>repubs.. ya made them all; BROKE! HOW can the pay taxes</Title><Msg>IDIOTS!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365376402176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365376537731-43</Id><Title>Oh, by definition ALL the debt us caused by repubs</Title><Msg>Interst from ragun bushe 1/3 the debt RIGHT THERE!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365376537731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365376640353-44</Id><Title>More Americans Die For Obama's Stupid War In Afghanistna!! " Signed corpiss.. AKA... TYMETODIE!</Title><Msg>corpiis.. you'e 100% SCULIARCRAPHD!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365376640353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365376713274-45</Id><Topic><Title>only morons are amazed that taxes have to come from where the money is, at the top</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365280609771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 16:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and ntm that over the last 40 years or so US corporation have cut their taxes in half. many US corporations make many billions of profit but pay zero income tax. many are of theses corporations are liars and cheats who claim that all their profits are really from Bermuda or other tax cheat havens.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365376713274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365376861560-46</Id><Title>even a poor wal mart worker paid more income tax than Bank of America &amp; BOA got billions in welfare</Title><Msg>Bank of America is the #1 largest bank and the 5th largest corporation in our country, holding over $2.2 trillion in assets, and yet it pays less in taxes than the average American household. In fact, the federal government gave Bank of America $2.3 billion in 2009 while it made $4.4 billion in profits. Bank of America is Bad for America. Despite ruining the economy with their reckless greed, Bank of America consistently avoids any form of accountability to the American taxpayer. Bank of America pockets billions in profits and bailouts, but then pays $0 in American taxes and even gets tax refunds.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365376861560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365387141520-47</Id><Topic><Title>even a poor wal mart worker paid more income tax than Bank of America &amp; BOA got billions in welfare</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365376861560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 19:21:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Say it ain't so Joe. Why are all libiots idiots. Why are all libiots idiots. Why are all libiots idiots.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1365387141520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 22:12:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365387276606-48</Id><Topic><Title>only morons are amazed that taxes have to come from where the money is, at the top</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365280609771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 16:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me start with........why are libiots such idiots. Top one-two percent pay over 50 percent of all fed taxes. Let me end with..........why are all libiots such idiots.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1365387276606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 22:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365387395852-49</Id><Topic><Title>gop attorney general wants to make #$%$ s illegal again........bring out the gop bedroom cops...jeez</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365371126015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bet you know a lot about b...../l.......-o........-/w..........jobs.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1365387395852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 22:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365392202441-50</Id><Title>$ 80 million was paid in unemployment to people making more tha a million $'s each</Title><Msg>in 2011</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365392202441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 23:36:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>