<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371023203062-1</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1370966416367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 12:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>During an interview , former Rep. Ron Paul explained that he was concerned about the well-being of National Security Agency whistle-blower Edward Snowden. “I’m worried about that Obama might kill him with a cruise missile or a drone missile,” Paul explained. “I mean we live in a bad time where American citizens don’t even have rights and that they can be killed, but the gentlemen is trying to tell the truth about what’s going on.” Paul added that there were no signs of Snowden defecting to a foreign country, which meant that he was not really a threat.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1371023203062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 03:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371031800087-2</Id><Title>line from Leno</Title><Msg>"People always wanted a president that listens to all Americans. Now we have one."</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371031800087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371032078023-3</Id><Title>Snowden's girl friend Lindsay Mills</Title><Msg>whew! Smoking hot.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371032078023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371033723814-4</Id><Title>I don't hate Tebow and his new job but if I happen to see him PRAYING on the field, I will again</Title><Msg>despise the dude. KEEP your annoying faith to yourself and in church and Tebow followers,,,shut UPPP! I say,,,,,out going Christians are simply insecure with their faith.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371033723814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371033766340-5</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's girl friend Lindsay Mills</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371032078023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:14:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..and some people say you're gay................................just kidding</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371033766340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371034119764-6</Id><Title>People always wanted a president that listens to all Americans. Now we have one."</Title><Msg>Nothing different than what repubs wanted and got with bgroup EXCEPT Obama has NOT started a completely unnecessary war as bgroup did.DROPKICK!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371034119764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371039594502-7</Id><Title>Tebow haters: Do you also hate other athletes when they are interviewed after a game and their</Title><Msg>first words are "I thank God first....", as this is usually the first response about 98% of the time? Even more direct ---- is your Tebow hate based on his color? Racists!</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1371039594502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371040227014-8</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's girl friend Lindsay Mills</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371032078023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:14:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess he decided the grandstanding life of espionage was more important. He seems really hot to live in communist china or communist Russian. I wonder what services he has to trade for commie protection? USA tech secrets?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371040227014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371040438940-9</Id><Topic><Title>we're broke so let's get rid of homeland security......</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371003226833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 22:13:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pub? bags? where is your tantrum over this type of military spending.....just throw a tantrum and sequester all the money going to homeland security... why is boenhner such a weaking when it comes the this kind of spending.... he is quick write bills that cut aid to the poor..... where is the bill cutting the NSA ?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371040438940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371041789098-10</Id><Title>Until you all defend a women's right to medical privacy, you can't be taken seriously on privacy</Title><Msg>this is just more pub &amp; bag partisan whining and hypocrisy.... they were all for data mining, torture, warrantless wire taps and rendition in the bush days............ and they still demand to know what a woman is up to with her doctor...... the pubs and bags demand to know what a woman is talking about with the doc... the doc must report if she wants an abortion and the woman must then attend pub and bag indoctrination sessions............ also note how the pubs and bags are not demanding cuts in military and homeland spending..... why not.... obviously much resources are being used for data mine and etc....why not cut the military and homeland security by the same amount they cut the ATF or the IRS... both those out fits are getting by on the same staff they had decades ago...... do the same with the military return to 1988 or so levels of spending and personnel , do it now!</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371041789098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371042320359-11</Id><Topic><Title>Until you all defend a women's right to medical privacy, you can't be taken seriously on privacy</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371041789098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's a difference between women and girls, Pig! Something you haven't yet figured out!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1371042320359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:05:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371042590566-12</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's girl friend Lindsay Mills</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371032078023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:14:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More like lukewarm!!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1371042590566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371043059259-13</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close! Signed, one of the FATTTTTTEST repub hypocrites here! Or anywhere.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371006282894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 23:04:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every stinking Terrorist on the planet, certainly any linked to al-Qaeda, has known for YEARS that we have been tracking them, their phones, their conversations, emails, Internet activity, addresses, whereabouts and that of most of their relatives and friends! Snowden has not told them one thing of significance that they had not already known... in spades... or put a single American in danger, save of course for the 21st century neo-fascists now running our Government!!! What he did tell us, and the world, is that our Government, under the leadership of our Uber Constitutional Scholar &amp; Moralist, Barack The Magnificent, has expanded the tracking and tracing of American citizens, exponentially, on all 310,000,000 of us... and is using all aspects of HIS Governmental power to destroy and undermine his enemies (aka all those who don't agree him and kiss his skinny azzs!)! Indeed, the real TRAITORS are those who leaked, even proclaimed, that Bin Laden was put down by Seal Team Six... an act of Treason and utter Stupidity that got 18 of them (Seals) butchered in a "Revenge" hit by al-Qaeda, along with a dozen other Americans, 30 in total! And those Traitors include Obama, Biden, Clinton, Panetta and others. Real Traitors are those who deliberately denied needed protections to our Embassy staff in Libya and got 4 of them, our Ambassador included, butchered.... and further, never bothered to lift a helping hand to save them!! Clinton, Obama and several Generals are the real traitors!. Real Traitors are also those like Eric Holder, who deliberately lied to a US Court about the 'criminal threat' posed by a FOX journalist, James Rosen, getting him and his family put under Government surveillance for months! Real Traitors sick the IRS, FBI and HS on conservatives, libertarians and others who don't buy into their PC left spew!! We now have a Government filled with Traitors... not only in the White House but at or near the top of many Departments and Agencies!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371043059259</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:17:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371043321239-14</Id><Topic><Title>Until you all defend a women's right to medical privacy, you can't be taken seriously on privacy</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371041789098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as usual #$%$, you don't make a bit of sense, since in fact...... you phony balony righties are trying to pass all kinds of laws that require the state to be informed of a WOMAN'S medical decision to abort a fetus, and require the woman to also be indoctrinated with a message from you pubs and bags..........get it MORON.... YOU want the STATE to eavesdrop on what goes on between a woman and her doctor........YOU say the STATE has a right to interfere with HER and the DOCTOR's legal and private medical decisions.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371043321239</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371043366454-15</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close! Signed, one of the FATTTTTTEST repub hypocrites here! Or anywhere.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371006282894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 23:04:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe Biden: Minorities will automatically’ turn out for Markey 6/12/13 8:39 AM EDT At a fundraiser for Rep. Ed Markey’s Massachusetts Senate campaign Tuesday, Vice President Joe Biden warned that having President Barack Obama on the ticket will automatically get minority turnout.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1371043366454</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371044437351-16</Id><Title>"I don't want to live in a society that does these sort of things." - Ed Snowden</Title><Msg>he promptly fled to communist China and is seeking asylum in communist Russia. he is a man of principle!</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371044437351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371045269935-17</Id><Title>Prism began in 2007</Title><Msg>[prism] "provides for the targeting of any customers of participating corporations who live outside the United States, or American citizens whose communications include web content of people outside the United States. " According to The Washington Post, the intelligence analysts search PRISM data using terms intended to identify suspicious communications of targets whom the analysts suspect with at least 51 percent confidence to not be United States citizens, but in the process, communication data of some United States citizens are also collected unintentionally.[1 PRISM is a clandestine national security electronic surveillance program operated by the United States National Security Agency (NSA) since 2007.[1][2][3] PRISM is a government codename for a data collection effort known officially as US-984XN.[4][5] Documents leaked by Edward Snowden[6] in June 2013 describe the PRISM program as enabling in-depth surveillance on live communications and stored information. It provides for the targeting of any customers of participating corporations who live outside the United States, or American citizens whose communications include web content of people outside the United States. Data which the NSA is able to obtain with the PRISM program includes email, video and voice chat, videos, photos, voice over IP conversations, file transfers, login notifications and social networking details.[3]</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371045269935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371047084005-18</Id><Topic><Title>"I don't want to live in a society that does these sort of things." - Ed Snowden</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371044437351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oddly enough, Snowden went to work for the spy agency when everyone already knew they where engaged in this type of surveillance, so he choose to be involved with it but changed his mind about Prism which began in 2007, and of course similar had been going on much earlier. "Documents leaked by Edward Snowden[6] in June 2013 describe the PRISM program as enabling in-depth surveillance on live communications and stored information. It provides for the targeting of any customers of participating corporations who live outside the United States, or American citizens whose communications include web content of people outside the United States. Data which the NSA is able to obtain with the PRISM program includes email, video and voice chat, videos, photos, voice over IP conversations, file transfers, login notifications and social networking details.[3]"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371047084005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 10:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371048005402-19</Id><Title>Awesome</Title><Msg>I'm a beginner trader and signed up for their free service. Their picks are always on point. Just Text the word "stocks" without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT and don't miss out</Msg><Username>levipetty903</Username><Timestamp>1371048005402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 10:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371049830718-20</Id><Topic><Title>Until you all defend a women's right to medical privacy, you can't be taken seriously on privacy</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371041789098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poll: Obama's worst rating in Iowa By HADAS GOLD | 6/12/13 10:32 AM EDT A majority of Iowans now disapprove of the man they twice elected president, according to a poll. Poll: Bush favorability hits milestone By BREANNA EDWARDS | 6/12/13 7:13 AM EDT For the first time since 2005, Americans view him more favorably than unfavorably, the survey finds.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1371049830718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371051157516-21</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's girl friend Lindsay Mills</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371032078023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:14:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SNOWDEN: I'M NOT HIDING... More explosive details on US surveillance targets... Says Obama is a plant of the terrorist community.... His plans for the immediate future... Steps he claims the US has taken since he broke cover in Hong Kong... His fears for his family... DEVELOPING...</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1371051157516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371051346831-22</Id><Topic><Title>Until you all defend a women's right to medical privacy, you can't be taken seriously on privacy</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371041789098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A great many cuts could be made. So called "Foreign Aid" is one. Why is it there is enough money to build bomb shelters for people in a certain Mid-East country that are occupying land illegally but not enough to build tornado shelters at schools? We should also do what the Icelanders did. Tell the banksters to shove it. Any debt owed to the private money machine called the "Fed" has benn created fraudulently and should be cancelled fortwith.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371051346831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:35:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371051419444-23</Id><Topic><Title>Until you all defend a women's right to medical privacy, you can't be taken seriously on privacy</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371041789098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All hail to the great "god" Moloch.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371051419444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371051634757-24</Id><Topic><Title>"I don't want to live in a society that does these sort of things." - Ed Snowden</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371044437351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see sales of George Orwell's book, "1984" are going through the ceiling. Orwell was a part of the English gang that is associated with our gang. He knew their plans and how they operated and wrote the book as fiction. But it actually portrays truth. His real name was Eric Bloor.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371051634757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:40:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371051788926-25</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close! Signed, one of the FATTTTTTEST repub hypocrites here! Or anywhere.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371006282894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 23:04:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can believe it. Both parties have been taken over by the NWO crowd that want to rule the world. Do some reading on George Soros and his connections to ACORN and Obama.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371051788926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371052603358-26</Id><Topic><Title>Prism began in 2007</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371045269935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blah, Blah, Blah, Yada, Yada, Yada. Get off your soap box, goon. Some Dems say it's not the same. Like always, your distorted mentality is full of blanks and you ignore the fact that Obama broadened the scope of eavesdropping. AP is not too happy about it. Let the pols sort it out, your hysterical renderings here mean as much as buckwheat and his Bush obsession. Don't you have better things to do? Living on a Yahoo board must broaden your otherwise pitiful life. SMACK!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371052603358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371055509058-27</Id><Title>This Just In</Title><Msg>Outside the Dept of Justice in Wash stands the statue of Lady Justice, the symbol of truth and legal representation. Someone put a clothespin on her nose. SMACK!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371055509058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371056943929-28</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden Is No Traitor! Not Even Close! Signed, one of the FATTTTTTEST repub hypocrites here! Or anywhere.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371006282894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 23:04:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Illegal Crossings Up 9 Percent – No Wonder the GOP Is Leery June 12, 2013 While Americans anxiously scan their gizmos for signs of e-surveillance, thousands of illegals continue to jump the fence at our borders undetected. Increasingly, it looks like the bipartisan push for immigration reform may founder if the Obama administration cannot convince Congress – and especially Republicans – that our borders are secure. Are GOP hold-outs being obstructionist, or are they right to question the White House’s reassurances about ongoing illegal immigration? Republicans are demanding that in return for providing a path to citizenship for the eleven million immigrants in the country illegally – what skeptics call “amnesty” – the Obama administration must guarantee a certain level of security along our borders. Despite Janet Napolitano’s head-scratching assurances that “the border is as secure as it’s ever been,” the agencies involved are waffling. Napolitano, head of Homeland Security, pledged two years ago to develop a rigorous security standard and declared that the former term “operational control” was outmoded.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1371056943929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371057166588-29</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone on here actually here to talk about ORCL?</Title><Username>rocket455bc</Username><Timestamp>1370977769374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republicans are here to talk about ORCL but the Dems hate capitalists and just want to complain about Rs. Dems hate anyone who works and invests their money.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1371057166588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:12:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371057244838-30</Id><Topic><Title>Awesome</Title><Username>levipetty903</Username><Timestamp>1371048005402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 10:40:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice</Msg><Username>wyattmack173</Username><Timestamp>1371057244838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:14:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371057878806-31</Id><Title>Mittens set up some of the first data mining hubs,back when it was considered protecting America to most all</Title><Msg>(so many of you voted for mittens who is your words a fascist and tyrant for doing domestic surveillance ) Romney "was an affirmative, unapologetic proponent of building a domestic surveillance infrastructure" that is "really focused on 'the enemy within.'"" after arriving at the Massachusetts State House, Romney put what he learned into practice. He set up two of the country's first fusion centers, the controversial data-mining hubs that vacuum up and share intelligence from local, state and federal agencies and the private sector to detect terrorist plots. To some, the fusion centers suggest a Big Brother surveillance state. Romney also pushed for them as chairman of a federal task force on intelligence sharing. "He was definitely instrumental in laying the intellectual framework for fusion centers, and the role of state and local law enforcement in domestic counter terrorism and the need for clear guidelines concerning state and local domestic intelligence gathering," Filler said. But, as in other areas of governance where he tended to go it alone, Romney did not confer with state legislators or the public to address concerns about how the centers would affect privacy and civil liberties. He simply issued an executive order. To Carol Rose, executive director of the Massachusetts American Civil Liberties Union, that "penchant for secrecy" characterized Romney's administration. Shortly before he left office, for example, his aides quietly erased all of his administration's electronic records. Romney has said that as president he would continue to develop the fusion centers "and other innovative systems to collect and systematically analyze information about domestic activities." That confirms the worst fears of Rose, whose organization issued a report on surveillance in Massachusetts that raised concerns about the growing "intelligence network" the former governor established.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371057878806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371057992339-32</Id><Title>Tax the poor.</Title><Msg>We should raise taxes on the poor. They contribute nothing to society. They destroy schools and neighborhoods. IN China they tax welfare and tax people who have too many kids.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1371057992339</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371058801832-33</Id><Title>&amp; don't forget. Prism began on W's watch</Title><Msg>Some of you think that if you trade sex for money a few times you are not a prostitute. as if servicing 5 people a day instead of 10 changes anything....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371058801832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371059203986-34</Id><Title>most of you are big pumpers of the military industrial complex that Ike warned of</Title><Msg>you even voted for a guy wanting to spend MORE money on the military industrial cia nsa complex, part of which is the department of homeland security that W and the gop congress created.........Mittens was very hot to do more domestic surveillance to make sure American stays safe.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371059203986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371059307484-35</Id><Topic><Title>most of you are big pumpers of the military industrial complex that Ike warned of</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371059203986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:46:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GREAT. NOw we got Obama and he is doing the same thing and the Dems are taking the hit. LOL at Dems.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1371059307484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371059701647-36</Id><Topic><Title>&amp; don't forget. Prism began on W's watch</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371058801832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like prostitution relates to spying on US citizens? You're in need of serious analysis. You've worn out your hypocrisy DA. It's not the same, and you pretend otherwise, makes you a liar and an Obamie Zombie as in the walking dead, same thing. And don't forget the IRS commissioner visited the WH 854 times.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371059701647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371059838547-37</Id><Topic><Title>most of you are big pumpers of the military industrial complex that Ike warned of</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371059203986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:46:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you just stupid or what? Obama can't run for anything .....jeez..... and the far left have been against the domesting spying and the entire USA military empire for ages..... ....the far right , like YOU are just continuing to make jackasses out of themselves, YOU supported Prism on W's watch (and his invasions and occupations) and NOW you are against it........ ha ha ha...... you are just dishonest grandstanding hypocrites..... and fyi moderates of both parties can see that protecting America means making some sacrifices during a war........and you whine and can't even show how YOU have suffered from Prism .......You are pathetic to whine about your imagined loss of privacy...... how about the troops, did you ever live in a barracks? how about those who have made REAL sacrifices, loss of limb or life........ but sure whine on about poor you.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371059838547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371059972523-38</Id><Topic><Title>&amp; don't forget. Prism began on W's watch</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371058801832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do tell stupid dishonest person , how prism in 2009 was so much more evil than prism in 2008..... see what a stupid sob you are?..........................</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371059972523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:59:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371060591266-39</Id><Title>moderate people understand that war changes our level of accustomed fluffyness</Title><Msg>we might have to make some temporary sacrifices for survival and victory. some might have to risk life and limb fighting the enemy. just being in the military means NO privacy, as anyone who has been in knows. Some of you are so pathetic as to whine about your imagined loss of privacy ( just think of the troops coming home minus limbs to understand REAL sacrifice) Do let me know how your email or whatever to a foreign country or whatever has caused you any grief. and why were many of you OK with these measures in 2008, but in 2009 you say it is suddenly fascist,,? and why did you vote for mittens who is BIG on more money to the military and who supports surveillance?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371060591266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:09:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371060910165-40</Id><Topic><Title>&amp; don't forget. Prism began on W's watch</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371058801832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So did Winning the Iraq War... which your Boy Obama has now lost and left with his tail between his legs... just as he is doing in Afghanistan! That we should keep one American soldier there one more day is a travesty... nothing short of treating our troops like canon fodder for NOTHING!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371060910165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371061604354-41</Id><Topic><Title>The Snowden Diaries</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370883338155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 12:55:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repeated for the liberal goons who need a lesson in "Top Secret" info, which supposedly everyone knew all about it?? Rubbish. It wasn't top secret with Bush, it became that way with Obama as he broadened the purpose. Now that it's come to light liberals have to come up with these bogus assertions that it started with Bush. Well no. it really started with Nixon. And we saw how the goons went bezerk with that.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371061604354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062411949-42</Id><Topic><Title>&amp; don't forget. Prism began on W's watch</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371058801832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biggest difference we had a real president then, he knew US only had 50 states, not 57. You trust the Kenyan, Ill trust the Texan.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371062411949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:40:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062566495-43</Id><Topic><Title>moderate people understand that war changes our level of accustomed fluffyness</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371060591266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Different times, different president, different collection of information, different trust in our govt. Again, you trust the Kenyan, Ill take the Texan.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371062566495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062744197-44</Id><Topic><Title>most of you are big pumpers of the military industrial complex that Ike warned of</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371059203986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:46:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL @ Dems. YOu still live in high crime ghettos. Your kids go to bad schools. ARe you happy with Obama's Amerika?</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1371062744197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:45:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371062859849-45</Id><Topic><Title>most of you are big pumpers of the military industrial complex that Ike warned of</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371059203986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:46:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of you libiots are big pumpers of expanded govt that all our creators of the Constitution warned us about. You libs will always vote for the guy who wants more taxes, more spending, more waste. Obummer and his mafia are the perfect libiots to drive all these factors. Mittens was hot to bring back personal responsibility to America. Your boy in training is but a LOSER!</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371062859849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371063100840-46</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens set up some of the first data mining hubs,back when it was considered protecting America to most all</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371057878806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ACLU after the Bummer and his Chicago mafia big time. They don't favor taking away American freedoms, just Mooslim freedoms. When the ACLU turns on this libiotic administration, you know they're in trouble.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371063100840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371063248796-47</Id><Topic><Title>Prism began in 2007</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371045269935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buck, enjoy his ignorance. He's but a libiot lemming of the Bummer school of ignorance.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371063248796</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371063948670-48</Id><Topic><Title>Until you all defend a women's right to medical privacy, you can't be taken seriously on privacy</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371041789098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Until everyone in America favors killing the unborn, and even the newly born, libiots cannot be taken seriously on the right to life. Nothing but libiotic buying of votes from the ignorant who have no concept of the importance of life. They are all for killing unborn Americans but want more illegals to come to America. We should all demand what they want in America, a Mooslim state. And note that the libiots favor open borders so we can perhaps take on the mores of Sharia Law, where women have no right, infidels should all be killed, and the Bummer will become their president for life. Why not, it fits in perfectly to the libiotic way of life and has been going on for decades.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371063948670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:05:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371068571273-49</Id><Title>Snowden's storey is not holding up. Turns out he is a bit of a phony. he's not even a High School Grad....</Title><Msg>Nobody's disputing that the documents he leaked BUT some of the explosive details in the initial reporting of his NSA leaks aren't holding up to scrutiny, AND even the story he tells about himself is starting to unravel a bit. 1. Snowden overstated his salary... by a lot We'll start with the most inconsequential, and most easily verifiable, part of Snowden's humblebrag. In his video, Snowden says he is so concerned about exposing the government's overreach he gave up a comfortable life in Hawaii, with his girlfriend and a $200,000-a-year salary. On Monday — to the surprise of no one — his employer, Booz Allen Hamilton, fired him, "for violations of the firm's code of ethics and firm policy." It also casually mentioned his salary — $122,000. Not bad for a high school dropout who had been on the job for three months, but not $200,000, either. "The Guardian, which employs fact-checkers, either did not verify these details about Snowden's story or did not report them," says Joshua Foust at Medium. "How could it have missed such seemingly basic details? And should this call into question other reporting about Snowden and his leaked documents?" 2. Snowden didn't have 'authority' to wiretap anybody and He might not have had the ability to do so, either 3. Snowden's résumé is fishy: Several former CIA officials tell The Washington Post that it seems unlikely that the agency would hire somebody without a high school diploma, especially for a technical job, "and that the terms Snowden used to describe his agency positions did not match internal job descriptions," The Post says. Snowden's claim to have been placed under diplomatic cover for a position in Switzerland after an apparently brief stint at the CIA as a systems administrator also raised suspicion. "I just have never heard of anyone being hired with so little academic credentials," the former CIA official said. The agency does employ technic from 'The Week'</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371068571273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371070723003-50</Id><Title>Perry is "disappointed" Texas not getting Fed money he asked for</Title><Msg>Perry is whining about this.......jeez..... why didn't he just secede or whatever? or demand the money from the plant that blew up the infrastructure....... ala the "free market"...... why are pubs such weasel hypocrites? (Reuters) - The federal government's disaster agency rejected a request for aid to replace infrastructure destroyed near West, Texas, by an April fertilizer plant explosion that killed 14 people, Texas Governor Rick Perry's office said on Wednesday. ..........Additional funds were being sought to rebuild roads, water systems and other public property damaged in the blast. Local officials said costs are approaching $100 million for city and school repairs. A spokesman for Perry said in a statement that the governor was "very disappointed" that the town of West would not get "the assistance they need, qualify for, and deserve." "This explosion has impacted everyone in West in some way, and we are very disappointed that the administration is denying the people of West this important assistance," Perry's spokesman, Josh Havens, said</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371070723003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371071455384-51</Id><Title>Snowden gave up the job he held for 3 months to save our privacy</Title><Msg>and for a high school drop out it was a good job, $122K...... so he puffed that up a tad..i guess he lied to . make him more of a martyr to have given up a really big salary....but heck he was only on the job 3 months,.... maybe he failed the probationary period and they were going to fire him anyway? and to save our privacy he is seeking asylum in communist Russia........that really makes a lot of sense...</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371071455384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:10:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371073358480-52</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden gave up the job he held for 3 months to save our privacy</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371071455384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Communist" Russia? I think that ended a few years back. Proof that leftism doesn't work. Gee, I was a high school drop out too. I passed all my tests in the induction center with such good scores though that I got into the crypto school. They told me I was one of two that had ever gotten in without at least a high school diploma. My dad had a fifth grade education. He ended up as a chief engineer on oceanagraphic ships after retiring as a chief warrant officer with 27 years service in the navy. Love the way "liberals" look down their schnozolas at someone without a bunch of letters after their name. I've run into too many educated idiots to count.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371073358480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371073631241-53</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's storey is not holding up. Turns out he is a bit of a phony. he's not even a High School Grad....</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371068571273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All I ever heard on his salary was the lower figure. Of course you believe every word coming from a government spy agency that ALWAYS tells us the truth? You don't think they might try to discredithim?</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371073631241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:47:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371073922357-54</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden gave up the job he held for 3 months to save our privacy</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371071455384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jeez, are you trying to say Russia went broke with its wars in Afghanistan and its military empire around the world? like you want us doing...... and sure.... Russia is a civil liberties paradise, no wonder Snowden wants to go there, and sure they don't do any kind of spying on anyone and you trust them and snowden but you distrust the very people you vote for here... such as mittens who is a big hawk for domestic surveillance.... oh wait, you are such an individualist that you don't vote for anyone.......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371073922357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371074003239-55</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens set up some of the first data mining hubs,back when it was considered protecting America to most all</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371057878806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They've been going through peoples personal things for as long as I've been old enough to be politically active. They've monitored groups and individuals mail. Read up on the people Rosie the Red put in prison during WW2 claiming they were "seditionists" They were held with no charge and no trial until after the war. Judge Bolitha Laws after finally hearing the charges made dismissed them all and stated that he had never seen such a gross miscarriage of justice. This was done by the one that most "liberals" kow tow to, whose "best friends" were communists.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371074003239</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371074244111-56</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's storey is not holding up. Turns out he is a bit of a phony. he's not even a High School Grad....</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371068571273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope, you NEVER heard the lower salary from Snowden YOU LIAR" In [his] interview, Snowden described a comfortable lifestyle and a stellar career that included a $200,000 salary from consulting company and defense contractor Booz Allen Hamilton, "........................ only yesterday or so did his employer come out and announce that his salary was $122K...... not bad for a high school drop out just 3 months on the job, though......................</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371074244111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371074980275-57</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's storey is not holding up. Turns out he is a bit of a phony. he's not even a High School Grad....</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371068571273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bummer administration probably hired many Snowden's out there. Kept them off the dole and they didn't qualify for food stamps. Good for the Bummer.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371074980275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 18:09:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371075116086-58</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden gave up the job he held for 3 months to save our privacy</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371071455384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 17:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I trust their govt today more than the Bummers. Putin a better leader, also doesn't like #$%$.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371075116086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 18:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371075501976-59</Id><Topic><Title>Perry is "disappointed" Texas not getting Fed money he asked for</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371070723003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More $$$$$ directed to just his pet projects and pet states. Iowa residents now aghast they voted for this bozo not once, but twice. Wonder if they will vote donkey in 2016. Hahajajahahhahahahahahah.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371075501976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 18:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371075513526-60</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone on here actually here to talk about ORCL?</Title><Username>rocket455bc</Username><Timestamp>1370977769374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently not. I am confused like you, is this with a political chat room? I am at the point where most posters are on IGNORE.</Msg><Username>livermore923</Username><Timestamp>1371075513526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 18:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371075701579-61</Id><Title>Iowa residents amazed at this administrations dishonesty.</Title><Msg>Cannot believe they voted for bozo twice. Their senator still has never been to the Blackhouse.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371075701579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 18:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371080562990-62</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's storey is not holding up. Turns out he is a bit of a phony. he's not even a High School Grad....</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371068571273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know if his story holds up or not. Being a HS grad is irrelevant. Bill Gates is not a college grad. Snowden knows plenty even if he's not wise.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371080562990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 19:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371082798388-63</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's storey is not holding up. Turns out he is a bit of a phony. he's not even a High School Grad....</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371068571273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Snowden isn't even a HS graduate, doofus... and can't even seem to hold a job..... the one he gave up to save the privacy of America for he had for 3 months.......... and he wasn't making $200K like he said..... His employer said it was $122K when they fired him........not bad for a high school drop out on the job for 3 months....... but hardly a bill gates who graduated from an exclusive prep school, scored a near perfect 1590 SAT score and went to Harvard for several years before starting his own business.............Snowden is on the run and hoping to hide out in communist Russia........ really smart...... and ntm .... he disclosed nothing new, nothing that others hadn't already disclosed and well..... the Prism program began in 2007.... hardly anything new......... your guy mittens was all for domestic spying and even helped set up some of the first data mining operation in Ma as gov.... and of course mittens was all for giving MORE money for the military industrial complex...................</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371082798388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371084884483-64</Id><Title>Google says the gov is not demanding unfettered access for data mining</Title><Msg>(but no doubt the "free market" is in cahoots with the evil ones stealing our privacy for no reason but pure spite or whatever, right?) "Assertions in the press that our compliance with these requests gives the U.S. government unfettered access to our users' data are simply untrue." google ( I bet the gov might want user info on some al Qaida outfit trying to use google in the USA to map targets)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371084884483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:54:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371085903854-65</Id><Topic><Title>Perry is "disappointed" Texas not getting Fed money he asked for</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371070723003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right... we're better off spending our money on gifts of F-16s to Springing Islamic butchers and free condoms for Democrat coed #$%$!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371085903854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371086255308-66</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's storey is not holding up. Turns out he is a bit of a phony. he's not even a High School Grad....</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371068571273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A aesa accusation of "Phony"!??? LOL!! There are few phonier S00BBs on earth, mesa, than you and those for whom you pimp 24/7!!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1371086255308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371086444349-67</Id><Topic><Title>Perry is "disappointed" Texas not getting Fed money he asked for</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371070723003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>since you don't want to "live in the kind of society" that has universal healthcare maybe you should join Snowden and move somewhere else?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371086444349</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371086655798-68</Id><Title>"I can assure you that this isn't about spying on the American people. " US Senator Al Franken</Title><Msg>To summarize, senator Franken points out (much like the many Pubs like Newt or mittens or mcconnel) ...... he has availed himself of the briefings about NSA and nothing that was made public lately surprised him. He said, "There's certain things that its appropriate for me to know that its not appropriate for the 'bad guys' to know...So anything the American people know, the 'bad guys' know...I can assure you that this isn't about spying on the American people. This is about having the data available so that if there are suspicions about foreign persons or persons that have connections with terrorist organizations that we can connect the dots."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371086655798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371086872274-69</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone on here actually here to talk about ORCL?</Title><Username>rocket455bc</Username><Timestamp>1370977769374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are people hearing about the earnings? We do not need the same results as last quarter. Stock went down $3.</Msg><Username>hot_bloodedindian</Username><Timestamp>1371086872274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371087086517-70</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden's storey is not holding up. Turns out he is a bit of a phony. he's not even a High School Grad....</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371068571273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 16:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody's story doesn't make sense .. OR raises more questions !! Reports say ... o - Dropped out of school in sophmore year - (believable) o - had a very short military stint (6 or 8 mos) - (mmm ??) o - was released from Military on a "general discharge" .. (mmm ??) o - Hired by CIA .. (short career) ... (why hired by CIA after a "general discharge" from Military ??? ) o - Hired by Booz Allen Hamilton ... (with former CIA credentials ??) I don't think Snowden was anyone's "flunky" (listening to him speak) - but this reported history does not make any sense I think this boy 'sounds' smart as a whip, and I hope this was for patriotic good ?? As of tonight .. he does not want to run, but he wants to get his story out. Can he do it without exposing our foreign agents (??) ..... I'll reserve judgement for now - but hope for the best ....</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1371087086517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371088194516-71</Id><Topic><Title>Pregnant El Salvador Woman Denied Life-Saving Abortion (the gop wants the USA like this)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370106378927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a dam* dirty shame that your mother did not take advantage of the opportunity!</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1371088194516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 21:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371091237718-72</Id><Topic><Title>Pregnant El Salvador Woman Denied Life-Saving Abortion (the gop wants the USA like this)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370106378927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama administration takes side against NYPD in stop-and-frisk; outside monitor possible By DAVID SEIFMAN and BRUCE GOLDING Last Updated: 6:25 PM, June 12, 2013 Posted: 5:14 PM, June 12, 2013 In a stunning move, the Obama Administration has thrust itself into the middle of the explosive federal stop-and-frisk trial and is taking sides against the NYPD, raising the odds of a outside monitor being appointed to oversee the controversial crime-fighting program. "This is very bad news," said one City Hall source. The source said that Attorney General Eric Holder's office notified the city that it intends to file briefs in support of claims by the Center for Constitutional Rights that cops are stopping suspects on the basis of race. Ten weeks of testimony in the case concluded last month. But the federal government has the right to intervene in any federal case and Holder's office will do so before the end of the day, the last day for filing briefs, the source said. The presiding judge, Shira Schiendlin, has yet to issue a ruling. City officials feel privately that the NYPD held its own during the trial, leading to the hope that the judge would stop short of naming a monitor. "This gives her the cover to do that," said one concerned source.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1371091237718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 22:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>