<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369634602772-1</Id><Title>Repubs, admit it.10 years ago YOU THOUGHT dropkick was a 100% a$$wipe and you still do!</Title><Msg>That proves you recognize true reality! SLAM DUNK!</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1369634602772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 02:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369650539305-2</Id><Title>repubs don't like Obama's plans for new war on turrer but corpiss likes it...corpiss and obama feel the same way</Title><Msg>ya can't keep doin crazy bgroup style war on turrer, corpiss agrees</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369650539305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 06:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369653767402-3</Id><Title>Kissinger attended pow gettogether in Ca??? These idiot pow's! They should hate Kissinger..</Title><Msg>Not Fonda. Too much.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369653767402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 07:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369660960633-4</Id><Title>ACA health exchanges offer REASONABLE premiums, CONTRARY to loser pubbie blather</Title><Msg>“On average, the most affordable “silver plan” – which covers 70 percent of the average subscriber’s medical costs – comes with a $276 monthly premium. For the 2.6 million Californians who will receive federal subsidies, the price is a good deal less expensive…” “The premiums and participation in California, Oregon, Washington and other states show that insurers want to compete for the new enrollees in this market,” Gary Claxton, a vice president at the Kaiser Family Foundation, said via e-mail. “The premiums have not skyrocketed and the insurers that serve this market now are continuing. The rates look like what we would expect for decent coverage offered to a standard population.” Cohn is saying that, despite the political naysayers, the healthcare exchange concept appears to be working very well indeed in states like California, Oregon and Washington—the first states to publish the expected health exchange prices for purchasing coverage. These are also states that are actually committed to seeing the program work as opposed to those states whose leaders have a vested political interest in seeing the Affordable Care Act fail. Keep in mind that the entire idea of the exchanges is to require health insurance companies to compete openly with one another by offering identical coverage programs in the three created classes—each offering insurance coverage that actually delivers meaningful protection to customers—and then openly disclosing the price each insurance company will charge for that policy. Thus, shoppers can clearly see which company has the best price on an apples-to-apples basis."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369660960633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369662613392-5</Id><Title>New Gallup poll shows liberals share one brain for every 5 individuals.</Title><Msg>...which is why it takes 5 of them to change a light bulb, which they don't really change but they stand around together fretting about when the Feds will come and change it for them.</Msg><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1369662613392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369663156412-6</Id><Topic><Title>ACA health exchanges offer REASONABLE premiums, CONTRARY to loser pubbie blather</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369660960633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>loser pubs must really hate themselves for being proven wrong about most everything. they have become such lunatics and fanatics that they are against common sense and have even turned against ideas and methods they once were for such as: " the entire idea of the exchanges is to require health insurance companies to compete openly with one another by offering identical coverage programs in the three created classes—each offering insurance coverage that actually delivers meaningful protection to customers—and then openly disclosing the price each insurance company will charge for that policy. Thus, shoppers can clearly see which company has the best price on an apples-to-apples basis."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369663156412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369664321611-7</Id><Title>Health Insurance At 'Good Prices' Coming To Calif. Exchange</Title><Msg>Health Insurance At 'Good Prices' Coming To Calif. Exchange May 24, 2013 It's the first disclosure of prices in the nation's most populous state for individual health insurance that complies with the Affordable Care Act, and the menu of affordable options surprised some consumer advocates and analysts who had been expecting premiums to be much higher. "I'm impressed," said Betsy Imholz, director of special projects for Consumers Union. "I actually think they are good prices," she said, especially for those who will receive federal insurance subsidies. The worry had been that shoppers in the individual insurance market would face sticker shock when the sweeping changes of the health law take effect beginning in January 2014. The law prohibits health plans from rejecting people with pre-existing conditions and doesn't allow insurers to charge women and sicker people more. Nearly three dozen health plans submitted bids to sell their products in the competitive marketplace, and 13 were selected. But California exchange officials, authorized by state lawmakers to negotiate on behalf of consumers, rejected bids that were too expensive, they said, or failed to include enough choices of doctors and hospitals. "We've hit a home run for consumers," said Peter V. Lee, the executive director of the California exchange, known as Covered California. . The proposed premium prices vary depending on where in California t</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369664321611</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 10:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369664467991-8</Id><Topic><Title>Health Insurance At 'Good Prices' Coming To Calif. Exchange</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369664321611</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 10:18:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Under the premiums unveiled Thursday, a 25-year-old in Los Angeles could choose a Health Net catastrophic plan for $117 a month or a more comprehensive plan for $147 a month from L.A. Care, the nation's largest public health plan. People making less than about $45,600 per year would qualify for a subsidy that would lower the premiums further. More than half of Californians shopping for insurance through the state-run marketplace will be eligible for federal income tax credits. Those credits will help offset the price of private insurance: a 40-year-old individual in Los Angeles, for example, who earns $1,915 a month, or 200 percent of the federal poverty level, would pay a monthly premium of $90 for a Health Net HMO "Silver" plan in 2014, according to the rates released by Covered California."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369664467991</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 10:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369668372981-9</Id><Topic><Title>Kissinger attended pow gettogether in Ca??? These idiot pow's! They should hate Kissinger..</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369653767402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 07:22:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with the first half of your statement. But, Jane Fonda went to North Viet Nam and palled around with those that were killing our men and making them POW's. I hate them both for different reasons.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369668372981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 11:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369669500366-10</Id><Title>Now Back To Our Regular Programming</Title><Msg>Fox News has changed their slogan from "fair and balanced" to " I told you so". -Leno- "The government is responsible for more cover-ups than Maybelline". -Greg Gutfield- Here's the score, Benghazi- Obama says, wasn't me AP phone snooping- Obama says, wasn't me. IRS targeting- Obama says, wasn't me. Killing Bin Laden- Obama says, that was me. Can you imagine how much scht his library will contain?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369669500366</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 11:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369672468453-11</Id><Topic><Title>Kissinger attended pow gettogether in Ca??? These idiot pow's! They should hate Kissinger..</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369653767402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 07:22:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll go with Hanoi Jane. Treason is a serious offense. She should be imprisoned, maybe water boarded.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369672468453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:34:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369672584197-12</Id><Topic><Title>Health Insurance At 'Good Prices' Coming To Calif. Exchange</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369664321611</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 10:18:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And we all believe in the tooth fairy, Easter bunny, and Santa. What idiots we have in America, especially California.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369672584197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:36:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369672702024-13</Id><Topic><Title>Health Insurance At 'Good Prices' Coming To Calif. Exchange</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369664321611</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 10:18:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the insurers have announced THOSE prices, for all to see....jeez.....YOU are the idiot.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369672702024</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:38:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369672890636-14</Id><Topic><Title>ACA health exchanges offer REASONABLE premiums, CONTRARY to loser pubbie blather</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369660960633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're so gullible, the Indians would have laughed at you at Custer's last stand. You don't cover 30 million more people, many with preexisting conditions, and not rape other sectors of America. The cost of Bummer care escalates daily, even by CBO standards. But you keep finding these libiots who will say anything to support this oncoming train wreck. And the Bummer and Holder will say they didn't know nutting bout nutting.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369672890636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369673059261-15</Id><Topic><Title>teagag congressman: Starve The Poor While Personally Pocketing Millions In Farm Subsidies</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369613984561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 20:19:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to check out Nancy "Ill read it when we pass it" Pelosi's family wealth. Then we will talk. Idiot.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369673059261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369673259930-16</Id><Topic><Title>ACA health exchanges offer REASONABLE premiums, CONTRARY to loser pubbie blather</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369660960633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is a fact that every modern nation on the earth gets EVERYONE covered for less cost per capita than here and most have as good or even better care than here.... and , ignoramus, it is also a fact that Romneycare Didn't Increase Hospital Costs even with MORE people insured . Study: Romneycare Didn't Increase Hospital Costs May 16, 2013 According to a new analysis, health care reform in Massachusetts, popularly known as "Romneycare," didn't cause hospital use or costs to increase, even as it drove down the number of people without health insurance.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369673259930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369673462557-17</Id><Topic><Title>Health Insurance At 'Good Prices' Coming To Calif. Exchange</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369664321611</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 10:18:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Catasprophic coverage means little. State and Feds will be further responsible. Get a clue bubba. And by the way, you have been unanimously labeled king of the idiots for your selective articles written by libiots like yourself. Remember Benghasi, IRS fiasco, AP fiasco, Obummercare, and Holder. More to come. Bummer's mouthpiece said IRS scandal was inappropriate. As George retorted, using your salad fork on the entree is inappropriate. That fiasco was criminal.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369673462557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369673549226-18</Id><Topic><Title>teagag congressman: Starve The Poor While Personally Pocketing Millions In Farm Subsidies</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369613984561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 20:19:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is she the one demanding the poor family down the street give up their $100 a month in food stamps while they are unemployed........but collecting MILLIONS of $$$$ in cotton subsidies, like the teagag congressman?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369673549226</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369673581741-19</Id><Title>Yikes, how many killed.</Title><Msg>They are dropping like flies in Chicago. It parallels Detroit as the abyss of America. Maybe we should send these folk to Iran and N. Korea to take care of them.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369673581741</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 12:53:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369675138081-20</Id><Title>Texas Weekend Shooting Spree Leaves Two Dead</Title><Msg>(part of the 3 or 4 people murdered every day in Texas.......where the murder rate is about 5 per 100,000)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369675138081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369676446236-21</Id><Title>shocking: every day in the USA 44 people get murdered</Title><Msg>based on USA murder rate of about 5 per 100,000. USA population of about 320,000,000 do the math (3200 X 5 = 16,000.......................divide by 365 days to get 44 murders per day in the USA)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369676446236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369677012688-22</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Weekend Shooting Spree Leaves Two Dead</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369675138081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:18:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you should go to Chicago, Detroit, Philadelphia, Los Angelos, Denver, Tampa, Miami, etc. Makes the state of Texas seem angelic.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369677012688</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369677182273-23</Id><Topic><Title>shocking: every day in the USA 44 people get murdered</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369676446236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since 1973, we have had over 53 million unborn in America slaughtered by Progressive doctors like Our infamous Philadelphis surgeon. Takes a lot of days to add up to 53 mill.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369677182273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369677309115-24</Id><Topic><Title>teagag congressman: Starve The Poor While Personally Pocketing Millions In Farm Subsidies</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369613984561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 20:19:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not yet, but she and her family have raped America of many millions by her "progressive stance" on issues that have made them millions, taken from our govt.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369677309115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369677465346-25</Id><Topic><Title>ACA health exchanges offer REASONABLE premiums, CONTRARY to loser pubbie blather</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369660960633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep dreaming numb nuts. Nobody on this planet has better, more advanced medicine, than America. Next time you need surgery, go to some third world country with socialized medicine and stand in line.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369677465346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369677636013-26</Id><Topic><Title>New Gallup poll shows liberals share one brain for every 5 individuals.</Title><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1369662613392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:50:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gotta be one brain for 6-7 lib nuts if you read some of their inane gibberish on this board. These numbnuts will believe anything some liberal #$%$ writes, then quote them. How gullible can these lemmings be.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369677636013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369677949388-27</Id><Topic><Title>insiders SHORTING ??</Title><Username>trader_best</Username><Timestamp>1369445105215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 21:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats crazy</Msg><Username>davidjackson655</Username><Timestamp>1369677949388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369678115091-28</Id><Topic><Title>shocking: every day in the USA 44 people get murdered</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369676446236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so why were you posting about violence in Chicago? What a loser you are.....fact is about 44 people are murdered each day in the USA.......no wonder you have to change the subject back you wanting to chain women up , send them to birth prisons and force them to have children they don't want .</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369678115091</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:08:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369678304296-29</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Weekend Shooting Spree Leaves Two Dead</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369675138081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:18:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as usual you don't know what you are talking about...... Houston , texas tops most of those, and fyi the murder rate in texas is about at the avg for the USA close to 5 per 100,000. Crime statistics are listed for U.S. cities with a population of 250,000 or greater. Rates are based on cases per 100,000 people for all of calendar year 2011. violent crimes Houston, Texas .................... 974.6 Boston, Massachusetts........... 845.2 Anchorage, Alaska .................. 804.2 Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania .......802.3 San Francisco, California ... 659.6 New York, New York ...... 623.6 Denver, Colorado................ 607.3 Fort Worth, Texas............ 603.7 United States cities by crime rate From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369678304296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 14:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369682583400-30</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Weekend Shooting Spree Leaves Two Dead</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369675138081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:18:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you look at LA or Oakland's crime stats, the majority are committed by minorities, black and hispanics, many gang related. Why make distinctions between states? Nationally the commission of crimes and murders are outweighed in minority groups, Let's not forget that prison populations reflect that. Let's get real, Texas will execute the perps while Calif liberals will want to assess their abusive or neglected childhoods. So they get to sit on death row for 20 or more years getting more than they deserve.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369682583400</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 15:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369689373045-31</Id><Title>the trumped up pubbie 'scandals' have already faded away</Title><Msg>soon to be considered as ridiculous and false as the birther nonsense</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369689373045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 17:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369692251578-32</Id><Topic><Title>the trumped up pubbie 'scandals' have already faded away</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369689373045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 17:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369692251578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369693154584-33</Id><Title>Since 1973, we have had over 53 million unborn in America slaughtered</Title><Msg>Not nearly enough! ,and,..if repubs were not anti birth control and sex education imAGINE HOW LITTLE THE NUMBER WOULD BE.,........ YOU IDIOTS! Why are you against birth control but not against pills that give men bon ARS! Ya think it's OK for insurance to pay for bone aaaaare meds but not BC pills? YOU GOT NUTHIN! DROPKICK!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369693154584</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369693984755-34</Id><Topic><Title>shocking: every day in the USA 44 people get murdered</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369676446236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems I read recently that most of the murders happen in five cities. All of which have stringent gun laws and are run by leftist Democrats. I remember four of those cities. Chicago, (naturally) Detroit, New Orleans and DC (again, naturally) The fifth might be Miami but I'm not sure. There are several other similarities among the five. Bet you can figure it out with little problem.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369693984755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369694383349-35</Id><Topic><Title>the trumped up pubbie 'scandals' have already faded away</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369689373045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 17:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it's "birther" nonsense then why can't I get a copy of the birth certificate? Those records are STILL SEALED in spite of Liver Lips showing off a purported copy? Many experts consider it a forgery. Just finished a book about Liver Lip's "Father Fihure" Frank Marshall Davis. Apparently he was in Hawaii at the time Liver Lips was born. Very interesting book titled; "The Communist." Perhaps he was more than just a father "figure".</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369694383349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:39:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369695215671-36</Id><Topic><Title>ACA health exchanges offer REASONABLE premiums, CONTRARY to loser pubbie blather</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369660960633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My wife and I are paying about $250 per month on top of Medi-care. We are also paying large co-pays. Luckily the company I retired from has a drug insureance policy that offsets some of that expense. I had Kaiser Permanente in California. Co-pays were a flat $20 for any doctor. The same for any prescription. Even a stay in the hospital or visit to the ER wasn't bad. I had no problem seeing a specialist or getting non emergency hospital treatment. The care was excellent and I and my family had it from 1970 until last year. The insureance companies get in bed with state legislators and pass laws that make it very difficult for competition to come into a state. These are the same racketeers that wrote "Obama Care" which none of the scurvy Representatives in Congress even read before passing it.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369695215671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 18:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369702690589-37</Id><Topic><Title>shocking: every day in the USA 44 people get murdered</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369676446236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>53 million / 40 years / 365 days = 3630 deaths by abortion per day.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1369702690589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 20:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369703347390-38</Id><Topic><Title>the trumped up pubbie 'scandals' have already faded away</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369689373045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 17:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So say Libiots. And Obama wishes it were true. If they "went away" why's Lerner Lady taking the Fifth? Oh, I forgot, it's because she'd done nothing wrong and is totally innocent! Indications are this is pervasive activity across many Bureaus &amp; Agencies and leads straight to the Top. Benghazi &amp; AP Scandals are hardly started. Gitmo Scandal continues. Good odds that Obama gets impeached after 2014 elections. Maybe Biden gets impeached too. That leaves Speaker of the House, Boehner as President!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1369703347390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 21:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369703424378-39</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs, admit it.10 years ago YOU THOUGHT dropkick was a 100% a$$wipe and you still do!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1369634602772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 02:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, we still do!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1369703424378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 21:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369711350014-40</Id><Title>Uh, the only scandal fading away is then where some thought our president was competent.</Title><Msg>They are quickly learning otherwise. The other 6, which highlight the incompetence, are still alive, kicking, and growing.</Msg><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1369711350014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 23:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>