<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-01"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364816599529-1</Id><Title>runners says it's in US cemetaries abroad where crosses not allowed and I doubt even that</Title><Msg>Just more right wing garabage bs</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364816599529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 07:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364816640576-2</Id><Topic><Title>nwesmax says the end of the world is near!</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364748144186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 12:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That company is really low class</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364816640576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 07:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364816738564-3</Id><Title>bgroup had 8 years to stop N. Korea, 8 years to stop Iran they did NUTHIN!</Title><Msg>Ya got NUTHIN!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364816738564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 07:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364816808287-4</Id><Title>BTW, ya REALLY think N Korea can actually hurt us?</Title><Msg>They can't and bgroup had ample time to do something.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364816808287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 07:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364819406060-5</Id><Title>Ben Stein rails against gop nonsense about taxes on the rich</Title><Msg>"We have gotten to the point that the discussion of taxes is just a joke," Stein scoffs. In his lifetime he's watched the top tax rate fall from 90% (when he was a kid) to 70% (when he was writing speeches for Nixon) to a situation where no one actually pays the listed tax rate — but the government still shuts down over the prospect of a 3% or 4% hike for the wealthy. "Really, high-income people can afford to pay a lot more taxes," he shouts, in a naked betrayal of his class.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364819406060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 08:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364825617371-6</Id><Title>Obama a lot like Hoover - why expect different results?</Title><Msg>Scenario: A President enters office during an economic crisis.  His responses?  demand  action from Washington (Federal), not from the private economy demonize  the big banks and Wall Street blame the previous President for everything and anything  stay clueless on the ubiquitous threat of "modern day" terrorism In short, his modus operandi was to try and convinced the country that others, and capitalism, was the cause of the economic problems. The result was to make things worse. You can see how closely Obama is paralleling Mr. Hoover!</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1364825617371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364825828154-7</Id><Title>On taxes, all that matters is effective tax rates. There nev really WAS a 90% tax rate from that view.</Title><Msg>The effective individual tax rate in 1979 for the top 1% was 21.8% while the top marginal rate was 70% The effective individual tax rate in 2005 for the top 1% was 19.4%% while the top marginal rate was 35%</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1364825828154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364827410264-8</Id><Topic><Title>On taxes, all that matters is effective tax rates. There nev really WAS a 90% tax rate from that view.</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1364825828154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:17:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOP marginal rate in the eisenhower years was 91%. Top marginal rated avg 49% for the 1980s Now it is 39.6% .............................. In 1955 the IRS took 51.2% of the top 400 incomes.......Recently the top 400 have paid just 16.6% on an astounding average income of $345 million. that is the EFFECTIVE RATE, btw..... notice how the EFFECTIVE rate is determined by the marginal rates..... notice how a the HIGHER MARGINAL rates of the past meant that the rich paid much higher effective rates than they do now.... which is why many rich republicans are pointing out what a disgrace the gop in on taxes , as did Ben Stein today: We have gotten to the point that the discussion of taxes is just a joke," Stein scoffs. In his lifetime he's watched the top tax rate fall from 90% (when he was a kid) to 70% (when he was writing speeches for Nixon) to a situation where no one actually pays the listed tax rate — but the government still shuts down over the prospect of a 3% or 4% hike for the wealthy. "Really, high-income people can afford to pay a lot more taxes," he shouts, in a naked betrayal of his class.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364827410264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364827551649-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ben Stein rails against gop nonsense about taxes on the rich</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364819406060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 08:30:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and btw, the decline in tax rates for the rich never produced more investment or jobs or helped the economy. The rich simply got richer and everyone else got poorer: "Declining Tax Rates Haven’t Stimulated Investment: Cutting taxes on the richest Americans has not led them to invest more in plant and equipment. Over the past 50 years, as tax rates have declined, there has been no increase in investment spending as a percentage of GDP. (The flat trend line shows that changes in the highest marginal income-tax rate have not affected investment much, one way or the other.) Instead, the investment share of the economy has been determined by other factors, such as aggregate demand, rather than tax policy Lower Taxes, Slower GDP Growth: Despite lower and declining tax rates, especially on the rich, the United States has had slower productivity growth over the last several decades than other advanced economies. Overall, lower taxes are associated with slower growth in GDP per hour worked. A 10 percentage point increase in taxes as a share of GDP is associated with an increase in the productivity growth rate of 0.2 percentage points. (See Figure 5.) The Great Tax-Cut Experiment Has cutting tax rates for the rich helped the economy? GERALD FRIEDMAN is a professor of economics at the University of Massachusetts-Amherst.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364827551649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364827676049-10</Id><Title>Walmart: America's real 'Welfare Queen' (the rich got richer, everyone else got poorer, the walton's are tax subsidized )</Title><Msg>Walmart: America's real 'Welfare Queen' . Walmart, one of the richest corporations in the world, refuses to pay its employees a livable wage or provide any form of decent healthcare, increasing reliance on government assistance, and the need for a social safety net. by Paddy Ryan At over $446 billion per year, Walmart is the third highest revenue grossing corporation in the world. Walmart earns over $15 billion per year in pure profit and pays its executives handsomely. In 2011, Walmart CEO Mike Duke – already a millionaire a dozen times over – received an $18.1 million compensation package. The Walton family controlling over 48 percent of the corporation through stock ownership does even better. Together, members of the Walton family are worth in excess of $102 billion – which makes them one of the richest families in the world. What is shameful is that CEO Mike Duke makes more money in one hour, than his employees earn in an entire year. Yet, Walmart – which employs millions of people in its stores, distribution centers, and warehouses – continues to abuse its employees and refuses to pay them a livable wage. The company has frequently been charged with wage theft claims by workers who point to the most common forms of wage theft: the refusal to pay proper overtime, the refusal to honor the minimum wage, and illegal paycheck deductions. Meanwhile, Walmart routinely blocks any attempt by workers to organize, using anti-union propaganda and scare tactics, firing employees without just cause, failing to provide any form of decent healthcare coverage or a livable wage. To make matters worse, these abusive Walmart policies have increased employee reliance on government assistance and the need for a government funded social safety net. In fact, Walmart has become the number one driver behind the growing use of food stamps in the United States with "as many as 80 percent of workers in Wal-Mart stores using food stamps."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364827676049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:47:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364829671122-11</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart: America's real 'Welfare Queen' (the rich got richer, everyone else got poorer, the walton's are tax subsidized )</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364827676049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CURL: The Obamas live the 1 percent life Comments (809) By Joseph Curl Sunday, March 31, 2013 President Barack Obama waves to the crowd as he watches the first half of the East Regional final in the NCAA men's college basketball tournament between Syracuse and Marquette, Saturday, March 30, 2013, in Washington. (AP Photo/Mark Tenally) Being president of the U.S., the most powerful man in the world, is often most about perception. The man (or, one day, woman) in the job takes actions large and small every day, but it is the perception of the man that seeps into the everyday lives of working Americans. That’s why presidential candidates always hit Philadelphia for a cheesesteak during campaigns (Democrats to Pat’s, Republicans to Geno’s). Sure, they’re running billion-dollar operations trying to win the White House, but one picture of them wolfing down a Cheez Whiz-covered glob of meat on a Philly street hits home with millions of voters: “Hey, that guy’s just like me! He loves him a Pat’s [or Geno’s] cheesesteak, too!” (Unless you’re John F. Kerry and order Swiss cheese — then everyone hates you.) Sometimes, that perception cuts to the core. Like when President George W. Bush stopped playing golf in 2003, at</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1364829671122</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 11:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364830155745-12</Id><Title>Reagan economic success dwarfs Obama</Title><Msg>The data is pretty clear on the effectiveness of different Presidents to create GDP from debt. Reagan added $1.32 in GDP for each additional dollar of debt while inheriting a stupendous recession Obama added $.24 (24 cents) for each additional dollar of debt while inheriting a stupendous recession. Sorry, lefties---- Reagan buries Obama!</Msg><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1364830155745</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 11:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364830171596-13</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart: America's real 'Welfare Queen' (the rich got richer, everyone else got poorer, the walton's are tax subsidized )</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364827676049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CHICAGO – Mexican drug cartels whose operatives once rarely ventured beyond the U.S. border are dispatching some of their most trusted agents to live and work deep inside the United States -- an emboldened presence that experts believe is meant to tighten their grip on the world's most lucrative narcotics market and maximize profits. If left unchecked, authorities say, the cartels' move into the American interior could render the syndicates harder than ever to dislodge and pave the way for them to expand into other criminal enterprises such as prostitution, kidnapping-and-extortion rackets and money laundering. Cartel activity in the U.S. is certainly not new. Starting in the 1990s, the ruthless syndicates became the nation's No. 1 supplier of illegal drugs, using unaffiliated middlemen to smuggle cocaine, marijuana and heroin beyond the border or even to grow pot here. But a wide-ranging Associated Press review of federal court cases and government drug-enforcement data, plus interviews with many top law enforcement officials, indicate the groups have begun deploying agents from their inner circles to the U.S. Cartel operatives are suspected of running drug-distribution networks in at least nine non-border states, often in middle-class suburbs in the Midwest, South and Northeast. "It's probably the most serious threat the United States has faced from organized crime," said Jack Riley, head of the Drug Enforcement Administration's Chicago office.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1364830171596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 11:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364830558806-14</Id><Topic><Title>Ben Stein rails against gop nonsense about taxes on the rich</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364819406060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 08:30:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you so naive as to believe that "The Rich" ever paid a lot in taxes? When the higher rates were in effect there were so many loopholes that many of the mega rich paid little in direct taxes. It was all BS for stupid people.. Small investors got a similar break with REIT's a while back. As soon as many people began catching on to this tax writ e off they changed the rules so few would qualify. But, people like the Kennedy's and Rottenfellers got to keep it though had no direct hand in management of their assets. As the witch in New York said long ago; "Taxes are only for the little people."</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1364830558806</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 11:35:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364831892213-15</Id><Title>World News Entertainment</Title><Msg>North Korea warns the US that war with South Korea will erupt and threatened an attack on the US west coast. Obama's reaction. "Get me Dennis Rodman." Just make the guy ambassador, he's no more flaky than Joe Biden. Joe struck again, telling an anti-gun rally that Gabby Gifford was shot and mortally wounded. As entertainment value, he could trip over a cordless phone. Yuk Yuk!</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1364831892213</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 11:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364832526980-16</Id><Topic><Title>Ben Stein rails against gop nonsense about taxes on the rich</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364819406060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 08:30:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dear doofus, are you so silly as to think the rich prior to Reagan did not pay MORE income taxes than now....jeez....... and fyi during WW2 the rich were taxed 100% of their income above $350K after taxes in todays money... in other worlds , to pay for the debts then ,the government taxed 100% of all income over $25K ($350K today) only irresponsible ajoles like bush and the gop would lower taxes on the rich while ramping up spending for war and profiteering....Reagan's budget director Stockman said yesterday that Bush and crew wrecked the USA with that irresponsibility........... here is how it should have been done: "The cost of World War II was financed primarily by a highly progressive Income Tax, as well as other taxes on corporations to prevent excess profits being derived from government contracts. Even the Vietnam War was largely financed by a surtax on incomes, paid largely by wealthier citizens rather than by the transfer of a payroll tax-generated social security Surplus to cover U.S. budget deficits. "</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364832526980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 12:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364832914402-17</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart: America's real 'Welfare Queen' (the rich got richer, everyone else got poorer, the walton's are tax subsidized )</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364827676049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the silly pubs here whine about walmart worker's demanding livable wages........ and then they also whine about them having to get foodstamps to live............... the silly pubs here think that sales work, cashiers , food service, janitors and so on....don't deserve to get paid enough to live on..... but then they whine if those people have to get food stamps or Medicaid.......jeez....... and to top it off, the silly pubs here think the Walton's should pay lower taxes and cheer on the gop who threaten to shutdown the government if taxes are hiked 3 or 4% on the rich............ who have seen huge declines in their tax rates over the last many years at the same time as they have reached into the till and taken more income, ceo pay rising from 50 times the avg worker 30 or so years ago, to over 350 times that now.......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364832914402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 12:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364833048574-18</Id><Title>David Stockman, Ex-Reagan Budget Director: George W. Bush's Policies Bankrupt The Country</Title><Msg>David Stockman, Ex-Reagan Budget Director: George W. Bush's Policies Bankrupt The Country . Posted: 03/31/2013 1:36 pm EDT A former adviser of Ronald Reagan has some choice words for George W. Bush. David Stockman, Reagan’s budget director from 1981 to 1985, slammed Bush and his former boss in an op-ed in The New York Times Sunday. Stockman argued in the piece that Reagan’s view on the deficit “created a template for the Republicans’ utter abandonment of the balanced-budget policies of Calvin Coolidge.” “(Reagan’s deficit policies) allowed George W. Bush to dive into the deep end, bankrupting the nation through two misbegotten and unfinanced wars, a giant expansion of Medicare and a tax-cutting spree for the wealthy that turned K Street lobbyists into the de facto office of national tax policy,” Stockman wrote</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364833048574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 12:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364834116894-19</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation UPDATED CHART!</Title><Username>kootcharmorgan</Username><Timestamp>1364827540174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am looking for.</Msg><Username>plumatellagwendolyn</Username><Timestamp>1364834116894</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 12:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364834602213-20</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart: America's real 'Welfare Queen' (the rich got richer, everyone else got poorer, the walton's are tax subsidized )</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364827676049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5 paragraphs of Pure Pigshyt!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1364834602213</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 12:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364835063380-21</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation UPDATED CHART!</Title><Username>kootcharmorgan</Username><Timestamp>1364827540174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>checking the chart now</Msg><Username>maccarthsocorro</Username><Timestamp>1364835063380</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 12:51:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364835690485-22</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation UPDATED CHART!</Title><Username>kootcharmorgan</Username><Timestamp>1364827540174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you and please keep it coming.</Msg><Username>receptoryashlee0</Username><Timestamp>1364835690485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364836236977-23</Id><Title>Will go higher..</Title><Msg>CEO is a smart guy..he will bring it up...only one quarter issue..good time to add.</Msg><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1364836236977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:10:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364836794122-24</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation UPDATED CHART!</Title><Username>kootcharmorgan</Username><Timestamp>1364827540174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>laptyevmabel</Username><Timestamp>1364836794122</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364837663564-25</Id><Title>Walmart pays more Ghana livable wage. Their only "sin" is being non-union!</Title><Msg>Walmart employs 1.2 million Americans, is 8% of total U.S. retail sales,  and has a  turnover rate is 44 percent -- basically  the retail industry average. Walmart pays an average full-time hourly wage of  $9.98, (which is higher than Macy's, Target, Kay Jeweler, Kohl's, JC Penney, Office Mx, etc).  In  metro areas (defined as areas with a population of 50,000 or more) the average Walmart rate climbs to   $10.38, with higher rates in more expensive urban areas  (examples: $11.03 in Chicago, $11.08 in San Francisco, and $11.20 in Austin.) The average hourly pay in the US  for  retail Sales Associate it is about $8.50. All in all, Walmart can and does pay a livable wage. It does NOT pay union wages, or have unions at all. This explains why they employ 1.2 million Americans</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1364837663564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364838119621-26</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation UPDATED CHART!</Title><Username>kootcharmorgan</Username><Timestamp>1364827540174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it. Good job mate.</Msg><Username>moomophyllis</Username><Timestamp>1364838119621</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364838124852-27</Id><Title>I can only repeat the data: Reagan economic success dwarfs Obama's.</Title><Msg>Hope I am not confusing you by using accurate data.</Msg><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1364838124852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364838273629-28</Id><Title>Spell check - "Ghana" should be "than a "</Title><Msg>iPad auto changes bad spelling, sometimes to weird stuff!</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1364838273629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364839956021-29</Id><Topic><Title>I can only repeat the data: Reagan economic success dwarfs Obama's.</Title><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1364838124852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>reagan TRIPLEd the debt, wasted more money than anyone,,and took office at the end of a down cycle.a REGULAR down cycle.....obama took office near the top of the worst economical disaster in our lifetimes caused BY REAGAN and Bushes!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364839956021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364840006756-30</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart pays more Ghana livable wage. Their only "sin" is being non-union!</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1364837663564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WMT IS the reason people work and are still very poor and on welfare.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364840006756</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364840093844-31</Id><Title>Mexican drug cartels whose operatives once rarely ventured beyond the U.S. border</Title><Msg>But bush let them in</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364840093844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364840142296-32</Id><Topic><Title>David Stockman, Ex-Reagan Budget Director: George W. Bush's Policies Bankrupt The Country</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364833048574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 12:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DROPKICK!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364840142296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364840590835-33</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart pays more Ghana livable wage. Their only "sin" is being non-union!</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1364837663564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Alexandria Fisher, NBCChicago Several teens were arrested after dozens of mob groups began attacking pedestrians on Chicago’s downtown Magnificent Mile area on Saturday night. Police responded to reports of disturbances near Michigan and Chicago Avenues. Police said 28 teens were arrested during the incident and no serious injuries were reported. The teens charged with misdemeanor reckless conduct and battery and later released, according to News Affairs Officer Perkus. Eleven other teens were charged with the same misdemeanor charges after they attacked a group of women on the CTA Red Line, police said. “You have over three to four hundred teenagers with mob action, jumping on individuals that are downtown,” said community activist Andrew Holmes. “Multiple people have been arrested and I caution those parents that get this call about your child being arrested -- maybe you need to check your child.” Officers began breaking up the attacks by ushering teens to the Red Line. Chaos continued underground but many attackers reportedly left the area. “I just saw a cluster run down to the Red Line,” said Red Line passenger Amanda Dobson. “I didn't know what was going on. I just kind of stepped back and let the police do what they needed to do.” Police continued to patrol the area on bikes, horses and on foot as smaller groups wandered around the Loop.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1364840590835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:23:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364840717683-34</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart pays more Ghana livable wage. Their only "sin" is being non-union!</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1364837663564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On Saturday, Mar. 30, the bodies of 23-year Army veteran and Kaufman County District Attorney Mike McLelland and his wife Cynthia were found in their home, the victims of an apparent assassination. Speaking on condition of anonymity, a law enforcement official described the scene at the McLelland’s home as “awful,” with “shell casings everywhere.” This caused Forney Mayor Darren Rozell and local defense attorney Eric Smenner both to suggest the McLellands were targeted: In December, the Texas Department of Public Safety had issued a statewide bulletin warning that authorities had received “credible information” that the Aryan Brotherhood was “actively planning retaliation against law enforcement officials” who helped secure indictments in Houston against dozens of members, including the gang’s leadership. “High ranking members… are involved in issuing orders to inflict ‘mass casualties or death’ to law enforcement officials who were involved in cases where Aryan Brotherhood of Texas are facing life sentences or the death penalty,” the bulletin stated. A national security expert who has spent several years in intelligence gathering operations around the Mexican drug cartels' criminal insurgency into the continental United States told Breitbart News, "This assassination of DA McClellend and his wife is meant to send a message: no one is safe, no one is beyond our reach. We will kill you and your loved ones. We are in control here." "This is a significant point of escalation in the crisis," he continued. "This type of high-profile targeting of public officials is a classic insurgent tactic. Its escalating use inside the US shows a complete lack of fear of consequences and demonstrates the fundamental shift in the strategic landscape that has already occurred. "The criminal insurgencies and their gang foot soldiers have exported the type of warfare that brought Mexico to its knees deep into our sovereign territory. They are waging a war: targeting, assa</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1364840717683</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364841700067-35</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Insiders Selling ?</Title><Username>coxevan881</Username><Timestamp>1363886774305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great</Msg><Username>walkerssteve</Username><Timestamp>1364841700067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364842364661-36</Id><Title>BCCI to open 3 more locations!!!</Title><Msg>YAHOO NEWS</Msg><Username>fkiesereda</Username><Timestamp>1364842364661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:52:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364842470321-37</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart pays more Ghana livable wage. Their only "sin" is being non-union!</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1364837663564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama 2 for 22 at Easter Egg Roll 12:08 PM, Apr 1, 2013 • By DANIEL HALPER Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts Via the pool report: POTUS at basketball court, with kids and Washington Wizards (don't have all names but John Wall included -- will get details for final wrap) POTUS stepped to free throw line and kids were asked to stand on opposite sides, depending on whether they think he would sink it. Most kids moved in one direction, but one boy went to the "miss" side."Oh, man," a stunned POTUS said, hands on hips. The boy didn't budge. And three others joined.In sharp form, POTUS released the ball. It bounced off the rim and circled it -- miss."Come on. Come on. Did you see that?" Obama said.It got worse.A little while later, after playing tennis, Obama started to take shots amid the kids and pros. Miss. Miss. Off the rim. Miss. Miss. Off the rim. Airball. He moved closer to the net.But time and again, he missed. Of 22 shots POTUS took, he made two. (22 was general consensus of poolers)At one point, POTUS handed a ball to a boy and asked for help. The boy made the layup."He couldn't make one. I had to help him out," said Kahron Campbell, 10, of Landover, MD.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1364842470321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364843424291-38</Id><Title>Their only "sin" is being non-union!</Title><Msg>There's NOTHING good about WMT from whatever angle ya look at it. Nothing. Not good shopping there not goodworking there. There are an abomination.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364843424291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 15:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364843572564-39</Id><Title>Just a thought...</Title><Msg>Assuming ORCL executives realized they were going to "miss the quarter", wouldn't it be wiser to "miss" by more &amp; pre-load the next quarter than to barely "miss" and still get crushed by analysts. If ORCL doesn't "blow out" it's next quarter then my assessment is wrong, but having been in this same situation in my professional life....I wouldn't bet against it....GLTA.</Msg><Username>atrue42long</Username><Timestamp>1364843572564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 15:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364843617411-40</Id><Title>Michele Bachmann sideshow is hurting the GOP</Title><Msg>How great. Gop should have told her to get lost years ago.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364843617411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 15:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364844982553-41</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation UPDATED CHART!</Title><Username>kootcharmorgan</Username><Timestamp>1364827540174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this article. Keep it coming.</Msg><Username>omphalecalice</Username><Timestamp>1364844982553</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 15:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364845039178-42</Id><Topic><Title>Mexican drug cartels whose operatives once rarely ventured beyond the U.S. border</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364840093844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:14:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>China mobilizing troops, jets near N. Korean border, US officials say Published April 01, 2013 Washington Free Beacon China has placed military forces on heightened alert in the northeastern part of the country as tensions mount on the Korean peninsula following recent threats by Pyongyang to attack, U.S. officials said. Reports from the region reveal the Chinese People's Liberation Army (PLA) recently increased its military posture in response to the heightened tensions, specifically North Korea's declaration of a "state of war" and threats to conduct missile attacks against the United States and South Korea. According to the officials, the PLA has stepped up military mobilization in the border region with North Korea since mid-March, including troop movements and warplane activity. China's navy also conducted live-firing naval drills by warships in the Yellow Sea that were set to end Monday near the Korean peninsula, in apparent support of North Korea, which was angered by ongoing U.S.-South Korean military drills that are set to continue throughout April. North Korea, meanwhile, is mobilizing missile forces, including road-mobile short- and medium-range missiles, according to officials familiar with satellite imagery of missile bases.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1364845039178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 15:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364845504824-43</Id><Title>strong buy ORCLe and Strong Short HP: make money in April</Title><Msg>short HP and buy ORCL Left and Right</Msg><Username>adamwangwang47</Username><Timestamp>1364845504824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 15:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364845582250-44</Id><Title>what a surprise</Title><Msg>message boards I thought were discontinued a few weeks ago. Just happened to stumble back in. What changed?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1364845582250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 15:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364846910035-45</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation UPDATED CHART!</Title><Username>kootcharmorgan</Username><Timestamp>1364827540174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>lamicedjoann</Username><Timestamp>1364846910035</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 16:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364847105896-46</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation UPDATED CHART!</Title><Username>kootcharmorgan</Username><Timestamp>1364827540174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this a good Investor Report?</Msg><Username>overspanningenfern</Username><Timestamp>1364847105896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 16:11:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364847981446-47</Id><Title>message boards I thought were discontinued a few weeks ago. Just happened to stumble back in. What changed? Signed Seebe</Title><Msg>seebe!!!!!! Hows it goin? You thought WHAT? I agree...it's been weird/</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364847981446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 16:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364848225329-48</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation UPDATED CHART!</Title><Username>kootcharmorgan</Username><Timestamp>1364827540174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is this thing going any where?</Msg><Username>overspanningenfern</Username><Timestamp>1364848225329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 16:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364848500805-49</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation UPDATED CHART!</Title><Username>kootcharmorgan</Username><Timestamp>1364827540174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>checking the chart now</Msg><Username>overspanningenfern</Username><Timestamp>1364848500805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 16:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364851494889-50</Id><Title>"Nanny State" Fascist Obama Bankrupting The Country At Twice The Rate Of Bush!!</Title><Msg>and gleefully! At least Bush had a couple of REAL threats to eliminate.... al-Qaeda in Afghanistan and a whack-job Regime of Saddamite mass-murdering terrorist-backing Baathists in Iraq... a Kim Jung Un Regime with a Trillion Dollars in Oil Wealth and whatever weaponry they wanted!! The only thing Obama has done is Double-Up on Bush's "Nation Building" fiasco! He's far worse than Bush.... and Bush would have at least gotten a Status of Forces Agreement with Iraq! #$%$ Pigs.... you got nuthin'!! Comprende Baggers!?</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1364851494889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 17:24:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364852877104-51</Id><Topic><Title>what a surprise</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1364845582250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 15:46:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welcome back seebe. Yahoo, for a few days had "Connection refused" when accessing the boards but they returned and I believe the Yahoo boards that were discontinued were the numerous chat boards. They left the stock boards intact for investors who do get some informational benefit from an open forum like this. You didn't miss much, I'm sure. As a matter of fact, neither did I. Any given day, my topic list shows up to 20 posts that "have been hidden" due to the ignore feature. :o)</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1364852877104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 17:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364854346716-52</Id><Title>Nanny State" Fascist Obama Bankrupting The Country At Twice The Rate Of Bush!!</Title><Msg>When the debt is at $24 TRILLION THEN you can say that if Obama is in office but not until THEN</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364854346716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:12:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364854398197-53</Id><Title>At least Bush had a couple of REAL threats to eliminate.... Signed corpiss......</Title><Msg>NOPE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Ya fat f.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364854398197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364854486652-54</Id><Topic><Title>Nanny State" Fascist Obama Bankrupting The Country At Twice The Rate Of Bush!!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364854346716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:12:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction! IF the debt is at $48 TRILLION and Obama still in office you can say that.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364854486652</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364855589939-55</Id><Title>When debt is at $24 trillion and Obama in office THEM he did as badly as bgroup. Till then#$%$!</Title><Msg>check and double check</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364855589939</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364855761661-56</Id><Title>Nanny State"</Title><Msg>#$%$ does that mean? "Obama phones" NOT from Obama........massive jobless..not from Obama.LESS govt workers.THAT'S Obama</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364855761661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364855812709-57</Id><Topic><Title>Nanny State"</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364855761661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DOUBLING DEBT! That's bgroup...TRIPLE debt.thats #$%$ reagan.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364855812709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364856497789-58</Id><Title>Nanny State.broup started that in the 21 st century ater 9/11 when they said we couldn't survive w/o them</Title><Msg>#$%$ Bgroup starte treating people like children</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364856497789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:48:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364860226575-59</Id><Topic><Title>"Nanny State" Fascist Obama Bankrupting The Country At Twice The Rate Of Bush!!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1364851494889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 17:24:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's run-rate continues at an unbelievable Trillion dollars a year of ever increasing debt... and this Nanny State #$%$ says "we don't have a debt problem"! Obama treats all of us as his Jesters and the Country as his Fiefdom!!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1364860226575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 19:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364860383367-60</Id><Topic><Title>"Nanny State" Fascist Obama Bankrupting The Country At Twice The Rate Of Bush!!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1364851494889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 17:24:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nanny State #$%$!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1364860383367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 19:53:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364860849420-61</Id><Topic><Title>"Nanny State" Fascist Obama Bankrupting The Country At Twice The Rate Of Bush!!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1364851494889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 17:24:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try 5lut! Better?</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1364860849420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 20:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364861924381-62</Id><Topic><Title>At least Bush had a couple of REAL threats to eliminate.... Signed corpiss......</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364854398197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To quote a "leftist". "Bush lied and men died". American forces are being used as a cats paw by those that really run the U.S. Our pols are enthralled by the money given them and the lying propaganda that can make or break them. I knew an intelligence officer that had worked in Riyadh, Saudi Arabia. Dead now but he told me many things and let me read several non classified books. He did it because my daughter's reserve hospital unit was activated for Gulf War I. EVERY BODY needs to quit believing the lie bund that propagandizes for those that want to rule the world.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1364861924381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 20:18:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364863751923-63</Id><Topic><Title>At least Bush had a couple of REAL threats to eliminate.... Signed corpiss......</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1364854398197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 18:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, jeez, saddam was not a threat, heck Reagan and the neocons gave him money to do what he did, oppress Iranian radicals....... and W let bin laden get away.....Obama got him though.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364863751923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 20:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364863954346-64</Id><Topic><Title>David Stockman, Ex-Reagan Budget Director: George W. Bush's Policies Bankrupt The Country</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364833048574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 12:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stockman is one of the few honest guy. He's absolutely right that the Fed is deadly ‘instrument of speculation’ and a serial bubble machine and that there is no good way out of its current printing binge.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1364863954346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 20:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>