<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374235166541-1</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, I suspect the Hispanic man called Zimmerman would have followed anyone in that age bracket</Title><Username>say92liberals</Username><Timestamp>1374182520337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 17:22:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zimmerman and anyone else in that community, or any other community, had every right to follow whomever they wanted to follow... and an even greater right to defend themselves when attacked! And who gives a flying rats #$%$ what some punk operator in a 911 call center had to say... what he thought might be appropriate means jackshyt! Trayvon Martin made a stupid mistake that is often made by Black teenage punks... try to be the tough guy and kick some creepy white cracker's azzs!!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1374235166541</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 07:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374238568277-2</Id><Topic><Title>Another example of Phony Liberal Insidiousness</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374190470600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:34:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She boasted that she voted twice in last November's presidential election. She was charged with repeatedly voting illegally over three elections using the names of others, including her sister who has been in a coma for a decade. Now 58-year-old Melowese Richardson, a veteran Cincinnati poll worker, will be spending the next five years in prison for voter fraud. "You were the lifeguard, to make sure the system was conducted fairly, the greatest system on earth, the free election system," declared Court of Common Pleas Judge Robert P. Ruehlman, who sentenced Richardson to the five-year term. She faced up to 12 years behind bars after pleading no contest to four state counts in May. "Your job was to make sure it was conducted fairly, but what did you do? You used this position of lifeguard, this position of trust to vote illegally." Richardson's sister has been in a coma since 2003, and authorities said that the votes Richardson cast using her name counted in both the 2008 and 2012 presidential elections. She was also accused of illegally voting in November's election in the names of other people, including her granddaughter India Richardson, who told Fox News that "it wasn't a big deal." But prosecutors ended up charging Richardson with multiple voter fraud counts for voting both in person, and by absentee ballot, in November. In February, Richardson admitted on camera to a local TV station that in November, "I voted twice... I, after registering thousands of people, certainly wanted my vote to count, so I voted. I voted at the polls." But she claimed there "was no intent on my part to commit any voter fraud." "I'll fight it for Mr. Obama and for Mr. Obama's right to sit as president of the United States."</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1374238568277</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 08:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374238690554-3</Id><Topic><Title>would zimmerman have called the cops and followed Jesus?</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374180964618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 16:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are such a racist that you have to make Jesus into a special kind of semetic person, white, blue eyed and blond. You see that a lot in the mid east, huh? "By the 19th century theories that Jesus was European, and in particular Aryan, were developed and later appealed to those who wanted nothing Jewish about Jesus, e.g. #$%$ theologians. Madison Grant for example claimed Jesus was of the Nordic race." wiki</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374238690554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 08:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374241025453-4</Id><Title>the only solution - repamarations</Title><Msg>thats what the protest will be about</Msg><Username>suitcase8858</Username><Timestamp>1374241025453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 09:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374242047896-5</Id><Title>Zimmerman followed a person who was not doing anything wrong and shot him dead</Title><Msg>and nobody knows how the fight started. Zimmerman killed the other person present. For all anyone knows Zimmerman attacked trayvon first and intended to shoot him all along. what is know is that Zimmerman is racist, has a history of violence and had his bail revoked for being a liar.</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374242047896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 09:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374242330703-6</Id><Title>time to get....NRBT</Title><Msg>STRONG BUY</Msg><Username>jimlala94</Username><Timestamp>1374242330703</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 09:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374245105712-7</Id><Topic><Title>I'm afraid that this..</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1374167377929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 13:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, doing my own DD I see that the following companies have reported earnings and/or revenue misses within the past week:, IBM followed by SAP followed by MSFT (not to mention GOOG). In May CRM also missed it's numbers. Do you really think Oracle's poor revenues last Q was company-specific in light of that context? Oracle sold off nearly 10% after earnings while the revenues miss was only 1.5%. Do you think that sell-off was justified? Personally I think the sell-off, while understandable, was overdone relative to the miss. Read the ORCL articles here under 'stock headlines." If you recall sales force issues had been a problem in the past. But you'll see they have a new head of salesforce training--someone with ties to SAP and CRM. She didn't even want the job, but they convinced her to stay. And the other part of my DD tells me that possibly even this quarter, HW could turnaround and become a growth segment. That should provide some upside to the stock. Another reason there was a large sell-off was the reshuffling from Nasdaq to the NYSE. Oracle is not longer a member of the Nasdaq-100 among other indices, so funds would have to sell it off to reflect those changes. That selling pressure is over. Yesterday and Today's price action imo is due to the competitors in the sector reporting some poor numbers. Yesterday it was SAP and IBM. Today it's MSFT. IF you're surprised by that, you need to do more DD yourself. And I would like a rationale behind your statement. I gave your mine for as why I think you're wrong. Now I'll listen for more details from you. TIA.</Msg><Username>the_huntress_7</Username><Timestamp>1374245105712</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 10:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374245166226-8</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman followed a person who was not doing anything wrong and shot him dead</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374242047896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 09:54:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well mesa, it must simply be an over-riding obsession that brings twisted joy to your black rotting heart!! You never give up lying... an endless 24/7 stream of Pigshyt spew!! There's a very nasty place in Hell reserved for you! Bet on it!</Msg><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1374245166226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 10:46:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374245581736-9</Id><Title>If you haven’t seen WAFR you need to drop everything else</Title><Msg>Investors make their move on WAFR, sending market valuation off the charts</Msg><Username>oconnorjonathan477</Username><Timestamp>1374245581736</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 10:53:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374246757839-10</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman followed a person who was not doing anything wrong and shot him dead</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374242047896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 09:54:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still on your rant? Everything Zimmerman said has been backed up by witnesses. If you don't want to get shot don't attack people. I went to school with this type of punk. I know what trhey are like.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1374246757839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 11:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374247154688-11</Id><Topic><Title>would zimmerman have called the cops and followed Jesus?</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374180964618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 16:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Israelites were taken into Babylkon. After the fall of Babylon many migrated through the Caucusus Mts. into Europe that's why they are called "Caucasians". Read Flavius Josephus's book "Antiquities of the Jews". He tells how Alexander showed favor to the few left in Judea because he knew his ancestors had migrated from there. "19th Century?" I have a copy of a letter to the Pope in the 1400's from Scottish Chiefs stating that they knew they were descended from ancient Israelites. Names of people and lands change through the years and people move.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1374247154688</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 11:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374247572410-12</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman followed a person who was not doing anything wrong and shot him dead</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374242047896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 09:54:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What we ałso know is that Zimmerman was acquitted. Jimmy carter agrees with jury. Bill Cosby agrees. Charles Barkley agrees too. Mesa, you are a racist.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374247572410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 11:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374249728141-13</Id><Topic><Title>would zimmerman have called the cops and followed Jesus?</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374180964618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 16:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Takes Romney’s Advice on Detroit By Chris Stirewalt Power Play Published July 19, 2013 “We refused to throw in the towel and do nothing. We refused to let Detroit go bankrupt. We bet on American workers and American ingenuity, and three years later, that bet is paying off in a big way.” -- President Obama in his weekly address, Oct. 13, 2012. Just before Detroit became the largest municipality to ever file bankruptcy, the failed city’s emergency manager, Kevin Orr, pleaded with top White House officials, including senior adviser Valerie Jarrett, for help. But no help was coming. That detail in the Wall Street Journal’s coverage of how the once-great city, now $11 billion in debt, finally succumbed may be the most telling of any in the slew of obituaries for Detroit. For all of the invective launched by President Obama and his campaign against challenger Mitt Romney last year for having argued for structured bankruptcy for the city’s Big Three automakers, in the end, the most liberal, most pro-union president since LBJ opted to take Romney’s advice when it came to the city itself. Detroit has been teetering on the brink for years. Its huge debt is mostly from unfunded employee benefit programs, constituting some $9 billion of the total. Those pensions and bennies were negotiated in fatter days for government worker unions there, but the contracts stayed in place long after the collapse of the Big Three’s superpower status made such self-dealing for government workers and the Democrats they patronized unsustainable.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1374249728141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374250597121-14</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman followed a person who was not doing anything wrong and shot him dead</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374242047896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 09:54:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so what, OJ was acquitted. like I said, Zimmerman started the affair because of his racist and stupid ASSumption and because he was a bully who decided to follow. Nice how you think Zimmerman is not responsible for his own bad decisions. and btw. For all ANYONE knows, Zimmerman attacked trayvon. Easy to see you are the typical racist in denial about your own racism</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374250597121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374250777348-15</Id><Title>Momentum Picking up in WAFR</Title><Msg>Oil and gas player WAFR brings strategic prowess to exploding industry</Msg><Username>jonathansherman190</Username><Timestamp>1374250777348</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:19:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374250862497-16</Id><Title>Have you checked out WAFR</Title><Msg>WAFR is waking up investors with its outstanding gain potential</Msg><Username>jonathansherman190</Username><Timestamp>1374250862497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374251095308-17</Id><Topic><Title>would zimmerman have called the cops and followed Jesus?</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374180964618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 16:56:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, sure, Jesus spoke English, has blonde hair and blue eyes and was really a Viking or a Russian or a hun or other northern European and so were Mary and Joseph and the rest of the folks in the Mideast at the time. I think Moses may have been told to expect a messiah that was not like any of the locals.The disciples were blond and blue eyed too and so were the Romans, the master race of the time.</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374251095308</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:24:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374251664924-18</Id><Title>BK Detroit</Title><Msg>Liberalism on parade. Congrats libs. The inevitable outcome of your ideology. You own it so wear it.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374251664924</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374253112514-19</Id><Title>Piers Morgan should be deported</Title><Msg>The consummate liberal #$%$ cracker. Just one in a long line of BSNBCs ditzy commentators. It's no wonder they're ratings are in the gutter. That whole crew should be doing commercials for car insurance or erectile dysfunction.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374253112514</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374254158698-20</Id><Title>Liberal Democrats! Corrupt Black Pols! Insatiable Unions! GM Stupidity! Nanny-Town Mentality!</Title><Msg>Gee... who woulda guessed that Detroit would go Bankrupt! Bulldoze it and start over with immigrants from Eastern Europe and the Far East... who get free airfare, free cars, free homes and citizenship if they agree to Regenerate this Pigsty!! The only good thing is that the Emergency City Manager, a Black guy, looks like he has some smarts and backbone! Democracy is pure garbage when the electorate and the elected are pure garbage!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1374254158698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374254466382-21</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Democrats! Corrupt Black Pols! Insatiable Unions! GM Stupidity! Nanny-Town Mentality!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1374254158698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:15:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem with liberalism is that eventually you. Run out of other people's money. That is exactly what happened in Detroit. More cities the size of Detroit will follow. It,s an inevitable culmination of liberalism.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374254466382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374255353895-22</Id><Title>Trayvon's parents in denial</Title><Msg>Trayvon was truant numerous times from school, was suspended 3 times for misconduct, had a drug problem, His mother couldn't control him so she sent him to live with his father. By all accounts this kid was headed for trouble. Now they're saying he was a wonderful boy, characterizing him as a saint and the only thing causing his death was that he was black. If a civil suit goes forward, their personal lives will be hung out as well. Chances are the verdict would be the same.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374255353895</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:35:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374255487168-23</Id><Title>god is not a white and blue eyed viking or hun and the bible says so more or less</Title><Msg>God created man in his own image. most of the men on earth are not white or blue eyed. therefore god is not white or blue eyed. and Jesus should be depicted as a looking of swarthy Middle Eastern appearance, as were others from that region. Not that it matters what a person looks like as long as they are not black and wearing a hoodie and walking innocently down the street in a WASP neighborhood, right?</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374255487168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374255617383-24</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Democrats! Corrupt Black Pols! Insatiable Unions! GM Stupidity! Nanny-Town Mentality!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1374254158698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:15:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dems won't let the money run out and Obama will bail them out.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374255617383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374255641827-25</Id><Title>Obama quote of the day</Title><Msg>If I had a city it would look like detroit</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374255641827</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374255758719-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama quote of the day</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374255641827</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:40:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has a nation that will look like Detroit soon.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374255758719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374256380407-27</Id><Title>Zimmerman was just keeping it real and upping his street cred.</Title><Msg>Zim did not want to be a sellout by acting white.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1374256380407</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374256494208-28</Id><Title>AFronomics is failing in Detroit</Title><Msg>You can not redistribute brains and work ethics.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1374256494208</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374257012690-29</Id><Title>Obamas other quote of the day</Title><Msg>Trayvon could have been me 35 years ago No he couldn't,t have. 35 years ago Obama wass in Hawaii. What a stupid remark.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374257012690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374257748436-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obamas other quote of the day</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374257012690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:03:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He meant smoking pot and divorced parents.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374257748436</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374258794154-31</Id><Title>Michael Moore Divorcing!!</Title><Msg>Well... one thing for sure! It damm well can't be "another woman"... at least his! But I hope his wife takes him to the cleaners.... 21 year marriage! She takes half of everything! He's worth millions! A good day for America!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1374258794154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:33:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374259900056-32</Id><Title>insider selling</Title><Msg>catz sells another $100 million or so this week. any questions? mw</Msg><Username>mrwright192234</Username><Timestamp>1374259900056</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374263961282-33</Id><Title>Why We Should Stop Subsidizing Sky-High CEO Pay</Title><Msg>corporations deduct it from their income taxes, causing the rest of to pay more in taxes to make up the difference. Last year 107 CEOs of Standard &amp; Poor 500 companies got performance-based awards totaling $1.4 billion even though their companies showed negative returns relative to an index of all stocks, according to an analysis by Bloomberg Business. Not only are shareholders taken to the cleaners by these maneuvers. So are you and I and other taxpayers. Almost everyone knows CEO pay is out of control. It surged 16 percent at big companies last year, and the typical CEO raked in $15.1 million, according to the New York Times. Meanwhile, the median wage continued to drop, adjusted for inflation. What’s less well-known is that you and I and other taxpayers are subsidizing this sky-high executive compensation. That’s because corporations deduct it from their income taxes, causing the rest of to pay more in taxes to make up the difference. So what’s the answer? As I argued 20 years ago, keep the cap at $1 million and get rid of the performance-pay loophole. Executive pay in excess of $1 million shouldn’t be deductible from corporate taxes, period. Why We Should Stop Subsidizing Sky-High CEO Pay robert reich</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1374263961282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 15:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374264491442-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obamas other quote of the day</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374257012690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:03:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>State says Obamacare will force 72 percent increase in individual insurance plan rates Jul. 19, 2013 | Written by Tony Cook President Barack Obama speaks in the East Room of the White House in Washington, Thursday, July 18, 2013. Obama has stumbled on an unusual partner in his quest to combat climate change: China. / (AP Photo/Susan Walsh) Insurance rates in Indiana will increase 72 percent for those with individual plans and 8 percent for small group plans under President Barack Obama's healthcare overhaul, according to the state’s insurance department. The spike in costs is due primarily to new mandates under the law, which requires insurers to cover those with pre-existing conditions and to offer a minimum level of benefits, said Logan Harrison, chief deputy commissioner with the Indiana Department of Insurance under Republican Gov. Mike Pence. New taxes and fees under the law also contributed, Harrison said. “This new data regrettably confirms the negative impact of the Affordable Care Act on the insurance market in Indiana,” he said. “The Affordable Care Act requires many Hoosiers to purchase more comprehensive and more expensive health insurance than they may want or need. These rates call into question just how affordable health insurance will really be for many Hoosiers.”</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1374264491442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374265230213-35</Id><Title>Michigan has been run almost exclusively by the gop for decades</Title><Msg>currently gop governor and gop super majority of both houses of state congress. The Michigan Senate has been controlled by the Republicans since 1983 and the house has been gop for all but 5 of the last 23 years. Michigan has had a gop governor for 15 of the last 23 years.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1374265230213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374265682082-36</Id><Title>Obama's racist offensive comments today.....</Title><Msg>We are all supposed to understand the "black communities" perspective on this... Yet pathetic libs refuse to consider the "white communities" perspective... A black youth jumped a lighter skinned man... yet we are to believe that the lighter skinned man did not fear for his life... consider the history of young black males committing violent assaults... It happens to be a common occurrence... In the Zimmerman/Martin fiasco... everyone points to the "Stand your Ground law" (defense) which was not even invoked by the defense... they put up a classic old style self defense case and won.... Obama needs shut that big fat lipped trap.... because not only is he himself an offensive racist.... he's starting to really tick off those of us who have taken the time to get legal guns Screw with me.... I'm gonna tell you I'll more than screw with you filthy racist in chief</Msg><Username>mktplyr517</Username><Timestamp>1374265682082</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:28:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374266077985-37</Id><Title>Just another bad day for Obama in 2013</Title><Msg>Nothing seems to go his way anymore</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1374266077985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374267205705-38</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan has been run almost exclusively by the gop for decades</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1374265230213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:20:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's your point? Detroit has had a dem mayor since 1961</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374267205705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374268911093-39</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan has been run almost exclusively by the gop for decades</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1374265230213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:20:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Michigan in not the problem, azzswipe! Detroit is!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1374268911093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 17:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374277375209-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obamas other quote of the day</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374257012690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:03:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has more in common with Zimmerman ----- one white parent.</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1374277375209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 19:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374278373416-41</Id><Title>Has Anyone Heard Obama Speak</Title><Msg>of all the murders in Detroit or Chicago? Speak about those bros being like him? Not so surprising that he distances himself from the crime infested world that Trayvon aspired to join. He and most blacks are missing the boat by ignoring black crime and how it is affecting their young people. When are they going to submit to reality?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374278373416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 19:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374279718968-42</Id><Topic><Title>Has Anyone Heard Obama Speak</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374278373416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 19:59:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>F. O. idiot!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1374279718968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374279785854-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obamas other quote of the day</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374257012690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:03:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHAT an idiot you continue to be BOY!!!!!</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1374279785854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:23:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374279927264-44</Id><Topic><Title>Why We Should Stop Subsidizing Sky-High CEO Pay</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1374263961282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 15:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost everyone knows CEO pay is out of control. Blame the Republicans for that Jacko!!</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1374279927264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374281149720-45</Id><Title>Another Official Embarrasses the Dems</Title><Msg>Top Dems silent on San Diego mayor scandal. As usual they sweep it under the carpet. This is so obvious, it's funny. He's likely thanking his lucky stars that he's a Dem. Spitzer and Weiner are high on liberal tolerance and running again. The audacity of sleazebags!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374281149720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374289763364-46</Id><Topic><Title>Another Official Embarrasses the Dems</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374281149720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:45:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Morally bankrupt donkeys.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1374289763364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374289932491-47</Id><Topic><Title>Why We Should Stop Subsidizing Sky-High CEO Pay</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1374263961282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 15:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It happens in communist countries, why not here! Everyone should make the same amount of money in America, except for the govt ruling class. They work REALLY hard.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1374289932491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374290071759-48</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan has been run almost exclusively by the gop for decades</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1374265230213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:20:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hydroencephologousmessybird knows it's the black bastion of politics and unions, just can't face facts. Remember, all libiots are idiots.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1374290071759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374290153970-49</Id><Topic><Title>Just another bad day for Obama in 2013</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1374266077985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:34:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he is Dingy Harry's brother! Really. Really.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1374290153970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:15:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374290368104-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obamas other quote of the day</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1374257012690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:03:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Albert, Buck is right. Read Sheriff Hurley's take after he was fired. Trayvon should have been in jail for theft, fighting, maryjane use, breaking and entering, etc. Just a thug.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1374290368104</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374290486302-51</Id><Topic><Title>Has Anyone Heard Obama Speak</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374278373416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 19:59:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alberto, another apt description of truth. They badly need to address the killings in their own back yard.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1374290486302</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:21:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374290562111-52</Id><Topic><Title>Michael Moore Divorcing!!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1374258794154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is one hunk of a worthless POS. Dingy Harry, here he comes.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1374290562111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374290670334-53</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman was just keeping it real and upping his street cred.</Title><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1374256380407</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If he was all white, Obummer and Holder would have gone to Floida themselves to prosecute an innocent man.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1374290670334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374290735158-54</Id><Topic><Title>god is not a white and blue eyed viking or hun and the bible says so more or less</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374255487168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:38:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My goodness, you are popular.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1374290735158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374290922850-55</Id><Topic><Title>Piers Morgan should be deported</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1374253112514</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They obviously ran him out of England. Scalia overwhelmed him in a one hour interview recently. The English screwball didn't know whether to wind his watch or sheet himself.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1374290922850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>