<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362562791668-1</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation on MAD MONEY TODAY!!</Title><Username>efrain.mercer</Username><Timestamp>1362394647203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great news!!!!</Msg><Username>charlesjohn584</Username><Timestamp>1362562791668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 04:39:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362567319136-2</Id><Topic><Title>Hugo Chavez dead</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1362524939633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 18:08:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>repubs are silly, childish and dumb and their reaction to Chavez illustrates it well. DUMMIES! The US is usually to blame when others don't get along with us...did you know that?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362567319136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 05:55:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362569648800-3</Id><Title>"Maximum Pain" Obama!! Sequestration Scam On The Tortured Mice Of America!</Title><Msg>The lying S0B and fraud won't "water-board" a few low-life mass murdering Islamic terrorists because it's just oh so "immoral" and un-American, but he's thrilled to inflict Maximum Pain on Americans, torturing them with long lines, fear tactics and childish pranks to try and make his "Sequestration Scam" appear real! We all know it's just more Pigshyt from a PC fascist President trying to set himself up for the final TWO years of an Obama-Pelosi-Reid "Maximum Rape" of America!!!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1362569648800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 06:34:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362572619915-4</Id><Title>Repubs have no right at ALL</Title><Msg>to complain about sequester...you pretend to hate debt, .then what's your problem? You're FAKE, DISHONEST corpiss db's.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362572619915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:23:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362573989523-5</Id><Topic><Title>being an Americanbuiz person means you're a lying POS #$%$!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362527607909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 18:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does anyone feel they can trust anyone you're spending money with US BIZZ will RIP YOU OFF at every opportunity. No,..businesspeople are NOT to be worshipped. They are to be closely watched and regulated. say the worst people are business people. Money makes them that way. FACT, Jack.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362573989523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:46:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362574232526-6</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>moyasefangelina</Username><Timestamp>1361889545234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:39:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this article.</Msg><Username>ricomincjoanne</Username><Timestamp>1362574232526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:50:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362574445191-7</Id><Topic><Title>Hugo Chavez dead</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1362524939633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 18:08:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hating Chavez is like hw IGNORANT Amerians hate Iran.. US is 100% to blame for our problems with Iran. WE STARTED THEPROBLEMS! Why can't Americans be HONEST? Instead hey're dumb.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362574445191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:54:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362574519669-8</Id><Topic><Title>Hugo Chavez dead</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1362524939633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 18:08:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.and the ignorant Cuban Americans in Miami</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362574519669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 07:55:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362575548180-9</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation on MAD MONEY TODAY!!</Title><Username>efrain.mercer</Username><Timestamp>1362394647203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>jackbrown538</Username><Timestamp>1362575548180</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:12:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362575992873-10</Id><Title>DRONES!!!!!!!!!!!!! Repubs are full of corpiss</Title><Msg>When bgroup were in WH repubs LOVED DRONES! Ya loved ANYTHING repub WH did. Ya loved it when they SLAUGHTERED as many people as possible,..ya loved it when "Patriot" Act stepped on our civil rights. Take your concerns and shove them up your corpisses. You all are 100% dishonest.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362575992873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:19:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362576404285-11</Id><Title>Pardon me while I weep for that left wing dictator piece of #$%$.,,,says seeebe</Title><Msg>............now............if he had been a RIGHT-wing dictator THAT would be different,,, signed seebe.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362576404285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:26:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362578927754-12</Id><Title>This will make your day</Title><Msg>Revenues approximately doubled last year as did earnings and expected again this year. Perfect size company (only 600 mil sales. Price needs to rise just to get to where the normal p/e of a typical fast growing company should be. It has a p/e of 22 and should have one of 40. Not only should the price rise for a higher p/e but also it should rocket up with the expected fast rise in earnings. We could easily see the price triple in one year considering these items. The SYMBOL: (AL) - a high profit airline leasing business. Company has billions of dollars in new jets ordered from Boeing and Airbus so obviously they expect a lot more business. I have 20 years experience evaluating hundreds of companies, this is one of the top 3 company stocks I have ever found. The company reported great earnings again and also leased 2 - Boeing 777's, and ordered 10 more Boeing 777's. Symbol (AL) Another interesting but more speculative stock is (edap). The company is big into ultrasound and they finished a study showing ultrasound works on prostate cancer without side effects like chemotherapy. The company is applying for approval with the FDA and it is expected to go through on a fast track because of the excellent results. This undiscovered company is priced at only $4. (edap)</Msg><Username>emsggim</Username><Timestamp>1362578927754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:08:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362582324288-13</Id><Title>Whining Democrat, President Obama, loses his bluff and is now pouting like a 5-yr old girl...</Title><Msg>...at a tea party with her stuffed animals! Because he loses 2.5% of the INCREASE in spending, he is trying to slow down, or stop, the government. No White Hiuse tours? Hey, cut Michele's record budget by 10%, dude! he cant take his ball and go home like the worthless Harry Reid in the Senate, so he pulls this #$%$. What a child!</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362582324288</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:05:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362582460660-14</Id><Title>Hypocrite Democrats and their lemming followers love drones now, but uder Bush</Title><Msg>...they hated them. DO you guys ever get consistent, or do you just enjoy lying, crying, and whining so much you just gotta do it! Get that monkey off of your backs and get on a 12 step program.</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362582460660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:07:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362582563197-15</Id><Topic><Title>Dropkicks stupidity as it relates to businesses can only mean he believes.....</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362535239112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 21:00:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>about 1/3 as much as a politician, especially a Democrat! So, if there are no businesses, dropkick, what do we do for commerce, income, food, h2o, etc? Get it from Uncle Obama, Uncle Harry, or Auntie Nancy?</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362582563197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:09:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362583536912-16</Id><Title>Is Oracle or Sap buying NTWK ???</Title><Msg>Does anybody know ????</Msg><Username>jesus_loves_ntwk</Username><Timestamp>1362583536912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:25:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362583615533-17</Id><Topic><Title>Look at this report. It will definitely change your mind!</Title><Username>roy_sparker</Username><Timestamp>1361887356209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:02:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>important information !</Msg><Username>perkins.jack</Username><Timestamp>1362583615533</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:26:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362583651428-18</Id><Title>How about some real data on taxes -- the Democrats are taking more than enough from us</Title><Msg>In 1955, the margina top rate was 91%. However,the EFFECTIVE tax rate was 35.8% for those earning $1 mil, 35.6% for those making $500k to $1 mil, and 36.8% for those making $200k to $500k' In other words, the tax code allowed so many writeoffs that it diminished the actual taxes paid by about 2/3s. in 2012, the top marginal rate was 35%, but the effective taxes paid by the top 1% was about 21%, a much smaller difference as writeoffs have consistently been taken away, especially during the REAGAN and BUSH tax plans were enacted. in other words, lower rates were traded for less writeoffs. Now, for the pea brains out there, the number of people at these top rates is much higher than in 1955. thus, the amount of total taxes being paid by them is much, much higher. delucks, you do follow the simpler maths, yes?</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362583651428</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:27:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362583697770-19</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone see our wimpy president yesterday whining and sniveling about the mean GOP</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1362493800554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 09:30:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is still at it today!</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362583697770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:28:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362583757850-20</Id><Topic><Title>And Obama = no new jobs, no inteest income, and $1.76 trillion in regulation costs</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362515192153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 15:26:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about all those new jobs!</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362583757850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:29:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362583842982-21</Id><Topic><Title>The top 1% make 19% of the income and pay 38% of all taxes, yet that's not progressive.....</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1362493299954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 09:21:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrat morons cannot fathom simple math --- things ike too much debt, to few jobs, the tax system is more progressive than ever, not enough "rich" people to close the deficit, etc.</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362583842982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:30:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362583992398-22</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation on MAD MONEY TODAY!!</Title><Username>efrain.mercer</Username><Timestamp>1362394647203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perfect one</Msg><Username>johnbussell595</Username><Timestamp>1362583992398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:33:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362584708936-23</Id><Topic><Title>"Maximum Pain" Obama!! Sequestration Scam On The Tortured Mice Of America!</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1362569648800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 06:34:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well... at least we're done with one fascist President... loved by most of the PC Press sluts!</Msg><Username>itsthepress_stupid</Username><Timestamp>1362584708936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:45:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362585781562-24</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>moyasefangelina</Username><Timestamp>1361889545234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:39:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>lovelinesslou</Username><Timestamp>1362585781562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:03:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362586114010-25</Id><Topic><Title>"Maximum Pain" Obama!! Sequestration Scam On The Tortured Mice Of America!</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1362569648800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 06:34:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya got nuthin corpiss. Nothing to indicate you have any ethics, standards or scruples.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362586114010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:08:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362586996656-26</Id><Topic><Title>restore progressive taxation! and return to the top tax rates of the Eishenhower years</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362507955371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 13:25:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 1955 the IRS took 51.2% of the top 400 incomes.......Recently the top 400 have paid just 16.6% on an astounding average income of $345 million............................and the trickle down from the rich getting richer made everyone better off right?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362586996656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:23:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362587082980-27</Id><Topic><Title>lamebrain pubs are always flabbergasted that taxes come from where the money is</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362432510645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 16:28:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>12% of all income goes to the entire 70 million in the bottom half..... where else can income axes come from but where it is at the top?...but the pubs here are flabberghasted!!! omg....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362587082980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:24:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362587199234-28</Id><Topic><Title>lamebrain pubs are always flabbergasted that taxes come from where the money is</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362432510645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 16:28:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>March 6, 2013, 6:03 AM Obama administration struggles to illustrate pain from sequester 225 Comments / 213 Shares / 193 Tweets / Stumble / Email More + The Obama administration has overreached three times in the past 10 days in attempting to illustrate the negative impact of the sequester spending cuts in the short term, giving fodder to those seeking to play down the impact of the cuts. On Monday, Homeland Security Secretary Janet Napolitano told reporters that major airports had seen lines ballooning to 150-200 percent their normal size. The Transportation Security Administration later clarified that it was not yet seeing longer-than-normal checkpoint lines, though Customs and Border Protection told CBS News there had been increased wait times at two airports due to reduced staffing. The Wall Street Journal reported Tuesday, however, that "officials representing a dozen major airports said there were few if any unusual flight delays or lines at security or customs checkpoints." That included an official at John F. Kennedy Airport in New York, which is one of the two airports that had been specifically cited by Customs and Border Protection. On Friday, meanwhile, President Obama said that janitors at the U.S. Capitol would receive a pay cut due to the sequester cuts. Carlos Elias, the superintendent of the U.S. Capitol building and the Capitol Visitors Center, quickly emailed employees to say "This is NOT TRUE," adding that "The pay and benefits of EACH of our employees WILL NOT be impacted." The prior Sunday, Education Secretary Arne Duncan had said on CBS' "Face the Nation" that "There are literally teachers now who are getting pink slips, who are getting notices that they can't come back this fall." He later acknowledged that he "misspoke" after fact checkers found no evidence for the claim. On Monday, White House Press Secretary Jay Carney was asked what was being done to ensure the figures were not being exaggerated. Carney responded by pointing to long-term projections of job losses from economic analysts and "numerous examples already of what's going to happen," including plans to furlough 750,000 Department of Defense Workers. Pressed about the issue again Tuesday - specifically why Napolitano did not check her facts before making her claims regarding longer lines - Carney said it is a "fact" that "there will be negative effects on our air traffic because of the reductions in FAA man hours, air traffic controllers in particular."</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1362587199234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:26:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362587283589-29</Id><Title>Democrat morons cannot fathom simple math</Title><Msg>bgroup, 99% of repubs back in 2001-2002 are the ones that couldn't do math. They cut revenues and doubled spending. WITH YOUR SUPPORT! Ya got NUTHIN at least until you apologize and admit what you are..,,a PUNK.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362587283589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:28:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362587671620-30</Id><Topic><Title>lamebrain pubs are always flabbergasted that taxes come from where the money is</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362432510645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 16:28:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pub states are the first to start whining... the fed gov is the largest employer in many. texas , for one, Utah for another: "The federal government is the biggest employer in the state, employing 34,000 people in Utah. The list of the largest state employers is topped by Hill Air Force Base, a mammoth, 6,650-acre installation that specializes in aircraft maintenance. A city unto itself, Hill features residences, “a modern shopping complex,” plus “a bowling center, fitness center, clinics, chapel, museum, recreation center, officer and enlisted clubs, dining facilities and a child development center.” It has 1,475 buildings and 228 miles of roads. According to Natalie Gochnour, chief economist of the Salt Lake Chamber of Commerce, Hill directly employs 9,300 military personnel and 16,300 civilians, with a combined annual payroll of $1.2 billion. In addition, the base purchases $832 million in goods and services locally each year. But wait, there’s more. A large regional IRS processing facility in Ogden (here’s a street view) employs between 4,000 and 5,000 state residents."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362587671620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:34:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362588180099-31</Id><Title>gop govs whining about sequester cuts</Title><Msg>Arizona Gov. Jan Brewer (R) – also wouldn't rule out tax increases as part of an eventual solution to avoid the sequester. Speaking on "Face the Nation," Governor Brewer noted that her state would be hit particularly hard by the cuts to border patrol agents. "We don't like increases in taxes," she said. "But … we know we have to be pragmatic. We know that there has to be some type of compromise Gov. Rick Perry (R-Texas) warned that "lives will be put in jeopardy" from cuts to military and air-transit funding. &amp; state Republican officials are already starting to freak out. Virginia Governor Robert McDonnell, a onetime Tea Party favorite, is worried the sequester will affect the large military and government operations in his state. That’s to be expected. Economically speaking, the Commonwealth of Virginia is rapidly becoming an exurb of the District of Columbia. But Washington pols may soon be hearing about the negative impact of the sequester from some distant Republican redoubts – like Utah. the sequester is going to make the music really discordant in Hatch’s home state, which is disproportionately dependent on the federal government. The federal government is the biggest employer in the state, employing 34,000 people in Utah. The list of the largest state employers is topped by Hill Air Force Base, a mammoth, 6,650-acre installation that specializes in aircraft maintenance. A city unto itself, Hill features residences, “a modern shopping complex,” plus “a bowling center, fitness center, clinics, chapel, museum, recreation center, officer and enlisted clubs, dining facilities and a child development center.” It has 1,475 buildings and 228 miles of roads. According to Natalie Gochnour, chief economist of the Salt Lake Chamber of Commerce, Hill directly employs 9,300 military personnel and 16,300 civilians, ....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362588180099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:43:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362588374822-32</Id><Topic><Title>restore progressive taxation! and return to the top tax rates of the Eishenhower years</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362507955371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 13:25:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Progressive Taxation my azzs! It couldn't get anymore Progressive than it already is, you mouthy idiot!! The lower 50% pay Jackshyt in Income Taxes and get 99.9% of Obama's Nanny State payouts!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1362588374822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:46:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362588401929-33</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation on MAD MONEY TODAY!!</Title><Username>efrain.mercer</Username><Timestamp>1362394647203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>love that report!</Msg><Username>frederickstone909</Username><Timestamp>1362588401929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:46:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362588828110-34</Id><Topic><Title>restore progressive taxation! and return to the top tax rates of the Eishenhower years</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362507955371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 13:25:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you are lamebrain or what? the guy making $400 million pays the SAME rate as the guy making $45 million or the one making $450K...... jeez......... zero progessivity for the rich and super rich...... and btw, in In 1955 the IRS took 51.2% of the top 400 incomes.......Recently the top 400 have paid just 16.6% on an astounding average income of $345.................OBVIOUSLY many in the middleclass paid a higher burden of their income than did the top 400 returns........so you are indeed a lamebrained liar.....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362588828110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:53:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362589192434-35</Id><Title>The lower 50% pay Jackshyt in Income Taxes and get 99.9% of Obama's Nanny State payouts!</Title><Msg>You ugly repub fool...............just look at defense spending and cuts..........are they the people to whim you refer?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362589192434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:59:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362590987190-36</Id><Topic><Title>restore progressive taxation! and return to the top tax rates of the Eishenhower years</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362507955371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 13:25:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure. Let's also cut all the taxes that did not exist during the Eisenhower years and eliminate all the welfare prorgrams that did not exist.</Msg><Username>paul374</Username><Timestamp>1362590987190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:29:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592043586-37</Id><Topic><Title>restore progressive taxation! and return to the top tax rates of the Eishenhower years</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362507955371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 13:25:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the guy making $1000 pays the same as the guy making 35,000... Jackshyt! The top 30%, making $70,000 plus, pay about 90% of all Federal Income taxes! And they get Jackshyt from the Federal Govt other than a #$%$ and demand to pay more... all while the Lower 50% keeps sucking up the taxpayer funded Nanny State bennies and demanding even more! Stuff your Progressive BS and ObamaPhone where the sun don't shine!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1362592043586</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:47:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592047185-38</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Insiders SELLING?!</Title><Username>caballero_ashley</Username><Timestamp>1362318802861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:53:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362592047185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:47:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592086207-39</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation on MAD MONEY TODAY!!</Title><Username>efrain.mercer</Username><Timestamp>1362394647203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>floydpotter938</Username><Timestamp>1362592086207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:48:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362592088902-40</Id><Title>Well... at least we're done with one fascist President... loved by most of the PC Press sluts!</Title><Msg>Chavez???????????? Loved by the press????????? #$%$ do you think you're saying? You're full of corpiss.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362592088902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:48:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592418616-41</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>moyasefangelina</Username><Timestamp>1361889545234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:39:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An article that's worth a read.</Msg><Username>quietpadela</Username><Timestamp>1362592418616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:53:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362592634542-42</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH ORCL Analyst Report .</Title><Username>zelmastafford</Username><Timestamp>1361112271314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 09:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>almeda.mosley</Username><Timestamp>1362592634542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:57:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362592839050-43</Id><Title>The wealthy and all big earners "TAX" the system, they TAX the infrastructure, they receive most the benefits</Title><Msg>They SHOULD pay BY FAR most the taxes. Again and again, ALL OF GOVT was put in place initially FOR the wealthy,,.every gd thing govt did for most the first 150 years was for the wealthy and it still is. .and again, bankruptcy, police protection, SIPC, FDIC all the rest DRAWBRIDGES..YOU NAME IT all installed and created for the wealthy. The wealthy BY FAR get the most benefit from govt and all of society. The wealthy are the ones govt mostly lends an ear to...</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362592839050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:00:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362593138172-44</Id><Topic><Title>restore progressive taxation! and return to the top tax rates of the Eishenhower years</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362507955371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 13:25:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are just a liar. there would be ZERO tax on an income less that the standard deduction, moron... which IS not the case of an income of 35K.....and jackass, the wall street billionaires just raked in billions in bonuses taxed at 15% carried interest and it was only because they got bailed out by the taxpayers, so there is the welfare for the rich..... I say return to the top rates of the eisenhower era... then the top 400 would pay 50.2% of their income as they did then and not the 16.6% they pay now.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362593138172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:05:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362593218886-45</Id><Title>BTW, class warfare is a republican thing</Title><Msg>They hate the poor and others and want to F them as much as possible.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362593218886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:06:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362593373898-46</Id><Title>Doomed to Repeat History</Title><Msg>You have to laugh when these DA liberals say the DOWs numbers are some masterful stroke by Obama. It's called a stock market bubble. Remember back in early 2000s when hundreds of companies went bust. At that time the real estate bubble was holding up the economy thanks to Fannie/Freddie. That went sour and the fat cats need another bubble and will falsely inflate the market as long as the Fed keeps printing money. Obama's cronies on WS run the racket. and he knows it. . When the balloon blows, 1929 will look like mardi gras.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1362593373898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:09:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362594670724-47</Id><Title>You have to laugh when these DA liberals say the DOWs numbers are some masterful stroke by Obama. Signed, asssbuckeroo</Title><Msg>repubs prefer 8 years of bgroup with double digit net LOSSES. REpubs are jealous</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362594670724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:31:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362596450179-48</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation on MAD MONEY TODAY!!</Title><Username>efrain.mercer</Username><Timestamp>1362394647203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great, thanks!</Msg><Username>georgethompson382</Username><Timestamp>1362596450179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:00:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362598443119-49</Id><Title>does anyone really think a ceo works 300 or 400 times more than the avg employee?</Title><Msg>they get paid 300 or 400 times more....... only a few decades ago they got paid about 25 times more... and USA corps were run just as well....... (and ntm they had to pay higher taxes then)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362598443119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:34:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362598970210-50</Id><Title>Switzerland to vote on allowing shareholders to limit CEO pay (&amp; most favor that)</Title><Msg>"The heated debate in Switzerland on “fat cat” pay has led to a consensus of sorts: shareholders should have a say in top managers’ salaries. Just how much of a say, a nationwide vote on March 3 on the so-called Minder initiative will decide."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362598970210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:42:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362599042721-51</Id><Title>Swiss overwhelmingly vote to rein-in executive pay: projection</Title><Msg>A large majority of Swiss voted Sunday to rein in executive pay and force business leaders to give up golden parachutes, according to early results and projections. Official first results of the popular vote showed that in Geneva, where polling ended at noon (1100 GMT), 67.7 percent voted in favour of the initiative, with similar numbers in the canton of Vaud and Fribourg. And projections from Switzerland's financial capital Zurich, where voting will continue until 6:30 pm, showed 71 percent of voters want the so-called Minder Initiative, after its sponsor businessman and senator Thomas Minder, passed into law. "The people have decided to send a strong signal to boards, the Federal Council (Swiss government) and the parliament,"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362599042721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:44:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362599118973-52</Id><Title>time for some austerity for the fat cats, shareholders should cut ceo pay</Title><Msg>the fat cats preach austerity, but not for them of course.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362599118973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:45:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362599298085-53</Id><Title>search and find this video: Watch: The Staggering Extent of Wealth Inequality in the U.S.</Title><Msg>watch it all! you too, limbots!! Watch: The Staggering Extent of Wealth Inequality in the U.S. . do a search for : ........Watch: The Staggering Extent of Wealth Inequality in the U.S. An infographic-heavy video on wealth distribution that went viral over the weekend reveals that the gap tween the rich and the poor in the U.S. is probably much worse than you think</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362599298085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:48:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362599911783-54</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT REPORT ON ORCL</Title><Username>riley_hughes</Username><Timestamp>1361406576123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:29:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job mate. Thank you</Msg><Username>henryclark930</Username><Timestamp>1362599911783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:58:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362600336050-55</Id><Topic><Title>IMPORTANT REPORT ON ORCL</Title><Username>riley_hughes</Username><Timestamp>1361406576123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:29:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER !!</Msg><Username>daxwang</Username><Timestamp>1362600336050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:05:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362601332172-56</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Insiders SELLING?!</Title><Username>caballero_ashley</Username><Timestamp>1362318802861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:53:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !</Msg><Username>douglas.goddard</Username><Timestamp>1362601332172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:22:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362601729128-57</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH ORCL Analyst Report .</Title><Username>zelmastafford</Username><Timestamp>1361112271314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 09:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !</Msg><Username>douglas.goddard</Username><Timestamp>1362601729128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:28:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362601938878-58</Id><Title>House approves bill preventing shutdown March 27</Title><Msg>Why? Does anyone think their changes will be any better? HA! Again,..if those repubs don't like the auto cuts..............then.............I do. In fat I love them.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362601938878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:32:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362602865601-59</Id><Topic><Title>Doomed to Repeat History</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1362593373898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:09:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to laugh when these DA liberals say the DOWs numbers are some masterful stroke by Obama. Admit it IDIOT,you just hate to see ANYTHING go good under Obama.He's fixing the mess left by Georgette W Bush and it's killing you rightwing bimbos.Racist?</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1362602865601</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:47:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362604623678-60</Id><Topic><Title>Doomed to Repeat History</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1362593373898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:09:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U sound like the racist as you are attributing skin color to another's opinion or observation. U need help. As for the market,it is a simple matter of people searching for a return since Obama's Fed has destroyed the risk/return equation in the bond market with ongoing zero rates. Pretty simple stuff.</Msg><Username>cykdelic</Username><Timestamp>1362604623678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:17:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362604732082-61</Id><Topic><Title>Swiss overwhelmingly vote to rein-in executive pay: projection</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362599042721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:44:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am a fiscal conservative and I am all for eliminating golden parachutes.</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362604732082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:18:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362605037530-62</Id><Title>1% of earners pay 38% of all taxes, yet make only 19% of income --- VERY progressive indeed!</Title><Msg>So what is so wrong with this you moronic, lemming-like lefties? It seems pretty dang progressive to pay taxes at a rate 2X your income generating levels.</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1362605037530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:23:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362605092159-63</Id><Topic><Title>And Obama = no new jobs, no inteest income, and $1.76 trillion in regulation costs</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362515192153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 15:26:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hello? Where are the Obama jobs? Hello?</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362605092159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:24:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362605194270-64</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrite Democrats and their lemming followers love drones now, but uder Bush</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362582460660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:07:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about those drones?</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1362605194270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:26:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362605357979-65</Id><Title>Speaking of drones and Democrats</Title><Msg>Does anyone know (or have a hypothesis) on why Homeland security is stockpiling automatics weapons and drones, etc.?</Msg><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1362605357979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:29:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362606616443-66</Id><Topic><Title>restore progressive taxation! and return to the top tax rates of the Eishenhower years</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362507955371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 13:25:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pigshyt idiot! A husband and wife with 1 child small home mortgage making $35,000 /yr and standard deduction will pay virtually nothing in Fed Income taxes!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1362606616443</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:50:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362607360664-67</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation on MAD MONEY TODAY!!</Title><Username>efrain.mercer</Username><Timestamp>1362394647203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well done</Msg><Username>stevenhill681</Username><Timestamp>1362607360664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:02:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362607761163-68</Id><Topic><Title>restore progressive taxation! and return to the top tax rates of the Eishenhower years</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362507955371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 13:25:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i see ,you want to impoverish people barely getting by to make sure the top 400 continue to pay an average 16.6% on their avg $345 million a year incomes? who do you suppose would by more cars, refrigerators and furniture if they made a little more...... 70 million people in the bottom half scraping by on $35K or less who take in less than 12% of all US income......or the 1.4 million who take in 20% of all USA income...........your idiot, anti democracy, anti USA regressive tax policies are starving the economy......if the trend of the rich getting richer and everyone else getting poorer continues soon there will be even less demand for products and less jobs and so on until you end up with your ideal, since you are a tory, an arisitocracy and a class of paupers.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362607761163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:09:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362608085196-69</Id><Title>Pigshyt idiot! A husband and wife with 1 child small home mortgage making $35,000 /yr and standard deduction will pay virtually nothing in Fed Income taxes!</Title><Msg>You UGLY fat punk,..how much ya think they can AFFORD to pay you #$%$!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362608085196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:14:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362608465501-70</Id><Title>TAKE A LOOK AT- NTWK-MY SOFTWARE PICK FOR 2013-THIS IS A REAL COMPANY !!IM LONG !!!</Title><Msg>LOAD UP !!!</Msg><Username>cccpc008</Username><Timestamp>1362608465501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:21:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362610702205-71</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Report and Stock Poll</Title><Username>moyasefangelina</Username><Timestamp>1361889545234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-26 09:39:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>scoutstrina</Username><Timestamp>1362610702205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:58:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362613308793-72</Id><Topic><Title>You have to laugh when these DA liberals say the DOWs numbers are some masterful stroke by Obama. Signed, asssbuckeroo</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362594670724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:31:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You see why we laugh at you, buckwheat. You think Bush and Obama are directly responsible for the market ups and downs. May I remind you that before the Dems got a majority in the senate in 2006,, jobs were plentiful and gas was much cheaper. Obama should really do something about that instead of conducting market trends. LOL! I would rather have 8 years of Bush than 1 year of the community organizer who can't organize his own adminstration , no one knew how or why Benghazi happened. Just another entry in the oops colume for BO.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1362613308793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:41:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362613308863-73</Id><Title>the top 1% of the population have 40% of the wealth and the bottom 80% have 7%.</Title><Msg>An excellent, appalling,video on wealth inequality in America, where the top 1% of the population have 40% of the wealth and the bottom 80% have 7%. It's gone viral, probably because so many are hurting and angry and visuals are so much more arresting than news stories on the sequester. search and find the informative video Weatlh Inequality in America</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362613308863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:41:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362613539803-74</Id><Title>The new crime for paying a CEO too much money?</Title><Msg>Two-thirds of a national referendum (in one of the finance capitals of the world!) voted to give shareholders the right to slash their executives' compensation and banned "golden parachutes" for outgoing executives. The new crime for paying a CEO too much money? As much as three years in jail or six years' salary in penalties.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1362613539803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:45:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362614147815-75</Id><Title>Does anyone know (or have a hypothesis) on why Homeland security is stockpiling automatics weapons and drones, etc.?</Title><Msg>bgroup exec order</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362614147815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:55:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362615848025-76</Id><Topic><Title>Does anyone know (or have a hypothesis) on why Homeland security is stockpiling automatics weapons and drones, etc.?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1362614147815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 18:55:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anti-Drone Senators Mount Filibuster Kentucky Sen. Rand Paul launches into an old-fashioned filibuster — and is joined by other Republicans and even a Democrat — trying to hold up the nomination of John Brennan for CIA director over concerns about President Obama's authority to kill Americans who oppose him with drones.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1362615848025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 19:24:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362620064869-77</Id><Title>end of the U.S.</Title><Msg>Eric Holder in the news today: -saying that Wall Street firms are "too big to prosecute" -saying that the U.S. can target civilians in the U.S. with drone attacks great super what a hero this guy should be fired, but he's just towing the line same as Obama yikes</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1362620064869</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 20:34:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>