<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365048420951-1</Id><Title>what's wrong w/ repubs is that they constantly LIE!</Title><Msg>Like runners with his no crosses in military cemetaries and other db claiming obama debt is accumulating 8 times faster than reagan debt. They never stop! With their lies.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365048420951</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 00:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365048525233-2</Id><Title>we should all not worry and be happy.... /that was first stinking bushs theme song after reagan tripled the dent</Title><Msg>DROPKICK you pos</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365048525233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 00:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365070619744-3</Id><Title>Obama wants immigration bill rushed thru</Title><Msg>one possible reason for the rush? If the murder of the TX DA was done by the Mexican drug cartel, as many think, such might put the brakes on a vote, no?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365070619744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 06:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365076343723-4</Id><Title>the profundity of Chuck Hagel</Title><Msg>"North Korea's provocative and "bellicose" actions in recent weeks must be taken seriously," Defense Secretary Chuck Hagel ... Whoa! really Chuck? Well, give him credit for using "bellicose," a 3 syllable word.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365076343723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 07:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365078717285-5</Id><Topic><Title>What Should I do With ORCL...Buy, Sell or Hold???</Title><Username>l_stave</Username><Timestamp>1364912872695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:27:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish i would have seen this earlier</Msg><Username>lisaphillips522</Username><Timestamp>1365078717285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 08:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365080028120-6</Id><Title>the profundity of Chuck Hagel,, wonders seebe</Title><Msg>COME ON! Who talks like that ? Who uses that word?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365080028120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 08:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365080116061-7</Id><Title>Obama wants immigration bill rushed thru,,,gee, I never noticed reubs bush or reagan say their backed bills should be rushed</Title><Msg>repubs TRY not to be hypocrite double talkers,, that's a laugh,</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365080116061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 08:55:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365080545270-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wants immigration bill rushed thru,,,gee, I never noticed reubs bush or reagan say their backed bills should be rushed</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365080116061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 08:55:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The number of Americans filing new claims for unemployment benefits rose to its highest level in four months last week, suggesting the labor market recovery lost some steam in March. Initial claims for state unemployment benefits increased 28,000 to a seasonally adjusted 385,000, the highest level since November, the Labor Department said on Thursday. It was the third straight week of gains in claims. Coming on the heels of data on Wednesday showing private employers added the fewest jobs in five months in March, the report implied some weakening in job growth after hiring accelerated in February. Economists polled by Reuters had expected first-time applications last week to fall to 350,000. The four-week moving average for new claims, a better measure of labor market trends, rose 11,250 to 354,250. A Labor Department analyst said claims for California and the Virgin Islands had been estimated and there were no special factors in the underlying state-level data. While the claims report has no bearing on Friday's nonfarm payrolls data for March as it falls outside the survey period, it hinted at some weakness in hiring.</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1365080545270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365080626815-9</Id><Title>GM to invest $332 million in 4 US factories,,, sorry rep[ubs, I know ya hate that,,,ya #$%$</Title><Msg>repubs give their feelings away and show everyone what p's o s they all are</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365080626815</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365081528431-10</Id><Topic><Title>GM to invest $332 million in 4 US factories,,, sorry rep[ubs, I know ya hate that,,,ya #$%$</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365080626815</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:03:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right Pig... maybe they'll build a new plant, somewhere in the South, that might keep their "steering wheels" from falling off and employ people who aren't total FUPS!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1365081528431</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:18:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365081688362-11</Id><Title>corpiss,..you're a fhed, a FAT fhead at that,, corpiss and all repubs hate America and</Title><Msg>Americans.......and they ADMIT IT!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365081688362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365081769363-12</Id><Title>rose to its highest level in four months last week, You can hope for the worst all ya want but the trend is for BETTER</Title><Msg>times,..no matter wat your hope is</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365081769363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365082155464-13</Id><Title>W and crew didn't bother with the real wmd in N. Korea</Title><Msg>W spent trillions getting rid of imaginary wmd in Iraq instead. N korea has no oil so bush &amp; his oil cronies didn't see much money to be made for themselves there, I guess.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365082155464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365082361450-14</Id><Topic><Title>the profundity of Chuck Hagel</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365076343723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 07:52:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"North Korea's provocative and "bellicose" actions in recent weeks must be taken seriously," Defense Secretary Chuck Hagel ... Whoa! really Chuck? Well, give him credit for using "bellicose," a 3 syllable word. I know you had to look it up in the dictionary to find out what he meant.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1365082361450</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365082375119-15</Id><Topic><Title>=(BREAKING NEWS) Analyst Downgrades ORCL =(MUST READ)</Title><Username>johnnyford834</Username><Timestamp>1363881147525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:52:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report.</Msg><Username>markgray783</Username><Timestamp>1365082375119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:32:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365086229309-16</Id><Topic><Title>the profundity of Chuck Hagel</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365076343723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 07:52:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Though the White House has been singing the sequester blues, the Obamas still have managed to scrape together enough cash to throw a star-studded concert celebrating "Memphis Soul" later this month. The White House announced Tuesday that the 10th concert in its "In Performance at the White House" series would go on April 16. Set to perform are Al Green, Ben Harper, Queen Latifah, Cyndi Lauper and Justin Timberlake, among many others. Though the White House last month decided to suspend official tours of the "people's house" citing the sequester, the budget cuts apparently have not impeded the concert schedule. Since their inception in 2009, the White House concerts have featured Paul McCartney, Stevie Wonder and other stars. The concerts are not for the Obamas' ears only. The events are streamed live on whitehouse . g ov/live, and the April 16 concert will be broadcast on PBS stations across the country. It will also be broadcast to U.S. forces overseas at a later date. Virtually every social event held by the first family, though, has come under scrutiny, given the impact of the sequester. Republican lawmakers ripped the administration for its decision to cancel White House tours, which affected school groups and others who had made spring plans to visit. The administration claimed that it made the call in order to save the Secret Service money, and in turn reduce the need to furlough agents.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1365086229309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365086884282-17</Id><Topic><Title>the profundity of Chuck Hagel</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365076343723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 07:52:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has a James Stockdale demeanor when he stands up and attempts to speak.</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365086884282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:48:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365086973461-18</Id><Title>Hey, how about all those new jobs Obama didn't create!</Title><Msg>Add another month of dismal failure to Obama's economic record. 51 and running. Bully taw!</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365086973461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365087210357-19</Id><Title>Obama still trying to steal Marco Rubio's immigration policy and pretend it is his own.</Title><Msg>Without an original thought in his head, Obama continues to steal Rubio's policy and call it his own. Are there ANY examples of Obama original thought in anything ? His Obamacare idea is 70 years old. His immigration policy is Rubio's. His economic policy is.......well, he actually doesn't have one, he just does whatever is the opposite of capitalism.</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365087210357</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365087397923-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama adds debt at 6x the rate of Reagan!</Title><Username>cykdelic</Username><Timestamp>1365025498049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:44:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the sad truth ---- Reagan added about $200 bil a year, while Obama is adding about $1.2 TRILLION a year.</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365087397923</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:56:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365087474686-21</Id><Title>Reagan added about $200 bil a year, Obama is adding about $1.2 TRILLION a year</Title><Msg>I hope the truth doesn't hurt your little socialist feeling to much.</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365087474686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365089914625-22</Id><Title>Trading was never so easy</Title><Msg>I texted “stocks” to 555888 and got daily picks sent to my phone. I’ve improved as a trader simply following their picks.</Msg><Username>adamkelly804</Username><Timestamp>1365089914625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:38:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365090197889-23</Id><Topic><Title>Eleven children escaped Newtown classroom while Adam Lanza was reloading</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364999862870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:37:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The caliber makes a lot of difference. The whole purpose of a 45 caliber is to knock a person down because it hits harder. A 22.3 is slightly larger than 22 caliber, which generally is harder to make a quick kill with. I believe the 22.3 is supposed be high velocity and the impact is from the high velocity, not the weight of the slug. The military type rounds are also supposed to "key hole" on impact (tumble end over end) and the tumbling bullet does more damage. I am not sure this applies to 22.3 home ammunition rounds. I've also heard stories that high velocity, small caliber bullets can speed right through a body and do little damage. One well placed shot to the head or heart will kill almost instantly. One could also spray a target with 7 bullets and hit arms &amp; legs and other non-vital areas and the person might suffer awhile before dieing. If one were sadistic, one could make a point of doing 2 or 3 non-lethal hits just to torture the victim. If Lanza had only shot each person only 2 or 3 times it is plausible that some victims might have survived their wounds. Shooting each victim 5, 6 or 7 times tends to guarantee they are dead, even obliterated. Again, to me, that many shots per victim implies fear, rage, excitement and inexperience in the shooter. It simply is not necessary to shoot a child that many times to kill them. The idea that it is a faster and less painful death is speculation on your part. I believe elite military forces are trained to control their shooting so as not to waste bullets shooting people who are already dead.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1365090197889</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:43:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365090755051-24</Id><Title>Reagan added about $200 bil a year, Obama is adding about $1.2 TRILLION a year ///YOU SIMPLETON MORON POS REPUB!</Title><Msg>You're kidding right??? Any idea how much $200 bil in the 80's equates to NOW? Regan TRIPLED the debt nearly during his 8 year nap.. TRIPLE then is TRIPLE now y mo ron. TRIPLE MEANS TRIPLE fface! I know you're kidding and realize reagan was the worst..you'r just pretending to be a complete idiot. You're only a 3/4 idiot.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365090755051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365090773038-25</Id><Topic><Title>Eleven children escaped Newtown classroom while Adam Lanza was reloading</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1364999862870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:37:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Resorting to insults and curses only proves you're a moron. (Another "feel good" liberal approach!) I merely point out that the focus on high capacity magazines is misguided. Would we have been less horrified if Lanza had ONLY killed 15 to 20 people, instead of 26? Would we have been less horrified if the crime had taken 4 minutes &amp; 21 seconds instead of "only" 4 minutes? That us essentially the difference based on magazine size..</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1365090773038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365090878703-26</Id><Title>Rubo is a moron... a simpleton,.. a liar and a fake</Title><Msg>he's a fool, he's a spanish speaking dan quayle hes got nuthin.,,,,,,,,hes perfect,</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365090878703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365092448193-27</Id><Title>NYC pols eating their own.</Title><Msg>One dem sells out another. Folks, this is the kind of entertainment you'd pay big bucks to watch. Bronx Assemblyman Eric Stevenson, sold out by one of his corrupt colleagues, was charged Thursday with pocketing nearly $20,000 in bribes to boost the launch of an adult day care center. Stevenson was busted with the aid of Assemblyman Nelson Castro, a fellow Bronx Democrat, according to the 38-page court filing and sources familiar with the matter. Stevenson was arrested Thursday morning. According to the criminal complaint, Stevenson accepted one cash-stuffed envelope outside a Bronx steakhouse, and a second from a cooperating witness who was once an assembly candidate — but now worked for the adult home. Castro, after agreeing to cooperate in January 2012, wore a wire to record Stevenson and others as officials investigated the influence-peddling scandal. One of Stevenson’s co-defendants, during an initial conversation with Stevenson, told the assemblyman he would be “blessed” with the cash for his help, the documents show. Stevenson, in a later taped conversation, was caught asking for more cash from his four co-defendants, Igor Belyansky, Rostislav Belyansky, Igor Tsimerman and David Binman.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365092448193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365092701253-28</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Insiders Selling ?</Title><Username>coxevan881</Username><Timestamp>1363886774305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great !</Msg><Username>melaniehilfinger</Username><Timestamp>1365092701253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365093041564-29</Id><Topic><Title>What Should I do With ORCL...Buy, Sell or Hold???</Title><Username>l_stave</Username><Timestamp>1364912872695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:27:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guys lets buy the Stock And earn money</Msg><Username>brownjeff73</Username><Timestamp>1365093041564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365093200932-30</Id><Topic><Title>NYC pols eating their own.</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365092448193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be so dramatic...ya think this is ANYTHING ?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365093200932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365095222577-31</Id><Title>Why does Left keep comparing Obama to Reagan, Bush_41 &amp; Bush_43?</Title><Msg>Because Obama is a failure. And he needs to show it's anybody elses fault. If things were going well, we would only hear how wonderful Obama was doing.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1365095222577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:07:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365095357322-32</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Insiders Selling ?</Title><Username>coxevan881</Username><Timestamp>1363886774305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks</Msg><Username>trevorparker141</Username><Timestamp>1365095357322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:09:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365095514992-33</Id><Title>Open letter to Xi Jinping &amp; Li Keqiang</Title><Msg>Please leash and control your vicious little pet.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1365095514992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365096098825-34</Id><Topic><Title>NYC pols eating their own.</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365092448193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah I think it's something. While most people assume pols are self-centered crooks, this episode confirms it. If it involves a politician, nothing happens unless envelopes of dough first wind up in the hands of one.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365096098825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365096484206-35</Id><Title>The Numbers Show Gun Owners Really Do Back Obama The problem is stinking repubs in congress bought by nra</Title><Msg>DISGUSTING!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365096484206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365096563772-36</Id><Topic><Title>NYC pols eating their own.</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365092448193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. It seems the #$%$ making the laws do not put our best interests FIRST,..like repubs in congress regarding guns.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365096563772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365096874079-37</Id><Topic><Title>NYC pols eating their own.</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365092448193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at it this way... politicians believe themselves to be above the very laws that they write and swear to defend</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1365096874079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:34:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365097073528-38</Id><Topic><Title>The Numbers Show Gun Owners Really Do Back Obama The problem is stinking repubs in congress bought by nra</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365096484206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:28:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pigshyt!! The only thing truly disgusting in America is White PC Pigs!</Msg><Username>itsthepress_stupid</Username><Timestamp>1365097073528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365097413519-39</Id><Title>itsthepress_stupid •..and ANOTHER corpiss id</Title><Msg>WHAT is wrong with you? WHY are you so fat, stupid, ugly and change id's all the time?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365097413519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365097465775-40</Id><Title>runners!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Where'd you hear crosses not permitted in US cemetaries abroad?</Title><Msg>TELL ME!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365097465775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365097676371-41</Id><Topic><Title>NYC pols eating their own.</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365092448193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there you go again drop...asuming guns taken from the hands of the law abiding will lead to less crime. Meanwhile guns ithe hands of criminals will remain there. If you get your way it will be all the bad guys and no you. You feel good about that?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365097676371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:47:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365098206480-42</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst ORCL Price Target Reduced =SEE REPORT</Title><Username>vandammarc</Username><Timestamp>1364409400371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 14:36:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>exelent news</Msg><Username>cristianomerteza</Username><Timestamp>1365098206480</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:56:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365098596660-43</Id><Title>there you go again drop...asuming guns taken from the hands of the law abiding will lead to less crime.</Title><Msg>TAKEN AWAY from???????????????????????NO ONE IS SAYING DO THAT...Correct me if I am wrong You truly want to keep it the way it is now?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365098596660</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365098969273-44</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Insiders Selling ?</Title><Username>coxevan881</Username><Timestamp>1363886774305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very useful info</Msg><Username>mirandacosgrove406</Username><Timestamp>1365098969273</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365099132615-45</Id><Topic><Title>there you go again drop...asuming guns taken from the hands of the law abiding will lead to less crime.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365098596660</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:03:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're right. I got ahead of myself. They won't be taken away yet, but not because the left doesn't want to. Eventually they'll get to that. Nothing wrong with law abiding cits keeping their weapons. The laws you support will do nothing to stop Newtowne from happening again.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365099132615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365099876514-46</Id><Topic><Title>Rubo is a moron... a simpleton,.. a liar and a fake</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365090878703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moron, simpleton, liar and fake. So you're saying Rubio is just like Obama? What's with the "spanish speaking"? Rubio is American and like many others knows more than 1 language. So now you're the racist? You really are a sleazy, pretentious, mindless, prejudice DA dago who outdumbs Joe Biden, if you want to point to VPs. For every push, there's a SMACK. I win! Haha, I bet your wife loves Rubio. .</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1365099876514</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365100485706-47</Id><Topic><Title>the profundity of Chuck Hagel,, wonders seebe</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365080028120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 08:53:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seebe . COME ON! Who talks like that ? Who uses that word? The dumbazz seebug,who else?</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1365100485706</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365100983666-48</Id><Title>The dumbazz seebug,who else? I didn't say that.he said that but seriously seeb,,, what made you use that word</Title><Msg>I had to look it up to be sure I knew it</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365100983666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365101547608-49</Id><Topic><Title>The dumbazz seebug,who else? I didn't say that.he said that but seriously seeb,,, what made you use that word</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365100983666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:43:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me? I used "bellicose?" Only when I quoted Chuck Hagel. I quoted Hagel because I was amazed that he used or even knew a 3 syllable word to describe the North Korea situation. Was that really hard for you and Phil to figure out?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1365101547608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365101716886-50</Id><Title>Reagan added 54 times the debt that eisnhower did</Title><Msg>In Eisenhower's 8 years the USA he added only $31 billion to USA debt Reagan added 54 times that......$1,692 billion Ronald Reagan Republican WOW that is quite a record!!! for Obama to have done the same with a president 30 years previous, ie , Reagan, he would have to spend the same 54 times increase that Reagan did on the guy 30 years previous to him....Eisenhower so 54 times Reagan's $1692 billion = or $91368 billion.......easy to see Reagan was the all time big spender.......to equal what he did over Eisenhower, Obama would have to add 91.4 trillion to the national debt......................(of course all of this is for the moron's who can't quite get it that Reagan tripled the nation's debt something Obama won't do) increases to national debt in millions $153 Franklin D. Roosevelt Democratic $55 Harry S. Truman Democratic $31 Dwight D. Eisenhower Republican $20 John F. Kennedy Democratic $58 Lyndon B. Johnson Democratic $115 Richard Nixon Republican $145 Gerald Ford Republican $280 Jimmy Carter Democratic $1,692 Ronald Reagan Republican</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365101716886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:55:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365101818405-51</Id><Title>WARNING--CHINA HOUSING BBUBBLE IS COLLAP$ING--WARNING!!!</Title><Msg>GET OUT CHINA NOW! GO TO USA!</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1365101818405</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365102378928-52</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan added about $200 bil a year, Obama is adding about $1.2 TRILLION a year</Title><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365087474686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not familiar with the concept of exponential? Looks like you suck at maths.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1365102378928</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365102636250-53</Id><Topic><Title>That's total BS. The only rate that makes sense is the % increase by year.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365045933248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 23:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly. The US population increases 1.3%/y The US GDP increases 2% per y US prices increase 3% per y ... exponentials... Why would it make sense to compare nominal numbers from 30 years ago to now? It doesn't.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1365102636250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365102795455-54</Id><Topic><Title>Credit Hos are back in force.</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1365034731788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:18:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You dummies let this happen. You want to help the country? Don't borrow money. - except to buy a house and then put 20+% down. That's simple.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1365102795455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365102985562-55</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Insiders Selling ?</Title><Username>coxevan881</Username><Timestamp>1363886774305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finance Search Thu, Apr 4, 2013, 3:12 PM EDT - U.S. Markets close in 48 mins. Advertisement Advertisement Stock Watch Panera Bread Gets Goldman Boost, Hits Record High IBM Quashes Oracle's SPARC Claims ZacksBy Zacks Equity Research | Zacks – 3 hours ago Email Recommend Tweet 3 Print RELATED QUOTES Symbol Price Change INTC 21.12 0.08 HPQ 22.25 0.34 IBM 211.00 -1.66 ORCL 32.34 -0.06 Reportedly, International Business Machines (IBM) has retorted to Oracle’s (ORCL) claim that the recently-launched SPARC servers (powered by T5 and M5 chips) are much faster and cheaper (delivers 5 times to 12 times better cost performance) than IBM Power servers. IBM challenged Oracle’s findings and said that the comparisons were primarily made with older systems (3 to 5 year old systems according to Business Insider). Hence, the data does not reflect the current performance of the systems. Oracle had cited data from Standard Performance Evaluation Corporation (“SPEC”) and Transaction Processing Performance Council (“TPC”) to validate its claims. Moreover, IBM also quashed Oracle’s claim that its new T5-8 server, priced at $270K, is much faster than IBM’s P780, which costs approximately $1.9 million. IBM said that the systems were not comparable and for a similar type of setup, its price range is equivalent to Oracle’s recent releases. IBM and Oracle are traditional rivals. The competition intensified after Oracle entered the hardware market in 2010. The relationship took an ugly turn in 2012, when IBM forced Oracle to pull advertisements that claimed superiority of its Exadata products over IBM systems. The recent spat reflects escalating rivalry between the two global giants as Oracle continues to search for ways to boost its sagging hardware business. Oracle’s recent releases target IBM’s dominant position (more than 50% market share) in the high-end UNIX server market.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1365102985562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365103994018-56</Id><Title>Anemic</Title><Msg>Performance by this stock. Incapable of moving up today. Stuck in mud!</Msg><Username>inbounds7</Username><Timestamp>1365103994018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:33:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365104100344-57</Id><Title>Obama &amp; Bernanke Are Driving The Country Straight Into Bankruptcy!</Title><Msg>These Ivy League Keynesian Sluts have WASTED $10 Trillion in 50 months and the Country is worse off NOW than it was in Jan 2009! Both the Government and the Fed are broke... left only to printing and borrowing money by the Boatload!! In just over FOUR Years Obama has taken Federal Debt from $10 Trillion, to $11 Trillion, to $12, $13, $14, $15, $16 and NOW even $17 Trillion while Bernanke has pushed Fed liabilities from less than $1 Trillion to over $3 Trillion! A total Debacle and the markets haven't a FING clue... save that Obama and Bernanke are spending OUR MONEY and our FUTURE like totally insane Whack-Jobs! Markets love being awash in Money no matter that NONE of it, not a penny, has been Earned!!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1365104100344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365105073398-58</Id><Title>so runners,...where the hell did you hear cross aren't alowed in American cemetaries abroad?</Title><Msg>Just askin, I gotta tell ya... I HATE it when people say things like you did if you're wrong. Are ya wrong? Too many people base their feelings on inaccurate information.. You one of those dummies?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365105073398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:51:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365105170001-59</Id><Title>Obama &amp; Bernanke Are Driving The Country Straight Into Bankruptcy! Reagan tripled debt bush doubled it</Title><Msg>most the money that's been spent since Obama was in wh was signed off on by repubs in the HOUSE! fOFF</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365105170001</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365105734978-60</Id><Topic><Title>What Should I do With ORCL...Buy, Sell or Hold???</Title><Username>l_stave</Username><Timestamp>1364912872695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:27:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool thanks for sharing that. I will be sure to look into that.</Msg><Username>pplaleen</Username><Timestamp>1365105734978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365107831472-61</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan added 54 times the debt that eisnhower did</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365101716886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:55:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you notice that Reagan took the debt he started with and TRIPLED it? That is a record, the record. and fyi Reagan added 54 times the debt that Eisenhower did. has Obama added 54 times the debt that Reagan did? no way not even close..... that is for the morons who want to compare the actual dollars Reagan spent compared to Obama.... do the same with Eisenhower then to get a glimpse of the HUGENESS of Reagan's debt.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365107831472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365108151900-62</Id><Topic><Title>Obama &amp; Bernanke Are Driving The Country Straight Into Bankruptcy!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1365104100344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And all the King's PC Pimps keep spewing the same old warn-out phony excuses for our thoroughly incompetent radical country-screwing President and his pack of White Ivy League azzs-kissers!!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1365108151900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365108367804-63</Id><Title>Only an  idiot believes taxing, say, Silicon Valley businesses and giving more...</Title><Msg>..to the government can help the economy.</Msg><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1365108367804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:46:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365108598007-64</Id><Title>What is so hard to understand that the 1% paying 40% of all taxes now, and only 20% in 1980</Title><Msg>is pretty freaking progressive? That even after all socialists crying about lower marginal tax rates for the "rich" from Reagan and Bush, they are actually paying a tax burden TWICE as high as before?</Msg><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1365108598007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365108736663-65</Id><Title>I get it! We are in Obama's "Japanese Solution" to the economy! Just 11 more years before progress.</Title><Msg>The Japanese have tried this "government spending to get out of recession" idea ----- after 16 years (a lost decade and a half!), they MIGHT be starting to build an economy again. Clearly, Obama sees this as success!</Msg><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1365108736663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365108856224-66</Id><Topic><Title>Obama &amp; Bernanke Are Driving The Country Straight Into Bankruptcy!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1365104100344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's add that the #$%$ Fed policy is a major driver of the "record profits". Basically, free money on the taxpayers dime (two ways: we will be paying off the debt AND we get no return on our saved monies).</Msg><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1365108856224</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365108877805-67</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan added 54 times the debt that eisnhower did</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365101716886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:55:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eisehower understood the "Military Industrial Complex" and the banksters that ran the racket. He shut down the racket in Korea and saved many lives, maybe mine. Boobus Americanus doesn't comprende what he said though and continues to vote in the stooges of the NWO.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1365108877805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365108965164-68</Id><Title>Gosh! If we are going back to Immaterial times, Obama added a bazillion times Adam's debt!</Title><Msg>Oh my!</Msg><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1365108965164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365109117118-69</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan added about $200 bil a year, Obama is adding about $1.2 TRILLION a year</Title><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365087474686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RU not familiar with simple math???? Uh, $1.2 trillion is, uh, let's see, carry the double naught, move the stickies to the left........yep! 6x!</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365109117118</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:58:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365109254294-70</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan added about $200 bil a year, Obama is adding about $1.2 TRILLION a year</Title><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365087474686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you like Obama's returns on his debt. After ball, he got us 24 CENTS for every dollar of debt ha added. Say, did you have $$$ with Maddoff?</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365109254294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365109291512-71</Id><Topic><Title>Obama &amp; Bernanke Are Driving The Country Straight Into Bankruptcy!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1365104100344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Especially for the Banks!!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1365109291512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365109381046-72</Id><Topic><Title>Rubo is a moron... a simpleton,.. a liar and a fake</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365090878703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Passthebuckaroo, Delucks has always been a misogynist racist. Nothing new there. Hey, delucks ---- back up your swill, moron. Share some specific lies with us.</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365109381046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365109463268-73</Id><Topic><Title>Obama adds debt at 6x the rate of Reagan!</Title><Username>cykdelic</Username><Timestamp>1365025498049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:44:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Careful there, cyk. Are you being exponential?</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365109463268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365112792804-74</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan added 54 times the debt that eisnhower did</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365101716886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 14:55:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reagan is the king of debt and the king of growing government and the king of tobacco advertising!</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365112792804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:59:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365113279797-75</Id><Title>So Obama gives back a meager 1700/ wk in salary,than spends $170k to fundraiser?</Title><Msg>Even though he cannot be elected again? Sounds like his usual investment methods.</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1365113279797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365113349264-76</Id><Title>Nancy Pelosi's campaign manager, Barrack Obama, has little time left to create jobs...</Title><Msg>for the middle class, who continue to get hammered under his failing policies.</Msg><Username>say92liberals</Username><Timestamp>1365113349264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365113536591-77</Id><Title>Delucks non-logic on debt appears to support his idiot investment strategy .</Title><Msg>Delucks is the slow thinking type who prefers 30% of $1 over 10% of $100 because "..... 30% is bigger!"</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1365113536591</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:12:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365114754720-78</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan added about $200 bil a year, Obama is adding about $1.2 TRILLION a year</Title><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365087474686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot reagn TRIPLED the debt..obama hasn't even doubled it.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365114754720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365115087063-79</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan added about $200 bil a year, Obama is adding about $1.2 TRILLION a year</Title><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365087474686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cheney said deficits///debt/ don't matter as repubs doubled debt in 2000's as reagan tripled the debt in 80's you #$%$ said it was great nearly all of obama defict spending has been signed off on by repubs in house over a trillion of "obama debt" was already in pipeline from bush and the rest was carved in stone FROM bush bgroup took over with budget surplus and they then squandered it with unnecesary wars and unnecessary tax cuts when they had no business giving tax cuts. YA GOT NUTHIN!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365115087063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365115177004-80</Id><Topic><Title>So Obama gives back a meager 1700/ wk in salary,than spends $170k to fundraiser?</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1365113279797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:07:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try your calculations again moron!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365115177004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365115206407-81</Id><Topic><Title>So Obama gives back a meager 1700/ wk in salary,than spends $170k to fundraiser?</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1365113279797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:07:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much have repubs agreed to give back?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365115206407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365116606663-82</Id><Title>McDonald's strike: Fast-food workers want to double wages</Title><Msg>I'm stickin with the union</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365116606663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365116844906-83</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan added about $200 bil a year, Obama is adding about $1.2 TRILLION a year</Title><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365087474686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Add into the equation that #$%$ reagan and bushes created $12 tril in debt that is still there and the interest assocated with that $12 tril and that $12 tril was money back in THOSE years which is now much more,,,basically..regan and bushes are 99% to blame for ALL DEBT! TRILLIONS of that debt are from INTEREST from reagan and bushes dbt.,..FOFF! JUST from the interest from those three #$%$! REPUBS ARE 99% to blame!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365116844906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365117015516-84</Id><Title>So Obama gives back a meager 1700/ wk in</Title><Msg>AGAIN I POINT OUT YOU FLUNK W/ Go ZINTAS!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365117015516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365117038715-85</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan added about $200 bil a year, Obama is adding about $1.2 TRILLION a year</Title><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1365087474686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do a linear comparison on numbers that grow geometrically. You suck at maths. The debt will pass $30 trillions by 2021. That's regardless of what ugly republicans or democrat is president at that time.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1365117038715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365117856417-86</Id><Title>trillions of debt since obama are from interest on reagan bush debt</Title><Msg>repubs99% to blame</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365117856417</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:24:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365118769322-87</Id><Topic><Title>What is so hard to understand that the 1% paying 40% of all taxes now, and only 20% in 1980</Title><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1365108598007</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:49:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice assertion repeated all over conservative media, targeted at intellectual dwarves that can't see how specious it is. For example, it doesn't say what percent of revenues go to 1% in 1980 vs now. (would be useful, no?) It doesn't say either what percent of revenues people in the top 1% pay as tax, and compare that to other people. As it turns out, the top 1% pays about the same percent of revenues as taxes than the top next 10%, and maybe 5% more than people in the middle 20% in spite of enormous differences in revenues. They get a disproportionate share of their revenues from unearned income that is taxed at a lower rate than revenues that require to do, you know, actual work.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1365118769322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365120585513-88</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Insiders Selling ?</Title><Username>coxevan881</Username><Timestamp>1363886774305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice report!</Msg><Username>ethansmith188</Username><Timestamp>1365120585513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365123095548-89</Id><Topic><Title>trillions of debt since obama are from interest on reagan bush debt</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1365117856417</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:24:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama’s insulting salary stunt Posted by Richard Cohen on April 4, 2013 at 10:27 am I once had a boss who was independently rich, and when I asked him for a raise, he turned me down, adding that he, too, had forsaken a raise that year. A surge of anger, resentment and sheer hatred welled up in me, and were it not that I needed the job, I would have gone for his throat. His unthinking and unthinkable attempt to make common cause with me brought to mind Anatole France’s observation that “The law, in its majestic equality, forbids the rich as well as the poor to sleep under bridges, to beg in the streets, and to steal bread.” Now it brings to mind Barack Obama. President Barack Obama (EPA/Tannen Maury) President Barack Obama (EPA/Tannen Maury) The president yesterday announced that he would return 5 percent of his salary to the Treasury Department. This is an effort to make common cause with federal employees who may have to take a similar paycut. This is the way this tone-deaf White House put it: The president has decided that to share in the sacrifice being made by public servants across the federal government that are affected by the sequester, he will contribute a portion of his salary back to the Treasury. The president makes $400,000 a year. In addition, he is provided living quarters on Pennsylvania Avenue, several limos, a very nice (Rose) garden, an (Oval) office and some very nice bedrooms, one named for a former occupant, the late President Lincoln. The president also gets a $50,000 expense account and an additional $100,000 for travel. The average government worker, I dare say, does not get quite that much for travel and might have to live in his or her own home, invariably not on Pennsylvania Avenue, necessitating a tiring and expensive commute.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1365123095548</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>