<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-30"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372588278746-1</Id><Title>In charge of everything, responsible for nothing., thank you assbuckeroo</Title><Msg>You're right. That;s the bgroup regarding everything. From turrrrism and war to the economy. Nice dropkick pauper!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1372588278746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 06:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372592370704-2</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, abstinence works every time it's tried.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372592370704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 07:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372592506526-3</Id><Title>repubs, stop complaining that you're all crackers...........</Title><Msg>being REPUB:ICAN is 1,000 times worse.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1372592506526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 07:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372596526310-4</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, Texas Rick Perry's abstinence policy has led to Texas having one of highest teen pregnancy rates in the nation. Nice work stick with it. His praying for rain also ended the drought in in Texas too, right?....jeez</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372596526310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 08:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372597347700-5</Id><Title>Rick Perry loves Rush Limbaugh, just the kind of person he is</Title><Msg>" God bless Rush Limbaugh!" says Rick Perry....... No wonder god gave Texas more drought after Rick Perry's prayed for rain ............jeez...................I guess perry is a fan of draft dodging, drug abuse, lies and the whoring in the Domincan Republic that Rush is infamous for......</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372597347700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372598000470-6</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's a policy in Texas? Hardly nitwit. Actually it's an educational effort to promote abstinence. And what on earth could possibly be wrong with that? huh Mesa?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372598000470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372598406261-7</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not only is it policy of the gop in Texas, but the hypocrites use federal tax dollars.......Texas received $16,040,338 in federal funding for abstinence-only-until-marriage programs in Fiscal Year 2005.............. gee.. $16 million spent in one year to teach "just say no".... no wonder Rick Perry hates federal taxes..... why can't he just pray for more abstinence like he prays for rain and save the tax payers some money?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372598406261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372599013758-8</Id><Title>ignorance as policy and goal of the gop</Title><Msg>from Texas GOP’s platform: "We oppose any sex education other than abstinence until marriage." here are the facts that show the total failure of pushing ignorance as above: "Abstinence-only programs have been proven to have no real impact on rates of sexual abstinence. On the other hand, an increased understanding of contraception directly correlates to a decrease in young adults’ risky sexual behavior. And while U.S. teen pregnancy rates are on the steady decline, states with more rigid abstinence-only policies lag behind the national average. Mississippi — where abstinence-only is the state standard — boasts the highest teen pregnancy rate in the country. Contrast that with the state with the lowest rate, New Hampshire, where comprehensive sex education includes information about condoms and contraception. A 2007 report showed that only about half of the sexually-active high school students in Texas used a condom when last having sex. Texas Republicans’ abstinence-only stance — coupled with the states parental opt-out policy — engenders this massive education gap that results in young people doubting birth control is an effective way to avoid unwanted pregnancy.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372599013758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372599441210-9</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perry and others say "abstinence works"... but that is just a lie......... and FACTS prove it is a lie: "The results? Teen pregnancy in Texas went up -- higher than before "abstinence only," and more than 50 percent higher than the national average. Even more troubling was that repeat teen pregnancy went up -- to the point that it, too, led the nation. It turns out that Texas kids thought that "if birth control doesn't work, why use it?" "[texas teens].... In fact, teens in almost all high school grades were having more sex after undergoing the abstinence only program. By 2007, Texas had the highest teen birth rate in the nation. Nevertheless, the program continued. By 2009, 94 percent of Texas schools, which at the time were educating more than 3.7 million students, were giving no sex ed whatsoever beyond "abstinence only," a curriculum that includes emphasizing that birth control doesn't work. Instead of providing fact-based information, the programs use fear and Jesus -- over-emphasizing the risks of sexually transmitted diseases leading to cervical cancer, radical hysterectomy and death, together with Christian morality. The results? Teen pregnancy in Texas went up -- higher than before "abstinence only," and more than 50 percent higher than the national average. Even more troubling was that repeat teen pregnancy went up -- to the point that it, too, led the nation. It turns out that Texas kids thought that "if birth control doesn't work, why use it?" It's also extremely tough for teenagers to get contraceptives in Texas. "If you are a kid, even in college, if it's state-funded you have to have parental consent," said Susan Tortolero, director of the Prevention Research Center at the University of Texas in Houston. But none of this seems to matter t</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372599441210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372599891873-10</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please explain how abstinence, a deliberate decision to refrain from sex, doesn't work in avoiding pregnancy?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372599891873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:44:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372600054576-11</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>put another way, Mesa, I guarantee you no pregnancy would result from 2 heteros deciding not to have sex. Gee, what a concept.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372600054576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372600368269-12</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>immaculate conception. Mesa believes pregnancy can result from 2 heteros deciding not to have sex.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372600368269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:52:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372600423733-13</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't be silly. it is a fact that abstinence only policy is a FAILURE.... that resulted in MORE teen pregnancy..... you see, IGNORANCE leads to more teen pregnancy... as PROVEN by the failure of such "just say no" policies everywhere they replaced actual sex education. "The results? Teen pregnancy in Texas went up -- higher than before "abstinence only," and more than 50 percent higher than the national average. Even more troubling was that repeat teen pregnancy went up -- to the point that it, too, led the nation. It turns out that Texas kids thought that "if birth control doesn't work, why use it?" "[texas teens].... In fact, teens in almost all high school grades were having more sex after undergoing the abstinence only program. By 2007, Texas had the highest teen birth rate in the nation. Nevertheless, the program continued. By 2009, 94 percent of Texas schools, which at the time were educating more than 3.7 million students, were giving no sex ed whatsoever beyond "abstinence only," a curriculum that includes emphasizing that birth control doesn't work</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372600423733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:53:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372600857074-14</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you said that abstinence doesn't work. I said it works every time it's tried. Try to refute that. But go ahead and ridicule abstinence education. I promise you it's more worthwhile than the sex lessons kids currently get in school.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372600857074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372600895690-15</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you and your ilk are childish wishful thinkers. You think if there is no sex education teens will just stop having sex.... 'just say no'.......... that is the gop's sex education...........jeez....... and guess what..... that kind of ignorance has done just what any rational person would expect, it has led to MORE teen pregnancy.....nice work silly people, just stick your head in the sand, ignorance is bliss and just pretend that problems will just go away......... the fact is that the educational policy of abstinence has INCREASED teen pregnancy in Texas and the few other states that use it.........(and sure, you liars confront facts like that with the childish lie that 'abstinence works'.......but you only demonstrate that you are a liar)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372600895690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372601235674-16</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so what if a liar like you "promises" that NO sex education other than "just say no" is " more worthwhile"..... It is just a lie..... and it is a failure as public policy.........so typical of the gop to push ignorance and moral rectitude over education........................ you people fear knowledge and education obviously........ and you are hypocrites....... Perry blesses Rush Limbaugh who trots off on sexcations to the domincian republic and is a drug abuser...... who couldn't "just say no" to his hillbilly heroin.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372601235674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:07:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372601583341-17</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry loves Rush Limbaugh, just the kind of person he is</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372597347700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey Rush.... just "say no" to being fat! "just say no"..... to your drug addiction.... how could you have ever been addicted to drugs ... "just say no" but you didn't?????? and you don't just "say no" to your unhealthy appetite for huge amounts of food and cigars???? come on... just "say no" to being such a glutton........................ you expect teens to just "say no" to sex....... but you can't "say no" to gluttony and you couldn't "say no" to drug abuse?/</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372601583341</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372601732515-18</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mesa, you're stupid. Sex education resembles nothing of the sex education I got in school. Mine was basically the birds and bees. Some biology. What they often get today is "how to." Some programs even promote sex. I mean...they're going to do it anyway so let's teach them all the stuff. That's the attitude your ilk promotes. Some give condom demonstrations of cucumbers and bananas. It's ridiculous and it gives kids license. What's a kid supposed to think? Gee, they showed it in school so it must be what's expected. Isn't that your general attitude Mesa. It certainly is? Or how 'bout the moms who say they're going to do it anyway and it shouldn't happen in the backseat of the Ford. So why not provide them clean sheets and privacy where they can do it right. Anotehr example of liberal attitudes.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372601732515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:15:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372602514011-19</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are such a liar and ignoramus.. the FACT is, states with REAL sex education have LOWER rates of teen pregnancy and also, btw, lower rates of teens having sex.............. but sure stick with ignorance and denial....... pretend that just sticking your head in the sand is better than education........... you are the champion of ignorance is bliss.......</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372602514011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372602541427-20</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry loves Rush Limbaugh, just the kind of person he is</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372597347700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as far as I know Rush has said no. So he is walking testimony that "no" works. Do you know otherwise? Huh?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372602541427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372602855451-21</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry loves Rush Limbaugh, just the kind of person he is</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372597347700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rush did not "say no" to drugs...... he did not "say no" to viagra fueled sexcations in the dominican republic, he obviously can't "say no" to his gluttony.................he did "say no" to serving his country in a war that he supported (by sitting on his rear end at home)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372602855451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372603097866-22</Id><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Msg>"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask you much about what you did about keeping government small, but he's going to ask you what you did for the poor. You'd better have a good answer," Kasich, the republican governor and Christian conservativesaid - , supporting the Obamacare - expansion of Medicaid healthcare coverage for the poor - and he has a warning for his fellow party members about the moral consequences of blocking it."............................ The Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality •The Bible mentions poverty more than 2,000 times. •Same sex issues are mentioned just a few times, many which are not about homosexuality but are the misleading words of homophobic translators. •Jesus himself never mentions same-sex issues. Many Christians ask, “What would Jesus do?” •The answer seems much closer to feeding the hungry and doing one’s part to alleviate world poverty. •Above all, over and over again, Jesus tells us to love. “The whole law is fulfilled in one word: love your neighbor as yourself.” Glatians 5:1</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372603223399-23</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry loves Rush Limbaugh, just the kind of person he is</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372597347700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, you don't know what you're talking about? Rush once said yes to drugs and as far as I know he now says no. Do you know otherwise? You don't. So he is walking testament that saying no works. You can't refute that unless you know he's still on drugs. And you don't.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372603223399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372603378707-24</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah I know Mesa. In your world the purpose of government is to take care of the poor, to ensure equality. In my world man's purpose is to care for the poor. And he/she does a much more effective job of it than the government.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372603378707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372603917627-25</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Love your neighbor as yourself." And the government is here to make sure you do.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372603917627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:51:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372607319620-26</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry loves Rush Limbaugh, just the kind of person he is</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372597347700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if your hero Tush can't "say no" to abusing drugs for many years , why can't you face up to the fact than most teens can't just "say no " to sex? Tush can't even 'say no' to over eating and his obvious gluttony.........better to give teens real sex education , better for them and better for society as is shown by the fact that the "say no" bs that has replaced sex education in some red states has actually INCREASED teen pregnancy and the number of teens who say they have had sex.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372607319620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372607542287-27</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, in your world it's everyman for himself...... even though you hypocritically spout the bible when it comes to sex.............. and ignore it when it comes to poverty . You aren't fooling god, that's for sure as the gov of ohio pointed out: "When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask you much about what you did about keeping government small, but he's going to ask you what you did for the poor. You'd better have a good answer," Kasich, the republican governor and Christian conservative said</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372607542287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:52:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372607770965-28</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are seven things in scripture called "obamanations". Homosexuality is one. Ever read the OT on race? Doubt it. Reasd why Solomon sinned. Ity was actually why Sodom and Gomorrah were destroyed. "They wnt after "strange" flesh. Look up "strange" in Strong's Concordance. New Testament also says that if you won't work you shouldn't eat. I am more than willing to help those that can't and do when I see a need. But, I have a strong animosity to lazy bums that can work and don't. I could always find work from the time I was twelve. Even if you have to get a lawnmower and go door to door you will find someone that needs the work done. Some of my relatives lived in Pensacola where lots were a quarter acre and covered with St. Augustine grass. Young Black kids would scrape up enough to get a power mower and cut these yards. Where there is a will there is a way.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372607770965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372607781244-29</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Godly Board....Me Likey....Amen</Msg><Username>sullivanrobertl</Username><Timestamp>1372607781244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372608114851-30</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's gonna ask you if you know Jesus ? and you hope Jesus know's U.....</Msg><Username>sullivanrobertl</Username><Timestamp>1372608114851</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372608180300-31</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Abstinence does work. It just isn't practiced. Jesse Ventura said it very pointedly when he ran for governor years ago. I doubt I can get it by the censors so you can guess what he said. I have a friend who was one of sixteen kids with eight girls. None of their boyfriends would have done anything wrong because they knew what my friend would do to them.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372608180300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372608454497-32</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously Palin's daughter DID NOT practice abstinence. You must have a short in your brain. You can hand out all the pills and other things you want and the low IQ types won't use them. Other hazards in that type of activity besides pregancy.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372608454497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:07:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372608603357-33</Id><Topic><Title>"Abstinence works," Perry said</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372534457595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stop it, silly. abstinence is the part of the Texas gop platform stating: "We oppose any sex education other than abstinence until marriage." That policy is a colossal failure in Texas and every red state using it. Ignorance is NOT the best policy, the facts prove it and no matter that you are one of the biggest advocates and examples of ignorance around.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372608603357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372608938554-34</Id><Title>Texas gop platform: "We oppose the teaching of Higher Order Thinking Skills"</Title><Msg>In the you-can’t-make-up-this-stuff department, here’s what the Republican Party of Texas wrote into its 2012 platform as part of the section on education: Knowledge-Based Education – We oppose the teaching of Higher Order Thinking Skills, critical thinking skills and similar programs that are simply a relabeling of Outcome-Based Education (OBE) (mastery learning) which focus on behavior modification and have the purpose of challenging the student’s fixed beliefs and undermining parental authority. Yes, you read that right. The party opposes the teaching of “higher order thinking skills” because it believes the purpose is to challenge a student’s “fixed beliefs” and undermine “parental authority..........." (In other words if a texas republican says that people once rode dinosaurs, school kids shouldn't question that assertion)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372608938554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372610133555-35</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have an answer when my time comes. It has to do with what I've done personally. My answer will not include what the government has forced me to do.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372610133555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372610950300-36</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gee whiz, do tell "what the government has forced me to do'....... forced you to do what? help feed the poor?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372610950300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372613174300-37</Id><Topic><Title>In charge of everything, responsible for nothing., thank you assbuckeroo</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1372588278746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 06:31:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SMACK time. It was Clinton who passed on taking Bin Laden when he had the chance. It was the Dems who expanded the creative lending formula that caused the mortgage collapse. It was Obama who stimulated us into insurmountable debt. It was Obama who reneged on leaving Afghanistan. It was Obama who disregarded the situation in Benghazi. It was his AG that ran guns into Mexico and you leftwing goons have no comment and the same for Obama arming Syrian rebels, but the Iran-Contra operation, you p'ed your bloomers. You DA VVop. Nice SMACK pauper!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1372613174300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 13:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372613627641-38</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do what I can to help the poor. Whatever I do is plenty more than you do personally...an educated guess. In general conservatives are generous with their own money. Certainly more generous that Algore or Joe Biden. Need I again cite Algore's personal charitable giving? It was paltry and embarrassing....something like $342 for a whole year. Liberals are generous with other people's money. That should embarrass you. It doesn't. Conservatives are much more apt to get involved on a personal level. Liberals care only in the abstract, No doubt you regard taxes as charity. It isn't.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372613627641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 13:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372616867253-39</Id><Title>Frustrated Americans will finally see some IRS leaders in jail soon!</Title><Msg>IG puts libiot spin &amp; lies to rest, determines without a doubt that conservative groups were singled out. Also, Lerner DID forfeit right to ghetto 5th, so she talks or goes to jail.</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1372616867253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372617187860-40</Id><Title>Obama's Syrian Rebel "Buddies" Behead A Catholic Priest!</Title><Msg>Wonder if "beheading knives" were among the weapons sent to this pack of Islamic #$%$ by the Obama Regime!?? In large measure, the "Rebel" trash aren't any better than the Assad butchers! Is there anything, just one thing, that our clueless President and his stupid Regime cannot FUP?? Oh right... national Elections!! And that, only because Stupid Morons make up half the electorate!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1372617187860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372617290760-41</Id><Title>Ohio Sen. Nina Turner is a moron making an argument that amounts to a non sequiter</Title><Msg>Trying to equate making late term, or partial birth, abortions illegal, and not using taxpayer money to pay for birth control pills, to a guy purchasing impotency pills with his own money is moronic. Like Van, I would prefer to not see tax money or insurance companies pay for either.</Msg><Username>dontmissthatplace</Username><Timestamp>1372617290760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372617330122-42</Id><Topic><Title>Frustrated Americans will finally see some IRS leaders in jail soon!</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1372616867253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:27:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better yet, when it's Obama who sitting in prison! Now wouldn't that be a dream come true!</Msg><Username>itsthepress_stupid</Username><Timestamp>1372617330122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:35:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372617513276-43</Id><Topic><Title>Frustrated Americans will finally see some IRS leaders in jail soon!</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1372616867253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:27:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should read ".....Lerner DID forfeit the right to TAKE the 5th, so she talks or goes to jail".</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1372617513276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372618158057-44</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gee whiz, do tell "what the government has forced me to do'....... forced you to do what? .........you didn't say what the government is forcing you to do..............did you? you just bragged out how much more generous you are than some other people at least in your own mind.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372618158057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372618706463-45</Id><Title>There is no IRS scandal, there is an Issa the liar and phony scandal though</Title><Msg>1. Now it’s clear Issa played us this whole time, thanks to new documents that show the IRS also targeted “progressive” and “Occupy” groups, in addition to Tea Party ones. And if it targeted groups on both sides, it wasn’t really singling anyone out (the only group actually denied tax-exempt status was a progressive one, after all) and the whole scandal falls apart. 2. Issa selectively disclosed parts of transcripts that supported his narrative, and threw a fit when Democrats wanted to release the rest, which revealed that the IRS official in charge of the program was a conservative Republican 3 Issa knew the IRS targeted progressive groups too........... Why didn’t the inspector general’s report mention this critical bit of data? Russell George, Treasury’s IG, told lawmakers that the “inspector general launches audits on topics requested by lawmakers. The targeting audit requested by House Oversight and Government Reform Chairman Darrell Issa specifically requested a review of IRS actions related to conservative groups,” Politico reported yesterday.........................get it? Issa TOLD the IG to ONLY report on what ISSA wanted to hear......jeez</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372618706463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372619309350-46</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>taxation is force. Try not paying taxes and see what happens. That's force. Bragging about my own charitable giving? No. I just do what I think is right to help others. And I know my own charitable giving ,whether it's time, talents, or cash, is much more effective than taxation. You think it's bragging because you know, we all know, libs don't do it to a great degree. They think, you think, taxes = charity. It's not. Not even close. I am a practicing Catholic. One way I contribute to the poor is selling Christmas trees for close to the past 20 years. I am the coordinator for my parish's Christmas tree enterprise. I arrange for everything that makes our little Xmas tree business a success. Every cent goes to the church. I have no idea how they spend it, but I know it goes for good. All of us volunteer. It's a huge volunteer commitment. We have fun, drink lots of beer, and sell Christmas trees. Our motto is chainsaws, fire, and beer. It brings in the volunteers. Last year we cleared close to 10K. Not bad. Not bad at all. Would a committed lib do all that? No, they wouldn't.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372619309350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372619881204-47</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good grief... poor you "forced" to pay taxes, what an outrage. funny how you and your ilk don't also want the military supported by charity, by the same voluntary giving you say that feeds poor and old americans.... kinda funny that your ilk like ryans' family or mittens family need tax dollar supports at times, since of course....per you all that is needed is charity.......</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372619881204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:18:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372620638738-48</Id><Title>a third of all "charity" in the USA is given to religion</Title><Msg>and of course the religions don't account for the money...... for sure these use a lot or most of it to pay themselves and to build nice churches and so forth..... but they sure like to brag about helping people.. but lets see the numbers of what, for instance is given to the catholic church and what they spend on helping people and what they spend for their own salaries, pensions, healthcare and buildings and etc. som facts on charity in the USA: Individual giving as a percentage of disposable personal income remained at 1.9 percent in 2011, the same as in 2009 and 2010. Giving USA estimates total charitable donations increased to $298.42 billion in 2011 Giving to religion religious organizations—$95.88 billion in 2011—retained its traditional spot as the largest type of recipient at 32 percent of the total Giving to human services ↑ $35.39 billion, donations to human services-related charities</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372620638738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372621982165-49</Id><Title>examples of how conservative "charitable" donations are used</Title><Msg>conservatives brag that they are more charitable....(but they are not......much of what they consider "charity" is not really charity , the real charity of feeding the poor or aiding the sick and etc). 1.......For instance, donations to the Knights of Columbus, a Catholic organization, are tax-deductible. Yet the organization gave almost $2 million to fund anti-gay campaigns by the National Organization for Marriage. If the "charitable" Catholics who gave that money had directly donated it to NOM, they would never have received a tax write-off. 2...A study by the Center on Philanthropy at Indiana University found that the residents of New Hampshire -- which ranked dead last in both surveys by The Chronicle -- weren't stingy; they were simply nonbelievers. "New Hampshire gives next to nothing to religious organizations," says Patrick Rooney, the center's leader, "but their secular giving is identical to the rest of country." 3. tithing ..... religious people tithe......... they support their church...... pay for salaries and benefits and pensions and buildings .......but NO DOUBT a" a local fundamentalist church may spend the bulk of its resources degrading and attacking other faiths, insulting gay people and leading crusades to strip people of their civil liberties. They may never feed the hungry, clothe the naked, or comfort the afflicted. Yet when people give that church money they call it "charity" no matter how uncharitable the uses for which the money is actually spent.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372621982165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372622275267-50</Id><Title>taxation is force. Try not paying taxes and see what happens. Seebe says</Title><Msg>Did you EVER say that during 20 years of reagan bush and bush???? WHY SAY IT NOW???????? Because you're a partisan repub.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1372622275267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372622830078-51</Id><Title>Study: Conservatives and liberals are equally charitable, but they give to different charities</Title><Msg>Conservative individuals and individuals in red states were more likely to donate to religious organizations Conversely, blue states were likely to give to secular organizations Washington post 2012 One big difference is that secular charities publically ACCOUNT for their donations...... for instance one food bank that I donate too proves that 97% of money it gets goes to feed the poor.........conservatives BRAG about how much they give, but most of it goes to their CHURCH.... and just show me a church making a similar public accounting as the food bank in my example.......</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372622830078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372623055589-52</Id><Topic><Title>taxation is force. Try not paying taxes and see what happens. Seebe says</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1372622275267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:57:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>poor crybaby seabagger, he is "forced" to pay taxes....omg!!.....</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372623055589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:10:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372623056298-53</Id><Topic><Title>Study: Conservatives and liberals are equally charitable, but they give to different charities</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372622830078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm a libiot tree hugger. I give to the EPA so all the trees can live but unborn babies can be killed. Messybird is such an idiot, can't disguise his libiot bent.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372623056298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:10:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372623131784-54</Id><Topic><Title>Study: Conservatives and liberals are equally charitable, but they give to different charities</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372622830078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope, you are just the same old liar and stupid person.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372623131784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:12:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372623136400-55</Id><Topic><Title>taxation is force. Try not paying taxes and see what happens. Seebe says</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1372622275267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:57:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the excessive waste bubba, the waste.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372623136400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:12:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372623378017-56</Id><Topic><Title>examples of how conservative "charitable" donations are used</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372621982165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:53:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You give to save the trees and kill the unborn, and I will give to the Knights cause I am a Knight and know where the money goes. One hundred percent goes to charity of their choice, so if we don't believe in killing the unborn or don't believe in perversion, amen.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372623378017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372623634700-57</Id><Topic><Title>a third of all "charity" in the USA is given to religion</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372620638738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:30:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to know a lot about the Catholic religion. We are terrible people but you libiots already know that. You like the secularists who feel good about saving trees, animals, and perverts but not the unborn of the world. Your blah, blah, blah would be better served trying to save us from socialism/communism that has invaded our country.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372623634700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372623854822-58</Id><Topic><Title>Bible talks more about poverty than homosexuality,"When you die and get to the meeting with St. Peter, he's probably not going to ask yo</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372603097866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gore, Biden, and most libiots going to he'll, they won't even get $200 when they pass go.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372623854822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372623921224-59</Id><Topic><Title>examples of how conservative "charitable" donations are used</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372621982165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:53:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, we know libs. We know what they are about. They say they care for the poor but we know it's an abstract thought. We know that they believe taxes = charity. We know they are wrong. Libs are a selfish bunch. In general, libs do not contribute much to charity. That is a fact. Algore and Joe Biden exemplify it.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372623921224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372623973673-60</Id><Topic><Title>is god a man? (just curious)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1372181900561</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes that's what I said! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372623973673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:26:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372624051018-61</Id><Topic><Title>is god a man? (just curious)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1372181900561</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All this talk of wieners is making mine hard (sort of). Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372624051018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372624107241-62</Id><Topic><Title>Study: Conservatives and liberals are equally charitable, but they give to different charities</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372622830078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope about what? Why are you libiots such idiots. No, that's IDIOTS.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372624107241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372624165826-63</Id><Topic><Title>There is no IRS scandal, there is an Issa the liar and phony scandal though</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372618706463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:58:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe Wilson tells me, you lie like the Bummer. And Joe was right it turns out.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372624165826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372624249150-64</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry loves Rush Limbaugh, just the kind of person he is</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372597347700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's that hope and change working so far doofus? More like dope and deranged!</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372624249150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372626536908-65</Id><Title>Pubs are so ridiculous, they only say to make helping the poor voluntary</Title><Msg>Pubs say voluntary charity is best for the spending they don't like, like feeding the poor or Medicaid.... when it comes to the military they of course want to spend MORE and to pay for it by "forcing" people to pay taxes.........</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372626536908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372626841191-66</Id><Title>does god have a belly button?</Title><Msg>Some say we are made in his (HIS?) image... we have a belly button..... so does that prove god has a belly button........... ( or a pee and sperm delivery system wiener?).................or does this prove that god does not exist because the idea of god with a belly button is absurd....... (god has a mother?)..........</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372626841191</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372626952826-67</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry loves Rush Limbaugh, just the kind of person he is</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372597347700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if your hero Tush can't "say no" to abusing drugs for many years , why can't you face up to the fact than most teens can't just "say no " to sex? Tush can't even 'say no' to over eating and his obvious gluttony.........better to give teens real sex education , better for them and better for society as is shown by the fact that the "say no" bs that has replaced sex education in some red states has actually INCREASED teen pregnancy and the number of teens who say they have had sex.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372626952826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:15:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372627416283-68</Id><Topic><Title>There is no IRS scandal, there is an Issa the liar and phony scandal though</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372618706463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:58:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe Wilson is a notorious liar...... he lied when he said Obama was lying...................and he lied about his mentor and hero Strom Thurmond's screwing his black maid and having a child out of wedlock..... the Liar Joe Wilson told Thurmond's love child that she was a liar......jeez..... and again... Joe Wilson was the liar... and Thurmond's family told him to shup up and stop lying. and btw, liar Joe Wilson apologized for his outburst to Obama....(just like he apologized for his lies aboutStrom Thurmond's black daughter.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372627416283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372635095509-69</Id><Topic><Title>taxation is force. Try not paying taxes and see what happens. Seebe says</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1372622275267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:57:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You phony liberal, when Bush had the NSA obtain phone records of known or suspected Al Queda associates when the calls were to and from foreign countries, you and the other goons were railing day after day about how Bush was invading privacy. When Obama has the NSA obtain everyone's phone records for our "own safety" , you accept it without question . WHY NOT SAY SOMETHING NOW????? Because you're a partisan goon who can't quite see the monkeys for the monkey scht, to paraphrase forest for the trees. Nice SMACK pauper!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1372635095509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372636099013-70</Id><Title>Obama's global warming plan</Title><Msg>Called Medieval witchcraft. We have had global cooling for the last 15 years. Just sayin..........</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372636099013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:48:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372636450109-71</Id><Topic><Title>There is no IRS scandal, there is an Issa the liar and phony scandal though</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372618706463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:58:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like you be changing the subject to that KKK guy Robert Byrd, er Strom Thurmond. Joe Wilson was 100 percent correcto mundo when he said there was a provision for undocumented aliens, aka illegal aliens. Say it ain't so Joe.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372636450109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372636547447-72</Id><Topic><Title>does god have a belly button?</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372626841191</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The question is: does a libiot have a brain? I would say, based on past evidence, a big NO!</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372636547447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372636614642-73</Id><Topic><Title>Pubs are so ridiculous, they only say to make helping the poor voluntary</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372626536908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One serves to protect us, one serves to destroy us.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372636614642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372636728971-74</Id><Topic><Title>ignorance as policy and goal of the gop</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372599013758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:30:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good thing libiots believe in birth control, otherwise the country would be overrun by more libiots.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372636728971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372636834056-75</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, Hillary, Holder</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1372563008291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 23:30:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget those worthless POS's Dingy Harry and Fancy Nancy.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372636834056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 20:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372647489788-76</Id><Title>This Just In</Title><Msg>Oliver Stone says Snowden is a hero. What a movie this would make. Exposing the unlimited power of an out of control government whose primary interest is thwarting their opposition with deceit, intimidation and treachery. Dems played a losing game by using underhanded tactics. By the time Obama's term ends, he will be in the low 30s. Mission Accomplished and it ain't Repubs who can take credit. LOL!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1372647489788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372647572016-77</Id><Title>More Liberal Logic</Title><Msg>Violent crimes can be eliminated if we have just one more law restricting the 2nd Amendment rights of law abiding citizens.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1372647572016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:59:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372649760693-78</Id><Title>So hydroponicucolonicu is really messadewsshbag in disguise</Title><Msg>You can always tell this jerks posts.</Msg><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1372649760693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 23:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>