<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373632196742-1</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman lawyers says following people with a loaded gun is just fine</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373575305551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:41:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>George Zimmerman Trial: Zimmerman's Other Enemy is President Obama Alexandra Booze in Politics 14 minutes ago Mic this! 0 0 0 submit to reddit 0 george, zimmerman, trial:, zimmermans, other, enemy, is, president, obama, George Zimmerman Trial: Zimmerman's Other Enemy is President Obama On the night of February 26, 2012, a 17-year-old African American boy, Trayvon Martin, died of a gunshot wound inflicted by 28-year-old volunteer neighborhood watch captain George Zimmerman. Although the exact details of the tragic incident were murky and tensions high, 27 days later on March 23, President Obama stood in the White House Rose Garden declaring "If I had a son, he would look like Trayvon,” words that would soon emotionally involve him in a local murder trial. Two days after the president's announcement, a little known unit of the Department of Justice called the Community Relations Service deployed to the town of Sanford, Florida where Martin was shot, unknowingly to the American public. While there, they helped to organize and manage rallies and protests against George Zimmerman, even though permission for the DOJ to intervene in local law enforcement cases are issued only when there is evidence that civil rights are being compromised. A month after President Obama’s announcement, protests consisting of Martin sympathizers ensued as media outlets broadcast the words “I am Trayvon Martin” across television screens nationwide. As the country faces potential threats of race-related riots pending the outcome of the Zimmerman trial, many can’t help but stop and wonder if Zimmerman even had a chance at a fair trial from the beginning. Although the Obama administration has recently attempted to distance itself from the Zimmerman case and the president’s original statement, many wonder if it is too late to forget about his emotional reaction and the outcomes that have since transpired. In the event that Zimmerman is found not guilty, Obama must be prepared with a rational and informed statement in which he is adamantly intolerant of those threatening unruly discourse and rioting against a justice system that is, or should be, color-blind. Surrounding the environment and circumstances of Martin’s death, some members of the media have compared the incident to that of a racial hate-crime that happened more than half a century ago. Contrary to that comparison, in response to the 1955 murder of 14-year-old Emmett Till, Martin Luther King, Jr. and his supporters peacefully united to fight segregation, racism, and the evil that lay behind both. Blacks, whites, Republicans, Democrats, Christians, and Jews worked together to ensure that racism became rare and socially unacceptable. Today, only 3.8% of Americans are reluctant to even have a neighbor of another race, and it remains one of the least racist countries in the world. Within two generations, American has elected a black president. Are these milestones not proof enough that a world in which we once knew to contain so much racial pain and fear is on its way to extinction? Almost 58 years later, the case of Emmett Till should not be confused with or compared to that of Trayvon Martin. Instead of promoting peace and faith in America’s judicial system, the federal government intervened in a criminal justice matter to highlight race hatred and fear for political advantage.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1373632196742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 08:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373638905388-2</Id><Title>Big Sis Napalitano to resign today</Title><Msg>How abrupt! Something must be up!</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1373638905388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 10:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373641313216-3</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman lawyers says following people with a loaded gun is just fine</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373575305551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:41:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SHOW JUDGE LIFE LONG DEM</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1373641313216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 11:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373641704066-4</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman lawyers says following people with a loaded gun is just fine</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373575305551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:41:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and she has been somewhat hostile to the defense. I pretty much guarentee you that the honorable jusge Debra Nelson has had at least one conversation with someone from the Obama Administration, probably one of Holder's lackeys from DOJ.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1373641704066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 11:08:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373641885609-5</Id><Title>Google TRTC then you figure it out</Title><Msg>Nuff said on TRTC</Msg><Username>soren025</Username><Timestamp>1373641885609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 11:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373643411440-6</Id><Topic><Title>Big Sis Napalitano to resign today</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1373638905388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 10:21:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right... it took Obama 5 1/2 years to figure out he had a moron and a liar in charge of defending America... something the rest of us knew in spades from February 2009 on!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1373643411440</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 11:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373643582826-7</Id><Title>Docs tell Texas legislature to "Get Out of Our Exam Rooms"</Title><Msg>The American Congress of Obstetricians and Gynecologists July 9, 2013 All eyes are on Texas again this week as the fate of a far-reaching measure to restrict abortions and close many abortion facilities faces its last days of debate. Unlike almost any other issue, abortion generates strong feelings on all sides. This is true within our own organization, the American Congress of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (ACOG), and we respect that our 58,000 members have deeply held personal beliefs on this topic. While we can agree to disagree about abortion on ideological grounds, we must draw a hard line against insidious legislation that threatens women’s health like Texas HB2 (House Bill 2) and SB1 (Senate Bill 1). That’s why we’re speaking to the false and misleading underlying assumptions of this and other legislation like it: These bills are as much about interfering with the practice of medicine and the relationship a patient has with her physician as they are about restricting women’s access to abortion. The fact is that these bills will not help protect the health of any woman in Texas. Instead, these bills will harm women’s health in very clear ways. We’re setting the record straight, loudly and unequivocally, with these simple messages to all politicians: Get Out of Our Exam Rooms</Msg><Username>sauerlraut</Username><Timestamp>1373643582826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 11:39:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373644158695-8</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman lawyers says following people with a loaded gun is just fine</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373575305551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:41:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zim was a volunteer watchman. Had a perfect right to check someone out. I've been stopped by police several times and checked out. Once while working shift work late at night in a telephone M/H. I didn't take offense and police left as soon as I explained what I was doing. Zim was assaulted by a pot smoking punk.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1373644158695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 11:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373644842384-9</Id><Title>National Neighborhood Watch Institute (NNWI)</Title><Msg>National Neighborhood Watch Institute (NNWI) Our Participants Handbook states, "Always remember that your responsibility is to report crime. Do not take any risks to prevent a crime or try to make an arrest. The responsibility for apprehending criminals belongs to the police/sheriff."</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373644842384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 12:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373648273675-10</Id><Topic><Title>National Neighborhood Watch Institute (NNWI)</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373644842384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 12:00:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another ID messy? And Zimmerman did call the police. He was keeping an eye on Trayvon to see what he was up to until the police got there. Trayvon thought he was in danger and turned on Zimmerman without just cause. He was the aggressor and Zimmerman's injuries testify to that. Zimmerman was not taking matters into his own hands until he was attacked. It has been established that he did nothing prior to that to suggest he was overstepping his bounds, no matter how you pretend it was. Those are the facts. The only reason I replied is to make you look like a fool again. Into the ignore you go, beavis.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1373648273675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 12:57:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373652718010-11</Id><Title>ORCL</Title><Msg>To the people who actually follow this stock on this message board...do you think the stock will rally in the last hour...since on Monday we are switching to the big board?</Msg><Username>hot_bloodedindian</Username><Timestamp>1373652718010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 14:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373657448858-12</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL</Title><Username>hot_bloodedindian</Username><Timestamp>1373652718010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 14:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO, I think the NASDAQ is just trying to stick it to ORCL. Some funds have to sell today because they focus on NASDAQ. You will definitely look for the POP on monday</Msg><Username>wall.street13</Username><Timestamp>1373657448858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:30:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373657519841-13</Id><Title>News</Title><Msg>What's the news on ORCL today to cause it to be the most active on NASDAQ?</Msg><Username>maxkissime</Username><Timestamp>1373657519841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373657528435-14</Id><Topic><Title>Buy ORCL and be happy...</Title><Username>almlk</Username><Timestamp>1373552634311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 10:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>getting to the NYSE is going to help this stock, today's sell-off will reverse MONday. It's just people wanting to get out as they have funds staying with NASDAQ</Msg><Username>wall.street13</Username><Timestamp>1373657528435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373657580964-15</Id><Topic><Title>News</Title><Username>maxkissime</Username><Timestamp>1373657519841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Becuase today is ORCL last day of trading on the NASDAQ. Come Monday it will be the most active on the NYSE</Msg><Username>wall.street13</Username><Timestamp>1373657580964</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373657608745-16</Id><Topic><Title>News</Title><Username>maxkissime</Username><Timestamp>1373657519841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Going to the bigboard on Monday....NASDAQ related funds are selling out...</Msg><Username>hot_bloodedindian</Username><Timestamp>1373657608745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373657612104-17</Id><Topic><Title>non-zimmermanabortionobama post</Title><Username>winthorpelouisiii</Username><Timestamp>1373593980433</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 21:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i hope you entered today :)</Msg><Username>wall.street13</Username><Timestamp>1373657612104</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 15:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373665683598-18</Id><Title>Any Idea about the last minute drop</Title><Msg>ORCL dropped from 31.61 to 31.25, just before market close.</Msg><Username>tom_thaliath</Username><Timestamp>1373665683598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 17:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373676703530-19</Id><Topic><Title>National Neighborhood Watch Institute (NNWI)</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373644842384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 12:00:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hydroencephologous or Messybird, same old crapola. Looks like Zimm got appended, not the thug. The Thug had four minutes to go 75 yards to his home. Think he may have been the aggressor.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373676703530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 20:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373676846445-20</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart is a Job Killer</Title><Username>dilemmabroccoli</Username><Timestamp>1373555220382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 11:07:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's called free enterprise dumbo.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373676846445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 20:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373677123717-21</Id><Topic><Title>Any Idea about the last minute drop</Title><Username>tom_thaliath</Username><Timestamp>1373665683598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 17:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Options expiration is my best guess.</Msg><Username>scott_1234567890</Username><Timestamp>1373677123717</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 20:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373677219655-22</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman lawyers says following people with a loaded gun is just fine</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373575305551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 16:41:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zimms nose and head injuries would indicate the fight was not his choice. What the hell are you smoking Encephologolousbirdbrain.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373677219655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373677460827-23</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman jury may consider lesser charge of manslaughter</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373559989609</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 12:26:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think that was live by the gun, die by the thug.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373677460827</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373677711760-24</Id><Topic><Title>DC sends Walmart packing</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1373537217173</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 06:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberal logic is an oxymoron. End of subject!</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373677711760</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373682528859-25</Id><Title>Watch out! Obama wants to push Neapolitano for SCOTUS.</Title><Msg>Ginsberg must be deteriorating</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1373682528859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 22:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373682616724-26</Id><Topic><Title>non-zimmermanabortionobama post</Title><Username>winthorpelouisiii</Username><Timestamp>1373593980433</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 21:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Had my order in @ .26 for the same calls again,never got filled. Glad I sold them yesterday for .44</Msg><Username>winthorpelouisiii</Username><Timestamp>1373682616724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 22:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373682761178-27</Id><Title>Can anyone explain how specific late term abortion issues are an overall threat to womens health?</Title><Msg>What does the data say? Of 1% of late term abortions involve a women's health, why not a simple add to the proposed laws that includes it?</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1373682761178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 22:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>