<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361107558771-1</Id><Title>protesters for Chris Dorner</Title><Msg>A few hundred protested Chris Dorner's death in from of LAPD. Spokesperson said stuff like "While we don't condone what Dorner did, police acted as judge, jury, and executioner." Gee, thanks for that indictment. What is wrong with people?? Is it barely possible that maybe the LAPD was right in dismissing Dorner? Is it barely possible that Dorner was wrong in his assessment of his dismisal? Amazing to me that many people just assumed w/o fact that Dorner was right and that LAPD was racist.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1361107558771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 08:25:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361110213458-2</Id><Topic><Title>protesters for Chris Dorner</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1361107558771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 08:25:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Florida prisoner who escaped after allegedly stabbing a detective with his eyeglasses has been shot and killed by law enforcement officers near Dallas. The Southlake, Texas, Department of Public Safety posted on Facebook Saturday morning that Alberto Morales was shot shortly before midnight following a foot chase. Police responded to an area near Lake Grapevine in North Texas after receiving information from a local resident. ....................................................................................................................................................................... The man was wronged by police I tellya. The police are totally to blame for shooting this guy. Fight the power.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1361110213458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 09:10:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361113855091-3</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH ORCL Analyst Report .</Title><Username>zelmastafford</Username><Timestamp>1361112271314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 09:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks a lot!</Msg><Username>nunoginny</Username><Timestamp>1361113855091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 10:10:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361115934782-4</Id><Title>IOC boots wrestling as a olympic sport</Title><Msg>I believe wrestling is as ancient an olympic sport as there is. I admire wrestlers. They are the best conditioned athletes as I've ever seen. But not glamorous enough and poor TV ratings I guess. But beach volleyball gets to stay. And as far as I know curling stays as well.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1361115934782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 10:45:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361117514961-5</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH ORCL Analyst Report .</Title><Username>zelmastafford</Username><Timestamp>1361112271314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 09:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice report! thanks a lot!</Msg><Username>watskydave</Username><Timestamp>1361117514961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 11:11:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361122446389-6</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH ORCL Analyst Report .</Title><Username>zelmastafford</Username><Timestamp>1361112271314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 09:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very nice and good report!</Msg><Username>hazelwright705</Username><Timestamp>1361122446389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 12:34:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361124308419-7</Id><Topic><Title>(BREAKING NEWS) Analyst Downgrades ORCL</Title><Username>hbrown301</Username><Timestamp>1359975678439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 06:01:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice one</Msg><Username>boothfreddie</Username><Timestamp>1361124308419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 13:05:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361126698710-8</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to debate</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1361044310017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 14:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you listened to Obama's SOTU track played backwards? Full admission: “I am a Black Panther when this is over I’m going to smoke weed and do hip hop songs”</Msg><Username>jmsmttly</Username><Timestamp>1361126698710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 13:44:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361133786077-9</Id><Title>McCain... "Massive Cover-Up By Obama Administration On Benghazi"!</Title><Msg>Gregory then pressed McCain on what the Arizona senator meant by "a massive cover-up." "I'm asking you, do you care whether four Americans died?" McCain said. "And shouldn't people be held accountable for the fact that four Americans died?" "Well, what you said was the cover-up--a cover-up of what?" Gregory asked. "Of the information concerning the deaths of four brave Americans," McCain replied. "The information has not been forthcoming. You obviously believe that it has. I know that it hasn't. And I'll be glad to send you a list of the questions that have not been answered, including 'What did the president do and who did he talk to the night of the attack on Benghazi?'" McCain continued: "Why did the president for two weeks, for two weeks during the heat of the campaign continue to say he didn't know whether it was a terrorist attack or not? Is it because it interfered with the line 'Al Qaeda has [been] decimated'? And 'everything's fine in that in that part of the world'? Maybe. We don't know. But we need the answers. Then we'll reach conclusions. But we have not received the answers. And that's a fact."</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1361133786077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 15:43:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361140707735-10</Id><Title>"The American With No Abilities Act"... isn't it just wonderful?</Title><Msg>The Americans With No Abilities Act President Barack Obama and the Democrat-led Senate are considering sweeping legislation that will provide new benefits for many Americans. The Americans With No Abilities Act is being hailed as a major legislative goal by advocates of the millions of Americans who lack any real skills or ambition. "Roughly 50 percent of Americans do not possess the competence and drive necessary to carve out a meaningful role for themselves in society," said California Sen. Barbara Boxer. "We can no longer stand by and allow People of Inability (POI) to be ridiculed and passed over. With this legislation, employers will no longer be able to grant special favors to a small group of workers, simply because they have some idea of what they are doing." In a Capitol Hill press conference, former House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid pointed to the success of the U.S. Postal Service, which has a long-standing policy of providing opportunity without regard to performance. Approximately 74 percent of postal employees lack any job skills, making this agency the single largest U.S. employer of POI. Private-sector industries with good records of non-discrimination against the inept include retail sales (72 percent), the airline industry (68 percent), and home-improvement warehouse stores (65 percent). At the state government level, the Department of Motor Vehicles also has an excellent record of hiring POI. (63 percent). Under the Americans With No Abilities Act, more than 25 million mid-level positions will be created, with important-sounding titles but little real responsibility, thus providing an illusory sense of purpose and performance. Mandatory non-performance-based raises and promotions will be given to guarantee upward mobility for even the most unremarkable employees. The legislation provides substantial tax breaks to corporations that promote a significant number of Persons of Inability (POI) into middle-management positions, and give a tax credit to small and medium-sized businesses that agree to hire one clueless worker for every two talented hires. Finally, the Americans With No Abilities Act contains tough new measures to make it more difficult to discriminate against the non-abled, banning, for example, discriminatory interview questions such as, "Do you have any skills or experience that relate to this job?" "As a non-abled person, I can't be expected to keep up with people who have something going for them," said Mary Lou Gertz, who lost her position as a lug-nut twister at the GM plant in Flint, Mich., due to her inability to remember righty tighty, lefty loosey. "This new law should be real good for people like me. I’ll finally have job security." With the passage of this bill, Gertz and millions of other untalented citizens will finally see a light at the end of the tunnel. Said Sen. #$%$ Durbin: "As a senator with no abilities, I believe the same privileges that elected officials enjoy ought to be extended to every American with no abilities. It is our duty as lawmakers to provide each and every American citizen, regardless of his or her inadequacy, with some sort of space to take up in this great nation and a good salary for doing so."</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1361140707735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 17:38:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361145939910-11</Id><Topic><Title>"The American With No Abilities Act"... isn't it just wonderful?</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1361140707735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 17:38:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make the perfect POI!! Comprende Pigboy!??</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1361145939910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 19:05:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361149801300-12</Id><Topic><Title>IOC boots wrestling as a olympic sport</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1361115934782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 10:45:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Table Tennis stays too. Ping Pong, the first game to go video as "pong" Not glamorous either and only shown on Chinese networks. If that's a sport why isn't darts.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1361149801300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 20:10:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361154915217-13</Id><Title>Tax Increase</Title><Msg>Our Fed taxes will increase, from 16% to 25%. As if inflation hasn't decreased consumer spending. Obama spends to his hearts content saying it will help the economy. Yeah, the stimulus proved that. He sure stuck it to the 1%ers. Their making money thru the backdoor with Fed support, their profits are soaring while decreasing employee headcount. The rich get richer, etc, etc. and liberals love Obama.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1361154915217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 21:35:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361159644704-14</Id><Topic><Title>Who remembers Intheknow's Tonite's Thoughts?</Title><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1361066117610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 20:55:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dorner my hero? lol, i'd pay money to see his charred corpse hanging from a tree</Msg><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1361159644704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 22:54:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>