<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347772409105-1</Id><Topic><Title>The only people voting for Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347761750597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 22:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying that 53% of the country is on welfare?</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1347772409105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 01:13:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347773812454-2</Id><Title>hawcreek plead guilty</Title><Msg>ought to be not shown the key</Msg><Username>spiderlinks_uuuhtp</Username><Timestamp>1347773812454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 01:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347774060174-3</Id><Title>Obamanure not working on voters!</Title><Msg>"If you want to understand why President Obama has run such a scorchingly negative campaign, consider this: In a new poll conducted for The Hill, only 40 percent of likely voters said they felt Obama deserves a second term. Fifty-two percent said he did not. "</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347774060174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 01:41:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347774534204-4</Id><Title>"Why I (now) hate Apple"</Title><Msg>I don't, but one John Carroll does. You can google his article on Zdnet. Basically he is steamed about software patents, and Apple's wielding of them. So, why does one guy's opinion matter? Because it's indicative of a growing trend. It is becoming ever clearer to ever more people that software patents are a bad idea.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1347774534204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 01:48:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347775762147-5</Id><Title>hawcreek would do anything to keep a conversation going</Title><Msg>give up hawcreek</Msg><Username>spiderlinks_uuuhtp</Username><Timestamp>1347775762147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 02:09:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347785974609-6</Id><Topic><Title>THIS ELECTION IS ABOUT FREEDOM, LIBERTY AND PROSPERITY WHICH OBAMA WILL GIVE US</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1347732805686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 14:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Craper, the Chinese are known to refrain from commenting on complex issues because they are reluctant to sound simplistic or boorish. Maybe you should take a page from their book.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1347785974609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 04:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347786102031-7</Id><Topic><Title>THIS ELECTION IS ABOUT FREEDOM, LIBERTY AND PROSPERITY WHICH OBAMA WILL GIVE US</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1347732805686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 14:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba the devil.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347786102031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 05:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347786179906-8</Id><Topic><Title>so funny Hillary thought she could be President Obama just threw her under the bus</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347763150191</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 22:39:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347786179906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 05:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347787355615-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obamas Middle East policy could not be improved upon. Taliban decimated, Osama nuetralized, no new wars, several countries with new democratic governments.. This is probably not how the RWNJ define success, they would want more wars and instability.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1347641931227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 12:58:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamas Middle East policy could not be improved upon. Taliban decimated, Osama nuetralized, no new wars, several countries with new democratic governments.. This is probably not how the RWNJ define success, they would want more wars and instability You're kidding right? Have you looked at your TV lately? I guess you and craper really are the same lefty ideologued idiot.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1347787355615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 05:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347794619751-10</Id><Title>Why do Republicans hate America?</Title><Msg>Why do they publish baseless, seditious lies about our leaders and public servants in the attempt to subvert and damage our interests in time of crisis? Does their greed and deluded self-interest excuse them? Is the deranged adherence to a doomsday-cult version of "religion" sufficient excuse for their continued determination to promote hate and war? Perhaps it's time that their delusional, infantile, destructive and backward representatives be separated from the reins of Governmental power, since they clearly lack the restraint and good will to exercize their duties responsibly. Governance at the whim of a mob of reactionary ignoramuses didn't work under the Bush 43 administration and it's time to cut the dead-enders from that benighted era loose.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347794619751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347794874151-11</Id><Topic><Title>Got to Youtube and watch the Musllim from Kenya, Hussein, attack the Bible!</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1347755521302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 20:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As all xians are stupid #$%$ who cares?</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1347794874151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347794885633-12</Id><Title>IF YOU LIKE OBAMA'S MARKET, THEN DON'T VOTE FOR ROMNEY IN NOVEMBER</Title><Msg>Romney is Bush2 in disguise. Romney would take us back to the days of Bush2.</Msg><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1347794885633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347796203654-13</Id><Topic><Title>IF YOU LIKE OBAMA'S MARKET, THEN DON'T VOTE FOR ROMNEY IN NOVEMBER</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1347794885633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess what dumb #$%$ Bush's last 4 years were dumbocrap controlled. Vote dumbocrap is a vote for communism.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347796203654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347796237987-14</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek would do anything to keep a conversation going</Title><Username>spiderlinks_uuuhtp</Username><Timestamp>1347775762147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 02:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His commie mouth will hide after election.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347796237987</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347796702919-15</Id><Topic><Title>Got to Youtube and watch the Musllim from Kenya, Hussein, attack the Bible!</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1347755521302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 20:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then you Bible-beaters can run riot with your brothers-in-arms, the Koran-beaters. " As the Government of the United States of America is not, in any sense, founded on the Christian religion,—as it has in itself no character of enmity against the laws, religion, or tranquility, of Mussulmen [Muslims],—and as the said States never entered into any war or act of hostility against any Mahometan [Muslim] nation, it is declared by the parties that no pretext arising from religious opinions shall ever produce an interruption of the harmony existing between the two countries." Unfortunately, the Crusaders Bush and Cheney were weak, craven cowards and broke the faith entrusted to them by our Founders. The Bible is a book, written by humans with all their faults and their propensities for lies, foolishness and delusional graspings for power over the small-minded. In the hands of shrewd and calculating purveyors of hate and disunity intent on furthering their own narrow selfish goals it's as powerful a weapon as the Koran can be when distorted by fanatics intent on their own empowerment against the interests of their fellows. In no way will the laws of the United States be bound to the dictates of backward desert tribesmen spinning tales of their greatness in the eyes of an indifferent and likely fictitious "Almighty", no matter what the forces of evil that would abuse their "Holy Books" might wish. That pertains just as well to the false Christianist zealots who abuse and distort the teachings of their Messiah to further their greed and lust for power or the false abusers of Muslim teachings seeking their own aggrandizement over the bodies of their own followers. Quit pretending that you care about anything other than your short-sighted self-involved political agenda. You're a poor simulacrum of a religious person, primarily since your motivations are so obviously hate and greed.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347796702919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347801010223-16</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation from monetary means is what we want right now. The inflation whined about by the RWNJ is scarcity inflation and is only a side issue. Monetary inflation is caused by higher consumption. Isn't it obvious that we need higher consumption resulting from consumers with more disposable cash??</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1347643301821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 13:21:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's easy to go with your 'gut' but usually wrong.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1347801010223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347801085881-17</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke, Obama, and QE3 are collectively like the chronic gambler</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347800539171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:02:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Others simply call it the ravings of a lying bankrupt message board troll yearning for the deficit spending that fueled his ability to ceaselessly post nonsensical garbage on financial message boards promoting the POLITICAL OPINIONS of reactionary, moronic bigots while his "business" fell into bankruptcy and his family abandoned him to his obsessions and the fantasies he concocts about a life that he obviously doesn't have. If you get what you're asking for your welfare checks will stop and you'll likely be returned to the work camp to pay off your debt to society. You should save your "fury" for that. Fortunately for the rest of the world, you'll likely be denied access to the internet under the terms of your release and sane people won't have to be inundated with flood of garbage you spew onto this irrelevant message board under your many aliases.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347801085881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347802119243-18</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation from monetary means is what we want right now. The inflation whined about by the RWNJ is scarcity inflation and is only a side issue. Monetary inflation is caused by higher consumption. Isn't it obvious that we need higher consumption resulting from consumers with more disposable cash??</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1347643301821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 13:21:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you could explain how easy money raises prices for goods without also increasing consumption?? And NO, speculation does not apply as it is a zero sum game.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1347802119243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347802385466-19</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Republicans hate America?</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347794619751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:23:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just more lies and demagoguery promoting a false "patriotism" that would undermine our interests worldwide and here at home. If Tyranny and Oppression come to this land, it will be in the guise of fighting a foreign enemy. -- James Madison Cowards and liars banging war drums are all too familiar a fixture of the right wing's attempts to establish a tyranny to overthrow our elected Government. The would-be tyrant and his pack of belligerent, lying frauds needs to be thoroughly rejected by our most powerful weapon; our votes, exactly the weapon the tyrants would deprive us of.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347802385466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347803305477-20</Id><Topic><Title>"Why I (now) hate Apple"</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1347774534204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 01:48:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are a better idea than software licenses. The very idea that you have to buy software every year or so is ridiculous. Msft is a dinosaur going extinct.</Msg><Username>loeupinski</Username><Timestamp>1347803305477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347803654567-21</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals again have the horse pushing the cart on inflation</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347802488592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that profit can be maximized by minimizing the value invested into product, whether that's through abusive employment practices here in the United States or through the seeking of the most abusive environment for the employment of the disadvantaged in the global economic environment don't lead to any positive economic outcome. The increasing exaggerated enrichment of a few "celebrity" failures in financial and production management eliminates exactly the "demand driven recovery" your babbling about. Perhaps you should return to blaming Barney Frank and poor black people for the failure of the Bush 43 Republican backed "economy" that caused you to have such a "successful business" during the "boom-boom" years of massive deficit spending, incompetently waged warfare, inane thrashings toward the construction, destruction and reconstruction of a neo-conservative pseudo-capitalist paradise in Iraq after the WMDs Dick Cheney lied about turned out to be as non-existent as his national defence expertise, foreign policy experience and his patriotism and commitment to anything that the United States stands for.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347803654567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347805312910-22</Id><Title>Hawcreek goes Socialist.</Title><Msg>Insists that money be spread around instead of being hoarded by short-sighted, greedy fake "job creators" who depress the economy by demanding reduced or zero tax rates, putting the burden of financing the operations of the Government onto those least able to provide the means for it. His "Harrythedope" alias agrees, insisting that the private consumer needs to have the economic means to provide for the support of themselves and their families, and that it's short-sighted to insist that industrial capitalists make no contribution to the infrastructure that provides them the ability to engage in commerce and the protections against the mobs of disadvantaged citizens they've left unemployed and desperate by their policies of legalized tax evasion and unreasonable subsidization of industries they determinedly strip away from this country and park in the countries of our enemies because the governments of those backward nations allow the unchecked abuse of their citizens. Soon they'll be joining in a chorus of "L'Internationale", and award "each other" with their "Hero of the Worker's Revolution" medals. The only thing consistent about right-wingnuts is their stupidity. Their lies are too convoluted for their inadequate intellects to keep track of.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347805312910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347805822049-23</Id><Topic><Title>Got to Youtube and watch the Musllim from Kenya, Hussein, attack the Bible!</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1347755521302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 20:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In America we have freedom of religion. We don't ban any religion. We don't ban non religion. President Obama is a fine Christian man. Everything about him denotes a good Christian. He would forgive you for your unkind words, which your very un Christian behavior spews. That's the kind of Christian man he is. You, on the other hand are obviously not Christian but seem to be very obsessed with it, and Islam as well. Strange behavior, very strange.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1347805822049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347806225451-24</Id><Title>Republican Klansmen exploit reactionary "religous" terror for their political gain.</Title><Msg>"Beginning after the Civil War, members of the Protestant-led Ku Klux Klan organization began engaging in arson, beatings, cross burning, destruction of property, lynching, murder, rape, tar-and-feathering, and whipping against African Americans, Jews, Catholics, and other social or ethnic minorities. "They were explicitly Christian terrorist in ideology, basing their beliefs on a "religious foundation" in Christianity. he goals of the KKK included, from an early time on, an intent to "reestablish Protestant Christian values in America by any means possible," and believe that "Jesus was the first Klansman." Their cross-burnings were conducted not only to intimidate targets, but to demonstrate their respect and reverence for Jesus Christ, and the lighting ritual was steeped in Christian symbolism, including the saying of prayers and singing of Christian hymns. Many modern Klan organizations, such as the Knights Party, USA, continue to focus on the Christian supremacist message, asserting that there is a "war" on to destroy "western Christian civilization."" The takeover of the political apparatus of the former Republican party by the reactionary fringe remains of the traitors who cling to the ideals of the defeated Confederacy continues at an accelerated pace.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347806225451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347806320484-25</Id><Topic><Title>Got to Youtube and watch the Musllim from Kenya, Hussein, attack the Bible!</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1347755521302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 20:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All religions are idiotic self-deception. There are no gods, bibles and korans and torahs, etc, are just emergency toilet paper.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1347806320484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347806340201-26</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcreek goes Socialist.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347805312910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:21:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's all about racism, hawcreepy is a Democrat by his own words. Pure racism. Hairydope is someone else I think because all hawcreepys aliases disappeared with him recently when yahoo banned him.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347806340201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347806627350-27</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcreek goes Socialist.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347805312910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:21:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's exactly what you said. You're just that incoherent in your ravings. You should hop onto your Medicare financed Hoveround and get some fresh swamp air, perhaps your "northeast liberal gal" (who became "northeastern" when it became clear that "she" wouldn't know the Saugus flats from the Windsor jambs and had never seen a candlepin alley in "her" life) will lift the restraining order so that you can get some human companionship again. Not likely, but you could hope.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347806627350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:43:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347806747610-28</Id><Title>Are you going to let them do it to you?? These 'consevatives' on this board are tasked with protecting the interest of a very few in our country. They are given a well designed playbook that manipulates your emotions such that you see it their way. Don't let them manipulate your opinion with hollow empty emotional talking points.</Title><Msg>dont let em doit</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1347806747610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347806834413-29</Id><Title>How much did the Radical Arabs fear the Bush/Cheney Administration and the Republican controlled Congress on 9/11/2001? To compare a few deomonstrations at embassies with 9/11/2001 is absurd of Rush Limpballs!! (And the dittoheads)</Title><Msg>Rush Limpball dittoheads are very similar to peckerheads.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1347806834413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347807619401-30</Id><Title>Romney's new five point plan for the economy.</Title><Msg>1.) Denial 2.) Anger 3.) Bargaining 4.) Depression 5.) Acceptance This completes the unification of his formerly "59 point" plan for the destruction of the US economy with that of his predecessor-in-fact, George Bush the Lesser. It also unifies his plan for economic failure with his plan for his latest vanity political campaign. Perhaps when this fails to be the "shiny object" he needs to draw attention to himself he'll attempt to run on his record of ineptitude and failure as the half-term Governor of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts.</Msg><Username>nd1005</Username><Timestamp>1347807619401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 11:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347807783665-31</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcreek goes Socialist.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347805312910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:21:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kind of like your mentor, Limbaugh, when he's off on some inane rant at an empty chair. If you need some affirmation, perhaps you should get back to Stormfront for a break and the support of like-minded individuals.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347807783665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 11:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347810344373-32</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcreek goes Socialist.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347805312910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:21:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now we have all learned on the backwater msft message board, Obama is a socialist, communist, undignified, kenya born, muslim, thug, and racist.There are more, but that's enough. The backwater rwnj boys don't realize when they say these things, any swing voter reading this backwater board, which is about 2 per 5 years, will be swayed to Obama not away from.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347810344373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 11:45:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347812049481-33</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's new five point plan for the economy.</Title><Username>nd1005</Username><Timestamp>1347807619401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 11:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very good summary</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1347812049481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 12:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347812455004-34</Id><Title>It’s Official: The Era of the Personal Computer Is Over</Title><Msg>allthingsdDOTcom/20120915/its-official-the-era-of-the-personal-computer-is-over/ And M$ has failed in mobile......excellent.... As a signpost on the road to the so-called Post-PC Era we’ve been hearing about for so many years, this one is pretty hard to argue with: As of this year, personal computers no longer consume the majority of the world’s memory chip supply. And while it may not come as a terrible surprise to anyone who’s been paying attention to personal technology trends during the last few years, there’s nothing like a cold, hard number to make the point crystal clear. Word of this tipping point came quietly in the form of a press release from the market research firm IHS (the same group formerly known as iSuppli). The moment came during the second quarter of 2012. For the first time in a generation, according to the firm’s reckoning, PCs did not consume the the majority of commodity memory chips, also known as DRAM (pronounced “DEE-ram”). During that period, PCs accounted for the consumption of 49 percent of DRAM produced around the world, down from 50.2 percent in the first quarter of the year. The share of these chips going into PCs — both desktop and notebooks — has been hovering at or near 55 percent since early 2008, IHS says. As shifts in market share statistics go, it at first seems insignificant until you consider the wider sweep of memory chips in the history of the modern technology industry. PCs have consumed the majority of memory chips since sometime in the 1980s. IHS couldn’t say when exactly when the first personal computers started showing up in appreciable numbers in homes and businesses. And where are all those memory chips going? Tablets and smartphones for starters. IHS says that phones consumed more than 13 percent percent of memory chips manufactured, and it expects that figure to grow to nearly 20 percent by the end of this year. Tablets — including the iPad — consumed only 2.7 percent of the world’s memory chip supply. The remaining 35 percent, which IHS classifies as “other,” includes servers, professional workstations, and presumably specialized applications like supercomputers and embedded systems.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1347812455004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 12:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347814343310-35</Id><Topic><Title>THIS ELECTION IS ABOUT FREEDOM, LIBERTY AND PROSPERITY WHICH OBAMA COULD NOT GIVE US.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347674188144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 21:56:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama had almost four years to fix it. He was wrong choice in 2008. as an independent voter i did not vote for him and will not vote for him. i learned my lesson with carter. learn from your mistakes is my motto.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347814343310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 12:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347815874507-36</Id><Title>FactCheckOrg: Romney Did Indeed Ship Jobs Overseas To China</Title><Msg>Romney is responsible for shipping thousands jobs overseas. Romney, Grover Norquist, Carl Rove are decitfull priks who will lie to save their wealthy bosses any increase in tax money. They will ship your jobs to China, destroy USA businesses, break budgets with deficits to kill SSI, Medicare and Medicaide. They give twoschitts about working people.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1347815874507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 13:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347817153123-37</Id><Topic><Title>FactCheckOrg: Romney Did Indeed Ship Jobs Overseas To China</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1347815874507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 13:17:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ditto Rush Limpalls........heh....heh....heh....heh....heh....heh....heh....heh....heh....heh....heh....</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1347817153123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 13:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347820582995-38</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcreek goes Socialist.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347805312910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:21:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Angry? Impotent and filled wit rage at the loss of your "successful business" that you made up to fill your endless days of posting on a backwater financial message board? How sad you are. Pardon me while I laugh at you.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347820582995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347821909268-39</Id><Title>THIS ELECTION IS ABOUT FREEDOM, LIBERTY AND PROSPERITY WHICH OBAMA WILL GIVE US</Title><Msg>And the riddance of the tea party with the ryan's with ba's critiqueing real experts in economics, with ideas he has zero depth of understanding in</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1347821909268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347822071536-40</Id><Title>Team Romney:</Title><Msg>"No matter how badly the economy sucks, Mitt sucks even worse." Just when you thought they'd finally exhausted themselves flailing around lamely they get a transfusion of wingnut Mogul money (or Gelt, if it's from Adelzion) and think they can use them to "shake the etch-a-sketch" and "press the reset button". Hopefully the windows in the Hancock Tower were well sealed.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347822071536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347822331101-41</Id><Topic><Title>the hypocracy of the DNC No God on the platform for the homosexual vote, then yes God on the platform</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347822077064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bible is inane, dangerous garbage. Bibles are best used as toilet paper.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1347822331101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347822366949-42</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcreek goes Socialist.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347805312910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:21:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thug wanna be, that's a rare and new one. Your work here is of no consequence, your years ago posts are worth as much as used toilet paper laying in the bowl. Your minutes ago posts are worth as much as the toilet paper flying from #$%$ to bowl.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1347822366949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347822623659-43</Id><Title>Netan says there is no bus, relations were are and will be strong.</Title><Msg>too bad for romney, caught making stuff up again about Obama throwing Israel under the bus. damage control units alerted, lie fest to follow later on fauox hoax news</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1347822623659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:10:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347823427892-44</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcreek goes Socialist.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347805312910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:21:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama is tantrum prone" that's a good one, but romney and ann take the prize on that as we all know very well. Obama, the coolest most forgiving even tempered Pres of all time since GW 1, yeah right.. This is sort of fun, isn't it, hawfaeces bashers? time for some chores, unlike hawfaeces I have to do things around the homestead</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1347823427892</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:23:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347823922387-45</Id><Topic><Title>Team Romney:</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347822071536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:01:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STUPID PEOPLE VOTE FOR OBAMA.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347823922387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347827106970-46</Id><Topic><Title>Team Romney:</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347822071536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:01:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sucking the money out of them and selling off the remains to the Chinese. Equally as much a failure as Governor with record job losses, particularly in the manufacturing sector, and record accumulation of debt. My point is that Mitt Romney is not only an imbecile, but that he's maliciously incompetent. Perhaps you should get back to your Klavern meeting with Hawfreak to lay out some new plans of attack against the sitting President. Your favored candidate will be distributing fresh talking points for you brain-dead unemployable trolls to disseminate at your new ten cents a post rate. I'm imagining they'll be more in line with the garbage spewed by your obadoodoo partner in messageboard defacement, so your raise comes with a certain loss in "prestige".</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347827106970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 16:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347828352562-47</Id><Topic><Title>FactCheckOrg: Romney Did Indeed Ship Jobs Overseas To China</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1347815874507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 13:17:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should do better than just say Romney shipped jobs overseas, name them. I don't doubt it being true. Do you know any large co's who haven't? GM comes to mind - controlled by the president &amp; union.</Msg><Username>free2491</Username><Timestamp>1347828352562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 16:45:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347829500913-48</Id><Topic><Title>Got to Youtube and watch the Musllim from Kenya, Hussein, attack the Bible!</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1347755521302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 20:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They now have the Whitehouse, when they have controll of the house &amp; senate then we will learn how well you like sharia law. Sure it is coming just read the Bible.</Msg><Username>free2491</Username><Timestamp>1347829500913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 17:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347830024853-49</Id><Title>New York Times Story - Earnings Outlook in U.S. Dims as Global Economy Slows</Title><Msg>Go to New York Times Main Page for the story</Msg><Username>pricelinelong</Username><Timestamp>1347830024853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 17:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347831032772-50</Id><Title>Demon spawn,</Title><Msg>and poster child for nepotism, Elizabeth (Darthette) Cheney, insists that the Muslim Usurper Hawaiian Devil Baby, Ba-rock "the Islamic shock" Oblammer has abandoned our commitment with our Czechoslovakian "allies" (scare quores on that one until I check with DoS as to whether we're allied or non-allied with former Soviet block entities). Unfortunately for her remaining neuron, history has left her 1337 geopolitical skillz unsuitable for anything other than a quick round of "Streets of Slovak Rage" on her treasured Sega Genesis and only a little bit less up-to date than her gear. Since she has a law degree, perhaps daddykins could take her on his next captive duck ranch "hunting" expedition. A sixteen gauge with #6 shot would work just fine.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347831032772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 17:30:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347831152918-51</Id><Topic><Title>the hypocracy of the DNC No God on the platform for the homosexual vote, then yes God on the platform</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347822077064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know God isn't easy to get scheduled and He has been busy. Sometimes you get Him, sometimes not. Your criticisms are therefore misleading. You are free to read and interpret your Bible as you like, as am I. You are free to use the Bible as tp. Therefore, don't think yours is the only opinion that counts. God created all, right, so mind your own business and let Him handle it. Obama said it very well, it is first about love your neighbor, try that intead. That's how he explained his stance, which was extremely thoughtful. Obama is so right on. You probably didn't even listen to him, just criticize day and night. Goes for the atheists as well, mind your own business.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1347831152918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 17:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347831894463-52</Id><Topic><Title>the hypocracy of the DNC No God on the platform for the homosexual vote, then yes God on the platform</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347822077064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about that part of the Bible where God commands you not to bear false witness against your neighbor? When did the republicans repeal that commandment?</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1347831894463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 17:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347835474986-53</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS FOOLING YOU.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347641352210</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 12:49:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lugibroius, please see a psychologist. You need help.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1347835474986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 18:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347836791346-54</Id><Topic><Title>Are you going to let them do it to you?? These 'consevatives' on this board are tasked with protecting the interest of a very few in our country. They are given a well designed playbook that manipulates your emotions such that you see it their way. Don't let them manipulate your opinion with hollow empty emotional talking points.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1347806747610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are funny at a distance</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1347836791346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347836985289-55</Id><Topic><Title>the hypocracy of the DNC No God on the platform for the homosexual vote, then yes God on the platform</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347822077064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no god, phuckface.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1347836985289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347838887178-56</Id><Topic><Title>the hypocracy of the DNC No God on the platform for the homosexual vote, then yes God on the platform</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347822077064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phanny, the poster boy for being an aethiest, now that is a group i want to be a part of.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1347838887178</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347839473590-57</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation from monetary means is what we want right now. The inflation whined about by the RWNJ is scarcity inflation and is only a side issue. Monetary inflation is caused by higher consumption. Isn't it obvious that we need higher consumption resulting from consumers with more disposable cash??</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1347643301821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 13:21:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess that is why marc faber says that our printing money is going to destroy the global economy. course he is not as smart as you. lmao</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1347839473590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:51:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347841270971-58</Id><Title>Why was Omanure not prepared?</Title><Msg>"Libyan President Mohammed el-Megarif said he believes Al Qaeda is responsible for the deadly attack at the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi that killed four Americans and that roughly 50 people have arrested in connection with the violence, according to two broadcast interviews Sunday."</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347841270971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 20:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347841366673-59</Id><Title>Megarif to Obamanure, it was not the silly video, it was your incompetence!</Title><Msg>"Megarif, president of the Libyan National Congress, also differed with the Obama administration’s position that the attacks that started Tuesday were sparked by an anti-Islamic video on the Internet."</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347841366673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 20:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347841541250-60</Id><Title>Secretary of State view is preposterous! Megarif just made fools of Obamanure administration!</Title><Msg>"The idea that this criminal and cowardly act was a spontaneous protest that just spun out of control is completely unfounded and preposterous," Megarif told NPR. "We firmly believe that this was a pre-calculated, pre-planned attack that was carried out specifically to attack the U.S. Consulate."</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347841541250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 20:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347841763158-61</Id><Title>Bad week for Obamanure administration. Could not happen at a better time! Before the debates.</Title><Msg>"His [Megarif's] comments come on the same day Susan Rice, the U.S. ambassador to the United Nations, went on four Sunday morning talk show to back up the administration’s position that the video led to the violence, specifically in Libya."</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347841763158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 20:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347843727559-62</Id><Title>Obama has it locked up for his second term</Title><Msg>This means we are going to be able to hunt down the obadoodos of this country and lock them up and then deport them to Somalia</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347843727559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347843935215-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has it locked up for his second term</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347843727559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smoked too much Obamanure!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347843935215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347844012215-64</Id><Title>Megarif to Obamanure, it was the silly video, it was no ones incompetence!</Title><Msg>Obama and the US have handled the situation very skillfully and Megarif expects the US to evade any long term effects</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347844012215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347844107607-65</Id><Title>Megarif says that Obamanure administration completely ignorant on what happened in Lybia!</Title><Msg>But we knew that already! He just confirmed it.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347844107607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347844122565-66</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has it locked up for his second term</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347843727559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And ship both of them off to Canada. I hear Mitt has an "economic plan" to ship a lot of our tax money into one of his Cayman accounts by laundering it through tar sands "investments". The two of them can "follow the money", with an occasional stop to hose down obadogdoo. The rest he'll ship to his South American death squad business partners through shell companies he'll set up in Mexico as part of his "energy independence" stratergy.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347844122565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:08:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347844200262-67</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has it locked up for his second term</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347843727559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another Obamanure smoker!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347844200262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347844276044-68</Id><Topic><Title>Megarif to Obamanure, it was the silly video, it was no ones incompetence!</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347844012215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:06:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More Omamanure smoking!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347844276044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:11:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347844277751-69</Id><Title>Megarif stated that Obama and the US were very well prepared and responded quickly</Title><Msg>Megarif stated that the US responded quickly and effectivly "Libyan President Mohammed el-Megarif said he believes Al Qaeda is responsible for the deadly attack at the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi that killed four Americans and that roughly 50 people have arrested in connection with the violence, according to two broadcast interviews Sunday."</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347844277751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:11:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347844773302-70</Id><Title>With six million infants, toddlers, and small children starving to death every year</Title><Msg>The best that Romney can promise is to do away with planned parenthood, how wacky is that ???</Msg><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1347844773302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347844950696-71</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals again have the horse pushing the cart on inflation</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347802488592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's not forget that conservatives were against a women's right to vote, now they're against family planing, are they for real.....</Msg><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1347844950696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347845216323-72</Id><Topic><Title>Since President Obama took care of the Somalian Pirates</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1347735708492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:01:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The anti American wingnuts hate to see America succeed, so wont bother to even comment on that success...</Msg><Username>therwnjneedhelp</Username><Timestamp>1347845216323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:26:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347846669848-73</Id><Title>rWhy are regressive conservatives, baggers and flatearthers too stupid to understand US economics or foreign relations</Title><Msg>Its a well known fact that progressive liberals are head and shoulders above the RWNJs on these subjects</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347846669848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347850950208-74</Id><Title>U.S. Ambassador to U.N. Doubles Down on Claim that Film Responsible for Middle East Mobs. But Libyan president Mohammed el-Megarif is saying the attack Benghazi that killed the American ambassador was planned well beforehand.</Title><Msg>Who do you believe Obamanure or Libyan president?</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347850950208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 23:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347852296271-75</Id><Title>"Even [liberal] Media Isn't Buying White House's Explanation for Middle East Mobs". Obamanure losing the liberal media. Could not happen to a better buffoon.</Title><Msg>Bu-bye Mr. Obamamure!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347852296271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 23:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347852448900-76</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal ABC's Martha Raddatz asked, if there are American Marines in Paris, why are there not Marines in Tripoli?</Title><Username>dogeater2012</Username><Timestamp>1347850566211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 22:56:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The rats are leaving a sinking ship!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347852448900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 23:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347852540670-77</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Dogeater administration have no clue?</Title><Username>dogeater2012</Username><Timestamp>1347849416318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 22:36:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you expect from a buffoon leader, placing buffoons in leadership positions?</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347852540670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 23:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347852630605-78</Id><Topic><Title>"The Libyan account of the horrific events, however, contradicts what American officials are saying."</Title><Username>dogeater2012</Username><Timestamp>1347849573161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 22:39:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamanure's buffoonery directly led to 4 deaths.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347852630605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 23:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>