<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351923703891-1</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone tell me how Ballmer is CEO</Title><Username>highseas200</Username><Timestamp>1351880422596</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:20:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really don't understand? Ballmer has presided over a huge drop in market capitalization. He brought you Vista, Zune, Bing and Kin. He lost Microsoft's dominance in web browser share and mobile phones. He brought you the first product called "Surface" which was a monstrosity, though at least the name made sense for it; then borrowed the name for a tablet, for which the name doesn't make sense. The other day I saw on TV a discussion of the contention between Apple and Google over online mapping services. Appropriately, there was no mention that Microsoft also has a mapping service. Ballmer is a loose cannon. Do you understand what that expression means? If not, look it up.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1351923703891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351924108656-2</Id><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Msg>Admit yourself your mistake. Remember you did not fail, obama failed you.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351933123302-3</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT headed to 35 to 45 soon</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778602665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bought a Surface to play with it. Been a Mac user for many years. Is there anyway to import a large list of bookmarks? I exported a list to an HD SC card and plugged the reader into the USB port but can't find an import function in IE. Do all favorites have to be metro tiles???</Msg><Username>the_stock_warrior</Username><Timestamp>1351933123302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 04:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351943992677-4</Id><Topic><Title>Can someone tell me how Ballmer is CEO</Title><Username>highseas200</Username><Timestamp>1351880422596</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:20:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh please. when you watch TV and they show a map, which one do you see? It's Bing!</Msg><Username>jaceanne_gibson</Username><Timestamp>1351943992677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 07:59:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351945015664-5</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT headed to 35 to 45 soon</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778602665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Found this by searching through Bing: 1. Export your IE9 Favorites to a bookmark.htm file via ALT+F+I+N | Export Favorites. 2. Import the bookmark.htm file into IE10 Desktop via ALT+F+I+N | Import Favorites. ~Robear Dyer (PA Bear) MS MVP-Windows Client (IE, Mail, Security &amp; Update Services) since 2002</Msg><Username>jaceanne_gibson</Username><Timestamp>1351945015664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 08:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351946809148-6</Id><Topic><Title>Pennsylvania going Romney!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351903462410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 20:44:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People voting against Republicans.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1351946809148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 08:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351946834637-7</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama didn't fail the Somalian Pirated, Bin Laden, and other high profile terrorists, he kept the American homeland safe.. Was he perfect, no, but there were those who didn't think Jebus was perfect either</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1351946834637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 08:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351947319941-8</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT headed to 35 to 45 soon</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778602665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agreed but even much higher!!</Msg><Username>jravera</Username><Timestamp>1351947319941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 08:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351948743788-9</Id><Title>Pennsylvania going Obama!</Title><Msg>Most polls show an Obama edge in this traditionally Democrat state-- looks like Doomsday all over the map for the RWNJs and Baggers HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HYAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HA RHAR HAR HARHA HRA HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR tough titty diiildo</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351948743788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:19:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351949019594-10</Id><Topic><Title>Will The Right Wing Talking Teads Make a Retraction ???</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351870181689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you bet there is retraction owed. Its too bad the Scalia Supreme Court couldnt find against deliberately lying in the news- looks like the Citizenry is going to have to rise up and kick some butt- that means Fox Newspeak will be made to pay for their immorality</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351949019594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351949100271-11</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT headed to 35 to 45 soon</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778602665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, if the step 2 above does not work in Metro UI, do this: a.) Click Internet Explorer. b.) Swipe up from the bottom of the screen. c.) Right-click the wrench icon. d.) Click View On Desktop. e.) On the Desktop, right-click on top of the page shown by the Internet Explorer. f.) Click Menu Bar. You will see the Import/Export Favorites there.</Msg><Username>jaceanne_gibson</Username><Timestamp>1351949100271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351950195483-12</Id><Topic><Title>Which stocks Billionaires Love?</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905639453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 04:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bloomberg reports Mister Softee views a home-grown smartphone as a backup plan in the event this quarter's Windows Phone 8 launches (headlined by Nokia, Samsung, and HTC) disappoint. That's in-line with an October report from The Verge. Also: a Microsoft exec says WP8 still lacks a notification center (a feature long available on Android/iOS) because Microsoft "ran out of time" ahead of its launch.</Msg><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1351950195483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351951604517-13</Id><Title>MSFT - Special Dividend?</Title><Msg>With over 7.00 a share in cash it's difficult to believe MSFT is not considering a special dividend. Granted, most of the cash is overseas and they would be taxed the differential between countries if they repatriated the money. With interest rates so low why doesn't MSFT borrow billions to finance a dividend? They could borrow an awful lot at very low rates and still cover the interest with their incredible cash generation machine. Furthermore, if Obama wins the election MSFT might be "forced" to issue a special dividend if higher dividend taxes are expected. I'm sure Bill and Steve would rather pay a 15% tax rate vs. a 33+% tax rate? If Romney wins we could see incentives that allow corporations to repatirate at lower rates which could be an inducement for MSFT to increase their dividend significantly? Bottomline, MSFT can do a lot to unlock shareholder value in a very short period of time.</Msg><Username>sammsjohn99</Username><Timestamp>1351951604517</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 10:06:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351951787701-14</Id><Topic><Title>Will The Right Wing Talking Teads Make a Retraction ???</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351870181689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did the CIA lie then, or were they called on the carpet to lie now?" quote from Grover paid Moe. No, and no. And the birth certificate is real and honest too. The tea moes still taking about his BC. Apologies from the right are needed, starting with faux news. And it better be good.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351951787701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 10:09:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351953128316-15</Id><Topic><Title>Pennsylvania going Obama!</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351948743788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:19:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you as well as diiildo are going to lose your a.....s betting on the lying mormo n in Pennsylvania- he will only win in the ignorant racist states which means the sparsly populated high plains and the Confederacy and that aint enough HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR$ HAH HAR tough tiitty there hairy &amp; diiildo</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351953128316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 10:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351954863375-16</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a very sad day for the Romney partisans who have been rooting so hard for misery, who have fervently hoped that the government's final pre-election jobs report would reverse the nation's slow but steady economic recovery. They needed a massive explosion, something that would erase President Obama's small but durable polling lead in most of the swing states. Instead, they got a dud. The numbers released this morning by the Bureau of Labor Statistics aren't particularly stellar - nothing new there - but they continue to confirm our upward trajectory. The economy added 171,000 jobs during October (most economists had anticipated 125,000); plus, the BLS revised the August and September numbers - upwards. Turns out, 192,000 jobs were created in August, not the initial estimate of 142,000. And September jobs have upticked to 148,000, frm the initial 114,000. Meanwhile, the latest jobless rate is 7.9 percent. That's one-tenth of a percent higher than in September, but, as business experts point out, that's because more people have re-entered the labor force - and when more people feel encouraged to look for work, that too is good news. Good news for the economy, that is. And good news for Obama. He's not likely to get a huge electoral boost from those numbers, nor would he have expected to. Most importantly, the final jobs report does him no harm.</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1351954863375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351954907173-17</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I already voted Obama/Biden and for every Democrat and every Democrat supported issue. Obama has done an outstanding job, and is an outstanding man as well. Now just get the teamoes out of congress and trim off the hate brigade, then we'll zoom forward and up. Obama has done great given the situation in Jan 2009, we are lucky to have him in there. BIN LADEN'S SMIRK ABOUT 9/11 IS OFF HIS FACE FOR GOOD. And no, Obama doesn't blame Bush, he states the true facts, this country was on the verge of financial COLLAPSE AND WE WOULD HAVE TAKEN THE WORLD WITH US. Thank you, President Obama.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351954907173</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351955614348-18</Id><Title>Why did ryan and teamoes vote to reduce emabassy spending by 300 million?</Title><Msg>They want to decimate embassy funding further so people like romney can bank anoth 4-5% on their taxes? They say FEMA, oh we don't need that? Eucation, don't need? Energy, don't need? Protecting our environment for our grandchildren, don't need? But we need Romney to bank another million per year in tax breaks? Yah that's exactly what they say, and it's just a starter list. They were warned about security if embassy spending was cut, but you kow what? They have a common trait, they never listen, and nevere change even when proven wrong.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351955614348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351957782704-19</Id><Title>there is only one group that hates President Obama more than the ''terrorists" and other Bin Laden followers</Title><Msg>And that's the far right fringe in America..</Msg><Username>beemerbe</Username><Timestamp>1351957782704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351957966950-20</Id><Title>back in the 30s after tuesday steady and up mid 30s 6-9 months out plus div bump</Title><Msg>im impressed myself-bought 28.10 and happy-aapl heading south moved up to quick.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351957966950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:52:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351957998672-21</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT headed to 35 to 45 soon</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778602665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one cares. Windows 8 is a flop of epic proportions.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351957998672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351962400810-22</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wing Talking Heads Retraction ??? - Continued</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351958018325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Did the CIA lie then, or were they called on the carpet to lie now?" quote from Grover paid Moe. No, and no. " Both cannot be true, Moe" You said it, both cannot be true, no lie then, no called on carpet now, and they aren't true. You're just not smart. You are like faux news, form an opinion based on nothing but gut feeling, then go build stories to fit. Not workig here, we're smarter than you. How do you like my brand new shiny alias, moe foe?</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351962400810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:06:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351962464660-23</Id><Title>why wion't yahoo let me post an article found on "Buzzhill"</Title><Msg>regarding Obama being called" bat hou Barry" and " cake bo y' by Chicago blacks?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351962464660</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:07:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351962561598-24</Id><Title>#$%$ in the stew pot.</Title><Msg>My hotmail was switched to the new "Outlook." What a disaster. Contacts lost. Many having problems. Maggots had something working well, now #$%$.</Msg><Username>thorspal</Username><Timestamp>1351962561598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351962665668-25</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wing Talking Heads Retraction ??? - Continued</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351958018325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Havvcreek12 is stil availale, go look stupid again and get it, moe foe. I'm very funny.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351962665668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:11:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351963190561-26</Id><Title>According toReuters and The Daily Beast</Title><Msg>Revealed last week that gov officials and others noted thatFBI officers who interviewed security officers who worked at the consulate knew as early as Sept 14 that the attack was no protest. Yet Obama and Susan Rice repeatedly lied about the video. This episode reflects directly on his competence and honesty as Commander in chief. This is not just FOX anymore.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351963190561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351964605403-27</Id><Topic><Title>Why did Obama and Hillary have billions unspent for Embassy security and fail to grant request</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351956245370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:24:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 dead no protection no help, as dangerous as it could get. Yet NO PROTECTION</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1351964605403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351965024779-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says he will cut your taxes by 20% and raise military spending by $2Trillion.</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1351901817698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 20:16:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no way that the math adds up in his lame and transparent tax plan that sucks off billionaires. Romney is a crooked liar. He is under the control of Grover Norquist &amp; the K0ch Bros. Romney lies. He can't be trusted. He will shaft working people.</Msg><Username>veronica_meester</Username><Timestamp>1351965024779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351965977015-29</Id><Topic><Title>there is only one group that hates President Obama more than the ''terrorists" and other Bin Laden followers</Title><Username>beemerbe</Username><Timestamp>1351957782704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:49:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are wrong it is not the far right fringes it is fact the Main body of the GOP. Just about anybody with an r behind their name falls into to this group.</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1351965977015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 14:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351968170211-30</Id><Topic><Title>there is only one group that hates President Obama more than the ''terrorists" and other Bin Laden followers</Title><Username>beemerbe</Username><Timestamp>1351957782704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:49:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually there is only one group that Obama hates much more than the terrorists is the American people,. I'm not even sure he hates the terrorists all that much. He won't even call them that.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351968170211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 14:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351969359220-31</Id><Topic><Title>there is only one group that hates President Obama more than the ''terrorists" and other Bin Laden followers</Title><Username>beemerbe</Username><Timestamp>1351957782704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:49:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction, I mean the chief, the President, was ultimately responsible for the use of the tools at his disposal, namely the seals, for getting Bin Laden. My bad. It's the darn swamp gas coming through the floorboards in my trailer down here, and the owner of the trailer won't even seal the holes. Just because I am late on rent shouldn't be an excuse not to maintain his trailer, and it is only 8 feet long, so what the hay. Sorry about all the Obama bashing. I am starting to get sober now, and besides Grover has been late with his payments to me, so....eff him, the moe. Later. hawrcreek12</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351969359220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 15:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351971648167-32</Id><Title>Latest Polls Puts Obama Ahead of Romney in Ohio and Florida</Title><Msg>Latest Polls Puts Obama Ahead of Romney in Ohio and Florida Bloomberg President Barack Obama holds leads in the key swing states of Ohio and Florida over Republican challenger Mitt Romney, according to a poll released today. The NBC News/Wall Street Journal/Marist College survey of likely voters put Obama ahead of Romney in Ohio, 51 percent to 45 percent, and in Florida, 49 percent to 47 percent. In Ohio, 52 percent of likely voters viewed Obama favorably and 45 percent viewed him unfavorably. Forty-eight percent viewed Romney unfavorably and 45 percent favorably. By 48 percent to 46 percent, they said Obama would do a better job than Romney in handling the economy.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351971648167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 15:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351973799424-33</Id><Topic><Title>Uber Liberal Tampa Bay Times: Romney Remains on top (in Florida)</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351972105518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 15:48:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank God,.... .... and Patriotic Freedom loving Americans everywhere.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351973799424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 16:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351975071725-34</Id><Title>There is only one "terrrorist" group that hates America</Title><Msg>The sinister anti American 5th columnist terrrorist group is called the DNC.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351975071725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 16:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351975685344-35</Id><Title>America always favors the Underdog = Mitt Romney,... not the eve ill Overlord =</Title><Msg>... Barrack Hoo'is'insane O'Boodthirstybama.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351975685344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 16:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351976501444-36</Id><Title>Why is the Ken'yan even campaigning?</Title><Msg>He has a record now. Including murrder.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351976501444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351976662310-37</Id><Title>SupplySide Economics DOES NOT WORK! Romney Will Crash This Economy AGAIN!</Title><Msg>Dubya's economic advisors are now on the Romney team. Electing Romney will crash this economy!! Romney is Dubya/Norquist Part 2.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351976662310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351976712405-38</Id><Title>Governor Romney said he will be president of ALL the people, not just some.</Title><Msg>O'Budthrusty Hussein said he will seek "revenge" on his "en'emies." The American people.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351976712405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:05:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351977302005-39</Id><Title>It's good that the Muslum is encouraging his people to vote</Title><Msg>Little does he know that they're voting against him. He's that stoopit.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351977302005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:15:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351978840343-40</Id><Topic><Title>Governor Romney said he will be president of ALL the people, not just some.</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351976712405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President of ALL the bigots, fearmongers, greedy fools and liars.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1351978840343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351980698939-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama slips, reveals his inner feelings of hate,: Voting for him is "revenge?"..against whom?</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351910225156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The elitist arrogant pious pompous pustule Hussein has an innate hatred and disdain for anything and everything and anyone that isn't him.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351980698939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:11:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351981120523-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama slips, reveals his inner feelings of hate,: Voting for him is "revenge?"..against whom?</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351910225156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama to supporters: Voting 'best revenge' against Mitt Romney" Sounds perfect to me, beautiful. I already voted just like that against Romney, and enjoyed every second of marking the ballot and mailing it in against that liar and tax cheat, not to mention draft dodger, mormon, poor memory, poor fact checking, and about a dozen more overlooked by redneck right wingers, faults.... Way to go Pres, right on...</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351981120523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351981542459-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obama slips, reveals his inner feelings of hate,: Voting for him is "revenge?"..against whom?</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351910225156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Grover said all he needs is a hand with fingers to hold the pen, to sign the docs. He actually said that, I heard him myself. I am not going along with that takeover, he's a lobbyist, a nobody, I got my one vote of REVENGE. Sorry hawcreek10-12-14, I know he is your boss and paycheck but hey it's just wrong.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351981542459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351982065108-44</Id><Title>One thing is for cetain</Title><Msg>it's curtains for the Ken yen.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351982065108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351982140026-45</Id><Topic><Title>One thing is for cetain</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351982065108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>God bless President Romney.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351982140026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351982488587-46</Id><Title>Payroll Growth Shows U.S. Labor Market Healing Before Election</Title><Msg>Bloomberg Payroll Growth Shows U.S. Labor Market Healing Before Election American employers hired more workers than forecast in October while an influx of people joining the labor force pushed the jobless rate higher, according to the last job market report before the presidential election. Payrolls expanded by 171,000 workers following a 148,000 gain in September that was bigger than first estimated, figures from the Labor Department showed yesterday. Octoberâ€™s increase exceeded the highest forecast in a Bloomberg survey with a median projection of 125,000. Unemployment rose to 7.9 percent</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351982488587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351983400843-47</Id><Topic><Title>Obama slips, reveals his inner feelings of hate,: Voting for him is "revenge?"..against whom?</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351910225156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I am not going along with that takeover..." Pre-election, genius, not voting for your boss of romney's writing fingers, GroverNorquist. No wonder you can't find work.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351983400843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:56:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351983768087-48</Id><Topic><Title>Paychecks have steadily declined for four years under Obama</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351982766576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:46:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Considering the same happened under Bush I don't see how lower taxes fixes anything, and that is all Romney is offering. In fact Bush's economy was propped up by the housing bubble which let families refinance their homes over and over as the value of their property falsely grew. This put spending power in to people's pockets to makeup for the short falls in hiring and wage growth under Bush. What bubble is Romeny cooking up? If Obama hadn't had as much stonewalling in congress who knows where we'd be at. Nobody ever gave obama a chance. Not even Obamacares was what he really wanted and it was the only real legislative victory he can claim. If republicans would have been more worried about fixing the economy instead of just figuring out how to defeat Obama over the past 4 years we MIGHT be in a better place today. No jobs bill which Obama wanted. No infrastructure spending which Obama wanted. Nothing. Just filibuster after filibuster.</Msg><Username>a_conservative_hates_america</Username><Timestamp>1351983768087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351983836500-49</Id><Topic><Title>Obama slips, reveals his inner feelings of hate,: Voting for him is "revenge?"..against whom?</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351910225156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Are The Right Wing Wackos Soooooooo Void of Factual Information ???</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1351983836500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351984493848-50</Id><Title>I WANT higher taxes. I want 75% taxes for the richest. #$%$ THEM</Title><Msg>I remember as a kid everyone saying "we are just passing the spending on to our kids" and baby boomer politicians just raided their own social security funds to pay for missles, district kick backs and other social programs. And where are we today. My generation is now being asked to give back all the great tax "loop holes" that the baby boomers benefited from, such as child tax credit, mortgage tax credit etc. And we've got Romney Talking about reducing capital gains taxes. Yah? Easy for a guy who hasn't had any earned income in 20 years besides his governor pay check which was cheese compared to his investment income (which he doesn't pay SS on). Think baby boomers like Romney use the mortgage credit? Heck no, he pays cash. He doesn't have any children he can claim anymore, so of course he doesn't care about the child tax credit anymore. I'm sick of Baby Boomers. They bankrupted SS by borrowing from it. We wouldn't have a SS crisis if we had saved that money for its intended purpose. And I'm not being partisan about that either, #$%$ all baby boomers. They have borrowed and borrowed us in to debt and just like was said in the 80's, they are just going to die while WE pay their SS retirement, and we have no SS retirement to look forward to or fall back on. If you are a 60 year old making 1,000,000 in the market. Yah, its time for all the benefits you raped from us over the decades to come back to the American people that didn't create the problems our country is in right now. I didn't say it was ok to borrow from SS to pay for programs. That wasn't my decision. but now I'm being asked to carry the burden. I'm 100% for the "death tax"... one hundred f@cking percent. In fact it should be taxed at 90% over $1,000,000. They reaped all the benefits and now they are the ones passing that burden on to ME.</Msg><Username>a_conservative_hates_america</Username><Timestamp>1351984493848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351984553418-51</Id><Topic><Title>Obama slips, reveals his inner feelings of hate,: Voting for him is "revenge?"..against whom?</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351910225156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tries to scare people into voting for him and simpers like a baby when he's called on it. Soon he can go back to his mansions and car elevators and continue complaining about the people who he rips off for the fruits of their labor.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1351984553418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:15:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351984928964-52</Id><Title>Romney /Ryan Are ssA Boys For Grover Norquist &amp; The K0ch Bros</Title><Msg>Grover Norquist's plan is simple. Cut taxes until social safety net programs collapse. The plan of the far right is to starve social security, medicare, medicaide until they collapse. The goal of the far right, as directed by Grover Norquist, is to kill the Federal Government, thereby killing all social safey net programs as well as environmental and civil rights legislation. The billionaire olegarchy will fill the power vacuum when the Fed is gone.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351984928964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351985029230-53</Id><Topic><Title>Payroll Growth Shows U.S. Labor Market Healing Before Election</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351982488587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:41:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The economy is on the verge of a boom thanks to Obama. He deserves credit. Obama deserves to be reelected.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351985029230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351985083797-54</Id><Topic><Title>Governor Romney said he will be president of ALL the people, not just some.</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351976712405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try and keep your M'uslim Mess'iah out of this you gree d lie n feer mong r ing race ist foo</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351985083797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351985347598-55</Id><Topic><Title>Obama slips, reveals his inner feelings of hate,: Voting for him is "revenge?"..against whom?</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351910225156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why does mr president go around with that "i.ve been persecuted" all my life look? You know......the look all male blaaaaaccccks have.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1351985347598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:29:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351985987026-56</Id><Title>"I don't think I've ever really seen people running for political office threaten people with their employment,"</Title><Msg>"It might be fair game for somebody to say, I can improve the economy. I can grow the jobs market and you'll have more opportunities under me than the other guy. I've heard that. I don't think I've heard anybody come out like this and say: 'You're going to lose your jobs if you don't vote for me.' Pretty ridiculous. But he did." Romney was garbage as Governor and he'd be worse with more power to abuse.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1351985987026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351986205188-57</Id><Topic><Title>Obama slips, reveals his inner feelings of hate,: Voting for him is "revenge?"..against whom?</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351910225156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:37:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Are The Left Wing Wackos Soooooooo ignorant and stupid ???</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1351986205188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351986277022-58</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative and intellgent periodical "The Economist" chooses Obama for president.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351867254026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 10:40:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>worthy of yur consideration</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351986277022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351986329465-59</Id><Topic><Title>creek finds politically active blacks to be unworth associates. Now who is the racist???</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351686735756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:32:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah lets reconsider this one</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351986329465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:45:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351986444341-60</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom</Title><Username>therwnjneedhelp</Username><Timestamp>1351828886599</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 00:01:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RWNJ should be seen and not heard.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351986444341</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351986540269-61</Id><Title>Creek slips, reveals his true feelings about minorities, especially politically active blacks</Title><Msg>"""Can we expect a man who spent his years of training "seeking out" "politically active" "blacks", "Chicanos", and "Marxist professors" to have discussions on American imperialism and world wide oppression and who chose and married a politically active, angry, racist woman, and who openly stated the U.S. Constitution is a "deeply flawed" document, to forget all that training and indoctrination and lead a capitalist country and uphold the (in his mind) the "deeply flawed" document?""</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351986540269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351990116565-62</Id><Title>When times were tough, and everything came crashing down after the Bush bubble popped...</Title><Msg>Mitt and his financial wizard chums were only worried about their bailouts and their bonuses. Now they're only worried about their tax cuts and their foreign tax shelters, and Mitt and his buddies are lying when they try to tell you otherwise.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1351990116565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 20:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351990761216-63</Id><Title>ROMNEY JUST WON THE ELECTION</Title><Msg>In his speech in Englewood Colorado thats on right now he said that Obamma is calling for "revenge" and Romney said that he would rather people just love their country. The crowd is still chanting USA USA USA USA USA.........</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351990761216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 20:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351991269000-64</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY JUST WON THE ELECTION</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351990761216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 20:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's funny, every time the rabid vicious psychotic knee grow attacks Americans and Romney with his "revenge" comments and calling Americans "his enemy" Mitt just makes him look like the savage bllud thurst tee mentally unstable piece of she it that he is and thats how Governor Romeny is able to connect with the People of America as the calm level headed compassionate caring educated intelligent leader he is. All Hussein's good at is dividing the Nation and vaporizing Americans in Lib'ya.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351991269000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:07:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351991549859-65</Id><Topic><Title>Romney /Ryan Are ssA Boys For Grover Norquist &amp; The K0ch Bros</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351984928964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When did the Koch Br get control of Fox?</Msg><Username>ygslvn</Username><Timestamp>1351991549859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351991751108-66</Id><Topic><Title>Romney /Ryan Are ssA Boys For Grover Norquist &amp; The K0ch Bros</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351984928964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lordbalzy, I don't think that's ever "the goal". You just might argue that would be the "result" if you want, meaning if the policy doesn't work out.</Msg><Username>ygslvn</Username><Timestamp>1351991751108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:15:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351991927291-67</Id><Topic><Title>NJ Gov Christie praises Obama For Lightening Fast FEMA Response.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351705822562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:50:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has proved himself.....incapable.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351991927291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351992485278-68</Id><Topic><Title>"I don't think I've ever really seen people running for political office threaten people with their employment,"</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1351985987026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:39:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Dreams From My Father: "I found a solace in nursing a pervasive sense of grievance and animosity against my mother's race."</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1351992485278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351992521322-69</Id><Topic><Title>Creek slips, reveals his true feelings about minorities, especially politically active blacks</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351986540269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:49:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You add AND conditions where there were none in your post. Is this ALSO too difficult for you to understand, if so then the range of topics we can discuss will take a much sharper downward turn than previous estimates had predicted.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351992521322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351992726462-70</Id><Title>Look what the Musslim mutt did to "Ambassador" Stevens, one of his own that HE appointed</Title><Msg>Just think what he would do to YOU.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351992726462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:32:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351992747262-71</Id><Title>Creek, even under Romney your pile driving business will not flourish because it was U who drove it down</Title><Msg>get over it and take up 'another' hobby like wood carving or beer can collecting</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351992747262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351992799784-72</Id><Topic><Title>Creek slips, reveals his true feelings about minorities, especially politically active blacks</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351986540269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:49:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Dreams From My Father: "I never emulate white men and brown men whose fates didn't speak to my own. It was into my father's image, the black man, son of Africa , that I'd packed all the attributes I sought in myself: the attributes of Martin and Malcolm, DuBois and Mandela."</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1351992799784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351993455878-73</Id><Topic><Title>Look what the Musslim mutt did to "Ambassador" Stevens, one of his own that HE appointed</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351992726462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:32:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The same thing that he did to the Information Officer and 2 Navy SEALS.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351993455878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351993522699-74</Id><Topic><Title>NJ Gov Christie praises Obama For Lightening Fast FEMA Response.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351705822562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:50:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MOTHER OF SEAL: 'I BELIEVE THAT OBAMA MURDERED MY SON' By JEANETTE STEELE &amp; NATHAN MAX â€¢ U-T 12:01 a.m., Nov. 2, 2012 Updated 9:59 p.m. , Nov. 1, 2012 A father and a mother used the word â€œmurder.â€ A brother said he wonâ€™t second-guess decisions made in the heat of battle. The families of three Americans killed in the Sept. 11 U.S. consulate attack in Benghazi, Libya, are offering widely different reactions to recent reports that U.S. personnel issued several requests for help that were turned down. Patricia Smith, the mother of slain State Department employee Sean Patrick Smith, is now blaming President Barack Obama for her sonâ€™s death. â€œI believe that Obama murdered my son,â€ she said Thursday from the living room of her Clairemont home. â€œI firmly believe this.â€ Patricia Smith, who voted for Obama in 2008 at the insistence of her son, said reporting by Fox News is the basis for much of her belief that Obama is ultimately responsible for her sonâ€™s death. She said Sean, who went to Mission Bay High School but lived abroad, was a fervent supporter of the president. Smithâ€™s view echoes that of Charles Woods, father of Tyrone Woods, the 41-year-old former Navy SEAL from Imperial Beach who died fighting in Benghazi. Charles Woods appeared on Fox News shows over the weekend to denounce decisions made by U.S. officials during the Libya attack. â€œIâ€™m a retired attorney, and I know that these actions legally do not constitute murder. But in my mind the people in the White House, all of them who have authority to send in reinforcements to prevent what they knew was going to be the death of my son, are guilty of murdering my son,â€ Woods said Sunday on Foxâ€™s Sean Hannity show. The older brother of Glen Doherty, a former Navy SEAL from Encinitas working as a U.S. security contractor, said Doherty and Tyrone Woods were part of the force that responded to the consulate attack. â€œThey rescued a bunch of people and brought them to the (consulate) annex, and then people defended the annex after Glen and Ty fell. All those people didnâ€™t get overrun and wiped out. They had enough people to fight off that battle,â€ said Greg Doherty, who lives in Kensington in Northern California. In that light, Doherty said the debate over needing more help doesnâ€™t make sense to him, unless it might have been U.S. airstrikes against a mortar position used by attackers. â€œBut then you are getting into real specific strategy, and I donâ€™t think it is civiliansâ€™ job to pick apart an actual battle and talk strategy, unless you are a general,â€ said Doherty, reached by telephone Thursday. â€œIt just seems like people are looking to direct their anger at Obama somehow.â€ The debate about how the administration handled security for the Libya consulate is heating up in the week before the presidential election. Despite that, Charles Woods, reached by U-T San Diego Thursday afternoon, said, â€œI donâ€™t want this to become political and become dishonoring to Ty.â€ He declined to answer any further questions. The extended Navy SEAL community around San Diego is talking about the details of the Libya attacks.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1351993522699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:45:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351993977785-75</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama will do even better in his 2nd term. There are not enough old white men who like war to provide enough votes to win an election...</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1351993977785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351994111218-76</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT headed to 35 to 45 soon</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778602665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't see import favorites anywhere, tried both methods.... Btw no mouse w/ surface so right clicking I think is using the right alt key and touching....</Msg><Username>the_stock_warrior</Username><Timestamp>1351994111218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351994242942-77</Id><Title>Obamma praised for his lightning fast response</Title><Msg>.... in being able to come up with a video story excuse and cover-up almost instantaneously. For his execution of 4 Americans. Now you know why his followers praise and glorify him.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351994242942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351994386900-78</Id><Topic><Title>NJ Gov Christie praises Obama For Lightening Fast FEMA Response.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351705822562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:50:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BREAKING: NAACP Takes Over Houston Polling Station, Advocates for President Obama Katie Pavlich Katie Pavlich News Editor, Townhall Nov 03, 2012 05:46 PM EST Click if you like this post! HOUSTON, TX - Friday afternoon at an early polling place located at 6719 W. Montgomery Road in Houston, NAACP members were seen advocating for President Barack Obama according to volunteer poll watchers on location at the time. According to Eve Rockford, a poll watcher trained by voter integrity group True the Vote, three NAACP members showed up to the 139 precinct location with 50 cases of bottled water and began handing bottles out to people standing in line. While wearing NAACP labeled clothing, members were "stirring the crowd" and talking to voters about flying to Ohio to promote President Barack Obama. After watching what was occurring, Rockford approached Polling Supervisor Rose Cochran about what she was seeing. "I went to the polling supervisor and let her know that it was not appropriate that they were in the building handing out water. She ignored me. I repeated my statement. She told me that she would handle it. She did nothing. I then went to the assistant supervisor and he stood up, walked over to another table and then sat down. I then walked into the waiting room and they were reloading another dolly with more cases of water," Rockford said in a True the Vote incident report. After handing out water and advocating for President Obama, the NAACP members started handpicking and moving people to the front of a long voting line inside the polling place according to the incident report. After multiple complaints from voters about the line cutting, Rockford received a phone call from downtown telling her to â€œstand down.â€ â€œAll of the sudden one of the clerks, Dayan Cohen, said that someone wanted to speak to me on the phone. It was someone from downtown. I got on the phone and she said she was from downtown and that I needed to stand down and that it was okay for the NAACP to be within 100 ft. and they could hand out water. I told her that the NAACP was inside the building, wearing the NAACP clothing and caps and were handing out water and moving people from the back of the lines to the front of the lines,â€ Rockford said. At this point, NAACP members were instructed to turn their clothing inside out, which they refused to do and said they werenâ€™t going to stop their actions inside the polling place. Their behavior and actions to move people to the front of the line continued for the rest of the evening. Texas State Representative Sylvester Turner, a former Texas NAACP leader, was also seen outside the building talking with voters. â€œThe NAACP basically ran this poll location and the judges did nothing about it,â€ Rockford said.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1351994386900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:59:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351995580083-79</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama failed no one. Bush left him and the country in a mess. Obama saved the day. If the Republican Party had been smart enough to pick Christie - they would have had a much better opportunity. Romney is a chameleon and a liar. - it is that simple.</Msg><Username>jcbrowns</Username><Timestamp>1351995580083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351995868261-80</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Black Pastor Receives Death Threats For Reversing Support For Obama Email One Sacramento pastor, whose congregation has thousands of members, voted for Barack Obama in 2008 but won't be doing the same in 2012. Stefanie Cruz reports.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351995868261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351995887062-81</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As Election Day nears, Obama supporters step up riot threats Posted at 9:18 pm on November 2, 2012 by Twitchy Staff | View Comments Parker @ManiStaySmileyy If Obama doesn't win, I will actually start a riot. This is not a joke. 2 Nov 12 A few weeks ago, Twitchy reported on Twitter users threatening to riot if President Obama loses to GOP rival Mitt Romney. With four days to go until Election Day, we decided this is a topic worth revisiting. The results of our Twitter searches are not pretty:</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1351995887062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351996785155-82</Id><Topic><Title>NJ Gov Christie praises Obama For Lightening Fast FEMA Response.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351705822562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:50:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I got on the phone and she said she was from downtown and that I needed to stand down" Good. Sounds like NAACP was doing a good thing, hope they keep it up, do it more. That's what you get when you try and prevent people from voting you don't like, they vote more. Good. Payback is a B isn't it.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351996785155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:39:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352000827105-83</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>-There are not enough old white men who like war to provide enough votes to win an election..- funny how the hawkooks of the world support war shut-in behind a key board.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1352000827105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 23:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352001237276-84</Id><Topic><Title>Creek, even under Romney your pile driving business will not flourish because it was U who drove it down</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351992747262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:32:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope your inventions work out, but i am skeptical for two reasons, first the difficulty of really inventing new things in our supersaturated environment and then my lack of faith in your technical skills which i acquired over our many discussions. IF you need any help let me know, I know you need help!!!!! I think you should go really conservative and not waste money on patents.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1352001237276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 23:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352001363204-85</Id><Topic><Title>Creek slips, reveals his true feelings about minorities, especially politically active blacks</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351986540269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:49:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you never said WHO is the source of the text in quotes. Yur original post surely didn't indicate this.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1352001363204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 23:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352001405031-86</Id><Topic><Title>Creek slips, reveals his true feelings about minorities, especially politically active blacks</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351986540269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:49:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you have a point??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1352001405031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 23:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352001536878-87</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My family and all my friends vote for romney. We are sick and tired of obama who became a president because of his color. No white man with obama's qualifications (i should say no qualifications) would've become the president.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352001536878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 23:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>