<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347336085402-1</Id><Topic><Title>Windoze 8 fails even before it hits the shelves</Title><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347304406274</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 fails before it hits shelves?? so says the HIV infected #$%$ who bashes Microsoft daily and spends his nights in the waterfront dives. The next morning he is pumping his lies again. Truth is th Iturds and suxturds are doomed all because of Windows 8 which is going to take over the planet. tough titty there phands</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347336085402</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347336330733-2</Id><Topic><Title>GM Spends $89,000 and sells for $40,000. That's ignorant liberal Obamanomics.</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347329863920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deeldo the cost figure is on 20,000 cars- when sales picks up and 200,000 cars are sold the cost per car becomes 8,900$$ you have to be stoooopider than a flatworm not to be aware of this. Do us a favor and off yourself eh</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347336330733</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:05:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347336455010-3</Id><Topic><Title>They are still shoveling the Obamanure from the DNC venues. They will have a bumper crop next year.</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347328305940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey deeldo I still cant get over your awsome ignorance about manufacturing costs and the GM Volt- My Gawd you are dumb</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347336455010</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347336684968-4</Id><Topic><Title>They are still shoveling the Obamanure from the DNC venues. They will have a bumper crop next year.</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347328305940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another Obamanurist ignorant liberal Marxist here!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347336684968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347336709024-5</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama, speaking earlier today in Florida, said that American manufacturers are "making products that we sell around the world, marked with three proud words: made in the U.S.A."</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347247319679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 23:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>liberals can count very well. BTW deeldo if it had not been for that liberal A Lincoln you would be picking cotton today and riding in the back of the bus- and the RWNJ slavers would be counting all the money they were saving being slave owners</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347336709024</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347336816485-6</Id><Topic><Title>GM Spends $89,000 and sells for $40,000. That's ignorant liberal Obamanomics.</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347329863920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 22:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody wants buy this Obamanure enhanced, ignorant, liberal crap that cost too much!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347336816485</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347337044798-7</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama, speaking earlier today in Florida, said that American manufacturers are "making products that we sell around the world, marked with three proud words: made in the U.S.A."</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347247319679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 23:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberal city schools produce the most ignorant kids in USA. Liberals can't count! However they really know the calendar, that is when the welfare checks is due to arrive!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347337044798</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:17:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347337383009-8</Id><Title>Barracks home town: Most kids killed, highest paid teachers, failed performance children, most welfare recipients. The left wing, liberal, Marxist success story of Barrack's home town</Title><Msg>Chicago: the place to raise your kids!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347337383009</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347337745627-9</Id><Title>NAMBLA and Democrat liberal Marxists, perfect together!</Title><Msg>According to Biden, " ... they'll put you back in chains." I guess the Liberals Democrats really know all about this!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347337745627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347353114217-10</Id><Topic><Title>NAMBLA and Democrat liberal Marxists, perfect together!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347337745627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:29:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch nobama 2016 and you will see nobumba wants to get us nuked.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347353114217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 04:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347353179142-11</Id><Topic><Title>Barracks home town: Most kids killed, highest paid teachers, failed performance children, most welfare recipients. The left wing, liberal, Marxist success story of Barrack's home town</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347337383009</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:23:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch nobama 2016 and you will see he wants all of america to look like shitcogo</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347353179142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 04:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347353252873-12</Id><Topic><Title>They are still shoveling the Obamanure from the DNC venues. They will have a bumper crop next year.</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347328305940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More like commie sewer rat traitor.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347353252873</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 04:47:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347353342537-13</Id><Topic><Title>along with ABC, CBS, CNN and Now NBC all losing viewers, the lib dem agenda not for the People</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347313971645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are all labeled commie stations. Watch the movie nobama 2016 and see where we are headed.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347353342537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 04:49:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347353366008-14</Id><Topic><Title>NEWS. ROMNEY 2012</Title><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1347328779281</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:59:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WINNERRRRRRRRR</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347353366008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 04:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347353434608-15</Id><Topic><Title>Miff Is In Trouble</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1347322974486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:22:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a sewer commie rat traitor you POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347353434608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 04:50:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347353481272-16</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe Governor KrispyCreme Can Help Miff</Title><Username>rush_limpballs_warning</Username><Timestamp>1347324763520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:52:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ you commie POS traitor.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347353481272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 04:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347353527042-17</Id><Topic><Title>Romney should debate Ryan first so they can get their story straight</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1347327902373</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ you commie sewer rat traitor.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347353527042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 04:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347353606876-18</Id><Topic><Title>Barrack biggest hoax perpetuated on Americans ever.</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347327935511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:45:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch nobama 2016 and you will see what he is. Commie muzzie rat traitor.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347353606876</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 04:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347363258201-19</Id><Topic><Title>Barrack biggest hoax perpetuated on Americans ever.</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347327935511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:45:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem is not Obama....it's the American people!! Through the years, the education system has been dumbing down the children. Now we have a young generation that doesn't know anything about government and what they're doing. You can thank the progressives for that..... Then you have 50% of the Americans who don't work, haven't worked and don't plan on working as long as the government will take care of them...... I would love to see a law where if you are on welfare, you can't vote. If you don't contribute, then you don't have a say in what happens. This election you have a choice, Mormon or #$%$ Choose wisely, look how bad Obama has brought this nation down, and just think what he could do in another four. This man is so anti-American, and has an agenda......my 2 cents.</Msg><Username>higgsernie</Username><Timestamp>1347363258201</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 07:34:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347367922170-20</Id><Topic><Title>Miff Is In Trouble</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1347322974486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:22:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Al Qaeda is praying to Allah that Mitt Romney wins. If you have a guy like Romney who can't decide what he wants, TERRORIST will be happy to easily kill Americans.</Msg><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1347367922170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 08:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347369225579-21</Id><Topic><Title>Windoze 8 fails even before it hits the shelves</Title><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347304406274</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iPad and iPhone aren't PC's. And they don't run Windows 8. Did you have a point?</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1347369225579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347370649902-22</Id><Topic><Title>Windoze 8 fails even before it hits the shelves</Title><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347304406274</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah right. Windows Vista and Kin were supposed to take over the world too. Blah, blah, blah. So how about a Windows 9 preview? Maybe it won't suck so bad.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1347370649902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347371501572-23</Id><Title>NTWK $5.5 UP 15c....UP AGAIN AFTER MONESTER EARNINGS AND 40% REVENUE GROWTH &amp; $1/SHARE 2013 GUIDANCE...PRICE TARGET RAISED TO $16......NTWK .has been up every day after a minor post-record earnings profit taking. The stock is just starting to rally and with a 3 million share float $15 soon is just around the corner (see chart). That would make it a 12 forward PE which is conservative for a company expecting to deliver $1/share net income and grow revenues 40% in 2013.........still very cheap even at $15</Title><Msg>SHORT TERM TARGET $10+ .......2013 GUIDANCE: 40% GROWTH AND $1/SHARE NET INCOME NTWK'S OTHER CLOUD DIVISION VROOZI ALREADY EXPLODED IN REVENUES IN Q4 2012.....POTENTIAL ACQUISITION TARGET WITH CLOSE TIES TO SAP 3M SHARE FLOAT......AFTER EARNINGS PROFIT TAKING OVER.....MAGNIFICENT CHART In its updated public cloud forecast in June, Gartner estimated that IaaS was the fastest growing cloud segment with a projected GAGR of 41.7%, and exceeding a $20 billion global market by 2016. "We made a calculated decision to enter this growing market given our years of experience as a software developer, the minimal investment required, and the revenue potential given just the breadth of our current relationships," said Najeeb Ghauri, chairman and CEO of NetSol. "I am fully confident in our highly capable team, reinforced by our talented group of IT professionals, to scale the business quickly and capture a portion of this burgeoning industry, creating an additional revenue driver and further diversifying our revenue mix by geography." "What we are offering, in essence, is private cloud performance at an elastic cloud price -- giving potential customers in our target market segment the performance, flexibility, reliability, and a no-nonsense fixed pricing model that they have long desired," added Imran Haider, COO of NetSol North America and head of NetSolCloudVM. "As a growing software company ourselves, we have critical insights into the efficiency and productivity needs of NetSolCloudVM's target customer base and look forward to unveiling our new services in the coming months." ===== 4Q and FY 2012 EARNINGS SUMMARY......9/4/2012 NetSol Technologies Reported RECORD Fiscal Fourth Quarter and Year-End Results - 9/4/2012 - Fourth Quarter 2012 Revenue Surges to an all-time quarterly record of $14.3 Million on Increased License Revenues and associated maintenance and service agreements going forward - Fourth Quarter 2012 Earnings Advance Significantly to $0.25 per Diluted Share - Full Year 2012 revenues a record $38M - Full Year 2012 Earnings of $0.39/share - Company Expects Record Fiscal 2013 Annual Revenue Growing over 30% to $46 million to $49 million, With Earnings per Diluted Share Advancing to $0.80 to $1.00 - Per the CC, Company anticipates doubling revenues and net income by 2015 NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Only 3 million share float - Fast growing profitable US-based global cloud and license-based software company with 8 offices worldwide (US, China, Australia, UK, Pakistan, Singapore, Thailand, Saudi Arabia) – - Trading at 5 PE and 1 times sales – This is about 25% of sector average - Revenues are increasing at double digit rates, - Guidance calls for 30% revenue growth in 2013 - 3 consecutive quarters of profitability, - Guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013!!! - Global alliances with Mercedes Benz and SANY Corp of China. - No. 1 in China and the APAC region in its niche market of leasing and financing software - It’s Vroozi Division is a fast growing Cloud Computing Play with strong relations with SAP, ORCL, MSFT. - Vroozi’s SAP-approved smartOCI procurement search catalog software built on SaaS is being adopted rapidly. Revenues exploded in 4Q 2012 and are expected to multiply in 2013 and a big reason for the 30%+ 2013 projected revenue increase - Vroozi has been created as independent entity to potentially IPO it or sell it to a cloud-acquiring giant like SAP and others - Strong balance sheet with $1/share Cash - With every license they sell a lucrative 5-year service and maintenance agreement building strong recurrent revenues - Huge and consistent insider buying. Insiders bought over 5% of the outstanding shares since 2010 - Strong institutional investor support grew to almost 20% from 11% last year - NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc.process of testing our new message boards. Please provide your feedback so that we can optimize the user experience</Msg><Username>jasmin_jk</Username><Timestamp>1347371501572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347371632033-24</Id><Title>9/11 The Anniversary Of Bush/Cheney/Republican Congress Criminal Negligence</Title><Msg>Despite repeated warnings from the CIA Bush/Cheney/Republican Congress were caught sitting on their thumbs on 9/11/2001. They should have been tied for their criminal negligence. Osama Bin Laden continued to elude Dubya for the remainder of his presidency until Obama got him May 2, 2011.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347371632033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347372424655-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's 'I saved GM fantasy/le'</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347320906273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:48:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My ex brother in law said let the autos fail back when ronmey said it. I need to email him so he knows he gets a lot of the credit for the bailout too. After the fact, hindsight is golden, monday morning quarterbacking, and 2-3 yrs late, but hey a lot of credit is a lot of credit. Gee it isn't so long ago not to have recordings of ronmey blasting what the President DID. Anyway goes without saying now, whatever ronmey says, on anything, is all made up for the moment.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347372424655</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347372973153-26</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama, speaking earlier today in Florida, said that American manufacturers are "making products that we sell around the world, marked with three proud words: made in the U.S.A."</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347247319679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 23:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>deeldo I guess you dont ever have to show a link or in any way prove your lies do you. I for one dont like liars on this board and Im complaining to Yahoo immediatly- I/we have had enough of your crap</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347372973153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347373041375-27</Id><Topic><Title>Funny, some people want to know who Romney is?????</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1347034588036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 12:16:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I’ll lean towards Romney/Ryan all they have to do is release their specifics relating to Tax Plan...Health Plan... Medicare Plan... Spending Cuts.. they will not tell us about it why?? A supporter of his actually said you’ll know after he is elected?? .. I’m no CEO, but I know better then not to buy till I see the buisness plan and my questions are answered!! ... Romney hiding his Tax returns... now its his specifics to his policies, this is very scary Romney and Ryan are coming off way to schemeing..</Msg><Username>rvelazb500</Username><Timestamp>1347373041375</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347373303965-28</Id><Topic><Title>THAT LITTLE WHO HAS CANCER WILL BE DEAD IF ROMNEY IS ELECTED AS POTUS</Title><Username>bambilensfy</Username><Timestamp>1346943025266</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I’ll lean towards Romney/Ryan all they have to do is release their specifics relating to Tax Plan...Health Plan... Medicare Plan... Spending Cuts.. they will not tell us about it why?? A supporter of his actually said you’ll know after he is elected?? .. I’m no CEO, but I know better then not to buy till I see the buisness plan and my questions are answered!! ... Romney hiding his Tax returns... now its his specifics to his policies, this is very scary Romney and Ryan are coming off way to schemeing..</Msg><Username>rvelazb500</Username><Timestamp>1347373303965</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347373899433-29</Id><Title>Windows 8 released to Manufacturing!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Aug 10 2012 by Brandon LeBlanc Today, I am excited to announce that Windows 8 has been released to manufacturing (RTM)! This means we’ve completed the product development and testing of the product and have started handing off the final code to our OEM partners. They can now begin preparing new Windows 8 PCs and devices they’ll introduce starting with General Availability. For more on RTM, I suggest reading this blog post from Steven Sinofsky on the Building Windows 8 blog. So when will folks be able to get their hands on the new Windows 8 RTM code? People will be able get Windows 8 starting on October 26th either by upgrading for $39.99 or on a new PC or device. And if you buy an eligible Windows 7 PC today, you will be able to purchase an upgrade to Windows 8 Pro for $14.99 (U.S.) through the Windows Upgrade Offer. However, we have a number of programs that provides various audiences early access to the Windows 8 RTM code to help prepare for Windows 8 as it enters the marketplace this fall: •August 15th: Developers will be able to download the final version of Windows 8 via your MSDN subscriptions. •August 15th: IT professionals testing Windows 8 in organizations will be able to access the final version of Windows 8 through your TechNet subscriptions. •August 16th: Customers with existing Microsoft Software Assurance for Windows will be able to download Windows 8 Enterprise edition through the Volume License Service Center (VLSC), allowing you to test, pilot and begin adopting Windows 8 Enterprise within your organization. •August 16th: Microsoft Partner Network members will have access to Windows 8. •August 20th: Microsoft Action Pack Providers (MAPS) receive access to Windows 8. •September 1st: Volume License customers without Software Assurance will be able to purchase Windows 8 through Microsoft Volume License Resellers. Please note: if a program you are in is not mentioned, please be patient as dates for Windows 8 RTM code availability for other programs will be communicated when the information becomes available. For more information on what the RTM of Windows 8 means for businesses including Volume License customers, see this blog post from Erwin Visser on the Windows for your Business Blog. This post, also from Erwin, on how Windows 8 will work in your business is also a good post to read. On August 15th, developers will be able to visit the Windows Dev Center to get access to all the tools and resources they need including the final build of Visual Studio 2012 to design, build, and sell apps in the Windows Store. Keep your eyes on the Windows Store for developers blog and Windows 8 app developer blog for more information. I am super excited to see the kinds of apps developers build for Windows 8! If you have the Windows 8 Release Preview installed, you can already check out some apps developers have created for Windows 8 today. In the meantime, if you’d like to give a pre-release version of Windows 8 a test-run, feel free to download the Windows 8 Release Preview! You can also read about my personal experience with the Windows 8 Release Preview here (hint: I put it on all my PCs!). UPDATE 8/16: If you are a student and your school or institution has a DreamSpark Premium Subscription, the Program Administrator for your Subscription will have access to Windows 8 as of August 15th through MSDN Subscriber Downloads. For students with accounts in their school or institution's DreamSpark Premium ELMS WebStore we are working as quickly as possible to make this available and have a release target of August 24th. Tags: Upgrade, Developer, Developers, Partners, OEM, MSDN, RTM, TechNet, Volume License, Windows 8, Windows Dev Center, Windows Store, Windows 8 Release Preview, Release to Manufacturing, GA, General Availability, Windows Upgrade Offer, Software Assurance, Microsoft Action Pack, Product Development, Microsoft Partner Network</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347373899433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347374066547-30</Id><Topic><Title>THAT LITTLE WHO HAS CANCER WILL BE DEAD IF ROMNEY IS ELECTED AS POTUS</Title><Username>bambilensfy</Username><Timestamp>1346943025266</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Thugs Rough Up Gallup For Polls They Don’t Like By Dick Morris on September 10, 2012 The Obama Administration’s Justice Department announced, on August 22nd, that it was joining a lawsuit by a former Gallup employee and whistleblower against the Gallup Corporation for allegedly overcharging the government on polling work. The announcement comes on the heels of a confrontation between Gallup staffers and Obama strategist David Axelrod in which he accused the company of using out of date sampling methods which, he said, generated polling data negative to the president. The whistleblower’s lawsuit has been kicking around since 2009, but the Justice Department joined the suit only after the run-in between Axelrod and Gallup in April of this year. In a scene right out of a typical authoritarian regime, Fox News reports that “employees at the venerable Gallup polling firm suggested they felt threatened by Obama campaign adviser David Axelrod when he questioned the methodology of a mid-April poll showing Mitt Romney leading the president – according to internal emails published Thursday.” That poll that sent Axelrod ballistic showed Romney leading Obama 48-43 percent. The Daily Caller published e mails that started when Axelrod sent a tweet to Gallup saying the tracking poll was “saddled with some methodological problems” and directing followers to a National Journal story in which a professor suggested outdated sampling. According to the email chain titled “Axelrod vs. Gallup,” the White House in addition asked that a Gallup staffer “come over and explain our methodology,” which was apparently perceived as a subtle threat. Fox News reported that “a Gallup official said in an email he thought Axelrod’s pressure ‘sounds a little like a Godfather situation.’” Gallup refused to change its methodology to suit the White House. And the Justice Department intervention in the whistleblower suit came three months later. The whistleblower, Michael Lindley, claims that Gallup violated the False Claims Act by overcharging the federal government for its services to the U.S. Mint, the State Department and other federal agencies. The Justice Department plans to add Gallup’s work with FEMA to the list of alleged overcharges covered in the lawsuit. Lindley charged that Gallup overestimated the number of hours of field work that the government surveys would require and that it billed the feds based on the inflated estimates. According to the Washington Times, Lindley worked for the Obama campaign in 2008 as an Iowa field organizer based out of Council Bluffs, Iowa. As the election progresses, this blatant effort to influence Gallup’s data and its poll numbers is an example of Chicago political thugs at their worst.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1347374066547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347374417449-31</Id><Title>THE WINDOWS PHONE * START SCREEN IS THE BEST OF ANY PHONE</Title><Msg>GIZMODO SEZ THE WINDOWS PHONE * START SCREEN IS THE BEST OF ANY PHONE I love Windows Phone 7's start screen: neatly organized square tiles that clearly show information in real time—from emails to photos to weather to travel progress—without having to click on applications. With Windows Phone 8 Microsoft has solved my only criticism: not enough information density. And it have done so without destroying Metro's simplicity and elegance. As WP8 chief Joe Belfiore said on stage today, this is going to be the feature that users will love the most. The new Windows Phone 8 Start screen allows for the same level of customization as the tablet and desktop versions of Windows 8. It lets you move tiles around in any way you want and resize the tiles to small, medium and large sizes: • The medium size is the square one that Windows Phone 7 has now. • The small size is one quarter of that size. • The large size takes over two of the square tiles. The tiles' content is highly customizable too. Apart from specific apps' live tiles, the system would allow you to create specific contact or group tiles, with all the relevant information—emails, Facebook updates, photo uploads, etc.—displayed in real time within the tile. It will also let you add as many apps as you want to the home screen as icons. By keeping these at the small size, you can create a grid of app icons as dense as the one in the iPhone. Except that here you can also combine those with larger live tiles. Simple, elegant, fully customizable. The new sizes are also compatible with current Windows Phone 7 apps' live tiles, so no change on the part of the developer is needed—and you won't need to re-download all the apps you already have. Microsoft is also adding more live tile color options, and now you can assign individual colors to tiles; something that users tired of a uniform block of blocks were demanding. Customization and variable information density without the mess Resizable custom tiles are precisely what the Windows Phone's start screen needed to be pretty much perfect from a user experience point of view. Much better and more elegant than the static grid of badge-peppered tiny icons of iOS. Or the painful and ugly clusterf*ck of widgets that you can see in most user-customized Android screens. Unlike the competition's start screen solutions, resizable tiles give users the ability to increase information density to the maximum allowed on a phone screen while keeping it clean, comprehensive, and pretty. The start screen will provide with as much data as users want, no matter if they are beginners who like just a few important tiles or advanced users who want an information overload. And the key to avoiding any user-induced design mayhem is as obvious as keeping an organizational grid. No matter what the user does, there's no way that the start screen would look ugly or confusing. Pretty simple and effective. Microsoft says that this new start screen can tailor each phone to fit each user's lifestyle. People whose lives revolve around sports would be able to create a screen in which their favorite teams and athletes' Twitter accounts or Facebook pages are combined with real-time scoring apps, all alongside their own live tiles for mail, weather or games. Those who love social networks would be able to have their favorite friends always on screen. And so on. It's really up to the user to decide what they want their phone to be. Microsoft is just making sure that happens, in as pretty and functional manner as we've ever seen.</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347374417449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347374481330-32</Id><Topic><Title>THE WINDOWS PHONE * START SCREEN IS THE BEST OF ANY PHONE</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347374417449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:40:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I LOVE WP7 AND I LOVE MSFT.</Msg><Username>tookzgain</Username><Timestamp>1347374481330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347374755857-33</Id><Topic><Title>THE WINDOWS PHONE * START SCREEN IS THE BEST OF ANY PHONE</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347374417449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:40:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Metro is fugly, unusable shyte.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347374755857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347374863851-34</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 released to Manufacturing!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347373899433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:31:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Total garbage about to a vista.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347374863851</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347374967882-35</Id><Title>Microsoft Noki Lumia 920 has no peer in the world of phones</Title><Msg>The Nokia Lumia 920 was shown off in New York last week and after checking out all of the coverage, I can say without a doubt that I will be purchasing one as soon as they are released. The color I choose will depend on which carrier(s) in the US get the high end Lumia, but with three carrier contracts I know at least one of my carriers will get the device. Based on just what we know so far, Microsoft was very tight lipped about Windows Phone 8, I have seven main reasons I think the Lumia 920 is the device for me. Reason one: PureMotion HD+ display The Nokia Lumia 900 has a ClearBlack display and some testing earlier this year revealed that the Lumia 900 has a better outdoor display than the iPhone 4S and Galaxy S. Nokia is now taking that ClearBlack display technology to the next level and showed us all their PureMotion HD+ technology that looks to be the leading display on smartphones today. The PureMotion HD+ display automatically adjusts to sunlight glare, has those gorgeous deep blacks, provides super smooth scrolling through pixel translation speeds that are 2.5x faster than other phones, and works with fingernails, fingertips, and fingers covered with gloves. Yes, you can use your Nokia Lumia 920 in winter with gloves on without needing anything special in the gloves or any other gimmick. This new display just works and does so in nearly any environment you need. I recommend you read the white paper on the display (PDF link) to learn more about the technology. Reason two: PureView camera technology The Nokia 808 PureView sets the bar for all camera phones and really stands alone. Nokia's Lumia 920 doesn't have as much of that amazing technology, but it still has been shown to be an outstanding camera and when the device gets out of the prototype stage you can bet that reviewers will thoroughly test the camera. Nokia has an interesting white paper (PDF link) on the details of the camera technology used in the Lumia 920. As Nokia states this is the second phase in PureView technology and includes some of the core pieces such as high performance Carl Zeiss optics and powerful image processing algorithms. Low light performance is a major feature in this new camera, along with video image stabilization. Reason three: Nokia Maps Nokia Maps is the best service Nokia has ever offered and I use it on several different platforms. I love the functional offline maps and GPS navigation features in Nokia Maps on my Lumia 900 and in the Lumia 920 Nokia improves that experience by rolling in several of the utilities that you can get now on the Lumia 900. You will find offline map support with free turn-by-turn navigation, daily commute and local traffic reports, Nokia Transport for public transit schedules, and Nokia City Lens for augmented reality discovery. Reason four: Windows Phone 8 I would probably have placed this higher in my list if Microsoft would have allowed Nokia to actually show it off, but it seems Microsoft is running a bit behind on the software so manufacturers are not able to give demos yet. We have seen eight new platform improvements coming in Windows Phone 8 and there are still many details remaining to be revealed. I look forward to seeing what Nokia does with NFC since they have been using it well on their Symbian devices and accessories. The new Start screen looks fantastic for the way I use my Windows Phones and WP8 just cannot get here fast enough for me. Reason five: Qi wireless charging I know this is not a huge feature, but it is something unique that distinguishes the Nokia Lumia from other Windows Phone 8 devices. I really appreciated the convenience of Qi charging with my Droid Charge and have been hoping there would be another manufacturer using this standard so I could pull out my pad and use it again. The partnership deals with coffee shops is excellent and I hope we see more of these moving forward too. Reason six: Nokia Music Nokia Music just launched late last week for US Lumia owners and I have been using it every day since then. I am working on an article comparing it to the Zune Pass and other subscription services, but the big deal here is that it is FREE for Lumia owners. If you enjoy music, then getting a free service like this can provide significant regular savings to your smartphone ownership costs. Reason seven: Color selection Again, this may not mean much to many people, but I personally like having color options for my devices and plan to purchase the yellow Lumia 920 as long as it is supported on one of my carriers. Even if Nokia doesn't sell a ton of the yellow models, I think bold colors like this will help get people into the stores and generate conversation around the device, which is exactly what Nokia needs to do to gain marketshare. Nokia looks to be doing everything possible to help Windows Phone succeed and make sure they are around to compete in the smartphone space. I don't know what else people were expecting from Nokia or Windows Phone 8, but in my opinion they went above my expectations with unique features such as the amazing display and Qi wireless charging. Related ZDNet content Nokia brings Nokia Music to Lumia devices in the USA Hands-on testing of Nokia Lumia 920 shows Nokia didn't need to lie about PureView performance</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347374967882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347374998849-36</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remind wally what a loser he is.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347374998849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347375092765-37</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Noki Lumia 920 has no peer in the world of phones</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347374967882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is true....it's certainly unequaled in total lack of sales.....except for Kin.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347375092765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347375126540-38</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 released to Manufacturing!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347373899433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:31:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be ready phands- Microsoft is going to make life so unbearable for you liars, haters and bashers that you will rush to off yourself and join Beelzibub in the hottest circle of hell</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347375126540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:52:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347375478103-39</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Noki Lumia 920 has no peer in the world of phones</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347374967882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Nokia 920 means that all Iturd phones are or will be pieces of crap junk the kind of thing phands likes</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347375478103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347375728097-40</Id><Title>SAMSUNG STEALS MARCH ON NOKIA W?FIRST WP* PHONE</Title><Msg>Samsung steals march on Nokia with first Windows phone inShare0Share this Email Print Related NewsSamsung strikes new Note after Apple suit Wed, Aug 29 2012 Samsung sees new Galaxy Note outselling predecessor Wed, Aug 29 2012 Samsung to ship first Windows Phone 8 model in fourth-quarter Wed, Aug 29 2012 After Apple bruising, Samsung to bounce back with new Note phablet Wed, Aug 29 2012 Apple seeks quick bans on eight Samsung phones Tue, Aug 28 2012Related TopicsBusiness Traveler » Samsung Electronics UK General Manager Damian Cusick presents the new Samsung ATIV S smartphone during the Samsung Mobile Unpacked event in Berlin, August 29, 2012. Credit: Reuters/Thomas Peter By Tarmo Virki and Miyoung Kim BERLIN/SEOUL | Thu Aug 30, 2012 6:41am EDT BERLIN/SEOUL (Reuters) - Samsung Electronics became the first handset maker to announce a smartphone using Microsoft's latest mobile software, making its surprise, hurried announcement just days before the highly anticipated launch of Nokia's version. The brief announcement on Wednesday at a Berlin electronics show comes amid expectations that smartphone makers may turn increasingly to Windows devices after a U.S. jury decided many of Samsung's Google (GOOG.O) Android-based phones infringed Apple Inc (AAPL.O) patents. "It looks like a good phone, and seems like a pre-emptive announcement ahead of Nokia," said Sid Parakh, an analyst at investment firm McAdams Wright Ragen, of the Samsung phone. "Microsoft or Windows never got their best teams, never got their best designs, just because Android was doing so well. With the change in the legal environment, there's a case to be made that Samsung will likely shift some of those resources to broaden out or diversify their own exposure." Nokia (NOK1V.HE), the ailing Finnish mobile firm, once the world's leading producer of phones but now struggling to reverse losses, is due to unveil its new Lumia line of smartphones using Windows Phone 8 in New York on September 5. Samsung's new phone called ATIV S - tacked onto the end of a long news conference in Berlin that focused on other products - may elevate expectations for the Lumia. Samsung's ATIV S Windows phone sports a high-end 4.8-inch display, Corning "Gorilla" glass, and an 8-megapixel rear camera and 1.9-megapixel front-facing camera, Microsoft (MSFT.O) posted on its official blog on Wednesday. "Expectations for a 40 megapixel or possibly 20 megapixel camera model are running high. If Nokia does not unveil a monster camera handset next week, many will be disappointed," said Tero Kuittinen, analyst at mobile analytics firm Alekstra. But "this leaves Nokia plenty of room to draw a clear contrast with its upcoming announcement." Samsung's Windows-based smartphone, introduced on Wednesday, marks the first in a "big lineup of new hardware" from the South Korean company based on Microsoft's software, Microsoft executive Ben Rudolph said in a blog posting. Analysts say the introduction of Samsung's Windows phone may be designed to assuage concerns that Microsoft will favor Nokia, whose Chief Executive Stephen Elop -- himself a former senior Microsoft executive -- has staked its future on the Windows platform. "The fact Samsung was allowed to be the first to announce is Microsoft's backhanded way of letting other vendors know that Nokia is not getting special treatment," Current Analysis analyst Avi Greengart said. But Jack Gold, an independent mobile consultant who runs J. Gold Associates, argued Samsung had signalled its commitment to Windows for a while, but Nokia will remain the primary driver of the new breed of Microsoft-powered devices. "Samsung has crossed the start line first and set the bar for Nokia's launch," said Geoff Blaber, analyst at CCS Insight. STEALING A MARCH Microsoft gave a preview of its Windows Phone 8 software in June, and promised the first phones would be on the market by the autumn. Windows Phone 8 looks similar to, and is built on the same core code as Microsoft's upcoming Windows 8 operating system, but is not the same product. Windows 8, which will run on tablets and PCs, is scheduled to launch on October 26. Samsung said the ATIV phone would hit stores in the October-November period but did not give an exact start date. On Wednesday, the Korean corporation also showed off a slew of tablets using Windows 8 software and the second generation of its popular Google Android-based Galaxy Note phone-cum-tablet "phablet" in downtown Berlin. Samsung has sold some 10 million of its original Galaxy Note devices, creating a new product category which has smaller screen than tablets, but bigger than smartphones. "I am pretty confident it will even outsell its predecessor," said JK Shin, Samsung's chief of mobile business. Samsung (005930.KS) hopes the new device will take the focus away from its loss of the court case. Apple is now seeking speedy bans on the sale of eight Samsung phones, moving swiftly to turn legal victory into tangible business gain. Samsung hopes the phablet upgrade will lift any post-Apple gloom. The new version of the Note features a thinner and slightly bigger 5.5-inch screen, quad-core processor, the latest version of the Android operating system called Jellybean, and improved stylus function. "There won't be huge innovative changes in design, but the Note 2 will feature quite a few improvements and enable Samsung to carry on its strong sales momentum in the category," said Lee Sun-tae, an analyst at NH Investment &amp; Securities. "With the launch, Samsung will also be trying to turn around downbeat sentiment after the U.S. legal defeat." Apple did not include the Note and other newly unveiled Samsung products in its original lawsuit. But the company and its lawyers are expected by many legal experts to try and use last week's legal victory to go after future gadgets, especially because the jury found infringing features in Samsung phones such as pinch-and-zoom and bounce-back -- common in Android. Shares of Microsoft finished up 2 cents at $30.65 on Wednesday. (Reporting by Harro ten Wolde and Tarmo Virki in Berlin, Bill Rigby in Seattle, Miyoung Kim in Seoul; Editing by Edwin Chan and Tim Dobbyn)</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347375728097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347375797981-41</Id><Topic><Title>THAT LITTLE WHO HAS CANCER WILL BE DEAD IF ROMNEY IS ELECTED AS POTUS</Title><Username>bambilensfy</Username><Timestamp>1346943025266</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good read.. I’ll narrow it down to one question for you to give some insight.. Neither Romney/Ryan nor his advisers want to answer the questions about the Tax Plan loopholes that they say they will close because I know they understand the math: even if politics were such that in closing every loophole that targets the wealthy was a possibility, it wouldn’t offset the trillions of dollars in lost revenue that Romney’s plan would cause…That means, as a recent Tax Policy Center analysis had made very plain, that Romney would have to abandon one of his core campaign promises by either raising taxes on the middle class or blowing a huge hole in the federal budget, which do you think?</Msg><Username>rvelazb500</Username><Timestamp>1347375797981</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347375833102-42</Id><Topic><Title>THAT LITTLE WHO HAS CANCER WILL BE DEAD IF ROMNEY IS ELECTED AS POTUS</Title><Username>bambilensfy</Username><Timestamp>1346943025266</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ObamaCare will kill more than that little girl. Read it and you'll see why you're a victim of it too. What ? too lazy to read the 2600 pages that Pelosi told us to vote for it and read it later. Here, sign this and I'll tell you what you signed later.</Msg><Username>nosepickins</Username><Timestamp>1347375833102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:03:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347376167876-43</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Noki Lumia 920 has no peer in the world of phones</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347374967882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hate to give up my rotary att desk phone, does this have the new touch tone feature as well?</Msg><Username>lithiumniobate</Username><Timestamp>1347376167876</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:09:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347376322805-44</Id><Title>HTC prepares Microsoft Phone 8 phones</Title><Msg>Credit: Reuters/Pichi Chuang By Sinead Carew NEW YORK | Thu Sep 6, 2012 7:18pm EDT NEW YORK (Reuters) - HTC Corp has high hopes that Microsoft Corp software will boost its smartphone sales due to a strong new design and support from wireless service providers, according to Jason Mackenzie, HTC's president of sales and marketing. Taiwan's HTC, which derives most of its revenue from phones based on Google Inc' Android software, is currently facing a sharp sales decline as it struggles to compete with iPhone maker Apple Inc and Android rivals such as Samsung Electronics. HTC will face a stiff battle with smartphone makers Samsung and Nokia Oyj, Microsoft's main handset partner, in the market for phones using Microsoft Windows Phone 8 software. But Mackenzie said on Thursday that HTC Windows devices will stand up well against its bigger rivals. Nokia did not name any wireless service provider partners when it unveiled its flagship Windows device at a New York event on Wednesday nor did it even give any general indication of operator support. In comparison Mackenzie said his company has firm commitments from operators to sell its Windows Phone 8 devices. "I feel very strongly we've got very concrete carrier support in every region around the world including the United States and I'm not talking about just one carrier," the executive told Reuters. "Our plan is to go big on Windows 8." Mackenzie declined to give specifics on where and when the phone would be sold. But he did promise that Taipei-based HTC would come out with "a unique (industrial design) language for Windows phones, a language that can be held up by Microsoft as a flagship." In comparison, he said, other Windows phones makers who also produce Android devices "haven't typically given their A plus designs to Windows phones." "They've been designating those to Android," he said. While Android phones generate the bulk of HTC's revenue today, Mackenzie said it would like to see "a more balanced portfolio" in terms of Android and Windows revenue. "That wouldn't mean we'd want to dial back on Android," he said. "We want to grow Android and grow Windows at the same time." However, this could be a tough job. While HTC's One-branded Android phones unveiled earlier this year have been enjoying good reviews by analysts and tech blogs, this has not been reflected in its sales. After its profit fell by more than half in the second quarter, HTC on Aug 3 forecast a third-quarter revenue decline of as much as 23 percent, which was much worse than analysts had feared. Earlier on Thursday HTC said its August sales were weaker than its July sales. But Mackenzie said that he sees HTC's current problems as "temporary" and that he hopes to turn the company's fortunes around with better marketing of its brand and its devices. "We have to get more efficient with the dollars that we're spending and turn every dollar into five," he said, while promising to use social media and online advertising to greater effect in its marketing. "It's about being more bold."</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347376322805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347378415472-45</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Noki Lumia 920 has no peer in the world of phones</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347374967882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rotary desk phone?? then the Iturd is for you- that will get you about half way to the current gen of phones</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347378415472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347379059150-46</Id><Topic><Title>9/11 The Anniversary Of Bush/Cheney/Republican Congress Criminal Negligence</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347371632033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:53:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pakistani Doctor Who Helped on Bin Laden Raid Describes 'Brutal' Torture By John Hudson | The Atlantic Wire – 2 hrs 22 mins ago Pakistani Doctor Who Helped on Bin Laden Raid Describes 'Brutal' TortureEnlarge Photo The imprisoned Pakistani doctor who helped the CIA find Osama bin Laden's compound, Dr. Shakil Afridi, managed to make a phone call to Fox News' Dominic Di-Natale and describe the brutal tortue he says he's been subject to since being arrested for treason last year. He described how during his own interrogation, in which he was tortured with cigarette burns and electric shocks, ISI officers attacked him for assisting the U.S ... “My clothes were removed and I was forced by a major to wear old dirty torn rags of an army conductor. It was difficult to eat food. I had to bend down on my knees to eat with only my mouth, like a dog. I sat on the floor.” He was blindfolded for eight months and handcuffed with his hands behind his back for 12 months, he says. His treatment has left a debilitating effect on his eyesight and limbs. There's no mention of how Afridi managed to conduct the interview in the Fox piece, but the BBC reports that Pakistani prison officials "were taken by surprise by reports of the interview" and "did not rule out that a phone could have been smuggled into his cell." Regardless, on the eleventh anniversary of 9/11, Afridi picked the perfect time to reach out to the American public, who are pretty much his only shot for an early release for his 33-year prison sentence. Afridi expressed love for America and claimed Pakistan's ISI intelligence agency sees the U.S. as its "worst enemy": “I tried to argue that America was Pakistan’s biggest supporter – billions and billions of dollars in aid, social and military assistance -- but all they said was, ‘These are our worst enemies. You helped our enemies.’” ... Afridi told Fox News he helped the CIA out of love for the U.S., and swore that he would help America again despite suffering crippling torture and psychological abuse during the 12 months he was held by Pakistan’s spy agency but not if Obama is president. Afridi's script certainly plays into the narrative that the White House and Congress have recited that Afridi is a hero for helping the U.S. find bin Laden. One thing to consider, however, is that Afridi, by his own admission, had no idea that he was helping find Osama bin Laden when he operated a fake vaccination campaign for the CIA. That scheme attempted to secretly collect DNA evidence from local Abbottabad residents in the hope of finding bin Laden's DNA and sending that information to the CIA. Someone willing to deceive his own patients in order to help a foreign spy agency catch an unknown person should certainly raise suspicions about Afridi's character, especially given previous allegations of corruption and quackery on his part. Still, the CIA, and by extension the U.S., hasn't forgotten how he helped them and continues to push for his release. Clearly, in the spy business, personal foibles don't always count against you.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1347379059150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347379269573-47</Id><Topic><Title>9/11 The Anniversary Of Bush/Cheney/Republican Congress Criminal Negligence</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347371632033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:53:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Americans Pause on September 11 to Remember... BIDEN: A 'bittersweet' moment... NEW YORK TIMES goes after Bush on 11th anniversary of attacks... NBC's 'TODAY' Show Skips Moment Of Silence For Kardashian Interview...</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1347379269573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347381270144-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's 'I saved GM fantasy/le'</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347320906273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:48:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moody's set to downgrade US without budget deal ASSOCIATED PRESS Last Updated: 12:04 PM, September 11, 2012 Posted: 10:08 AM, September 11, 2012 The US government's debt rating could be heading for the "fiscal cliff" along with the federal budget. Moody's Investors Service on Tuesday said it would likely cut its "Aaa" rating on US government debt, probably by one notch, if budget negotiations fail. A year ago, Moody's cut its outlook on US debt to "negative," which acts as a warning that it might downgrade the rating</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1347381270144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347384459289-49</Id><Topic><Title>Let me explain something to you 'tax the rich' lefties, a business primer</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347114542022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just because something is published does not make it a fact, most if not all items published on right wing blogs about Pres Obama are lies not facts. The us govt should make around 800 million on that give away with interest and dividends</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1347384459289</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347384472409-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obama poll numbers fade after convention bounce as people sober up</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347384287147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:24:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>under hy</Msg><Username>watkinsdavidrobert</Username><Timestamp>1347384472409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347384751417-51</Id><Topic><Title>Romney - New Tax Return Excuse</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1347382856446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's such a bad one he needs to etch a sketch asap. He already released one return, his dada said to release 12 yrs, and if you are truly an anonymous giver, you don't write it down on your return. You give anonymously like your faith tells you, AND DON'T EXPECT THE GOVT TO REIMBURSE YOU. .</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347384751417</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347384807902-52</Id><Title>My alter ego is worked up today due to the market increasing ya could say he is losing his shorts... And this reminds him of his past business that he drove into the ground literally. So I post more when irritated and the yahoo board has to put up with it cuz its a free country.</Title><Msg>yep thats it</Msg><Username>watkinsdavidrobert</Username><Timestamp>1347384807902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347386129032-53</Id><Topic><Title>Let Me Explain The Supply Side Scam</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347319860649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The theory goes like this. If you lower taxes on the wealthy (but not the middle class) they will buy things, like yachts and mansions. Then companies that make yachts have to hire more people. heh...heh...heh...heh...good one! Dubya cut taxes over 11 years ago. We are already operating under a supply side economy right here and now. How did that work out? NOT TOO GOOD!</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347386129032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347386280105-54</Id><Topic><Title>Let me explain something to you 'tax the rich' lefties, a business primer</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347114542022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama's Campaign Trashes '2016: Obama's America' 9:49 AM PDT 9/11/2012 by Paul Bond share 2016: Obama's America Poster - H 2012 The film, which its marketers dubbed, “the movie the White House doesn’t want you to see,” was on 2017 screens this weekend and is expected to be on the same number next weekend. For good measure, the website entry also bashes some of Obama’s harshest critics: Tea Partiers. Time to go see the movie.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1347386280105</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347386438775-55</Id><Title>Grover Norquist Controlled House Will Never Fix The Deficit. The fiscal cliff is loominmg but the House will never agree to a tax increase.</Title><Msg>The K*0*c*h Bros control the House Republicans thru Grover Norquist. We will go over the fiscal cliff because Grover Norquist will never allow a tax increase.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347386438775</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347386847353-56</Id><Title>Norquist, Karl Rove, Bush, The K*0*c*h Bros</Title><Msg>Norquist cemented his influence by forging an early alliance with Karl Rove and setting himself up as a gatekeeper to George W. Bush's inner circle. Then, after Obama was elected, this ultimate Washington insider positioned himself as a leader of the anti-establishment Tea Party, complete with financial support from the billionaire K*0*ch brothers. "These Tea Party people, in effect, take their orders from him," says Bruce Bartlett, an architect of the Reagan tax cuts. "He decides: This is a permissible tax action, or this is not a permissible tax action. And of course, anything that cuts taxes is per se OK."</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347386847353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347387317750-57</Id><Topic><Title>Romney - New Tax Return Excuse</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1347382856446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's nuts newbie. You are REIMBURSED for charitable contributions, if you can itemize of course, busyniss genyiss. Robme is not anonymous anymore when he sends in his return with his charitable deductions, AND HIS NAME IS ON THE RETURN. Get it? No? Keep trying. Bring back ghosanaon to help you. Do you remember that was the topic? Robme claiming he can't show his return for religious, anonymity of giving, reasons?? You know how stupid that is to say, stop defending him.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347387317750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347387881541-58</Id><Title>Documents Show Bush Ignored Numerous Warnings Prior to 9/11 Attack</Title><Msg>wwwDOTopposingviewsDOTcom/i/politics/foreign-policy/war-terror/new-gov-documents-show-president-bush-ignored-numerous-warnings?utm_source=OV+Newsletter+List+2&amp;utm_campaign=2aa73b26b9-OV_Newsletter_September_119_11_2012&amp;utm_medium=email Well, well, well.....the rethuglican #$%$ups just get worse..... Two weeks ago at the Republican National Convention, former Bush administration National Security Advisor Condi Rice attacked the Obama administration for not taking action in Syria. However, Rice did not mention how in 2001 the Bush White House failed to prevent terrorist attacks from Osama bin Laden, despite being warned numerous times. It has already been made public that Clinton/Bush anti-terrorism advisor Richard Clarke gave the Bush White House a briefing on August 6, 2001 with the now-infamous heading 'Bin Laden Determined to Strike in the U.S.' Now, the New York Times reports there were actually a series of warnings between May and August of 2001, which the Bush administration ignored. On May 1, 2001, the Bush White House was told by the CIA that "a group presently in the United States" was planning a terrorist attack, reports the Daily Mail. On June 22, 2001, the Bush White House was told an Al Qaeda attack could be "imminent." However, the neoconservatives in the Pentagon told the Bush White House that the CIA had been fooled into believing bin Laden was preparing an attack to distract the U.S. from Saddam Hussein. In response, the CIA prepared a brief on June 29, 2001 with over a page of evidence, including an interview with a journalist, in which aides to Bin Laden warned of an upcoming attack. That paper also said: "The U.S. is not the target of a disinformation campaign by Osama bin Laden." The CIA sent the Bush White House another warning on July 1, 2001 which said the terrorist attack had been delayed, but would soon take place. President Bush was told on July 24 that the attack was still being prepared, but had been postponed by a few months. President Bush requested a more detailed analysis of al Qaeda, which was the famous briefing created by Richard Clarke and given to the Bush White House on August 6, 2001. Following 9/11, the Bush White House said it had never been told when or where the attacks would take place. Amazingly, National Security Advisor Condi Rice wrote a March 22, 2004 column in the Washington Post that said: “No al-Qaeda threat was turned over to the new administration.”</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347387881541</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347387941121-59</Id><Topic><Title>Obama poll numbers fade after convention bounce as people sober up</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347384287147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:24:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah but are you sobering up Newbie? According to your recent theory where lower polls after the conventions mean victory later for the lower candidate, this means Obama is now gaining on Robme. Obama is gaining, yippee. IF your yapping is correct, which of course it is only but another banned poster lie from you.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347387941121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347388441281-60</Id><Topic><Title>Obama poll numbers fade after convention bounce as people sober up</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347384287147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:24:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bin Laden was killed thanks to intel collected at GITMO that OblameO wanted to close. By methods that OblameO campaigned against in 2008. He was killed by Seal Team 6 (God Bless), of which OblameO wanted to court marshall 3 of them. The same Seal Team the dumacrats campaigned in 2008 calling them "Cheney's assassins" and "baby killers"</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1347388441281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347389256438-61</Id><Topic><Title>Impeachment shows Clinton chasing skirts while 9/11 planned on his watch</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347389021262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:43:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBL started planing to attack the US back in 1983 after the US president turned tail and ran from Beirut</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1347389256438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347389446399-62</Id><Title>MY DAD SAYS WINDOWS 8 SUCKS</Title><Msg>He does not like it one bit. Windows 8 could be another disaster like VISTA.</Msg><Username>bambilensfy</Username><Timestamp>1347389446399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347389464522-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama poll numbers fade after convention bounce as people sober up</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347384287147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:24:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For a republican tracking firm like Rasmussen to put Pres Obama ahead is in itself very significant.</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1347389464522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347390422600-64</Id><Topic><Title>MY DAD SAYS WINDOWS 8 SUCKS</Title><Username>bambilensfy</Username><Timestamp>1347389446399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's far worse than vista.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347390422600</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:07:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347390909716-65</Id><Topic><Title>Obama poll numbers fade after convention bounce as people sober up</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347384287147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:24:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dem. governor takes on Obama Comments (0) By CHARLES MAHTESIAN | 9/11/12 3:00 PM EDT West Virginia Democratic Gov. Earl Ray Tomblin isn’t just putting some distance between his campaign and President Obama: He’s gone on the attack. In his first television ad, a 30-second spot titled “Coal Town,” Tomblin frames his efforts as a fight against the White House. “Since the day I became governor, I fought the Obama administration’s war on coal,” he says in the 30-second spot. “I took them to court and we won. I won’t let anyone push us around.” Given Obama’s low standing in West Virginia – a felon won 41 percent of the Democratic primary vote against him in May – Tomblin’s approach is a necessary one. Tomblin not only has to get distance from his party's president, he needs to inoculate himself against attacks from GOP opponent Bill Maloney, who frequently refers to the “Obama-Tomblin economy” and is running Obama-themed ads. In Maloney’s latest spot, a female character ends an ad by saying, “Let’s send a message to Obama.”</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1347390909716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347391074024-66</Id><Topic><Title>9/11 The Anniversary Of Bush/Cheney/Republican Congress Criminal Negligence</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347371632033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:53:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Despite repeated warnings from the CIA Bush/Cheney/Republican Congress were caught sitting on their thumbs on 9/11/2001. They should have been tried for their criminal negligence.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347391074024</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347391290517-67</Id><Topic><Title>Documents Show Bush Ignored Numerous Warnings Prior to 9/11 Attack</Title><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347387881541</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:24:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ooooohhhhh...the tealiban are all hoping this will go away....</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347391290517</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347394414050-68</Id><Topic><Title>Romney - New Tax Return Excuse</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1347382856446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, you are reimbursed the second you sign and send in the return. Reimbursement doesn't have to mean a check in the mail, it is a term. You owe more, but thanks to your church, you pay less, the second you apply your anonymous donation. Which of course it is no longer really anonymous, contrary to your defend robme's excuses at all costs attitude. NO one thinks a refund is a gift from the government but rather as a reimbursement for overpayment.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347394414050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347394607759-69</Id><Title>Romney's economic advisers are the old bush/ch*n*y advisers.</Title><Msg>Really, is anyone but a #$%$ voting for republicans???? Does anyone really want to go back to the bush years with two more wars, more trillions stolen by republicans, more jobs outsourced to china, india, mexico, brazil???? Bush's last months in office - 500,000 jobs lost each month. Obama has been steadily improving job creation in spite of republican obstructionism and filibusters and dedicated to making America fail. ROMNEY = MORE TRICKLE DOWN POVERTY!!</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347394607759</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:16:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347395449685-70</Id><Title>Romney still thinks Krushchov is still in power</Title><Msg>Soviets being our #1 enemy and all like he says</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347395449685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347395525961-71</Id><Topic><Title>Let me explain something to you 'tax the rich' lefties, a business primer</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347114542022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's media in action: NBC's 'Today' skips 9/11 moment for Kardashian (AP) – 57 minutes ago NEW YORK (AP) — Kardashian family matriarch Kris Jenner talked about her breast augmentation on NBC's "Today" show at the same time other news outlets were airing the solemn commemoration of the first plane striking New York's World Trade Center 11 years ago.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1347395525961</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347395951820-72</Id><Title>Romney likely to start nuclear war with the British.</Title><Msg>havv havv</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347395951820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:39:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347396015179-73</Id><Title>Stock Alert issued on (MSFT)</Title><Msg>A new technical analysis tutorial and stock alert has been issued on (MSFT) Watch the video on YouTube: youtu.be/P0lMbBMMaiw</Msg><Username>stockchump1</Username><Timestamp>1347396015179</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347396281490-74</Id><Topic><Title>Documents Show Bush Ignored Numerous Warnings Prior to 9/11 Attack</Title><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347387881541</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:24:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GoPtards won't touch this....</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347396281490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347396350437-75</Id><Topic><Title>Romney - New Tax Return Excuse</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1347382856446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But what's romney's excuse now, since that one doesn't fly well. He's hiding it so bad even he can't hide the guilt of it with his plastic look.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347396350437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:45:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347397397320-76</Id><Title>Total Android shipments since 2008 to hit 1 billion mark</Title><Msg>newsDOTcnetDOTcom/8301-1035_3-57510710-94/total-android-shipments-since-2008-to-hit-1-billion-mark/?part=rss&amp;subj=news&amp;tag=title Windoze phone? Oh, yeah....NOT QUOTED. Android device shipments are poised to pass the 1 billion unit mark in 2013, according to projections by IHS. IHS said that global unit shipments of Android phones will be 451 million in 2013, up from 357 million in 2012. Cumulative shipments by the end of 2013 will be 1.1 billion since the first Android device shipped in 2008. For comparison, Apple's cumulative iPhone shipments will be 527 million in 2013 and hit the 1 billion mark in 2015.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347397397320</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 17:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347397409894-77</Id><Topic><Title>Romney - New Tax Return Excuse</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1347382856446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>craper try getting out a little to show what an insignicant little pea brain you are.. I climed up to the Great Wall today. Did you get out of you housecoat?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1347397409894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 17:03:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347398725246-78</Id><Topic><Title>Romney - New Tax Return Excuse</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1347382856446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a man does for his recognized church is none of the State's or others business. Then the man does not tell his donation through legally signed document, to the State, or get a rebate, reimbursement, refund, or other discount of tax due funds from the State.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1347398725246</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 17:25:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347402687502-79</Id><Topic><Title>Impeachment shows Clinton chasing skirts while 9/11 planned on his watch</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347389021262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:43:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look up “ The lasting impact of 1983 Beirut attack” Clinton did not want a show trial where bin Laden could get off on all charges he did task the CIA to take bin Laden out try as they might they could not do it. Tell me did Paul Ryan run a marathon in under 3 hours? How much of Obama stimulus did Paul run through maybe it just seemed like a marathon.</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1347402687502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347407011216-80</Id><Topic><Title>Total Android shipments since 2008 to hit 1 billion mark</Title><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347397397320</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 17:03:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a joke- every droid;turd OS is down loaded 4-5 times before the droid turd becomes a boat ancher and that is because they are free and the user didnt like the last one so they keep trying another version- all it means is that sux and droid are crap from prehistoric times and will soon meet their demise with the advent of Microsoft phone 8- tough titty there phands</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347407011216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347407126828-81</Id><Topic><Title>I just let Corzine go who stole $1.6B from investor accounts. Its like Scottrade or TD Americtrade and the CEO just stole your money</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347405077959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And quit covering for that war criminal Cheney.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347407126828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347407327764-82</Id><Topic><Title>I just let Corzine go who stole $1.6B from investor accounts. Its like Scottrade or TD Americtrade and the CEO just stole your money</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347405077959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason the RWNJs are convinced Corzine is guilty of absconding with the cash register before his company went bankrupt is because thats exactly what a republican crook would do and they just cant understand why Corzine wouldnt do the same thing</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347407327764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:48:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347407594013-83</Id><Topic><Title>Impeachment shows Clinton chasing skirts while 9/11 planned on his watch</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347389021262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:43:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>liberals have given you pukes and baggers and flat earthers things like the emancipation proclamation and the 13th amendment, womens sufferage, etc etc Without the liberlals the pukes would still be picking cotton, riding in the back of the bus and their wives would still be poisonin them because they couldnt get the vote</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347407594013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347408734040-84</Id><Title>Rasmussen: Obama defeats Romney 48 / 44</Title><Msg>And Romney is still stonewalling on his tax returns, all because he thought it was "clever" to evade all Federal income and capital gains taxes for ten years straight.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347408734040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347409727053-85</Id><Title>Evidence piles up that Bush administration got many pre-9/11 warnings</Title><Msg>By Robert Windrem NBC News On the 11th anniversary of the worst terrorist attack on U.S. soil, there is mounting evidence that the Bush administration received more intelligence warnings than previously known prior to the Sept. 11 attacks that killed nearly 3,000.</Msg><Username>rush_limpballs_warning</Username><Timestamp>1347409727053</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347410055349-86</Id><Topic><Title>I just let Corzine go who stole $1.6B from investor accounts. Its like Scottrade or TD Americtrade and the CEO just stole your money</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347405077959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is KNOWN is that he gambled with money not his, a felony This statement is the product of paranoid schizophrenia and the intense paranoia generated by this kind of psychosis. This is the kind of psychotic lie old hawfecies is noted for and everybody can simply ignore his lie</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347410055349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347410133206-87</Id><Topic><Title>I just let Corzine go who stole $1.6B from investor accounts. Its like Scottrade or TD Americtrade and the CEO just stole your money</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347405077959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is KNOWN is that he gambled with money not his, a felony This statement is the product of paranoid schizophrenia and the intense paranoia generated by this kind of psychosis. This is the kind of psychotic lie old hawfaecies is noted for and everybody can simply ignore his lie</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347410133206</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347410996641-88</Id><Title>How Sheldon Adelson Could Save $2.3B Under Romney Tax Plan</Title><Msg>Assuming Romney's tax reform proposals were put into place, the billionarie casino magnate Adelson potentially stands to receive tax cuts adding up to more than $2 billion in savings. Geee I wonder why Adelson vows to donate $100M to Romney's campaign.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347410996641</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347411010481-89</Id><Title>Musllim obama kills 22 Navy SEALS in ancient Chinook helicopter</Title><Msg>Where's the outrage from the lame stream media? Why no outcry from the commie leftists? Liberals have NO regard for human life, all the parasites care about is power and freebies. After the copter was shot down by obama's Musllim brothers some apache helicopters zeroed in on the source of the rocket launcher that killed the Americans and were ready to fire but because of OBAMA'S ORDERS NOT TO RETURN FIRE they had to sit idly by and let the vermin escape. The POS Kenyan has more innocent blood on his hands than chairman Mao and Pol Pott and no one seems to care, they just keep chanting his evvil demonick name,..... HUSSEIN, HUSSEIN, HUSSEIN. Rot in helll the loser liberal anti American commie lot of'ya.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1347411010481</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347411384246-90</Id><Topic><Title>Rasmussen: Obama defeats Romney 48 / 44</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1347408734040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:12:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's six. And you know it.</Msg><Username>nd1005</Username><Timestamp>1347411384246</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:56:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347411386566-91</Id><Topic><Title>Evidence piles up that Bush administration got many pre-9/11 warnings</Title><Username>rush_limpballs_warning</Username><Timestamp>1347409727053</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:28:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kurt Eichenwald, a former New York Times reporter, wrote in an op-ed piece in Tuesday’s newspaper about a number of previously unknown warnings relayed to the White House by U.S. intelligence in the weeks and months prior to the attacks. Eichenwald wrote of the warnings in his new book, “500 Days: Secrets and Lies in the Terror Wars.” -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Follow Open Channel on Twitter and Facebook. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Advertise | AdChoices And former US intelligence officials say there were even more warnings, pointing to a little noticed section of George Tenet’s memoir, “At the Center of the Storm.”</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347411386566</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347411490607-92</Id><Title>Musllim lubber Bush bought the chopper which killed the Navy SEALS</Title><Msg>Why - he got a deal and got it cheap from the contractor- just goes to show you how vicious, mean, and irresponsible the pukes, RWNJs, baggers and flat earthers are- No doubt it is related to Bush's refusal to take one of the many chances he had to kill OBL. There was oil and money involved and he had that special relationship with OBL</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1347411490607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347415810572-93</Id><Topic><Title>White House declines Netanyahu request to meet with Obama</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1347410704796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:45:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES, PUNK FROM GHIGAGO. ROMNEY 2012</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1347415810572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347416111377-94</Id><Title>Barrack prefers selling Obamanure to meeting with Netanyahu</Title><Msg>What a hoax of a president! Empty suit!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347416111377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:15:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347416384155-95</Id><Title>Hussein pushing Obamanure while US flag being burnt in Egypt embassy!</Title><Msg>What an empty suit!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347416384155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:19:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347416807035-96</Id><Title>Under Obamanure's watch, "..most troubling is the conclusion that since 2008, the United States has slid from No. 1 in the world in "global competitiveness" to No. 7 this year. Out-ranking America are: Switzerland, Singapore, Finland, Sweden, the Netherlands and Germany."</Title><Msg>Thanks to Hussein and all those supportive Obamanurists.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347416807035</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347417240404-97</Id><Title>Chicago's Teacher Mafia at it again! Want more benefits in one of the worst school systems in USA!</Title><Msg>Here is the Obamanure plan for the country!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347417240404</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:34:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347417326596-98</Id><Topic><Title>Hussein pushing Obamanure while US flag being burnt in Egypt embassy!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347416384155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:19:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHAT a PUNK from CHIGAGO ????</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1347417326596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347417386637-99</Id><Title>Obamanure splats, doesn't bounce, just spreads. Polls are dead even now!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347417386637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347417490433-100</Id><Title>Voters bringing shovels in November. The Obamanure will be shoveled away!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347417490433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347417544765-101</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton defies history for Party line</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1347416244186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've been waiting almost 4 years for Obama to "do something". Time is running out for Obama. See you at the polls on Nov 6!</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1347417544765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347417622278-102</Id><Topic><Title>How Sheldon Adelson Could Save $2.3B Under Romney Tax Plan</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1347410996641</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:49:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney will be a puppet president with big money pulling the strings. Romney won't be the first nor the last Republican that sucks the weeners of billionaires.</Msg><Username>rush_limpballs_warning</Username><Timestamp>1347417622278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347417684072-103</Id><Topic><Title>Total Android shipments since 2008 to hit 1 billion mark</Title><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1347397397320</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 17:03:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 Phone is already dead on arrival. Nokia shares are hitting record lows. Nobody is impressed by the Lumina 920/820.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1347417684072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347417896858-104</Id><Title>Dumb and Dumber, Dubya and Romney</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney calls Russia 'geopolitical adversary' Republicans dangerously incompetent.</Msg><Username>rush_limpballs_warning</Username><Timestamp>1347417896858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347418706148-105</Id><Title>Obamanure administration apologies for free speech: "U.S. Embassy 'Condemns the Continuing Efforts by Misguided Individuals to Hurt the Religious Feelings of Muslims'."</Title><Msg>Four more years! Four more years! Four more years!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347418706148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347418880706-106</Id><Title>Obamanue's administration view on any religion except for Catholics in USA: "Respect for religious beliefs is a cornerstone of American democracy. "</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347418880706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 23:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>