<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345439700000-1</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamanuric!</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345439700000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 01:15:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345457527000-2</Id><Title>EPA to force 100 power plants to close</Title><Msg>due to strict new rules on emmissions of coal plants. (One emission gas is what you breath out called carbon dioxide which vegetation consumes) Expect more blackouts and expensive power bills. Many power plants in Maryland, Ohio, and Pennsylvania will be affected. The Republicans in the Democrat majority Senate, voted to block the EPA rules, but they were outnumbered. http://www.altoonamirror.com/page/content.detail/id/561888/Senate-vote-zaps-coal-plants.html</Msg><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457527000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345457606000-3</Id><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Msg>due to strict new rules on emmissions of coal plants. (One emission gas is what you breath out called carbon dioxide which vegetation consumes) Expect more blackouts and expensive power bills. The Republicans in the Democrat majority Senate, voted to block the EPA rules, but they were outnumbered. http://www.altoonamirror.com/page/content.detail/id/561888/Senate-vote-zaps-coal-plants.html</Msg><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345457896000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Economist confirms: Freddie and Fannie the "fuel" for financial crisis</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345417815000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AEI stooge and bankster board member can't gloss over the simple facts: " The European financial sector is also in dire need of reform. New regulations should be put in place that make banking collapse less likely, most importantly through the creation of credible means of measuring bank risks and requiring capital and liquidity commensurate with those risks. Europe should also put in place policies that transparently and predictably allocate authority across different national regulators in the event of a bank's collapse. Without a credible plan for resolving a large global bank crisis, politicians will tend to prefer bailouts as a means of avoiding unpredictable financial chaos." The ability to foist off the fraudulent paper generated worldwide by a corrupted ratings for the highest bidder process onto National entities and use the liquidity obtained by burdening the taxpayer, once again worldwide, with the costs of further even more speculative gambles into hokey derivatives caused the bankster meltdown. "Policymakers must learn that the "too-big-to-fail" problem is both dangerous and avoidable, and that choosing not to bail out banks is a viable option. Politicians today are frightened of transparency in the recognition of bank losses and are often unwilling to close insolvent banks out of a fear of "systemic risk." However, it is only by credibly recognizing banking-system losses that governments can put an end to uncertainties in the financial market." Iceland "credibly recognized" banking system losses by assigning them to the banksters who caused them, Ireland and Greece nationalized the losses and are suffering the consequences. The U.S. partly nationalized the losses, leaving you sitting in your tin shack snarling B.S. about how it's all the fault of poor black people, Nancy Pelosi and the Hawaiian devil baby. China does fine because they still execute financial frauds there.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345457896000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:18:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345459824000-5</Id><Title>Why does the social security admin need hollow point ammo?</Title><Msg>You dont use hollow points as training rounds! Wednesday, August 15, 2012 source - infowars First it was the Department of Homeland Security, then it was the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, and now the Social Security Administration is set to purchase 174,000 rounds of hollow point bullets that will be delivered to 41 locations across the country. A solicitation posted by the SSA on the FedBizOpps website asks for contractors to supply 174,000 rounds of “.357 Sig 125 grain bonded jacketed hollow point pistol ammunition.” An online ammunition retailer describes the bullets as suitable “for peak performance rivaling and sometimes surpassing handloads in many guns,” noting that the ammo is “a great personal defense bullet.” The synopsis to the solicitation adds that the ammunition is to be shipped to 41 locations within 60 days of purchase.</Msg><Username>gkcreamcheese</Username><Timestamp>1345459824000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345460209000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcraper, did the debt go up $5.35T on</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345308230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"bush left an economy that contracted 9% instead of the 3% that he promised when asking for $700 billion to bail out his 'have-more' constiuentcy" "bush misunderestimated job losses by more than five million in the private sector, leaving 8 million out of work instead of the 3 million he promised" "bush's cronies continued to eliminate tax revenues costing police, firefighters and teachers to be laid off in droves immensely pleasing the anarchist teabagger confederates and leaving the country a morass of backward lap drooling dolts like hawcreek, gibbering about how it's all the kenyan usurper"s fault and demanding to see his high school transcripts"</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345460209000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345460969000-7</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The EPA since 2009 has created a record number of new regulations to choke businesses and caused all sorts of industry to close in the USA and move overseas. Then Obama and the puppet media have the nerve to blame Bush and the rich. Obama and his 45 tsars need to be in prison.</Msg><Username>gkcreamcheese</Username><Timestamp>1345460969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 07:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345464811000-8</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not bad. I will have to give you a point for that one. However the article does contain this tidbit. ""But I hasten to add that even if you'd had these government housing subsidies, they alone were not enough to cause the crisis. Had prudential regulation functioned properly for Fannie and Freddie and for the banks, you wouldn't have had this crisis, even with the mortgage risk subsidies"" His point is valid but he still is not very clear as to whether or not the crisis outgrew fan and fred like most economists believe.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345464811000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345468268000-9</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the planet is rendered uninhabitable in the quest by the super rich for more profits at any cost, nothing else will matter....</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1345468268000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345468812000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Corpora (MSFT ) ) you will get corrected</Title><Username>crystalenglish214</Username><Timestamp>1345464213000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BEWARE - SPAM MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1345468812000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345468860000-11</Id><Topic><Title>I can't lose</Title><Username>laviniatmj289</Username><Timestamp>1345392199000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:03:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BEWARE - SPAM MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1345468860000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345469357000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why does the social security admin need hollow point ammo?</Title><Username>gkcreamcheese</Username><Timestamp>1345459824000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets see the link and lets see how hard you had to lie to come up with your BS</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345469357000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345469550000-13</Id><Topic><Title>EPA to force 100 power plants to close</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457527000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:12:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sh.tty dirty coal fired utilities to go?? Good deal - they can be replaced with those new GE Natural gas turbines- that are so efficient and since they are giving Natural gas away these days for free</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345469550000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345469627000-14</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;Expect more blackouts and expensive power bills. &gt;&gt; expect more natural gas fired plants and lower power bills</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345469627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470401000-15</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Great News" Possibly we all will be able to breath the air again safely and we might even stop melting the polar caps.</Msg><Username>jcbrowns</Username><Timestamp>1345470401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:46:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470407000-16</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bernie Madoff was a crook- that means that he was a republican- like all crooks seem to be</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345470407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470451000-17</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great news for GE too who will likely build the replacement turbines</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345470451000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470633000-18</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Altho Bernies wife was a liberal and a philanthropist- Bernie was a crook and that makes him a Republican. Virtually all crooks are Republicans If Mother Theresa was found to be a Republican you could then bet your bottom dollar that she was a crook</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345470633000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:50:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470721000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Humongous Truism: Bush Fcuked Us But Good!</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345406046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:54:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;On 9/11/2001, the Bush/Cheney Administration along with the Republican controlled Congress got caught flatfooted when Al Qaeda slipped it to them, killing thousands of Americans. To cover for their criminal negligence the Republican Party Boys started two unfunded, unpaid-for, wars on the credit card. The unfunded, unpaid-for,wars continue to create debt to this day. Then there were the Bush Tax cuts that threw gasoline on the deficit fire. To cap off their list of accomplishments the Republican Party Boys deregulated the banks and refused to enforce strict loan adminstration standards which created a bank failure, a housing collapse, and a global financial melt-down.&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt; THOSE REPUBLICAN DIRTYBASTARDS</Msg><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345470721000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470797000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Humongous Truism: Bush Fcuked Us But Good!</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345406046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:54:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;THOSE REPUBLICAN DIRTYBASTARDS &gt;&gt; Quad Errat Demonstratum</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345470797000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470867000-21</Id><Topic><Title>The current monetary system will start to collapse in 2013 .......</Title><Username>sky_walker618</Username><Timestamp>1345410473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:07:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The monetary system collapse will have spill-over effect over the short-term, i.e. within two years.</Msg><Username>sky_walker616</Username><Timestamp>1345470867000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:54:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345471394000-22</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone alone Bigger than all of MSFT</Title><Username>obadidoss</Username><Timestamp>1345419713000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's very impressive. Of course, in due time, Apple will face the same problems Microsoft faces. For example, how to maintain its revenue stream when the market is saturated and the product has every feature that can reasonably be piled onto it, and how to fend off similar products by other vendors, and how to adapt to the *next* generation.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345471394000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345471804000-23</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fannie and Freddie had 50% of the market at the time. It set industry standards for underwriting. With increase targets for subprime loans they pushed down the standards for mortgages they would purchase, that becomes the industry standard whether or not Fannie/Freddie actually purchase the loans because investors want the option to sell to them. The policy to push loans to low income borrowers allowed banks to make money on those loans so they did but that was not the driver of the lower standards. Government policy to help the poor only set them up to fail, now have a home that is underwater or a foreclosure and bankruptcy on their credit.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345471804000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345471837000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Humongous Truism: Bush Fcuked Us But Good!</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345406046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:54:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;why don't you blame Clinton for not taking Obama out under his watch?&lt; ??? Take the future president out where? On a date? moron</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1345471837000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345471923000-25</Id><Topic><Title>EPA to force 100 power plants to close</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457527000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:12:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. Your article says it is because of mercury emissions. mercury is not just a car's name. 2. Your article says the NYT reported possibly up to 100 of 500 coal fired plants could shut down due to epa regs and low natural gas prices. 3. you breathe in air and use the oxygen, you breathe out air that has more co2 than you breathed in. If you breathe in too much co2 from your air, you don't breathe as good. That's why grandma has her medicare approved oxygen tank. A little different than you say.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345471923000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345472035000-26</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jimmy Carter created the Department of Energy to reduce the nations reliance on foreign energy. We now import a higher % than ever. After spending billions year after year on failure Obama doubles down by using the EPA. Imported oil from Saudi Arabia is up 20% this year. Higher energy costs are regressive and do the most damage to lower income people. Obama is not helping the poor just using them as an excuse to spend government money on his campaign bundlers and fund his election.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345472035000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345472412000-27</Id><Topic><Title>EPA to force 100 power plants to close</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457527000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:12:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4. seal yourself up in a large bottle and see how sensitive the effects of co2 concentration in the air is to our breathing. 5. again, the article says mercury a little different than you say.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345472412000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345472641000-28</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>infactidkn - had we not addressed the problem with the EPA and used other tactics the amount of oil imported from Saudi Arabia would be much higher and we would find ourselves on a string which was being jerked by the oil producing states- Only a fraction of our oil actually comes from the Saudies And it actually all comes out of the world oil markets and their vendors. To say that Saudi oil imports are up 20% is meaningless. Most of our oil is from Mexico, South America and domestic production in reality. Imported oil is actually down from 60% to under 50% this year- I know you are too dumb to know that but you can believe it because I told you</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345472641000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345472932000-29</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fan and fred might be the match but the gasoline was pure ole fashioned speculation with a good dash of quant wizardry, see original post.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345472932000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345473181000-30</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052748704698004576104500524998280.html "'The existence of housing bubbles in a number of large countries, each with vastly different systems of housing finance, severely undercuts the thesis that the housing bubble was a phenomenon driven solely by the U.S. government. '"</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345473181000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345473201000-31</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The EPA and Dept of Energy are two of the most important depts we have. We should quadruple their funding.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345473201000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345473341000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Pretty cool report on Microsoft Corporation</Title><Username>ethelenesauseda</Username><Timestamp>1345472756000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:25:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BEWARE - SPAM MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1345473341000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:35:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345473487000-33</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we need less mercury, not the car, god, or planet, either, for the rwnj super thinkers out there</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345473487000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345473981000-34</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't eat much tuna, it will raise your mercury to unsafe levels. Yes, it has been verified and shown to be true. Breathe that nice fresh O2 balanced air in, because you need it.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345473981000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345474042000-35</Id><Title>AAPL, will it hit 1000 before MSFT holds 30</Title><Msg>//..................</Msg><Username>koubaro_dimitrios</Username><Timestamp>1345474042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:47:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345474051000-36</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cje.oxfordjournals.org/content/33/4/563.full ""The main thesis of this paper is that, although problems in the US subprime mortgage market triggered the current financial crisis, its deep cause on the financial side is to be found in the flawed institutions and practices of the current financial regime, often referred to as the New Financial Architecture (NFA).""</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345474051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345474351000-37</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>www.oecd.org/finance/financialmarkets/41942872.pdf ""When OFHEO imposed greater capital requirements and balance sheet controls on Fannie and Freddie, banks that had been selling mortgages to them faced revenue gaps and an interruption to their earnings. Their solution was to create their own Fannie and Freddie look-alikes: the structured investment vehicles (SIVs) and collateralised debt obligation (CDOs)."" How many papers do you RWNJ want as proof that fan and fred were the start but not the fuel.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345474351000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345475112000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why does the social security admin need hollow point ammo?</Title><Username>gkcreamcheese</Username><Timestamp>1345459824000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Must be nice to be ignorant!</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345475112000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:05:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345475278000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Why does the social security admin need hollow point ammo?</Title><Username>gkcreamcheese</Username><Timestamp>1345459824000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They need them to fan off all the elderly that will make a run at the SSA when they finally understand that Obamacare has redistributed their SS and Medicare from Senior to young welfare folks.</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345475278000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:07:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345475713000-40</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also great news for every low lying nation, state and island worldwide. Further rising of the seas will cause trillions of dollars in damage and millions of lost lives and additional poverty throughout the world. Possibly we will save a few mountains and trout streams in the process.</Msg><Username>jcbrowns</Username><Timestamp>1345475713000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345476226000-41</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you didn't include the whole quote, wonder why. """"When OFHEO imposed greater capital requirements and balance sheet controls on Fannie and Freddie, banks that had been selling mortgages to them faced revenue gaps and an interruption to their earnings. Their solution was to create their own Fannie and Freddie look-alikes: the structured investment vehicles (SIVs) and collateralised debt obligation (CDOs)."" So it would seem fan and fred were checked and the market in MBS took off without them. So much for you blaming people for not hindering fan and fred.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345476226000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345477459000-42</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL, will it hit 1000 before MSFT holds 30</Title><Username>koubaro_dimitrios</Username><Timestamp>1345474042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:47:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you know how it goes koubaro when you should short you keep thinking its going to go up- forever this is where you want to short- for max capital gains</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345477459000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345479051000-43</Id><Title>The all time greatest event of all time September 5th approaches</Title><Msg>http://www.slashgear.com/nokia-and-microsoft-schedule-windows-phone-event-for-september-5th-16243055/ Nokia and Microsoft schedule Windows Phone event for September 5th Reports indicated that Nokia and Microsoft would showcase Windows Phone 8 products at Nokia World in Helsinki on September 5th, but it looks like the duo will be taking to New York on the same day to unveil their latest wares. The team sent out invites yesterday to a press conference to be held in New York on September 5th at 9.30am EST using the familiar Windows Phone tiles interface, so you can probably imagine what to expect on the big day. Multiple reports have suggested that Nokia will be demoing new handsets on September 5th, but the New York location is a surprise. It remains to be seen if Nokia will be showing off any new handsets or Windows Phone 8 at Nokia World in Helsinki, but it’s possible that the Finnish smartphone manufacturer and Microsoft want to focus on the all important US market before turning their attention to Europe. Nokia is expected to release two new handsets on September 5th, the Lumia 910 and 920. Not much is known about the devices, but a front-panel that leaked just the other day for a Nokia phone featured the new Windows tile button, indicating the use of Windows Phone 8. The cut out for the display on the panel measured 4.3-inches, with the design featuring rounded corners and curves instead of the sharp angles of the Lumia 800 and 900. Microsoft, meanwhile, is expected to demo Windows Phone 8 on Nokia’s new handsets, showing off some more consumers oriented features in addition to what was first seen at the Windows Phone Summit in June. We’ll be sure to bring you all the details, so mark September 5th down on your calendar if you’re a Windows Phone fan looking forward to the next big thing.</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345479051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345479155000-44</Id><Topic><Title>The all time greatest event of all time September 5th approaches</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345479051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:10:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*yawn* As if anyone but MS employees and a handful of affiliated idiots cares.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1345479155000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345479234000-45</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And there wasn't anything that could have been done by bush or bawny or anybody else regarding fan and fred as wall street had already turned away from them. Just like i said.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345479234000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:13:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345479263000-46</Id><Topic><Title>The all time greatest event of all time September 5th approaches</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345479051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:10:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ghosansnon- you got to be most boring poster on this board- only when we can talk about your perversions and convictions does it get the least bit interesting</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345479263000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:14:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345479707000-47</Id><Topic><Title>The all time greatest event of all time September 5th approaches</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345479051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:10:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;only when we can talk about your perversions and convictions does it get the least bit interesting&gt; *yawn* We've always known this about the wally bot, so it's not news. But the first step toward solving your problem is to admit you have one.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345479707000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345481009000-48</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>inspector_renault must really be getting under your skin if this is the only way you can fight him.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345481009000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345481824000-49</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;I, inspector_renaul.., aka mohammad_atta, do hereby admit to being abused, used, and tattooded as a child and seem to have a bit of tolerance for substance abuse, voter fraud, and prostitution. &gt;&gt; not to worry- we stopped using clay tablets and smoke signals- sucks will go the same way</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345481824000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:57:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345482533000-50</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON TO REPLACE BIDEN?</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345394610000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:43:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now there's a report that Obama hates Romney!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345482533000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345482639000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Humongous Truism: Bush Fcuked Us But Good!</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345406046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:54:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CAN YOU READ MORON? &gt;&gt;&gt;To cover for their criminal negligence the Republican Party Boys started two unfunded, unpaid-for, wars on the credit card. The unfunded, unpaid-for,wars continue to create debt to this day. Then there were the Bush Tax cuts that threw gasoline on the deficit fire. To cap off their list of accomplishments the Republican Party Boys deregulated the banks and refused to enforce strict loan adminstration standards which created a bank failure, a housing collapse, and a global financial melt-down. Say "thank you" to the Republican Party Boys. &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</Msg><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:10:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345482693000-52</Id><Topic><Title>I made SO MUCH MONEY using this Info!</Title><Username>barneyzlbke0243</Username><Timestamp>1345478057000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:54:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BEWARE - SPAMMER RING - MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1345482693000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345482987000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Humongous Truism: Bush Fcuked Us But Good!</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345406046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:54:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...and then Obama compounded it big time. We are well and truly screwed now.</Msg><Username>deralteesel</Username><Timestamp>1345482987000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345482991000-54</Id><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Msg>Supply Side economics is a convoluted theory using pretzel logic to justify cutting taxes on the extremely wealthy. Wealth OWNS the Republican Party (Koch Bros, Sheldon Adelson etc.) hence the Supply Side Economic Theory Lie. Cut taxes on the job creators? We've done that under Dubya. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jobs_created_during_U.S._presidential_terms Dubya had the worst job creation record since Herbert Hoover(R). Don't take my word. Check the graph in the link.</Msg><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345483128000-55</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush's tax cut was for individuals. There was little passed during his administration that would pass for pro growth supply side economics. In the meantime we have seen the failure of demand side stimulus with Obama's policies. Failed just like the did for FDR whose policies lengthened the depression.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345483128000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:18:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345483237000-56</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;. There was little passed during his administration that would pass for pro growth supply side economics.,&lt;&lt;&lt; You're a Republican shill and a fcuking liar.</Msg><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345483237000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345483339000-57</Id><Topic><Title>Incredible dithering market</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345482553000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All waiting for Bernanke to create more money. How can anyone put a proper value on anything with Fed and Govt. manipulation creating imbalances everywhere. It will all end very badly.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345483339000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:22:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345483555000-58</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, tell me what supply side policies were passed during the Bush administration?</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345483555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345483854000-59</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;Failed just like the did for FDR whose policies lengthened the depression. &gt;&gt; except these policies didnt fail they were blocked by republican legislators and the amount of money expended was not near enough- but in 1941-1945 the amount expended was so much it increased the national debt to 130% of the GNP and it worked byond the wildest dreams of the New Dealers- so try to learn something and not sound so f....n ignorant eh infacti...</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345483854000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345484066000-60</Id><Title>I LOVE MY DIVIDEND STOCKS.</Title><Msg>Not to mention it will most likely be a 200 dollar stock some day. msft hopefully will keep giving investors dividend raises as the company keeps growing in value.</Msg><Username>richeydouglas</Username><Timestamp>1345484066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484095000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush?? Raygun increased federal expenditures by hundreds of billions with his 600 ship navy and B1 bomber which the USAF never wanted (the USAF wanted the B2)and tax cuts which are equivalent to expenditures and Ronnie was able to increase the national debt from 500 billion to more than 4 trillion. Bush sr and Bush jr like it so well they ran the debt to 11 trillion- some policy that supply side policy</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345484095000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484189000-62</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;we stopped using clay tablets and smoke signals&gt; Unfortunately, you didn't stop using Windows, so you're still very 1990's.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345484189000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:36:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484294000-63</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are now spending as a % of GDP as we were during WWII. Still no recovery. WWII was no recovery. People living with rationing of goods while sending over 400,000 off to die in war will reduce unemployment but that is no recovery. The population is now 3x as large as in the 1940's, we would have to kill off over 1.2 million workers for your policy to work. New Deal was a failure as admitted by FDR's own treasury secretary Morgantheau. Now back to the question, what supply side policies did Bush pass? Remember the individual tax cut is demand side. You can't answer because all you know is liberal talking points with no fundamental understanding of economics. No wonder you like Obama.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345484294000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345484591000-64</Id><Title>In Newsweek Magazine Niall Ferguson: Obama’s Gotta Go</Title><Msg>NEWSWEEK: http://www.thedailybeast.com/newsweek/2012/08/19/niall-ferguson-on-why-barack-obama-needs-to-go.html</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345484591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484610000-65</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;FDR's own treasury secretary Morgantheau.&gt;&gt; oh really?? now surely you would like to back up your bull sh.t with a link eh- try one of the Koch backed front organizations or Fox Newspeak or some other ultra trustworthy source eh</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345484610000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345484649000-66</Id><Title>In Newsweek Magazine Niall Ferguson: Obama's Gotta Go</Title><Msg>NEWSWEEK: In Newsweek Magazine Niall Ferguson: Obama’s Gotta Go http://www.thedailybeast.com/newsweek/2012/08/19/niall-ferguson-on-why-barack-obama-needs-to-go.html</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345484649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:44:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484965000-67</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you intend to write nonsense, if so you do it well.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345484965000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484969000-68</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What supply side policy did Bush pass? You said his supply side policies failed yet can't name one that he passed. As for your proof of the failure of the New Deal here is Morgantheau's quote. You can follow the link to it's origin which can be found in a document from the FDR library. "We have tried spending money. We are spending more than we have ever spent before and it does not work. And I have just one interest, and if I am wrong somebody else can have my job. I want to see this country prosperous. I want to see people get a job. I want to see people get enough to eat. We have never made good on our promises. I say after eight years of this Administration we have just as much unemployment as when we started. And an enormous debt to boot." http://www.burtfolsom.com/?p=1217</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345484969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:49:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345484978000-69</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey worst of all he didnt solve the European debt crises which contributes a lot to consumer demand and investor confidence- now Junior he would have ivaded the EU and solved the problem PDQ</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345484978000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345485094000-70</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The European crisis should be an enormous opportunity for the US not an excuse. If we did pass policies making the US more business friendly we would be attracting lots of foreign capital from that region. Obama takes opportunity and turns it into an excuse for failure.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345485094000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345485240000-71</Id><Title>WMD in Syria?</Title><Msg>Obama just said in what is jokingly called a "news conference" that there is WMD in Syria?? What? Deja vu all over again, lol</Msg><Username>k24chat</Username><Timestamp>1345485240000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345485294000-72</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;As for your proof of the failure of the New Deal here is Morgantheau's quote. You can follow the link to it's origin which can be found in a document from the FDR library.&gt;&gt; hey shouldnt take more than a day or two- I think you can find Morgenthau admitting that the economy boomed from 1946 till 1968 as a result of massive buying power in the hands of consumers. It took a massive expenditure to do it too- when you get to the hottest circle of hell you can expect to find deniers of all kinds - Keynesian economics, Roosevelts economic policys, MMGW among a lot of other things</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345485294000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345485385000-73</Id><Title>Could Apple hit 1K by Xmas.</Title><Msg>..............</Msg><Username>koubaro_dimitrios</Username><Timestamp>1345485385000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345485446000-74</Id><Title>Long MSFT and Strong Coal BTU/ANR/ACI today</Title><Msg>I like to invest bottom stocks and value stocks too. MSFT 38 soon while BTU/ANR/ACI is very easy to be double from current price. Hold long for retirement soon</Msg><Username>chasestockhigh</Username><Timestamp>1345485446000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:57:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345485543000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;Obama takes opportunity and turns it into an excuse for failure. &gt;&gt; therefore what?? are you trying to say Obama could have solved Europes problems for themselves?? Like Bush was doing I suppose</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345485543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345485727000-76</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong again. After WWII the government spending dropped dramatically. Economic growth resumed afterwards due to growth in private industry and individuals getting on with their lives. The exact opposite of what you claim. But please don't let facts get in the way, they just confuse you. FDR's policies prolonged Depression by 7 years http://newsroom.ucla.edu/portal/ucla/FDR-s-Policies-Prolonged-Depression-5409.aspx</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345485727000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345486365000-77</Id><Topic><Title>Pro-Americans Have Questions On Romneys Taxes</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1345485978000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was a CNN poll moron. &gt;&gt;&gt;CNN poll revealed that 63 percent of Americans believe Romney should release more of his tax returns&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt; I realize you suck Rush Limpballs but he is not considered mainstream by the sane.</Msg><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345486365000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345486477000-78</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Government spending is counted in GDP therefore it gooses up the GDP number but at the expense of future growth. Even when the CBO graded the original stimulus bill they predicted 12-18 months of increased GDP followed by lower GDP growth for the remainder of the decade. Much like a short term high on drugs followed by a long hangover. Never worth the price.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345486477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345487246000-79</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Corpora (MSFT ) ) you will get corrected</Title><Username>crystalenglish214</Username><Timestamp>1345464213000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you for your insightful view, as usual. a lot of people on this board claiming to be long, but very short-sighted</Msg><Username>danielsdirk538</Username><Timestamp>1345487246000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345487697000-80</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;And why are they in worse shape than us even though we fund most of their military defense??&gt;&gt; just what caused this new wave of lunacy- the US funds most of Europes Military defense?? We contribute to NATO but so do they- I want you to tell me who funds the German Leopard II tanks? the French LeClerc tanks, the French Navy- Oh we did provide the blueprints for the trident systems in theirs and the Brits missle submarines- so who buys those French Mirage airplanes, the Tornado and Typhoon airplanes - the ships in the British, French and German navies? or Spanish or Italian stuff- who pays the soldiers in all the NATO country armies- seems to me like they have to buy everything they get- lets hear it from a real defense expert</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345487697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345488047000-81</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;Wrong again. After WWII the government spending dropped dramatically. Economic growth resumed afterwards due to growth in private industry and individuals getting on with their lives. The exact opposite of what you claim.&gt;&gt; Hawfaeces the govt spending may have stopped but the consumer was sitting on a pile of cash that reached to the moon- that brought about the biggest consumer spending boom in our history and industry of all kinds prospered for 20 yesr. The wildest part of it is that the 130% of gnp debt was paid down to about 400 billion in 1980- before Raygun destroyed it all</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345488047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345488229000-82</Id><Topic><Title>100 power plants to close because of EPA</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1345457606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 06:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may not have noticed, but you're arguing both sides of the issue, are you a confused wingnut ???</Msg><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1345488229000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:43:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345488280000-83</Id><Topic><Title>In Newsweek Magazine Niall Ferguson: Obama’s Gotta Go</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345484591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You idiot! Newsweek Has been been a virtual third arm of the Obama campaign for more than 4 years. The mere fact that this would appear on the front cover of Newsweek says more than any story ever could. They recognize the huge failure of Obama as does every awake and thinking person in America.</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345488280000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345488546000-84</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;Oh yeah, its called socialism/communism. It doesn't work. The problem with it is you eventually run out of other peoples' money.&gt;&gt; If you stepped on a Texas sandbur and it hurt like hell you would call it soshulism/communism- that actually makes you sound like the village idiot. communism is deader than Ceasars ghost and its doubtful that it ever existed anyway. Socialism is existent for parts of the economy like medical care and medical insurance, public infrastructure, military forces - in other words all those things we have that require massive expenditure that private industry never had the balls to address and thats is why Socialism exists today in every nation on the face of the earth(a fact you are unaware of)</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345488546000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:49:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345488637000-85</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hell the deficit was below 200 billion before the Barney Frank, democrat led subprime debacle blew up in 2008 What they said: House Financial Services Committee hearing, Sept. 25, 2003: Rep. Frank: I do think I do not want the same kind of focus on safety and soundness that we have in OCC [Office of the Comptroller of the Currency] and OTS [Office of Thrift Supervision]. I want to roll the dice a little bit more in this situation towards subsidized housing. . . . Sept. 10, 2003 Rep. Maxine Waters (D., Calif.), speaking to Housing and Urban Development Secretary Mel Martinez: Secretary Martinez, if it ain't broke, why do you want to fix it? Have the GSEs [government-sponsored enterprises] ever missed their housing goals?</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345488637000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345488758000-86</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the economy grew quarter after quarter?? so just what the hell did the national debt do?? seems to me that you can buy yourself a big economy if you have the US treasury behind it all</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345488758000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345489064000-87</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;What is the name of the logic that says if you borrow $1.2T dollars to obtain $400B dollars in resulting GDP expansion, that is real "growth"? &gt;&gt; the logic is lots of people would keep their jobs and could continue their lives- the people working could also create wealth which would counterbalance the debt- public utilities, factorys, transportation vehicles etc etc continuing the heavier taxation of the rich would extract their fair share of the public debt and help keep it down or paid off. I for one doubt the truthfulness of your numbers- seems to me that about have the stimulus money remains unspent</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345489064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345489120000-88</Id><Topic><Title>In Newsweek Magazine Niall Ferguson: Obama's Gotta Go</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345484649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only person that's got to go is you OT political A holes.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1345489120000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345489209000-89</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;Much like a short term high on drugs followed by a long hangover. Never worth the price. &gt;&gt; it would be well worth while - high rate of growth followed by lesser rate of growth is still an increase in overall GNP and if it pulls the economy out of recession then whats not to like about it</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345489209000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:00:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345489272000-90</Id><Topic><Title>In Newsweek Magazine Niall Ferguson: Obama's Gotta Go</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345484649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Newsweek magazine is going to rue the day they turned into hardcopy Fox Newspeak</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345489272000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345489608000-91</Id><Topic><Title>In Newsweek Magazine Niall Ferguson: Obama's Gotta Go</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345484649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are just waking up to the facts of the Obama failure</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345489608000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:06:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345489784000-92</Id><Topic><Title>Supply Side: The Republican Scam Of The Century</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345482991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it would be well worth while - high rate of growth followed by lesser rate of growth is still an increase in overall GNP and if it pulls the economy out of recession then whats not to like about it --------- Wrong again economic ignoramus. The multiplier effect has been discredited many times over. Keynesian theory has a 100% failure rate. Multiplier effect has never happened. Borrowing and spending has never led to a sustainable recovery in the US or anywhere else. Did you enjoy the Morgantheau admission of the failure of the New Deal?</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345489784000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345490327000-93</Id><Topic><Title>You will be amazed to learn how much I made trading Microsoft Corporation</Title><Username>dilsnbmyg596628</Username><Timestamp>1345489793000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BEWARE - SPAMMER MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1345490327000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345490423000-94</Id><Title>I just luv how the media exposes RWNJ at every turn</Title><Msg>Idiots deny straight A student her diploma for using the word 'hell' in her speech. http://usnews.nbcnews.com/_news/2012/08/20/13377164-oklahoma-high-school-valedictorian-denied-diploma-for-using-hell-in-speech?lite</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345490423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345490429000-95</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Corpora (MSFT ) ) you will get corrected</Title><Username>crystalenglish214</Username><Timestamp>1345464213000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PLAIN CRAP SPAM</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1345490429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345490480000-96</Id><Topic><Title>Pretty cool report on Microsoft Corporation</Title><Username>alexandriasammis</Username><Timestamp>1345485308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:55:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UGLY SPAM MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1345490480000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:21:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345490496000-97</Id><Topic><Title>I just luv how the media exposes RWNJ at every turn</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345490423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops lets not forget this guy from todays RWNJ news. http://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/with-todd-akins-rape-comments-abortion-is-back-in-the-campaign-spotlight/2012/08/20/c497bae4-eac7-11e1-a80b-9f898562d010_story.html</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345490496000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:21:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345490886000-98</Id><Topic><Title>I just luv how the media exposes RWNJ at every turn</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345490423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why... Because its soooooo funny. Stephen Colbert. ..The minds of our young people are being poisoned by knowledge... I have long praised the Texas Board of Education for their valiant work rewriting our nation’s history textbooks. But now I believe they’ve got some stiff competition from the Texas GOP, who recently put a plank in their 2012 party platformn regarding children’s education which says, and I quote, ‘We oppose the teaching of critical thinking skills.’ Amen brother. For too long we have blindly accepted the idea of not blindly accepting ideas. “And you know who I blame? I blame Galileo.... For centuries we had a perfectly good explanation for the order of the universe. Bible says the sun goes around the Earth, making us the center of the universe. And you know what? Everyone was happy. And then numnuts over here gets a telescope for Christmas, uses his precious critical thinking skills and suddenly the Earth goes around the sun, blah blah blah and now we have lesbians. I’m here to tell you now the Texas GOP is on to you, critical thinking skills! They know that you have quote the purpose of challenging the students’ fixed beliefs, and a good teacher’s job is to maintain whatever fixed beliefs a student has when they enter first grade. Frankly folks, I am embarrassed that we conservatives did not think of this sooner.... Sure,we discredited the liberal activism of the ‘60s and the socialist policies of the New Deal... But folks, all of that is just child’s play compared to the Texas GOP, who with this one plank of their platform have called for the repeal of the Enlightenment. And as if to illustrate what is possible once you are freed from the shackles of critical thinking... The Texas GOP, when asked about this position, explained it as an oversight and should not have included the words ‘critical thinking skills.’ Now, when they were drafting the platform, somebody had to say ‘no critical thinking skills.’ Somebody else had to type those words and then the Texas GOP had to approve those words. Do you really think that would have been possible if anybody had been thinking critically? But thank God no one was. And if they get their way, nobody will be...</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345490886000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345491040000-99</Id><Title>Taxes Reveal The Person</Title><Msg>Reveal a person's taxes and you reveal the person. WHAT IS ROMNEY HIDING????</Msg><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345491040000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345492476000-100</Id><Topic><Title>Taxes Reveal The Person</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345491040000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being open with all records are important.</Msg><Username>free2491</Username><Timestamp>1345492476000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:54:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345493121000-101</Id><Topic><Title>Pro-Americans Have Questions On Romneys Taxes</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1345485978000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Important Campaign Issues http://news.investors.com/editorialcartoons/cartoon.aspx?id=622747</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345493121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:05:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345493729000-102</Id><Topic><Title>Pro-Americans Have Questions On Romneys Taxes</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1345485978000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We don't need to see Obama's taxes next year, probably maybe could be they were audited, so that means they are OK. We're fine with them not being shown. Yes this is an example of a right wing argument.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345493729000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345493810000-103</Id><Topic><Title>Pro-Americans Have Questions On Romneys Taxes</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1345485978000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:06:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The hawc team" doesn't have time to post every 5 minutes just to keep you entertained dipshet. BTW, pro-Americans will vote for the pro-American presidential candidate. You entitlement junkies can vote for the divider-in-chief.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345493810000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:16:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345494016000-104</Id><Topic><Title>Taxes Reveal The Person</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1345491040000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reveal a person's taxes and you reveal the person. &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; And of course, if you pay nothing, like you said, it reveals you are nothing. Just like I thought.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345494016000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:20:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345494042000-105</Id><Title>Apple Market Cap, will Microsoft ever reach that again?</Title><Msg>I have a feeling Microsoft is ready for a comeback, Windows 8 is a game changer. In the meantime, check out the cool graph on Apple's historical market cap. http://thebigstock.com/2012/08/20/apple-now-officially-the-largest-company-ever/</Msg><Username>barloparlo</Username><Timestamp>1345494042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345494969000-106</Id><Title>Sure glad Obama has control of the Arab situtation</Title><Msg>The Arab Spring takeover of Egypt by the M Brotherhood has run amok, with reports from several different media agencies that the radical M have begun crucifying opponents of newly installed President Mohammed Morsi. Middle East media confirm that during a recent rampage, M Brotherhood operatives “crucified those opposing Egyptian President Muhammad Morsi naked on trees in front of the presidential palace while abusing others.” “Arabic media call them ‘supporters,’ ‘followers’ and ‘partisans’ of the M Brotherhood,” Ibraham said. Ibrahim also says the victims can be anyone, including Egyptian Christians. “It’s anyone who is resisting the new government,” Ibrahim said. “In this particular case, the people attacked and crucified were secular protesters upset because of Morsi’s hostile campaign against the media, especially of Tawfik Okasha, who was constantly exposing him on his station, until Morsi shut him down.” Ibrahim said extra brutality is reserved for Christians, but the crucifixions are because of Islamic doctrine and are required by the Quran. The time and other details about the crucifixions were not readily available.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345494969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345497051000-107</Id><Title>Michelle has created more jobs than Barak</Title><Msg>First Lady Michelle Obama’s Servant List and Pay Scale The First Lady Requires More Than Twenty Attendants (that’s 22 attendants to be exact) 1. $172,200 – Sher, Susan (Chief Of Staff) 2. $140,000 – Frye, Jocelyn C. (Deputy Assistant to the President and Director of Policy And Projects For The First Lady) 3. $113,000 – Rogers, Desiree G. (Special Assistant to the President and White House Social Secretary) 4. $102,000 – Johnston, Camille Y. (Special Assistant to the President and Director of Communications for the First Lady) 5. $100,000 – Winter, Melissa E. (Special Assistant to the President and Deputy Chief Of Staff to the First Lady) 6. $90,000 – Medina , David S. (Deputy Chief Of Staff to the First Lady) 7. $84,000 – Lelyveld, Catherine M (Director and Press Secretary to the First Lady) 8. $75,000 – Starkey, Frances M. (Director of Scheduling and Advance for the First Lady) 9. $70,000 – Sanders, Trooper (Deputy Director of Policy and Projects for the First Lady) 10. $65,000 – Burnough, Erinn J. (Deputy Director and Deputy Social Secretary) 11. $64,000 – Reinstein, Joseph B. (Deputy Director and Deputy Social Secretary) 12. $62,000 – Goodman, Jennifer R. (Deputy Director of Scheduling and Events Coordinator For The First Lady) 13. $60,000 – Fitts, Alan O. (Deputy Director of Advance and Trip Director for the First Lady) 14. $57,500 – Lewis, Dana M. (Special Assistant and Personal Aide to the First Lady) 15. $52,500 – Mustaphi, Semonti M. (Associate Director and Deputy Press Secretary to The First Lady) 16. $50,000 – Jarvis, Kristen E. (Special-2Assistant for Scheduling and Traveling Aide to The First Lady) 17. $45,000 – Lechtenberg, Tyler A. (Associate Director of Correspondence For The First Lady) 18. $43,000 – Tubman, Samantha (Deputy Associate Director, Social Office) 19. $40,000 – Boswell, Joseph J. (Executive Assistant to the Chief Of Staff to the First Lady) 20. $36,000 – Armbruster, Sally M. (Staff Assistant to the Social Secretary) 21. $35,000 – Bookey, Natalie (Staff Assistant) 22. $35,000 – Jackson, Deilia A. (Deputy Associate Director of Correspondence for the First Lady) (This is community organizing at it’s finest.) There has NEVER been anyone in the White House at any time who has created such an</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345497051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345497212000-108</Id><Topic><Title>Sure glad Obama has control of the Arab situtation</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345494969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh you mean like Junior? Hell instead of invading Syria Junior probably would have invade Finland or something- hes about as dumb as you are</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345497212000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345497903000-109</Id><Topic><Title>Todd Akin: the female body has ways</Title><Username>onehot_fun_usa</Username><Timestamp>1345497609000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:20:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Todd Akin like other Taliban members never considered the 19th amendment (womens vote) legitimate and just knew he could trash the women when he wanted to. He probably makes his wife and daughters wear Burkhas and not go to public places without male members of the family attending as escorts</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345497903000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345497991000-110</Id><Topic><Title>The hypocrisy Of Romney Is Off The Charts!</Title><Username>onehot_fun_usa</Username><Timestamp>1345497918000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMEN.............</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345497991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345498926000-111</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's 13% Tax Rate Far Below Normal</Title><Username>do_your_fairshare</Username><Timestamp>1345498499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical Obama supporter pays no taxes at all. 47% pay no income taxes at all ... and of course most of them voted for Obama.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345498926000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499501000-112</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle has created more jobs than Barak</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345497051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:10:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Michelle Obama has her own welfare program ... rewarding her army of stooges with $1.7 million annuallylooted from American taxpayers.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345499501000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345500267000-113</Id><Title>Obama Looted $700 From Medicare to Fund Obamacare</Title><Msg>It's a fact, Obama looted $700 Billion from Medicare to fund the 20 million new people (mostly deadbeats) he put on Obamacare. In place of the looted $700B, he gave the elderly death panels to keep the costs down.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345500267000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345501225000-114</Id><Title>Biggest Lie From Left: Dems Didn't Cause Financial Trainwreck</Title><Msg>Of course the financial trainwreck was caused 100% by Democrats. Their hatchet man, Andrew Cuomo, HUD Secretary under Clinton was instrumental in bullying lending institutions into giving loans to any deadbeat that applied. Bawney Fwank and Chris Dodd and Obama converted Fannie and Freddie into welfare agencies for mortgages. They bought up all the toxic mortgages, enabling more and more to be issued. Obama, the Congressional Black Caucus and most of the rest of the Dems were "the heart and soul of Fannie Mae" as the CEO of Fannie said at a pep rally for Obama and the Congressional Black Caucus. The mountains of toxic mortgages the Democrats created was then sliced and diced by Wall St. Banksters and peddled around the world. This soon resulted in the financial trainwreck which transferred enormous wealth from middle America to the deadbeats and to the Wall St Banksters. We have shown the truth of this innumerable times but the lefties keep peddling their big lies.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345501225000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:20:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345501595000-115</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Looted $700 From Medicare to Fund Obamacare</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345500267000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:04:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, partially young deadbeats and other chislers. You can't give free medical care to 20 million new people without taking the money from somewhere else. Obama plundered Medicare of $700B to fund their medical care.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345501595000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:26:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345501833000-116</Id><Title>Obama Agrees to Release School Records</Title><Msg>Just kidding. No chance the gasbag would let the public know what he was doing during his college years or who paid his bills. No one in those classes even remembers him bing there.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345501833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345502666000-117</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's 13% Tax Rate Far Below Normal</Title><Username>do_your_fairshare</Username><Timestamp>1345498499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But it is what the typical taxpayer aspires to. Investment income is taxed less, as even a moron like you must know, because it involves risk, and it is good for the economy.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1345502666000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345503693000-118</Id><Title>Samsung Launches New Tablet</Title><Msg>This looks like the tablet I should buy, pending reviews. Some might see the stylus as a step backwards, but for the uses I have in mind, it's a huge plus. http://finance.yahoo.com/news/samsung-launches-tablet-212937006.html Samsung Launches New Tablet ZacksBy Zacks Equity Research | Zacks – 1 hour 26 minutes ago Samsung Electronics Co. launched its new tablet Galaxy Note 10.1 in the U.S., Great Britain and South Korea, and promised a worldwide launch in the not-too-distant future. Samsung’s new tablet will compete directly with Apple’s (AAPL) iPad, and the base price remains comparable with the 32GB model going somewhat cheaper. The new tablet is designed to eliminate stylistic similarities with the iPad that have the two companies battling in court. It therefore adds two new features that the iPad doesn’t have - a stylus called S-Pen for taking notes or sketching and a split-screen for using certain applications simultaneously. The tablet uses the Ice Cream Sandwich version of Google's (GOOG) Android OS, and a quad-core processor running at 1.4 GHz. It also has a standard 5-megapixel rear camera and 1.9-megapixel front facing camera. As per U.S. research firm IHS iSuppli, Apple has a 69.6% share of the tablet market, with Samsung far behind at 9.2% and Amazon (AMZN) third at 4.2%. The tablet war is really heating up with manufacturers launching newer versions. Microsoft (MSFT) is entering the market with its Windows 8 tablet priced at $199.0. This price range is similar to Google’s Nexus 7 and Amazon’s Kindle Fire. In any consumer market, the market leader tends to lose some share, so this is not a special negative for Apple (assuming that all the other devices taken together make a sizeable dent). As long as the market itself continues to grow, any player with a good product and solid strategy is likely to remain a winner.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345503693000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:01:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345504751000-119</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's 13% Tax Rate Far Below Normal</Title><Username>do_your_fairshare</Username><Timestamp>1345498499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;13% of $20M&lt;&lt; We don't know Romney paid even 13% you stoooopid redneck porker. He hasn't released his taxes. He may have paid 0%. We don't know. You dumb fcuker.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345504751000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345504988000-120</Id><Title>Tony Scott</Title><Msg>me, and Bill Gates, all have Jupiter in Leo. All three of us born 10+ years apart.</Msg><Username>swingingparrot_llllllll</Username><Timestamp>1345504988000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345505119000-121</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcraper, did the debt go up $5.35T on</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345308230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from their servitude to the gaggle of inbred Hunnish freeloaders but you'd be hard pressed to make it stick, Taffy half-wit.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345505119000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345505494000-122</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Market Cap, will Microsoft ever reach that again?</Title><Username>barloparlo</Username><Timestamp>1345494042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:20:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very doubtful MSFT will ever reach that level again. W8 is what is known among engineers as a "kluge". kluge   kludge    [klooj] Show IPA noun Computer Slang . a software or hardware configuration that, while inelegant, inefficient, clumsy, or patched together, succeeds in solving a specific problem or performing a particular task.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345505494000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345505717000-123</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung Launches New Tablet</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345503693000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:01:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL glad you approve, but don't really need permission.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345505717000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345505767000-124</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle has created more jobs than Barak</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345497051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:10:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, someone has to shop for her and manage her closet, lol. She has 400! pairs of shoes.</Msg><Username>kkness1</Username><Timestamp>1345505767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:36:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345506343000-125</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's 13% Tax Rate Far Below Normal</Title><Username>do_your_fairshare</Username><Timestamp>1345498499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No fcukhead, what about 2010? 2009? 2008? 2007? etc. How do we know Romney didn't pay ANY taxes for over a decade but got religion 2 years before his campaign? Get it redneck fcukhead? (doubtful)</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345506343000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345506694000-126</Id><Topic><Title>I just luv how the media exposes RWNJ at every turn</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345490423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is more every day. Announcing the formation of RWNJ news only found here.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345506694000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345507112000-127</Id><Title>Palin Created More Jobs Than Romney</Title><Msg>Romney out sourced more jobs to China than Palin created. Of course Palin created zero jobs. Romney out sourced millions of jobs to China.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1345507112000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345507245000-128</Id><Topic><Title>In Newsweek Magazine Niall Ferguson: Obama's Gotta Go</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345484649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They just figured out that the country is going down the drain under obama!!!!!??????</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1345507245000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:00:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345507415000-129</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's 13% Tax Rate Far Below Normal</Title><Username>do_your_fairshare</Username><Timestamp>1345498499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 2011 returns haven't even been filed. http://abcnews.go.com/images/Politics/Mitt%20Romney%202011.pdf His 2010 83(b) filings indicate he is still receiving compensation for services performed for (at least) Bain Capital Partners (AM) X, LLC http://abcnews.go.com/images/Politics/Mitt%20Romney%202010.pdf This is an entity that is not registered with the United States Securities and Exchange Comission http://www.sec.gov/cgi-bin/browse-edgar?action=getcompany&amp;company=bain%20capital&amp;owner=include&amp;match=contains&amp;start=0&amp;count=40&amp;hidefilings=0 Why are you such an uninformed idiot?</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345507415000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345507939000-130</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's 13% Tax Rate Far Below Normal</Title><Username>do_your_fairshare</Username><Timestamp>1345498499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>***********No fcukhead, what about 2010? 2009? 2008? 2007? etc. How do we know Romney didn't pay ANY taxes for over a decade but got religion 2 years before his campaign?***************</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345507939000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345508310000-131</Id><Title>Romney hasn't released two years worth of tax returns.</Title><Msg>The 2011 returns haven't even been filed. http://abcnews.go.com/images/Politics/Mi... His 2010 83(b) filings indicate he is still receiving compensation for services performed for (at least) Bain Capital Partners (AM) X, LLC http://abcnews.go.com/images/Politics/Mi... This is an entity that is not registered with the United States Securities and Exchange Comission http://www.sec.gov/cgi-bin/browse-edgar?... Hawcreek is a liar.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:18:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345508339000-132</Id><Title>You fools!!</Title><Msg>Stop tryin!!</Msg><Username>hawcreeksgatecult</Username><Timestamp>1345508339000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345508356000-133</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's 13% Tax Rate Far Below Normal</Title><Username>do_your_fairshare</Username><Timestamp>1345498499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey doyourfairshare,. I'm the normal taxpayer. How about you paying what I'm paying. that would be "fair" wouldn't it.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345508356000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345508530000-134</Id><Title>Romney Hiding Tax Returns Prior 2011</Title><Msg>Why is Romney hiding his tax returns prior to 2011? Did he pay any? WTF is going on with Romney's secret accounts in the Caymen Isl, Swiss Bank Accounts and the Bahamas?</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345508530000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345508548000-135</Id><Topic><Title>Romney hasn't released two years worth of tax returns.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:18:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumpingov/lughead.....WHO THE FK CARES Where are the JOBS \\ Romney releases 20 years of tax returs isn't going to produce 1 job. It's the economy stupid!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345508548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345508667000-136</Id><Title>Stonewalling Day 21: Thank Moroni for a distraction.</Title><Msg>At least "legitimate" rape draws attention away from Mitt's illegitimate "business" dealings and the fact that he paid ZERO Federal income and capital gains taxes for the ten years between 1999 and 2009. What little he has released shows that Bain Capital shares a "lifetime employment' guarantee with the Mafia (although Bain is significantly less ethical in its practices). I'm certain as cyborg "President", Mitt will serve Bain well. He certainly did as cyborg "Governor" of Massachusetts, ask him to tell you about that some time (unless it's one of the many things that should only be discussed in "quiet rooms").</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508667000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345508720000-137</Id><Title>Only parasites are worried about what</Title><Msg>Romney paid. Taxpayers are worried about what they will be paying next year. Not what Romney paid last year. Quit showing what hypocritical idiots you are. We taxpayers don't give a rip.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345508720000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345508747000-138</Id><Topic><Title>Romney hasn't released two years worth of tax returns.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:18:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He likes firing people. When your incessant nickle a post barrage doesn't get him elected he'll fire you too.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508747000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345508861000-139</Id><Title>lughead got tired of being humiliated</Title><Msg>so took up a new ID truthingove. Jigs up We know you are still the same idiot. Can't make a silk purse out of a sow's ear even with a new name.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345508861000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345508998000-140</Id><Title>Romney is a parasite.</Title><Msg>Leeching of the productive work of honest taxpayers while hiding how much he's stolen and holding hardworking Americans in contempt. His supporters on this board are a prime example of how foul and slimy he is; he attracts the dregs and stokes their hate and vituperation against all that is good about the United States.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508998000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:29:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345509373000-141</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a parasite.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508998000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:29:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the low-life scum who support Romney chimes in.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345509373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345509754000-142</Id><Topic><Title>I just luv how the media exposes RWNJ at every turn</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345490423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what lie did she tell. maybe hell was hell.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345509754000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345510182000-143</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a parasite.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508998000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:29:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamaloney at its best.</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345510182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345510351000-144</Id><Topic><Title>Romney hasn't released two years worth of tax returns.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:18:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still obligated to "provide services" to a corporate entity an at least 2010? He had filed a declaration with the Federal Election Commission that "Mr. Romney retired from Bain Capital on February 11, 1999 to head the Salt Lake Organizing Committee. Since February 11, 1999, Mr. Romney has not had any active role with any Bain Capital entity and has not been involved in the operations of any Bain Capital entity in any way." But his 2010 tax returns include an 83(b) election that states that: "The interest in future appreciation of the Partnership's business to which I am entitled pursuant to my Partnership interest is subject to forfeiture if I cease performing services for the Partnership." with respect to at least Bain Capital Partners (AM) X, LP. This is not a passive investment vehicle; either it explicitly requires Mitt Romney to "perform services" on its behalf, exactly as he's stated in his filing or Mitt Romney is lying once again. http://abcnews.go.com/images/Politics/Mitt%20Romney%202010.pdf</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345510351000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345510376000-145</Id><Title>Obama Released 10 Years Of Tax Returns</Title><Msg>http://www.taxhistory.org/www/website.nsf/web/presidentialtaxreturns Romney will release two years at the most. What is Romney hiding???</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345510376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345510458000-146</Id><Topic><Title>Romney hasn't released two years worth of tax returns.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:18:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your posts are retarded. Are you hawfreaks gifted son?</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345510458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345510575000-147</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Released 10 Years Of Tax Returns</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345510376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares!</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345510575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:56:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345510653000-148</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a parasite.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508998000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:29:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Bush worshipping, bankrupt message board troll with nothing to do but spend sixteen to twenty hours a day posting lies on a backwater financial message board to try to get Bishop Mitt elected because he thinks that it will save him from the sad spiral downward his life has taken after his Limbaugh fueled message board obsession destroyed his usefulness in society. I'm not "running", Kibbutznik. Your adult diaper is.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345510653000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345510670000-149</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Released 10 Years Of Tax Returns</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345510376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.taxhistory.org/www/website.nsf/web/presidentialtaxreturns</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345510670000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:57:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345510679000-150</Id><Title>Prez: release Fast-n-Furious info!</Title><Msg>We all know that White House did nothing wrong!</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345510679000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345510811000-151</Id><Title>Prez: release college records !</Title><Msg>We believe you have nothing to hide!</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345510811000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345510912000-152</Id><Title>Harvard is hard to get into</Title><Msg>We know you got there with great grades " in the high school haze" you were in in Hawaii.</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345510912000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345511465000-153</Id><Title>China’s Hottest Wheels for Executives</Title><Msg>China’s Hottest Wheels for Executives: A Buick Minivan By Bloomberg News - Aug 20, 2012 5:01 PM CT General Motors Co. (GM) sells a model in China so popular with executives that it’s often lined up outside galas and high-end restaurants: A Buick minivan http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-08-20/china-s-hottest-wheels-for-executives-a-buick-minivan.html THANKS OBAMA FOR SAVING GM!!</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345511465000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:11:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345512145000-154</Id><Topic><Title>In Newsweek Magazine Niall Ferguson: Obama's Gotta Go</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345484649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:44:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUMP!</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1345512145000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:22:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345512299000-155</Id><Title>Tarring Todd Akin</Title><Msg>Based on my viewing the video of Senate Candidate Todd Akin's remark, I believe a few things: 1. Akin clumily used the phrase "legitimate rape" in the sense of, "actual rape", just as I might say, "President Obama is legitimately the biggest liar on the planet." Of course my comment wasn't meant to infer that lying is legitimate; I was just substituting "legitimately" for "actually" for effect and I believe Akin's use of the word was colloquial to his area and for effect. It is clear from his later remarks that he had no intention of declaring any rape to be "legitimate". The video also made it clear that Akin is completely pro-life and his intent was to make it clear that the product of a rape is a distinct human being separate from the mother and father, a human being no one has a right to destroy. Yes, I recognize that's the hardest of hard cases to defend but if you're pro-life it's because you recognize that each life is as valuable as every other life; otherwise you're on your way down a slippery slope with Obama toward infanticide. 2. Of course the left wing media and democrats jumped on Akin's rhetorical gaffe as an opportunity to defeat him, keep the Senate in Democrat control and help Obama. There is no bottom to the level these skunks will not sink. 3. The response of some Republicans who called for his resignation was shameful. Instead of doing the obvious and decent thing by looking at Akin's real intent and helping him get through this, they jumped on him, called for his resignation and gave credibility to the vicious attacks by left wing media and the democrats.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345512299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345514000000-156</Id><Topic><Title>I just luv how the media exposes RWNJ at every turn</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345490423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, you seem to operate at the intellectual level of Stephen Colbert.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345514000000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345514164000-157</Id><Topic><Title>I just luv how the media exposes RWNJ at every turn</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345490423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, cfury, you seem to operate at the intellectual level of Stephen Colbert.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345514164000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345514190000-158</Id><Topic><Title>Tarring Todd Akin</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345512299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>/his intent was to make it clear that the product of a rape is a distinct human/ he said, women have a mode they can go into to prevent pregnancy during rape. Implying women who are raped and are pregnant weren't raped at all, otherwise they would have used the anti prego button. Yes a human outside of an insane asylum said this. there goes the last 1% of the woman vote to a republican, YOU RIGHTWING DINGBAT. That's all, rape is rape, listen to the President, you need to.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345514190000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:56:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345514395000-159</Id><Topic><Title>Tarring Todd Akin</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345512299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You rightwing anti-abortion freek, go spew your religion elswhere.</Msg><Username>ooouuu_poor_fatso</Username><Timestamp>1345514395000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345515034000-160</Id><Topic><Title>Tarring Todd Akin</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345512299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, you think that one who does not support murdering unborn babies is a "freek". Why you poor illiterate moron, that's 95% of the people in the world. So it seems you are that small minority of real freaks who condone murdering babies.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345515034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:10:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345515214000-161</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a parasite.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345508998000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:29:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>truth is another commie sewer rat POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345515214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345515440000-162</Id><Topic><Title>NBC losing $ Jay Leno huge pay cut</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1345513697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:48:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one watches Obamanetworks Inc. CNBC, MSNBC, NBC viewership declined by a huge margin. They do not command the advertisement $ that FOX does. That is why GE dumped this loser of liberal TV rags. Olympics coverage was a disaster as well!</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345515440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345515543000-163</Id><Topic><Title>Congressman skinny dip or Corzine goes free</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1345512753000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Depends if you watch Obamanetworks or FOX!</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345515543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:19:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345515662000-164</Id><Topic><Title>Tarring Todd Akin</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345512299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only fault I have with Akin's remarks is he seems to have heard somewhere that women undergoing rape might in some cases be able to avoid pregnancy by various strategems either during or after the rape. He did not infer that women who are raped were not raped at all; that is your invention.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345515662000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345515799000-165</Id><Title>Presidents 47,000,000 parasites todate</Title><Msg>4 more years will create millions more parasites.</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345515799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:23:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345515816000-166</Id><Title>Yahoo Posts Upside Down.</Title><Msg>Are the liberals in Yahoo turning everything upside down to suit Obama's upside down view of reality?</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345515816000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345516122000-167</Id><Topic><Title>Tarring Todd Akin</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345512299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>peppeek, I know what your problem is. You are dumb and don't even recognize that you contradict yourself ... in a single sentence!!!</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345516122000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345517679000-168</Id><Topic><Title>Tarring Todd Akin</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345512299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I contradicted nothing dingbat, only an insane person could defend this. rape is rape, all is forcible by definition, all is against the will of the person being raped. That's it. Akins said he heard it from a doctor, but sometimes the protection doesn't work. What an expert on it. He didn't say might in some cases, you said it. Even romney is saying it is wrong. now what are you gonna do come vote time, vote for yurself?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345517679000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345519264000-169</Id><Topic><Title>Tarring Todd Akin</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345512299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on my reading of your remarks, I believe one thing: you are full of kkkrap.</Msg><Username>a_poc_now</Username><Timestamp>1345519264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345519391000-170</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Released 10 Years Of Tax Returns</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345510376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is Romney hiring? a) He found ways to put $100,000,000 into an IRA. b) He took advantage of the IRS amnesty program on Swiss bank accounts. c) He really didn't pay 13% over the years he said he did. d) All of the above.</Msg><Username>a_poc_now</Username><Timestamp>1345519391000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:23:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345519937000-171</Id><Topic><Title>Tarring Todd Akin</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345512299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Democrats should offer to finance Akin’s campaign expense. What a gift this guy has granted them!</Msg><Username>loweringdevice</Username><Timestamp>1345519937000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:32:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345519963000-172</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Released 10 Years Of Tax Returns</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345510376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My hero. Every hard working person would love to do that. How about 47,000,000 that paid ZERO taxes?</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345519963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345520031000-173</Id><Topic><Title>Presidents 47,000,000 parasites todate</Title><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345515799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:23:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUMP!!!!!</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345520031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>