<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351570352641-1</Id><Topic><Title>Romney said to President Obama at debate, "you said spontaneous demonstration"</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351539848045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:44:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rose Garden speech was the next day after the attack, and he said the same words the following day, "act of terror", too bad your idea failed, huh. Romney didn't listen to the speech, yet at the debate, in front of everyone, accused the President of saying "spontaneous demonstration." To top it off he argued and went crying up to Crowley who straightened him out. Now faux news is scrambling to divert, hiring anyone and everyone eo say things to divert the camera off Romney's huge amateur blunder. The worrisome part is that Romney is at such a low intellectual level at his age of 65, that he hears false things on politicized shows like faux news and repeats it as fact, with no checking. That disqualifies Romney, not even close to being up to the job of President. C'mon he needs to just go away. enjoy his money, and forget about it.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351570352641</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351570412016-2</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really really awful....spent hours with the disaster...and STILL loathe it !</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1351570412016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351571127385-3</Id><Topic><Title>forbes says would help msft make x box a entertainment device</Title><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351547486428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:51:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's discuss something important,what do you think then again we can talk about romney</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351571127385</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351571290522-4</Id><Topic><Title>Republican,democrats is msft bidding for nflx?</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351551000658</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:50:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really can we possibly discuss msft bid for nflx?</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351571290522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351575519728-5</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Caught Lying Again.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351572405077</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to what source?</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351575519728</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 01:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351585537755-6</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you take into consideration the free stuff that comes with the Surface, it is way cheaper than an iPad. Office 2013 alone is about 200usd. free XBOX Music for 1year is 100usd, free USB, micro HDMI, micro SDXC is about 50usd, then the very high tech keyboard worth 120usd. Plus the best mobile OS. Surface is the cheapest and the best tablet.</Msg><Username>jaceanne_gibson</Username><Timestamp>1351585537755</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 04:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351588203773-7</Id><Title>Steve Ballmer says Windows 8 “preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7”</Title><Msg>Speaking at the Windows Phone 8 launch event Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer also had some reassuring words to say about Windows 8, which launched last week. He said "We’re seeing preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7, which is gratifying. We’re seeing retailers here in the United States and hardware manufacturers enthusiastic about the response." "The demand for touch on all-in-ones and laptops, in addition to tablets, has been really quite astounding, and certainly the lines we’ve seen at the Microsoft Stores have been heartening," Ballmer continued. His statements counter surveys, taken before Windows 8 marketing hit the airwaves, which found only 3% of those surveyed were extremely interested in buying a new PC running the OS. There have been many questions whether Windows 8 will stimulate flagging PC sales, but I suspect this has much to do with whether these devices answer the demand for touch and new form factors, or are only more of the same. One thing that the statement certainly demonstrates is that consumers are not afraid to learn new user interfaces, as demonstrated by their adoption of iOS and Android.</Msg><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351588203773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351589725744-8</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft stock is like Apple in 2002</Title><Username>er45phip</Username><Timestamp>1351560332092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft stock is like MSFT in 2003. Same share price. This stock is going nowhere.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1351589725744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351591153433-9</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Caught Lying Again.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351572405077</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The proof is your desperate attempts to project his mendacity onto others.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1351591153433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351599911332-10</Id><Topic><Title>Turn FOX on NOW AND WATCH CHARLES WOODS NAIL THE MUSLLIM TO THE WALL</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351561268646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:41:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just amazing how much you commies lie for your Musllim Messiah and politicize their deaths by concocting some fairy tale about some video insulting your Musslim Messiah's precious Mu'hammed saying Benghazi was some film maker's fault all while you swine were spinning your intentional web of lies and deceit and then spread that propaganda around for several weeks lying like the liberals you are and then after jigs was up YOU revel in that father's loss just like your blood thirsty Musllim Messiah did as he WATCHED THEM DIE ON LIVE TV WHILE HE ATE POPCORN you blood thirsty brain dead commie more on. He watched them die just as he watched the Bin Laden ordeal transpire on LIVE TV,..... only difference was,...... is that the Bin Laden raid was over in MINUTES, while the Benghazi terrorist attack took OVER SEVEN LONG GRUELING TERROR FILLED HOURS YOU STOOPID PIECE OF ANTI AMERICAN MUSLLIM WORSHIPPING garbage. Your Messiah finally said to Hillary after the first 2 hours or watching it,... turn it off, I'm tired of watching it, I have better things to do like get ready for Vegas baby, YEAH. CLICK!</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351599911332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351599917710-11</Id><Title>HEALTH CARE LAW KEEPS GETTING MORE EXPENSIVE</Title><Msg>Report: Health law's costs continuing to grow By Sam Baker - The most expensive part of President Obama's healthcare reform law keeps getting more expensive. The cost of providing subsidies to help people buy insurance could continue to rise, straining the federal budget more than expected, the conservative American Action Forum said in a paper published Monday. The think tank, led by former Congressional Budget Office director Douglas Holtz-Eakin, compared CBO's initial estimates for the Affordable Care Act to CBO's most recent analysis, issued this summer after the Supreme Court upheld the law. The estimated cost of insurance subsidies has risen nearly 25 percent since the law was passed, according to the AAF analysis. "The lesson is clear: in its brief existence, the ACA entitlement has already increased in cost by nearly 25 percent," the paper states. "Given the continued rise in health care costs in the United States, the stagnation of incomes during the post-2009 recovery, and the large upside risk due to employers no longer providing insurance, there is substantial reason to suspect that the price tag could rise much further yet." After the ACA passed, CBO estimated the federal government would pay a total of roughly $462 billion in subsidies by 2019. In the post-Supreme Court estimate, that total had risen to $574 billion, according to the AAF paper. Expected costs also rose in each individual year — CBO has upped its estimate for 2018, for example, from $106 billion to $129 billion. Some of the increase is a result of the Supreme Court's ruling: the court said states have the ability to opt out of the healthcare law's Medicaid expansion. As Republican-led states take advantage of that option, more Medicaid-eligible people will end up in the exchanges, getting subsidies from the federal government. Although the subsidies are a large new area of federal spending, CBO has said the healthcare law, taken as a whole, reduces the federal deficit. Subsidies will begin to flow in 2014, when new insurance markets known as exchanges are supposed to be up and running in each state. Exchanges will primarily serve people who don't get coverage through an employer, and people with incomes between 100 percent and 400 percent of the poverty level will get subsidies to help pay for their coverage. The subsidies are tied to family income so that poorer families get more help. They're also pegged to the cost of a healthcare plan, rather than a fixed amount of money — meaning the cost of subsidies will go up as healthcare costs continue to rise. Something for Craper to spend all day trying to "debunk". Have a great day!</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351599917710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351600879156-12</Id><Topic><Title>HEALTH CARE LAW KEEPS GETTING MORE EXPENSIVE</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351599917710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:25:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The anti American Marxist Musllim and his commie cohorts knew all that would happen long before he signed into law. It's all about politburo commie control. That's why the Musllim monkey had to force it down the throats of Americans against their will in a purely anti American despotic commie partisan totalitarian fashion. I have some land to sell you in Louisiana, just sign this contract first and I'll show you the land later on,.... if it's okay Bayou.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351600879156</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351602334184-13</Id><Topic><Title>HEALTH CARE LAW KEEPS GETTING MORE EXPENSIVE</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351599917710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:25:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""Although the subsidies are a large new area of federal spending, CBO has said the healthcare law, taken as a whole, reduces the federal deficit."" Well how bout that, ain't dat a good thing?? An wuts wrong with helping people get medical care, RWNJ want them to die and the sooner the better i would guess.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351602334184</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351603473979-14</Id><Title>MSFT insiders selling, Surface a flop, worst opening weekend for a product</Title><Msg>Nobody wants this junk. Stock going into death spiral.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351603473979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351603547185-15</Id><Topic><Title>Turn FOX on NOW AND WATCH CHARLES WOODS NAIL THE MUSLLIM TO THE WALL</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351561268646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:41:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>." So how many attempts at a coverup is that?" One too many! Panetta doesn't wipe his as without the Musllim Monkey's say so and the Musllim Monkey doesn't wipe his own without Soros's. The trail of blood leads DIRECTLY to the Kenyan because it's dripping from HIS hands. When it benefits him like the Bin Laden raid did, the lame steam media show's the Kenyan and his commie cohorts watching it live on tv in the situation room but when he watches the Benghazi terrorist attack in real time with the same commie clan for 7 HOURS and does nothing bur cover it up for political gain because it's his fault that it's happening and it's HIM that did NOTHING TO HELP because it was his own personal blood thirsty war that caused it and armed the rebels, then the same lame stream media suddenly goes dead silent as it tries to help him with his e vill cover up. Fortunately the American people aren't as stoopid as the Kenyan corpse man is and see right through him.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351603547185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351603963090-16</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Caught Lying Again.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351572405077</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama lies daily. His administration is so poisoned with lies, they are not credible at all.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351603963090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351605129732-17</Id><Topic><Title>HEALTH CARE LAW KEEPS GETTING MORE EXPENSIVE</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351599917710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:25:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"want them to die and the sooner the better i would guess." Yep, that's EXACTLY how your blood thirsty Musllim Messiah felt about a certain 4 AMERICANS IN BENGHAZI. After all, he DID have to hurry off to Vegas to campaign and party. But then again, THAT'S why you worship the e vill D min Kenyan thing. Ps. If the blood thirsty Kenyan WOULD HAVE sent help in to save those 4 Americans do you think he would be trying to cover THAT up. I don't think so either. You're so stoopid you stink and a bath won't help. But in your case, it couldn't hurt.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351605129732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351605438258-18</Id><Title>Win 8 is only $14.99</Title><Msg>People on ebay selling the info on how ANYONE can download a $14.99 copy of Windows 8. How does MSFT make money when they are giving away a product that they used to make a fortune off of. I bet they wish they never released this mess.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351605438258</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351605644861-19</Id><Title>Blue state union utility companies fail America</Title><Msg>Yet look at the red states? VA has almost no power outage. Dominion power vs PEPCO. World of difference.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351605644861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:00:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351606590366-20</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Caught Lying Again.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351572405077</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The seven dwarfs always left to go work in the mine early each morning. As always, Snow White stayed home doing her domestic chores. As lunchtime approached, she would prepare their lunch and carry it to the mine. One day as she arrived at the mine with the lunch, she saw that there had been a terrible cave-in. Tearfully, and fearing the worst, Snow White began calling out, hoping against hope that the dwarfs had somehow survived. "Hello, hello!" she shouted. "Can anyone hear me? Hello!" For a long while, there was no answer. Losing hope, Snow White again shouted, "Hello! Is anyone down there?" Just as she was about to give up all hope, there came a faint voice from deep within the mine. "Vote for Romney, Vote for Romney." Snow White fell to her knees, crossed herself and prayed, "oh thank you God, at least Dopey is still alive."</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1351606590366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:16:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351606839113-21</Id><Topic><Title>Win 8 is only $14.99</Title><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351605438258</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what does the activation key cost?? 50-60$?</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351606839113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351606847992-22</Id><Topic><Title>Romney said to President Obama at debate, "you said spontaneous demonstration"</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351539848045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:44:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He did say acts of terror, act, and attack several times. All of it was in reference to the Libya attack with a paragraph on 9/11 which has nothing to do with the reason and message of the speech. You aren't very intelligent, really. Yes the whole Romney interchange was about the rose garden speech specifically, romney wasn't perhaps referring to anything else, and Crowley corrected him on his awful blunder. The argument isn't about two weeks after it is about the rose garden speech the next day, that's what romney attaxked the President on. Romney is unqualified. You lose, start reading there are plenty of references to attack. I highlighted attack, act, and acts. Find spontaneous demonstration in here: Remarks by the President on the Deaths of U.S. Embassy Staff in Libya Rose Garden 10:43 A.M. EDT THE PRESIDENT: Good morning. Every day, all across the world, American diplomats and civilians work tirelessly to advance the interests and values of our nation. Often, they are away from their families. Sometimes, they brave great danger. Yesterday, four of these extraordinary Americans were killed in an ATTACK on our diplomatic post in Benghazi. Among those killed was our Ambassador, Chris Stevens, as well as Foreign Service Officer Sean Smith. We are still notifying the families of the others who were killed. And today, the American people stand united in holding the families of the four Americans in our thoughts and in our prayers. The United States condemns in the strongest terms this outrageous and shocking ATTACK. We're working with the government of Libya to secure our diplomats. I've also directed my administration to increase our security at diplomatic posts around the world. And make no mistake, we will work with the Libyan government to bring to justice the killers who attacked our people. Since our founding, the United States has been a nation that respects all faiths. We reject all efforts to denigrate the religious beliefs of others. But there is absolutely no justification to this type of senseless violence. None. The world must stand together to unequivocally reject these brutal ACTS. Already, many Libyans have joined us in doing so, and this ATTACK will not break the bonds between the United States and Libya. Libyan security personnel fought back against the ATTACKERS alongside Americans. Libyans helped some of our diplomats find safety, and they carried Ambassador Stevens’s body to the hospital, where we tragically learned that he had died. It's especially tragic that Chris Stevens died in Benghazi because it is a city that he helped to save. At the height of the Libyan revolution, Chris led our diplomatic post in Benghazi. With characteristic skill, courage, and resolve, he built partnerships with Libyan revolutionaries, and helped them as they planned to build a new Libya. When the Qaddafi regime came to an end, Chris was there to serve as our ambassador to the new Libya, and he worked tirelessly to support this young democracy, and I think both Secretary Clinton and I relied deeply on his knowledge of the situation on the ground there. He was a role model to all who worked with him and to the young diplomats who aspire to walk in his footsteps. Along with his colleagues, Chris died in a country that is still striving to emerge from the recent experience of war. Today, the loss of these four Americans is fresh, but our memories of them linger on. I have no doubt that their legacy will live on through the work that they did far from our shores and in the hearts of those who love them back home. Of course, yesterday was already a painful day for our nation as we marked the solemn memory of the 9/11 ATTACKS. We mourned with the families who were lost on that day. I visited the graves of troops who made the ultimate sacrifice in Iraq and Afghanistan at the hallowed grounds of Arlington Cemetery, and had the opportunity to say thank you and visit some of our wounded warriors at Walter Reed. And then last night, we learned the news of this attack in Benghazi. As Americans, let us never, ever forget that our freedom is only sustained because there are people who are willing to fight for it, to stand up for it, and in some cases, lay down their lives for it. Our country is only as strong as the character of our people and the service of those both civilian and military who represent us around the globe. No ACTS OF TERROR will ever shake the resolve of this great nation, alter that character, or eclipse the light of the values that we stand for. Today we mourn four more Americans who represent the very best of the United States of America. We will not waver in our commitment to see that justice is done for this terrible ACT. And make no mistake, justice will be done. But we also know that the lives these Americans led stand in stark contrast to those of their ATTACKERS. These four Americans stood up for freedom and human dignity. They should give every American great pride in the country that they served, and the hope that our flag represents to people around the globe who also yearn to live in freedom and with dignity. We grieve with their families, but let us carry on their memory, and let us continue their work of seeking a stronger America and a better world for all of our children. Thank you. May God bless the memory of those we lost and may God bless the United States of America. END 10:48 A.M. EDT</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351606847992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:20:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351606905901-23</Id><Topic><Title>Republican,democrats is msft bidding for nflx?</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351551000658</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:50:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cnbc wendsday</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351606905901</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351607168827-24</Id><Topic><Title>Romney said to President Obama at debate, "you said spontaneous demonstration"</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351539848045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:44:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"No ACTS OF TERROR will ever shake the resolve of this great nation, alter that character, or eclipse the light of the values that we stand for. Today we mourn four more Americans who represent the very best of the United States of America. We will not waver in our commitment to see that justice is done for this terrible ACT. And make no mistake, justice will be done." POTUSA in the Rose Garden the morning after the attack. Nothing about Romney's "spontaneous demonstations." Period.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351607168827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351607615073-25</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT insiders selling, Surface a flop, worst opening weekend for a product</Title><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351603473979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:24:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The East coast is suffering from a major disaster &amp; you sit on your duff staring into a screen &amp; bash MSFT? real good.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351607615073</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:33:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351609027410-26</Id><Topic><Title>Steve Ballmer says Windows 8 “preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7”</Title><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351588203773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why learn a new interface (e.g. Metro) when all it gets you is back to where you have been for years, in thrall to Microsoft?</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1351609027410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 10:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351609379948-27</Id><Topic><Title>Steve Ballmer says Windows 8 “preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7”</Title><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351588203773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why not get somebody to operate the toggle switch for you wotopimp and select Windows 7 mode so you dont have to strain your feeble brain</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351609379948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351609896437-28</Id><Title>Ballmer at the door</Title><Msg>just a little makeup and if Ballmer showed up at the door on halloween he would be terrifying...just sayin...</Msg><Username>paintertoe</Username><Timestamp>1351609896437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:11:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351610627973-29</Id><Title>Paid bashers cut and paste over the web. What do they fear? 8,8,8,8.</Title><Msg>Love my Surface.</Msg><Username>thefarm666</Username><Timestamp>1351610627973</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:23:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351610834200-30</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You can tell everybody I said so." HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR As if anyone gives a flying fk what you say about anything. ROTFLMAO!!!</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351610834200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351610914578-31</Id><Title>Wow, that seeking alpha author is a real loon. Go to his website if you dare.</Title><Msg>Hey seeking alpha guy, get out of your bunker.</Msg><Username>thefarm666</Username><Timestamp>1351610914578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351611589413-32</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting still no word rumor msft to offer nflx 90 dls a sh</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351543480347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>talked to msft they wont confirm if there talking to nflx,says they cant discuss at this time?</Msg><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351611589413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351611794363-33</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It is totally confusing to use" You're obviously too STUPID to use w8.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1351611794363</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351611802338-34</Id><Title>VMware, the bell tolls for thee, and Microsoft is ringing it</Title><Msg>VMworld is about a month behind us now and I’ve had a little more time to noodle on the joint survey I did with virtualization management vendor Xangati. There was a tremendous amount of energy at VMworld and the show floor was one of the biggest and busiest I’ve seen in a long time. This might give one the impression that the VMware franchise is impenetrable, but the survey shows differently. HALLOWEEN: Coolest tech-o-lanterns Before I go through some of the data, remember the survey was answered by current VMware customers, so the data is likely to be skewed pro-VMware, which makes the data even more surprising. VMware has had a virtual (pun intended) monopoly on the market, but there does seem to be some #$%$ in the armor that could be exploited by another solution provider. The first question regarding VMware competition was "What are your plans for implementing Microsoft Hyper-V in your virtual infrastructure?" While 58.5% of the respondent base said they had "no plans," 19.6% said they were currently implementing Hyper-V in production and test and dev environments. Another 20.9% are currently evaluating functionality within Windows Server 2012 for potential future deployment. Considering the survey consisted of existing VMware customers, this is a surprising large number. The decision to bring Microsoft into the environment is being brought in by more of the "hands-on" individuals versus IT management. Of the respondents that are considering or using Hyper-V, 53.2% reported it was the technical team. Another 30.6% of the time it was the manager/director level was pushing for the hybrid environment. And only 16.2% said the VP or CIO level makes the decisions to create a hybrid Microsoft/VMware environment. In the survey, we tried to uncover why customers are looking to add Microsoft to their virtualization environment by asking, "what are the executive-level drivers that are pushing a hybrid VMware/Microsoft hypervisor model?" The most common answer (34.7%) was VMware's licensing and pricing. Another 26.2% chose "Perception that Microsoft functionality is now ‘good enough.’" In some way, these are tied together. If one can get good enough functionality for a better price, why not look at it? Now, it’s no secret that VMware’s vRam pricing scheme wasn’t exactly a hit. The company moving away from vRam may change the minds of some potential defectors. It’s good to see that VMware listened to its customers and heard them with regard to pricing, and were willing to make the change. The second part of the above paragraph – whether or not Hyper-V is "good enough" - seems to be widely believed. Responding to the question - "based upon what you know of Hyper-V in Windows Server 2012 do you believe it can manage the performance of your infrastructure on par with vSphere?" - 52% of the companies said they did believe the technology was equivalent. Another 16.4% said they wanted different hypervisors for different applications. We didn’t ask much detail around this but I’m assuming that there’s a perception that Microsoft applications might perform better on Hyper-V. Only 10.2% responded they were bringing Microsoft in for price leverage, meaning the desire to use Hyper-V seems real. VMware has been an early mover, which is an advantage when combined with a weak competitive landscape for the better part of a decade. As technically sound as Xen is, it doesn’t have near the channel that Microsoft has. So from the survey results, it appears the VMware "free ride" is rapidly coming to an end. The timing of the pricing range was spot on. But watch your back VMware, because Microsoft is coming.</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351611802338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351612006447-35</Id><Topic><Title>Steve Ballmer says Windows 8 “preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7”</Title><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351588203773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hhahahahaha that was hilarious...How easy can one attack those with feeble brain</Msg><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351612006447</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351612054478-36</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting still no word rumor msft to offer nflx 90 dls a sh</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351543480347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, nitwit. If you're going to post the same nonsense using multiple nyms to talk to yourself, try not to misuse the same words and commit the same grammatical errors from nym to nym.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351612054478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351612092916-37</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Storm Affect the Election?</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1351612026761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what do you care- illegal aliens are not allowed to vote anyway</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351612092916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:48:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351612303149-38</Id><Topic><Title>Steve Ballmer says Windows 8 “preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7”</Title><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351588203773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Steve Ballmer says..." Steve Ballmer is a lying sack.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351612303149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351612374259-39</Id><Topic><Title>VMware, the bell tolls for thee, and Microsoft is ringing it</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351611802338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:43:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The above article is from Zeus Kerravala VMware, the bell tolls for thee, and Microsoft is ringing it Survey results from VMworld indicate that Microsoft is becoming a threat to VMware's user base. By Zeus Kerravala on Mon, 10/08/12 - 11:51am.</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351612374259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351612412809-40</Id><Topic><Title>Steve Ballmer says Windows 8 “preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7”</Title><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351588203773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Hhahahahaha that was hilarious..." So is your English.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351612412809</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:53:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351613111395-41</Id><Topic><Title>VMware, the bell tolls for thee, and Microsoft is ringing it</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351611802338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:43:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice work, jerkhov. Copy and paste an entire article and then throw in some attribution as an afterthought in another post. You, like your precious MS, are no respecter of the intellectual property rights of others. Copyright © 1994 - 2012 Network World, Inc. All rights reserved. And before you resort to your tired old tome about Linux being a "copy of UNIX" renamed, remember that it has already been adjudicated otherwise in federal court.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351613111395</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351613514808-42</Id><Topic><Title>Romney said to President Obama at debate, "you said spontaneous demonstration"</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351539848045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:44:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, all wrong, give it up, you lose, period. Learn to read. In your case all you do is meaningless word shifting all day to support your lies. It is getting close again to ignore land because you are really nuts over there sitting in your chair all day. "Of course, yesterday was already a painful day for our nation as we marked the solemn memory of the 9/11 ATTACKS. We mourned with the families who were lost on that day. I visited the graves of troops who made the ultimate sacrifice in Iraq and Afghanistan at the hallowed grounds of Arlington Cemetery, and had the opportunity to say thank you and visit some of our wounded warriors at Walter Reed. And then last night, we learned the news of this attack in Benghazi." Crowley had nothing to admit, she corrected the foolish Romney, "he did say acts of terror" and that was it, there is nothing to admit. you lose again, idiot. The issue is Romney's mistake, it was a big one, disqualifying him.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351613514808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351613622318-43</Id><Title>WINDOWS 8 is a complete "failure"~STOCK to $16-17....AGAIN !</Title><Msg>8 REALLY is awful....DO NOT download it over 7 or XP !!!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351613622318</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351613635340-44</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WIN8 gives all you mindless bashing troll culls the one finger salute. Very strong buy</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351613635340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351613655979-45</Id><Topic><Title>Romney said to President Obama at debate, "you said spontaneous demonstration"</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351539848045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:44:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then why did Candy admit she was wrong?</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351613655979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351613822760-46</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Caught Lying Again.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351572405077</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, so you refuse to reveal the source. That explains a lot. Next.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351613822760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351614191262-47</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT insiders selling, Surface a flop, worst opening weekend for a product</Title><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351603473979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:24:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can see WHY...8 is AWFUL...worse than VISTA ever was.....</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351614191262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:23:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351614275498-48</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Caught Lying Again.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351572405077</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the full transcript: "No acts of terror will ever shake the resolve of this great nation, alter that character, or eclipse the light of the values that we stand for. Today we mourn four more Americans who represent the very best of the United States of America. We will not waver in our commitment to see that justice is done for this terrible act. And make no mistake, justice will be done." What about the phrase "No acts of terror.." in POTUS statement regarding the attack is ambiguous to you, genius?</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351614275498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351614405767-49</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting still no word rumor msft to offer nflx 90 dls a sh</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351543480347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nit wit for your comments on using different names no that never happened,I have positions in 3 stocked msft my largest,nflx and a drug co qcor!</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351614405767</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351614489543-50</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are ya sure yur not talking about Windows RT? Ha.</Msg><Username>ygslvn</Username><Timestamp>1351614489543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351614668192-51</Id><Topic><Title>forbes says would help msft make x box a entertainment device</Title><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351547486428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:51:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Msft needs a blood transfusion,nflx gives Xbox a new meaning that what I think?</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351614668192</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351615216091-52</Id><Topic><Title>Steve Ballmer says Windows 8 “preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7”</Title><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351588203773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>English is not my mother tongue but I speak 4 languages fluently &amp; English is just the 5th...&amp; how about you stuck with just English?.......I traveled the world without a problem that's the advantage, so who cares about grammar if you a traveler...... W8 will be the dominant Ecosystem in less than 2 years &amp; there's nothing you can do about it...Can you......hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351615216091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:40:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351615481891-53</Id><Title>The blood thirsty Kenyan murders 4 Americans in cold blood then tries to cover it up</Title><Msg>And for this, his anti American commie followers love worship glorify and adore him. Because it wasn't any of THEIR family members that were murdered in Benghazi-Gate by the King of cover ups, Hussein, so they couldn't care less. They're worried that their free stuff might stop flowing, so they'll look the other way no matter how many Americans their Musllim Messiah murders. The liberals boo the patriotic Americans as they continue to blow the lid off of Hussein's Bengazi-Gate and cheer the hurricane because it takes the spot light off of their warmonger Musllim master for while. Liberals even hate the father of the fallen war hero, Tyrone Woods, for calling their Messiah what he is,... a "murderer." He knows that SEVEN HOURS is enough time to amass an army let alone scramble an F-16. Nope, the p o s Kenyan said to just send in an UNARMED drone to film it so he could watch for a while before heading off to Vegas to campaign, party, laugh it up and have a good old time.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351615481891</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351615570523-54</Id><Topic><Title>Steve Ballmer says Windows 8 “preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7”</Title><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351588203773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just tried Windows8 -- best feature was it allows you to switch back to the current desktop.</Msg><Username>bowsprit999</Username><Timestamp>1351615570523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351615862859-55</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT insiders selling, Surface a flop, worst opening weekend for a product</Title><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351603473979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:24:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet here you sit posting your nonsense while you "you sit on your duff staring into a screen". Real good.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351615862859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351616315172-56</Id><Title>Msft will open at $32.00 a pop</Title><Msg>Book it huge numbers on 8 surface phone will blow up also.</Msg><Username>bucks0501</Username><Timestamp>1351616315172</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351616396976-57</Id><Topic><Title>BILL GATES "SOLD" 35 million shares on Oct 22,23,24....no wonder...8 is a FLOP !!</Title><Username>pierreperrone</Username><Timestamp>1351615090942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suppose one could say MSFT is know for flops in the last few years and if this ls latest one is bad it is not gonna be good for the stockholders.......</Msg><Username>tradervic1963</Username><Timestamp>1351616396976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351617001951-58</Id><Topic><Title>BILL GATES "SOLD" 35 million shares on Oct 22,23,24....no wonder...8 is a FLOP !!</Title><Username>pierreperrone</Username><Timestamp>1351615090942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>according to ghosanon aka hawfaeces only Microsoft employs have been buying MSFTs stuff boy-- 4 million copies of W-8? I didnt know that Microsoft had 4 million employees- more like less than 100,000--- maybe each employee purchased 40 copies of W-8 to help reach that number- say that would be costly eh- even at $50 a copy would be $2000- what a sacrifice for ole Bill and Steve</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351617001951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:10:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351617284951-59</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Caught Lying Again.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351572405077</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The source, I discovered after you understandably refused to reveal it, is ultra-left wing columnist Oliver Knox. Figures.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351617284951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:14:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351618176900-60</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting still no word rumor msft to offer nflx 90 dls a sh</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351543480347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"on using different names no that never happened" Uh huh... Right... I suppose that it's just a fantastic yet thoroughly believable coincidence that both skipaway and terry_mcowen BOTH inappropriately substitute the adverb "there" meaning "in that place" for the pronoun "their", the possessive case of "they" the usage of which is as an attributive adjective. The most stunning "coincidence" is that you both fail to enter a space between your commas and the word immediately following as in "nflx,says", "happened,I", and "largest,nflx". Yeah... I believe you. Really I do. /sarcasm</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351618176900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351618339000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Caught Lying Again.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351572405077</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 00:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawfaeces II is off in his never never land of denial and endless posting to prove things he knows he lied about. To say Crowley said she agrees with Romney saying spontaneous demonstrations, referring to the argument Romney was having with POTUS, live on TV, is insane. Because we all saw her verify Obama was correct, which of course he was. You can post all the proof and transcripts and hawfaeces II will say it was about 9/11 now. That's his new excuse. He heard that on faux. Oddly why would a President who talked on 9/11 about 9/11, come back on 9/12 to talk about it again as the topic? It's all to take the camera off Romney's Big Blunder at the debate. Not working for most people who saw what happened live. hawfaecesII loses again.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351618339000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351619371590-62</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351618781941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better to have gone bankrupt and moved on than to bail out with tax payer money. Let the investors and bond holders take the brunt of the loss. NO more jobs would have been lost than there were anyway..... I stead they gave GM to the unions and Chrysler to Italy.... SWEET HUH... Plus we taxpayers still hold a large chuck of shares in GM that are way underwater....</Msg><Username>tradervic1963</Username><Timestamp>1351619371590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:49:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351619725517-63</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351618781941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you agree with Mitt that the federal gov should stay out of catastrophys? That the states should handle all of thehelp people need? Where would the money come from if the states handled such situations if the federal gov is not allolwed to help. Mitt proposed this scenario. No gov no FEMA NO help. Just individual states will handle the catastrophys.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351619725517</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351619730743-64</Id><Topic><Title>GM President on tape proudly proclaiming in China that 70% of GM cars are built outside the U.S.</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351619505959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They don't call him Chairman Mao'BO for nuth'in.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351619730743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351619734585-65</Id><Topic><Title>GM President on tape proudly proclaiming in China that 70% of GM cars are built outside the U.S.</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351619505959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They don't call him Chairman Mao'BO for nuth'in.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351619734585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351619842546-66</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Storm Affect the Election?</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1351612026761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will lose votes if it turns into another FEMA Fiasco.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351619842546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351619956663-67</Id><Title>NEW SLOGAN~~~~ "I HATE 8"........Windows 8 is AWFUL...Google it !</Title><Msg>so so bad......the WORST OS ever ..........</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351619956663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351619957337-68</Id><Title>NEW SLOGAN~~~~ "I HATE 8"........Windows 8 is AWFUL...Google it !</Title><Msg>so so bad......the WORST OS ever ..........</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351619957337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351619966665-69</Id><Title>O'Bloodthirsty Caught Lying Again....</Title><Msg>and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and..............</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351619966665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351619976221-70</Id><Topic><Title>Steve Ballmer says Windows 8 “preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7”</Title><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351588203773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ballmer is milking the Deferred Revenue from last quarter.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351619976221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351620289862-71</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably JUST AS BAD !</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351620289862</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:04:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351620352174-72</Id><Topic><Title>NEW SLOGAN~~~~ "I HATE 8"........Windows 8 is AWFUL...Google it !</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351619956663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ditto !</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351620352174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:05:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351620377831-73</Id><Title>Liberal Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Msg>And not just psychologically speaking either.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351620377831</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351620386511-74</Id><Title>Nflx CEO stepping down from msft board end of nov</Title><Msg>Why is the question,is it so to not have a conflict of interest,untill msft refutes the rumor iam inclined to believe Fridays release from both Forbes and benzinga according to their sources?</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351620386511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351620574265-75</Id><Topic><Title>GM President on tape proudly proclaiming in China that 70% of GM cars are built outside the U.S.</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351619505959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That's your Obama" He IS doing a great job, isn't he, even Gov Crispy said so this morning. That was enjoyable to hear. Thanks for that. Maybe you are too young to know GM, Ford, and Chrysler have for many decades been producing large quantities of vehicles outside the USA, and owned many other brands. You don't know jack about much of anything except how to plan bashing sessions on Obama, and how to sit 16 hours in a chair.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351620574265</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351620616949-76</Id><Topic><Title>BILL GATES "SOLD" 35 million shares on Oct 22,23,24....no wonder...8 is a FLOP !!</Title><Username>pierreperrone</Username><Timestamp>1351615090942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ONE WORD for MSFT ....disaster</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351620616949</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351620697073-77</Id><Topic><Title>BILL GATES "SOLD" 35 million shares on Oct 22,23,24....no wonder...8 is a FLOP !!</Title><Username>pierreperrone</Username><Timestamp>1351615090942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The SEC will be a "knockin" on his front door soon ????</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351620697073</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351621145256-78</Id><Topic><Title>BILL GATES "SOLD" 35 million shares on Oct 22,23,24....no wonder...8 is a FLOP !!</Title><Username>pierreperrone</Username><Timestamp>1351615090942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10/24/12 Gates William H III Director Sale 4,500,000 28.03 – 28.03 446,909,000 $126.1 M 10/23/12 Gates William H III Director Sale 5,500,000 28.06 – 28.06 451,409,000 $154.3 M 10/22/12 Gates William H III Chairman of the Board Planned Sale 20,000,000 -- – -- -- $572.8 M Gates William H III Director Sale 4,500,000 28.02 – 28.02 456,909,000 $126.1 M</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351621145256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:19:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351621219837-79</Id><Topic><Title>BILL GATES "SOLD" 35 million shares on Oct 22,23,24....no wonder...8 is a FLOP !!</Title><Username>pierreperrone</Username><Timestamp>1351615090942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10/24/12 Gates William H III Director Sale 4,500,000 28.03 – 28.03 446,909,000 $126.1 M 10/23/12 Gates William H III Director Sale 5,500,000 28.06 – 28.06 451,409,000 $154.3 M 10/22/12 Gates William H III Chairman of the Board Planned Sale 20,000,000 -- – -- -- $572.8 M Gates William H III Director Sale 4,500,000 28.02 – 28.02 456,909,000 $126.1 M</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351621219837</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351621328011-80</Id><Title>HERE THEY ARE~~Bill Gates SELL's on OCT 22,23,24 !!!</Title><Msg>10/24/12 Gates William H III Director Sale 4,500,000 28.03 – 28.03 446,909,000 $126.1 M 10/23/12 Gates William H III Director Sale 5,500,000 28.06 – 28.06 451,409,000 $154.3 M 10/22/12 Gates William H III Chairman of the Board Planned Sale 20,000,000 -- – -- -- $572.8 M Gates William H III Director Sale 4,500,000 28.02 – 28.02 456,909,000 $126.1 M</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351621328011</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351621874391-81</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351618781941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney says we need both with the emphasis on State control. Wrong, He said that states should be totaly responsible for any catastrophy. It is right in his new ad. That the gov should stay out. Who are the first to say we don't want gov involved in what we do. The states are. Then they turn right around and ask for federal assistance. I guarantee you if the states are to be put in charge 100% of the time you will have another katrina everywhere. The states don't have enough where abouts to mobilize quickly enough in the case of a catastrophy.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351621874391</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351621894716-82</Id><Title>rumors of a marriage between msft and nflx heating up!</Title><Msg>just read this isnt going away any time soon?</Msg><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351621894716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351622014540-83</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Advancement for MSFT Read Now!</Title><Username>jallen871</Username><Timestamp>1351611144919</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 11:32:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>markets will decide where each stock wil go</Msg><Username>garyfritch489</Username><Timestamp>1351622014540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351622473396-84</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we're RIGHT ...you need to hook up with the CNBC "hype" crew...8 is AWFUL.....</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351622473396</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351622492421-85</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351618781941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All you need to know to support Romney is he has an energy plan for independence. Maybe you think he is going to walk into office, wave his magic wand and poof more drilling more licenses It doesn;t happen that quick. Plus we have more drilling on public land then we ever have had before. It is the federal land that he is slow on developing. Mitts foreign policies are scary and his tax plan is scary as well. SS will have big changes along with medicare could be totaly gone. His health care plan is suspect as well with existing problems not being covered and also saying he would let the insurance companies run amuck even more. If you are voting for him just for his energy policy, you need to look twice maybe even thrice at the rest of his plans.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351622492421</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351622681936-86</Id><Title>AAPL will lose a war of attrition with MSFT</Title><Msg>Very good Forbes article: Eric SavitzForbes Staff Microsoft was the undisputed winner of the PC era, but the company hasn’t quite found its way in the era of Web 2.0 and social media. The smartphone war is down to two main combatants in software—Apple and Google (GOOG)—and two in hardware—Apple again and Samsung. And despite coming out with a tablet years before anyone else, Microsoft has been left behind on this front as well. Things are about to change. With the long-awaited release of Windows 8, Microsoft is making a real push into the world of touchscreens and tablets. Apple launched the first offensive in the smartphone and tablet wars, but in a long-term war of attrition it is doomed to lose for the same reasons that it lost the original PC war. Apple has always maintained a closed ecosystem and insists on making its own hardware and software. Steve Jobs’ pigheadedness is the reason why it was the Wintel platform and not the Mac that came to dominate the desktop and laptop markets. It’s all happening again. Apple again jumped out to a huge lead, but it will lose the war in the end. And what about Google? I like Google and I personally use an Android phone. But I believe that in a long war it is Microsoft that will win. I question whether Google really takes Android seriously. It’s a free product that generates revenues only indirectly by encouraging mobile web browsing via Google’s search engine. Meanwhile, Microsoft knows how to manage corporate clients, and corporate IT departments are comfortable with Microsoft products to a degree that they will never be with Google or Apple. As a value investor, I often get into trades too early. Not matter how I might try to game myself to avoid this, it seems to be hardwired into my DNA as an investor. So it’s entirely possible that I am early this time as well. That’s ok. If Microsoft takes longer than I expect to rise to the top, we still get to collect its 3.3% dividend and benefit from owning one of the cheapest major blue chip stocks in the world. Microsoft is a buy.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351622681936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351622811608-87</Id><Topic><Title>HERE THEY ARE~~Bill Gates SELL's on OCT 22,23,24 !!!</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351621328011</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SELL boys.............big time ! BACK to $ 15-17 quick !!!!!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351622811608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351622936357-88</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT insiders selling, Surface a flop, worst opening weekend for a product</Title><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351603473979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 09:24:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GET A CLUE poster !!!!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351622936357</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351623728782-89</Id><Topic><Title>BILL GATES "SOLD" 35 million shares on Oct 22,23,24....no wonder...8 is a FLOP !!</Title><Username>pierreperrone</Username><Timestamp>1351615090942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They Sold 4 Million already....</Msg><Username>jravera</Username><Timestamp>1351623728782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351623940671-90</Id><Topic><Title>NEW SLOGAN~~~~ "I HATE 8"........Windows 8 is AWFUL...Google it !</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351619956663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh the humanity...ALOT of firings over this !</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351623940671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:05:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351624156839-91</Id><Title>forbes,in buyout rumorvestopedia,benzinga,biz journal,wall st cheat sheet all reporting</Title><Msg>yea looks like forbes and benzinga sources were on to a possible marriage.</Msg><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351624156839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351624982827-92</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout rumors are 90% or so false, meant to get the big boys out</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351624428967</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you agree at least with what forbes said friday when he ran the buyout piece,that the xbox would become a entertainment device and that xbox is as of now just a game consol?</Msg><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351624982827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351625033678-93</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351618781941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not scary for the informed, SS will have big changes or be broke. Is it fair to ask a burger flipper to pay now on something he can never see under today's plan? Yep it sure is i paid into SS and was self employed for 40 years. So have may other people. How about you have you piad into SS? He didn't say he would let insurance companies run amuck [Mitt said he would let the private sector hunt for better prices.} Hmmm what does that mean. Insurance companies can run amuck and set prices to what they wish. You didn't answer about his foreign policy? Because he totaly agreed with Obama. Only difference is he lied and would have us in another warijust like gun slinger Bush/Chaney Obamacare fails and is intended to result in a European model over time, which is failing in many areas such as availability and rationing. Actualy Obamacare was taken right from Mitts example. Actualy Mitt said that was true and should work in big gov as well as it worked in Mass. Then he changhed his mind like he has 100 other times. Drilling is up and surplus is up. Federal land is the slow developer for oil. Lets not forget Bush was the only president to not raise taxes during war time to help pay for those 2 wars. As well he cut taxes which really created a deficit in which he inherited a surplus from Clinton that he blew right through. Since you seem to be a relatively smart person except for your last sentence. What would you have done if you got a banking system that was out of control, a full blown recession that could of gone into a full blown depression and a job market that was losing jobs in the last 1 1/2 years of the previous admin hand over fist.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351625033678</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351625877841-94</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout rumors are 90% or so false, meant to get the big boys out</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351624428967</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>30 million subs and the shot of streaming video mkt, google and amazon are trying to succeed in that mkt.would defintitely give msft an upper hand in the streaming video mkt.</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351625877841</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351626101569-95</Id><Title>Wow! Obama's military endorsements</Title><Msg>Hugo Chavez, Prime Minister, Venezuela Prime Minister Putin, Russia General Wesley Clark, USA, (Ret)General Colin Powell, USA (Ret)Major General Paul Eaton, USA (Ret)Admiral Donald Gutter, USN, former JAG of the Navy, (Ret)Admiral John Nathman, USN, (Ret)</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351626101569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:41:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351626131993-96</Id><Topic><Title>rumors of a marriage between msft and nflx heating up!</Title><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351621894716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes just within the last couple hrs 5 different media sites are writing there take on a possible marriage!</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351626131993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:42:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351626222543-97</Id><Title>And Romney's military endorsements</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney's Military Endorsements: Admiral James B. Busey, USN, (Ret.)General James T. Conway, USMC, (Ret.)General Terrence R. Dake, USMC, (Ret)Admiral James O. Ellis, USN, (Ret.)Admiral Mark Fitzgerald, USM, (Ret.)General Ronald R. Fogleman, USAF, (Ret)General Tommy Franks, USA, (Ret)General Alfred Hansen, USAF, (Ret)Admiral Ronald Jackson Hays, USN, (Ret)Admiral Thomas Bibb Hayward, USN, (Ret)General Chuck Albert Horner, USAF, (Ret)Admiral Jerome LaMarr Johnson, USN, (Ret)Admiral Timothy J. Keating, USN, (Ret)General Paul X. Kelley, USMC, (Ret)General William Kernan, USA, (Ret)Admiral George E.R. Kinnear II, USN, (Ret)General William L. Kirk, USAF, (Ret)General James J. Lindsay, USA, (Ret)General William R. Looney III, USAF, (Ret)Admiral Hank Mauz, USN, (Ret)General Robert Magnus, USMC, (Ret)Admiral Paul David Miller, USN, (Ret)General Henry Hugh Shelton, USA, (Ret)General Lance Smith, USAF, (Ret)Admiral Leighton Smith, Jr., USN, (Ret)General Ronald W. Yates, USAF, (Ret)Admiral Ronald J. Zlatoper, USN, (Ret)Lieutenant General James Abrahamson, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Edgar Anderson, Jr., USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Marcus A. Anderson, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Buck Bedard, USMC, (Ret.)Vice Admiral A. Bruce Beran, USCG, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Lyle Bien, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Harold Blot, USMC, (Ret.)Lieutenant General H. Steven Blum, USA, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Mike Bowman III, USN, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Mike Bucchi, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Walter E. Buchanan III, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Richard A. Burpee, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General William Campbell, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General James E. Chambers, USAF, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Edward W. Clexton, Jr., USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General John B. Conaway, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Marvin Covault, USA, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Terry M. Cross, USCG, (Ret.)Vice Admiral William Adam Dougherty, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Brett Dula, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Gordon E. Fornell, USAF, (Ret.)Vice Admiral David Frost, USN, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Henry C. Giffin III, USN, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Peter M. Hekman, USN, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Richard D. Herr, USCG, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Thomas J Hickey, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Walter S. Hogle, Jr., USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Ronald W. Iverson, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Donald W. Jones, USA, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Douglas J. Katz, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Jay W. Kelley, USAF, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Tom Kilcline, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Timothy A. Kinnan, USAF, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Harold Koenig, M.D., USN, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Albert H. Konetzni, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Buford Derald Lary, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Frank Libutti, USMC, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Stephen Loftus, USN, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Michael Malone, USN, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Edward H. Martin, USN, (Ret.)Vice Admiral John J. Mazach, USN, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Justin D. McCarthy, USN, (Ret.)Vice Admiral William McCauley, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Fred McCorkle, USMC, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Thomas G. McInerney, USAF, (Ret.)Vice Admiral Joseph S. Mobley, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Carol Mutter, USMC, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Dave R. Palmer, USA, (Ret.)Vice Admiral John Theodore "Ted" Parker, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Garry L. Parks, USMC, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Charles Henry "Chuck" Pitman, USMC, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Steven R. Polk, USAF, (Ret.)Vice Admiral William E. Ramsey, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Joseph J.. Redden, USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Clifford H. "Ted" Rees, Jr.., USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Edward Rowny, USA (Ret.)Vice Admiral Dutch Schultz, USN, (Ret.)Lieutenant General Charles J. Searock, Jr., USAF, (Ret.)Lieutenant General</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351626222543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351626640429-98</Id><Title>MSFT will go past 30, Windows 8 selling very well.</Title><Msg>Expect to go quickly past 30. A lot of analsts think it will hit 38 by Q2, 2013.</Msg><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351626640429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351626681878-99</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, here is an experiment: try to get to the Paint application from desktop mode in less than 3 clicks. Under Metro, look at the labels for where drive formatting are located, etc. It's a mess that turns basic UI rules from the last 30-years on their head. Metro is, basically, Zune on your phone, tablet and desktop computer. Or, try this: Hand a four-year old an iPad and a Surface. See which one is playing Angry Birds before the other. iOS is, IMO, 100X more intuitive and consistent as a UI. I'm telling you - Windows 8 will not be widely accepted in the enterprise. Windows 7 will be just like XP with a 5-10 year extended shelf-life.</Msg><Username>sillymuppets</Username><Timestamp>1351626681878</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351626805188-100</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I mean there are two ways to use it. The mobile interface and the standard Desktop. Isn't that right? So are you sure you're talking about the standard operation.</Msg><Username>ygslvn</Username><Timestamp>1351626805188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351626847608-101</Id><Title>Maria looks nice her mouth not roughed up like weekdays</Title><Msg>i notice it appears she must have to take a long lunch break.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351626847608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351626985503-102</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465650294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ballmer really bit the big one with Windows 8. Maybe Windows 9 will be better?</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1351626985503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351626990626-103</Id><Topic><Title>GM President on tape proudly proclaiming in China that 70% of GM cars are built outside the U.S.</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351619505959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And I am working " five Pinocchios rating</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351626990626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:56:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351627127352-104</Id><Topic><Title>rumors of a marriage between msft and nflx heating up!</Title><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351621894716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still talking to yourself?</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351627127352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351627153991-105</Id><Topic><Title>NEW SLOGAN~~~~ "I HATE 8"........Windows 8 is AWFUL...Google it !</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351619956663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a good thing Microsoft had the free Windows 8 Consumer Preview. Now less people will have to waste their money on it.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1351627153991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351627177064-106</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting still no word rumor msft to offer nflx 90 dls a sh</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351543480347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5 media sites are now reporting the buyout rumor,starting to get more interesting!</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351627177064</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351627424984-107</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351618781941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>answer to your energy and why things are picking up 30 October 2012 A natural gas company wants to build a 1,300-mile pipeline to carry crude oil from North Dakota through easternmost Wyoming on its way to the nation’s biggest storage terminal in central Oklahoma. Tulsa, Okla.-based Oneok Partners LP said the proposed Bakken Crude Express Pipeline would cost between $1.5 billion and $1.8 billion and would have the capacity to move 200,000 barrels of crude daily from the heart of North Dakota’s rich oil patch to the hub in Cushing, Okla. “As producers continue to aggressively develop crude oil from wells in the Bakken Shale, more crude oil pipeline takeaway capacity will be required,” Oneok Partners President Terry Spencer said in a media release. “This proposed pipeline will provide producers with efficient and reliable transportation of their product directly to one of the largest crude oil market hubs in the U.S.” Oneok spokesman Brad Borror said his company is negotiating commitments with oil suppliers that could put it on track to begin construction next year and complete a pipeline by 2015. Pipe threads eastern Wyo Oneok says the pipeline should closely follow the company’s earlier-announced 500-mile Bakken Pipeline, a $430 million to $500 million line to move Bakken play natural gas liquids — ethane, propane, butane and natural gasoline — from a gathering point in Montana through Wyoming and into the Overland Pass Pipeline in Colorado. Oneok project maps show the natural gas liquids pipeline entering Wyoming at its far northeastern corner before passing just west of Newcastle, east of Lusk and arcing around Torrington before heading due south into Colorado to meet the Overland Pass line. An Oneok map for its newly announced oil pipeline shows a track that mirrors its natural gas liquids pipeline. Eighty percent of the proposed oil pipeline’s path would follow Oneok’s existing or planned natural gas pipeline routes, Borror said. “We are currently working with producers of natural gas and natural gas liquids, so this would allow us to be a full-service provider,” Borror said. Construction on the natural gas liquids line is expected to begin next month and finish early next year, according to Oneok. Boon to Wyo producers The new pipeline isn’t only good for Bakken producers, who are struggling with ways to ship oil from North Dakota. Wyoming oil producers have faced pipeline jams with crude from the Bakken and Canada, tamping down prices for the product from the Rocky Mountain region, said Brian Jeffries, Wyoming Pipeline Authority executive director. The situation mirrors the former issues that plagued Wyoming natural gas producers, who had to contend with limited pipeline capacity to transport their product to consumers, which kept prices low. New, large natural gas pipelines have come on-line and solved the problem. “Principally, the Bakken growth has filled up the pipelines in this area, so oil sells for a discount compared to the oil in Cushing,” Jeffries said. As new pipelines come on-line, including Oneok’s Bakken Crude Express and a few lines between Cushing and the Gulf Coast, oil from Wyoming and other Rockies producers won’t be as steeply discounted, Jeffries said. That’ll likely spur investment and more production, and more tax revenue for the state, he said. “You start to unlock the whole bottleneck all the way from Wyoming to the Gulf Coast,” he said. Oil gluts North Dakota Shippers increasingly are using trains to get crude out of North Dakota, with rail shipments accounting for about a quarter of the more than 546,000 barrels produced daily in the state, said Justin Kringstad, director of the North Dakota Pipeline Authority. North Dakota is the nation’s third-largest oil producer and is expected to trail only Texas in crude output within the next year. The state’s burgeoning oil production is out pacing the ability to efficiently move the product to market, causing drillers to take deep price cuts. Oneok’s plan brings to six the number of pipeline projects proposed to help ship crude out of the Bakken shale and Three Forks-Sanish oil reservoirs in western North Dakota, Kringstad said. But he said commitments from suppliers will determine which projects become reality. Kringstad called Oneok’s proposal “very substantial” but said the market will determine if any of the proposed pipelines are built. “Ultimately, it will be up to the industry to decide which of the various projects it wants to support,” Kringstad said. Oneok also has nearly $2 billion in projects planned to ship and process natural gas and natural gas liquids from western North Dakota to Midwest and Rocky Mountain markets, Borror said. You would of let some of them go [banks] go broke but not all Not a sufficent answer. "Not scary for the informed, SS will have big changes or be broke. Is it fair to ask a burger flipper to pay now on something he can never see under today's plan Do you know how many times i heard that SS wasn;t going to bethre whe i get ready to take my first check. Enough times to pay for my SS. It is still here. perpetuate a slimy ponzi scheme foisted upon the country by liberals who are now dead and knew they would be when the bill came due. Liberals have no real conscience, just a pretend one. A typical neocon answer..................nasty tone Obama is transferring trillions from the middle class to the same crooks by printing money (the QEs) and low interest rates, pumping the market for re-election, to hell with the future. We avoided a deep deep depression you think that kid would be flipping burges if that happened? Alright then if you have these types of feelings then i suggest you give back all the money you have made in this market the past few years. Since you consider the money tainted and not worthy of your high standards set by ones self. Hey Bush had a surplus what did he do with it? He said to hell with the future i got 1war and i want another war with NO Means to pay for 2 wars. SS won"t be in trouble till 2224 under Obama. Under Mitt 2016 SS will be gone you need to do more reading hawk.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351627424984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351627444647-108</Id><Topic><Title>GM President on tape proudly proclaiming in China that 70% of GM cars are built outside the U.S.</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351619505959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would it be to much trouble for you to check into how many are SOLD outside the U.S. I will be glad when the lection is over and you can #$%$ with these cheap ignorant shots at our president.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351627444647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351627522996-109</Id><Topic><Title>Maria looks nice her mouth not roughed up like weekdays</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351626847608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:54:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the napkins must rough up the mouth area.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351627522996</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351627683366-110</Id><Title>Idy ot creek aka mr watkins is foaming at the mouth ridiculously.</Title><Msg>Most of it doesn't make half as much sense as his usual posting which is quite a low point indeed. Like the GM makes 70% of its cars outside the U.S. post. What about the other makers? What % are sold outside the U.S. Why does this have to do with the president keeping vast numbers of jobs going in the US in GM as well as the vast numbers of GM suppliers who would have closed down and left their other car customers in the lurch for parts.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351627683366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351628475674-111</Id><Topic><Title>Maria looks nice her mouth not roughed up like weekdays</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351626847608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:54:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>being Italian she must have a lot of sausauge,</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351628475674</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:21:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351628736208-112</Id><Topic><Title>NEW SLOGAN~~~~ "I HATE 8"........Windows 8 is AWFUL...Google it !</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351619957337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I googled 'Windows 8 Sucks' and Google found 55,800,000 search results. When I googled 'Windows Vista Sucks' there were only 1,090,000 search results. So this means Windows 8 sucks 51 times worse than Vista. On a side note, when I did a Bing search for 'Windows 8 Sucks' and only 22,700,000 search results were found.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351628736208</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351628787488-113</Id><Topic><Title>Nflx CEO stepping down from msft board end of nov</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351620386511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:06:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now5 different media sites are reporting possible buyout,starting to believe the rumor from Friday.nflx did 3 times vol and was up over6 dls</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351628787488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351628822479-114</Id><Topic><Title>Java Might Be a Has-Been......</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351620243510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:04:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not as Has-Been as Microsoft's Silverlight!</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351628822479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351629037685-115</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT will go past 30, Windows 8 selling very well.</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351626640429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great: im thinking 32-33</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351629037685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351629713270-116</Id><Topic><Title>Maria looks nice her mouth not roughed up like weekdays</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351626847608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:54:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sausage drips a lot.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351629713270</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351629822332-117</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT will go past 30, Windows 8 selling very well.</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351626640429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had some doubts about Windows 8 but I bought it on Sunday and installed it on my laptop. This is a great OS</Msg><Username>zoso925</Username><Timestamp>1351629822332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351629953793-118</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT will go past 30, Windows 8 selling very well.</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351626640429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With 3% dividend, what a great buy it was on Friday. Glad I added to my position.</Msg><Username>dscmsunw</Username><Timestamp>1351629953793</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351630201432-119</Id><Title>Obama the Master Debater Must have been....</Title><Msg>practicing his mater debating during the Benghazi attack.</Msg><Username>obamas_100_iq</Username><Timestamp>1351630201432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351630643992-120</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT will go past 30, Windows 8 selling very well.</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351626640429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>smart move:heading to 30s and div will increase over time.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351630643992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:57:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351630957125-121</Id><Topic><Title>NEW SLOGAN~~~~ "I HATE 8"........Windows 8 is AWFUL...Google it !</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351619957337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Installed Windwos 8 for a few days, and have to unstall !! It is so bad thant basically unusable !!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bjjc053053</Username><Timestamp>1351630957125</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631123352-122</Id><Topic><Title>NEW SLOGAN~~~~ "I HATE 8"........Windows 8 is AWFUL...Google it !</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1351619957337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are obviously too Stupid to use W8..!! Swallow a watermelon seed and grow a brain.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1351631123352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351631344405-123</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL will lose a war of attrition with MSFT</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351622681936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:44:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple's propriettary product system is their Achillies heel,MSFT's products will work with everything.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351631344405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351631496598-124</Id><Title>(PVHO) Provision inc. has made interactive glassless 3D slots, is microsoft</Title><Msg>looking into this company to expand on their gaming consuls. They need this technology to get more gamers and also create TV channels with music libraries on their consuls. they can change TV by grabbing market share from cable and satelite tv...</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1351631496598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:11:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351631879648-125</Id><Title>Why do we need a president ??</Title><Msg>Every one of them screws up something, spends too much money and blames the other party for something. The system has proved itself flawed as it tries so hard to turn us against each other, really sad. Can't we vote none of the above.</Msg><Username>alias_4ever</Username><Timestamp>1351631879648</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632128888-126</Id><Topic><Title>Why do we need a president ??</Title><Username>alias_4ever</Username><Timestamp>1351631879648</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who would we get to ride around in Air Force One 24/7?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351632128888</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632286028-127</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351618781941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a typical liberal, give me mine and eff the other guy. Not true. I totaly beleive like my parents and their parents before them. You pay ito the system. if you don't like it then don't pay or move. I see you were alost for words with the rest of my post. Pick and chose you are doing. Like i said give back all the money you have made if the policy was bad in you eyes. But that will never happen will it. Your kind complains but is happy to make money off of what you complain about. How ironic............</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351632286028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:24:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632516612-128</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351618781941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fact we can keep printing money and keep it liquid, not sure you'll be happy with $20 gas and $15 a loaf bread once the trillions printed returns to circulation. WEll i guess if gas goes that high then Mitt doesn't need to drill drill drill baby. His energy policy is out the window, Because the money will retuen eventually. I don't eat bread and we will be in a deep depression.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351632516612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632720144-129</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351618781941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Christie made some good comments about Obama today, finally some sense out of a republican. Gave a lot of praise to Obama, it was great. The only thing no one thought of is all Christie had to do was stand on the shore and block it</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351632720144</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351632722485-130</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Talking Heads Are Mad</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351618781941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 13:39:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is eaxactly what i was trying to press on creek. The states cannot handle it all on their own but this is what Mitt wants. Less gov better for the states when it comes to a catastrophy. I couldn't believe what i heard.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351632722485</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351633538067-131</Id><Topic><Title>And Romney's military endorsements</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351626222543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NICE!!!! And the only traitorous "military" schmuck that is backing the blood thirsty Black Panther Musllim mutt is another Black Power bro named Colin commie Powell (D). And the ONLY reason he's voting for him is because he's black. Because if he wasn't, he would be the last person he would vote for. Remember when Eric Holder referred to blacks as "My people" when talking about the Black Panther voter intimidation case in Philly that he TOTALLY ignored. Talk about racism and division among "Americans?" Holder, Hussein and Powell are always yelling BLACK POWER at their meetings. I wonder why? Obamma appointed more radical Musllims in his regime than Mahmoud Ahmadinejad's.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351633538067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351633875972-132</Id><Topic><Title>Why do we need a president ??</Title><Username>alias_4ever</Username><Timestamp>1351631879648</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Populice vote doesn't really matter that has been proven/You have to be special with the electorial vote cast.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351633875972</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351633925249-133</Id><Topic><Title>rumors of a marriage between msft and nflx heating up!</Title><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351621894716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all right mkt opens wendsday then we will get some answeres once and for all i think ?</Msg><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351633925249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351634020037-134</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Storm could cost as much as $20B, same an\mount Obama quietly stole from the middle class</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351633394622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>20bilion....20billion... skip skip skip....zzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351634020037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:53:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351634458344-135</Id><Topic><Title>And Romney's military endorsements</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351626222543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>racial thinking like this is why we take people like you and ship them out. You set americans back 50 years.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351634458344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351634668765-136</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Storm could cost as much as $20B, same an\mount Obama quietly stole from the middle class</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351633394622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>which news company. Lets see who wrote this..................another neocon person and station.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351634668765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351634770032-137</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Storm could cost as much as $20B, same an\mount Obama quietly stole from the middle class</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351633394622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The link to the crime itself was in the news, provided several times when permitted." ??oh well then, you have proved it....zzzzzzz</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351634770032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:06:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351635147547-138</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Storm could cost as much as $20B, same an\mount Obama quietly stole from the middle class</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351633394622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when permitted????????????? I really don't subscribe to neocon writings. Proof please.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351635147547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351635159720-139</Id><Topic><Title>Sandy Storm could cost as much as $20B, same an\mount Obama quietly stole from the middle class</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351633394622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when permitted????????????? I really don't subscribe to neocon writings. Proof please.</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351635159720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:12:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351635217746-140</Id><Title>Ronmey sez he wants to</Title><Msg>WALK AROUND THE DEVASTATION WITH CHRISTIE, WITH CAMERAS ON. CHRISTIE SAYS BLANKETY BLANK .U Yet earlier Christie gives a lot of Praise to Obama. Isn't it Great?</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351635217746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351635280046-141</Id><Topic><Title>forbes,in buyout rumorvestopedia,benzinga,biz journal,wall st cheat sheet all reporting</Title><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351624156839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:09:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only the lonely wanting to make a decision wednesday,will either company set the record straight?</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351635280046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351635615301-142</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey sez he wants to</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351635217746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:13:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>proof...............or more hypotheticalism from you..............</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351635615301</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351635628245-143</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey sez he wants to</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351635217746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:13:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>proof...............or more hypotheticalism from you..............</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351635628245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:20:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351635779356-144</Id><Topic><Title>Ok....Romney's Going To Win.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351635281085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:14:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So he has the naked cowboy with a geetar and Ted nugent who gets busted for illegaly hunting. Nice band so far. i guess Mitt can be the drummer and P90X will be the front man like Cheney..............</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351635779356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351637089050-145</Id><Topic><Title>Want proof that Obama stole $20B to give to the UAW</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351636612377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:36:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i thought you had something new.......Shooooooooooooooot come on man. It wasn't a crime or a robbery or anything that was hidden.............Geeeeeeeeeeeesh</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351637089050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351637301388-146</Id><Topic><Title>HEALTH CARE LAW KEEPS GETTING MORE EXPENSIVE</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351599917710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 08:25:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check out Chuck Woolery's commercial pointing out that AARP was in cahoots with the Kenyan and monetarily coerced a certain vote from a hold out to seal the D min's anti American deal forcing his commie health care scam down America's throat and now they're selling the elderly down the pike by their Musllim Messiah robbing $716 billion from Medicare. And AARP said that they weren't going to get involved in the political aspect of it, which, as it turns out, was a flat out lie. They're in the tank for the terrorist in the White t hating House.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351637301388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351637556021-147</Id><Title>LOADED WINDOWS 8 GARBAGE, BACK TO WIN 7 WORSE THAN VISTA</Title><Msg>and millilium mistakes. Horrible interface and major software campatibility issues, happy back to windows 7</Msg><Username>ibrant57</Username><Timestamp>1351637556021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351637582749-148</Id><Title>Obamma is his own worst enemy</Title><Msg>And America's too!!!</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351637582749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351638288974-149</Id><Topic><Title>Want proof that Obama stole $20B to give to the UAW</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1351636612377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:36:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think creek should make it quick and painful. just go vote..............</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351638288974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351638763994-150</Id><Title>Creek reports wrong side of CC</Title><Msg>CC governor of NJ was asked if he minded Mitt coming to NJ and spend sometime with CC going over matters. CC said i really don't care to i am very busy and i have NO need for a political motive. Good for him........ haw creek the desever.............</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351638763994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351639425727-151</Id><Topic><Title>LOADED WINDOWS 8 GARBAGE, BACK TO WIN 7 WORSE THAN VISTA</Title><Username>ibrant57</Username><Timestamp>1351637556021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all microsoft has done is play a shell game with the frustrated consumer, its horrible</Msg><Username>ibrant57</Username><Timestamp>1351639425727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351639549401-152</Id><Topic><Title>Creek reports wrong side of CC</Title><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351638763994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:12:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hawrcreek10, me, is an Obama supporter. The other one, hawcreek12, is a newer name on here that is an imposter of me, trying to degrade my Obama campaigning. He supports Romney of course, as he imagines Obama will take away his govt checks "just because." I think that's what you were getting at.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351639549401</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351639632645-153</Id><Topic><Title>Creek reports wrong side of CC</Title><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351638763994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:12:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is a silly debate....................later</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351639632645</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351639635120-154</Id><Title>Quid Pro Quo</Title><Msg>.... the blood thirsty Musllim got to go! Vote Patriot, vote Romney/Ryan and leave the blood thirsty Kenyan alone and cry'in.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351639635120</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:27:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351640308564-155</Id><Topic><Title>The blood thirsty Kenyan murders 4 Americans in cold blood then tries to cover it up</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351615481891</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:44:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a fact for you. Heard a comment on talk radio today that was very true.Caller said when Obama asked the SEALS for help, they were there.When a SEAL asked for help, Obama turned him down....and the SEAL died along with three others. Spin that.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351640308564</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:38:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351641293108-156</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting still no word rumor msft to offer nflx 90 dls a sh</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351543480347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hello are you reading the articles yesterday and today both days msft marriage to nflx repeated by 5 different sites,explaining msft and nflx would both win.</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351641293108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:54:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351641408870-157</Id><Topic><Title>Creek reports wrong side of CC</Title><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351638763994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:12:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"presidential. Satan likely sent the storm to help Obama." Wow, I had no idea Soros was that powerful.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351641408870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351642051214-158</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT will go past 30, Windows 8 selling very well.</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351626640429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>news out today that msft has sold 4 millions of Win 8 during the 1st 4 days in the market. This sounds really encouragin, and i hope they have also sold a nice number of Surface too. It is reported that quite many retails styores have sold out the Surface computers. In a couple of months, MSFT will also start to sell Surface Pro. Extra revenue from Surface computers as well as extra of some 2 billions of extra revenue carried over from the last 2 quaters will push top line for the next quater and the quater after really exciting!!!! expect great things from MSFT!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1351642051214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:07:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351642251698-159</Id><Topic><Title>Creek reports wrong side of CC</Title><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351638763994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:12:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is a silly debate.................... yes, it is, and that's how it becomes around hawcreek12. His conclusions are so far off the mark after awhile it becomes comical arguing with him. Romney definitely is not President or Presidential, and should shut up and get out of the way.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351642251698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351642623640-160</Id><Topic><Title>Steve Ballmer says Windows 8 “preliminary demand well above where we were with Windows 7”</Title><Username>riwm45</Username><Timestamp>1351588203773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 05:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>some 20 years ago, most peole used just using desktops, then for the last 10 years or so, most pople wre using laptops, and i think it is quite possible that over the next 10 years, people will star t to use mostly hybrid of (laptop and tablets). MSft represents the future, not Apple nor google!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1351642623640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351642624029-161</Id><Topic><Title>Creek reports wrong side of CC</Title><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1351638763994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 19:12:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawfaeces finally moves his raceometer a point up and says Obama looks Presidential. But that isn't the point now is it. The point is work needs to be done as people not party. I am surprised at Christie, he stepped up. Satan? Not quite, it's called weather coming from physical causes.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351642624029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351643855681-162</Id><Title>I like windows 8</Title><Msg>For 39 dollars, I feel like I purchased a new computer. It is like a tablet as well as like a desktop, take your pick. I will buy some MSFT stock tomorrow, now that AAPL is going down.</Msg><Username>jai_hakim</Username><Timestamp>1351643855681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351644143998-163</Id><Topic><Title>Ok....Romney's Going To Win.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351635281085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:14:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some days you get the bear and some days the bear gets you,.... but Ted didn't kill 4 Americans and run off to Vegas.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351644143998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351644290479-164</Id><Topic><Title>Why do we need a president ??</Title><Username>alias_4ever</Username><Timestamp>1351631879648</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need a president to tell idiots like you what to do.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1351644290479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351644389200-165</Id><Topic><Title>Ok....Romney's Going To Win.....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351635281085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:14:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because the smell of your diaper alerts the poor black children of your presence at 100 yards.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1351644389200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351645512736-166</Id><Title>Why a bidding war starts for Netflix below, 100-120 by friday out of aapl into NFLX cramer said sell aapl</Title><Msg>Tomorrow is going to be a blast, billions flow out of aapl and billions flow into NFLX over the next few weeks. Netflix could double in a hurry! If Microsoft was to offer 120 a share. I really believe Amazon would beat it for its Kindle fire. And my gut tells me microsoft would come back with a higher offer. They want this for the new xbox, the reason is it could be the deciding factor between the kid and parents that can't decide to get the kid the new xbox or new playstation that will be out not this christmas but next. If Sony was smart they would bid on Netflix, for the price they could get netflix for, (yes even after a bidding war) they can't build one better with such loyal customers, (and they are loyal) Even Google would have something to gain from Netflix. They could link it right to the google cloud for instance. No doubt in my mind this turns into a bidding war. The average kid will say yeah but with the xbox you get all the netflix movies with the xbox live suscription or something like that. If Sony Playstation does not wake up, they will be saying "what do you mean microsoft is selling 45% more xboxes because Microsoft has Netflix now. Sony would be #$%$, but it will be on them for not thinking, people that play games, also like to sit back with a joint when they are tired of playing gamesand watch a movie, and a lot of these kids just moved out and will spend every last dollar they have on a videogame system and games each month, but they can't afford cable when 90% of what is on they don't want to see anyway. People 10-30 like movies and only certain tv shows, dexter, boardwalk empire, boss,shameless</Msg><Username>namfong43</Username><Timestamp>1351645512736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:05:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351646265471-167</Id><Topic><Title>I like windows 8</Title><Username>jai_hakim</Username><Timestamp>1351643855681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>win 8 will be the start that will unite desktops, to laptops, to tablets, to x-boxes, then to smartphones. From big screen to small screen, no other company is in the positon to do this but MSFT!!!!! Someone has to think ahead for all of us. I hate to use different systems for different uses.</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1351646265471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351646489063-168</Id><Topic><Title>LOADED WINDOWS 8 GARBAGE, BACK TO WIN 7 WORSE THAN VISTA</Title><Username>ibrant57</Username><Timestamp>1351637556021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wins is to the past, and Win 8 is to the future. closed minded and stubbern is the sure a big loss. sooner or late, one has to learn Win8. It is way better to be now than later. Comaputers wree never desiged for lazy people! Do not wanting to learn is a presciption for for loser!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1351646489063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:21:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351646651858-169</Id><Topic><Title>LOADED WINDOWS 8 GARBAGE, BACK TO WIN 7 WORSE THAN VISTA</Title><Username>ibrant57</Username><Timestamp>1351637556021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"one has to learn Win8" No, I don't. No one has to, and no one cares. The company you shill for is going down.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351646651858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351646706564-170</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL will lose a war of attrition with MSFT</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351622681936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:44:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is no better thing than having Win 8 crating the standards for desktops, laptops, to tablets, to smatphones, and to X-boxes. Only MSFt wil be ablt to make this happen. One needs to look down the road 10 years from now, and 100 years down the road. Expect great things from MSFT!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1351646706564</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351647343369-171</Id><Title>MSFT is more like Rodney Dangerfield, gets no respect unfortunately!</Title><Msg>MSFT is like a trusted mule that is not attractive to look at, but carries heavy loads day after day without complaining. Unfortunately, the financial media and wall street honchos in general are enamored with a show horse called Apple. One should remember that show horses have very limited tenure, perhaps a few years (until people become tired of Iphone XXXLV and Ipad XXXLV!). Perhaps if charisma deficit baldy Balmer is replaced by Brad Pitt, we hapless, long suffering share holders would be richer, for a change.</Msg><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351647343369</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351648418956-172</Id><Topic><Title>Java Might Be a Has-Been......</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351620243510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:04:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Java is the language of choice in schools. There are many thousands of cheap Java developers. So it remains popular and the cycle continues.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351648418956</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351649012412-173</Id><Topic><Title>I like windows 8</Title><Username>jai_hakim</Username><Timestamp>1351643855681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's so funny how we all like Windows 8, and these posters tell us it's no good, msft is doomed. But, I will buy a surface and upgrade my Windows phone in the next few months. I absolutely love my windows phone and it's last years model. Can't wait for the new one.</Msg><Username>dscmsunw</Username><Timestamp>1351649012412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351649067724-174</Id><Topic><Title>Why a bidding war starts for Netflix below, 100-120 by friday out of aapl into NFLX cramer said sell aapl</Title><Username>namfong43</Username><Timestamp>1351645512736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow that's quite amazing you really put some good stuff down.</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351649067724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351649509658-175</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT will go past 30, Windows 8 selling very well.</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351626640429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now they have sold 8 million copies, pace ahead of Windows 7</Msg><Username>dscmsunw</Username><Timestamp>1351649509658</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351649775990-176</Id><Topic><Title>Msft will open at $32.00 a pop</Title><Username>bucks0501</Username><Timestamp>1351616315172</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:58:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have sold 8 million copies of Windows 8 already. I love it, so I will add to the total.</Msg><Username>dscmsunw</Username><Timestamp>1351649775990</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351650081934-177</Id><Topic><Title>Msft will open at $32.00 a pop</Title><Username>bucks0501</Username><Timestamp>1351616315172</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 12:58:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dubious claim self-serving claim, made only by Microsoft itself, is 4 million. You lie just like the company you shill for.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351650081934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351650113557-178</Id><Topic><Title>I like windows 8</Title><Username>jai_hakim</Username><Timestamp>1351643855681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and 14 other people.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351650113557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351650142044-179</Id><Topic><Title>Java Might Be a Has-Been......</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351620243510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:04:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's actually what I was referring to.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351650142044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351650325622-180</Id><Topic><Title>Why a bidding war starts for Netflix below, 100-120 by friday out of aapl into NFLX cramer said sell aapl</Title><Username>namfong43</Username><Timestamp>1351645512736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're pulling 120 a share out of the air. A bidding war is possible at $90, not $120. Direct TV could easily offer $92 a share, in turn I can see MSFT offering $94 a share which would be approx $5.2 Billion, which is just a tad over the $4.9 Billion they are currently speculated to have offered NFLX. For MSFT, $4.9 or $5.2 Billion is lunch money. On top of all this, the synergies between nflx and msft is what Hastings wants and Gates needs!</Msg><Username>e2ebuzz</Username><Timestamp>1351650325622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:25:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351652001401-181</Id><Topic><Title>I like windows 8</Title><Username>jai_hakim</Username><Timestamp>1351643855681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, Windows 8 is like watching reruns of "Family Ties" in 2012 because you like fluffy hair and neon clothes from 1987- it looks like a cross between the Zune UI and M$FT Bob (or Windows 3). It's absolutely, horrendously ugly and dysfunctional.</Msg><Username>sillymuppets</Username><Timestamp>1351652001401</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:53:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351652472976-182</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting still no word rumor msft to offer nflx 90 dls a sh</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351543480347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:44:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post bidding war,well written nanfong</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351652472976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351654002933-183</Id><Topic><Title>LOADED WINDOWS 8 GARBAGE, BACK TO WIN 7 WORSE THAN VISTA</Title><Username>ibrant57</Username><Timestamp>1351637556021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you have to learn a new OS, then why not Mac OSX, iOS, Android or Linux? Windows 8 ain't the only game in town you know. 40% of users either switched to non-Microsoft products or they're sticking with XP.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351654002933</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:26:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351654597361-184</Id><Topic><Title>Why do we need a president ??</Title><Username>alias_4ever</Username><Timestamp>1351631879648</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without a president, what would everybody discuss on this message board? Microsoft stock has been stagnant for a decade. MSFT is just plain boring. Except for Windows XP and Windows 7, this company is losing market share at an alarming rate. Windows 8 won't help MSFT market share with the lame Metro graphical interface. No Start Menu? Many users will 'Start' by swtiching to other products.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351654597361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351654755356-185</Id><Topic><Title>I like windows 8</Title><Username>jai_hakim</Username><Timestamp>1351643855681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 20:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are you smokin? Is Microsoft offering free medical marijuana coupons with Windows 8? Maybe more people would buy Windows 8 if ther were on drugs!</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351654755356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351654767475-186</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Visio 2010 has no upgrade edition available.</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351651715636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 22:48:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get serious man- Visio 2010 isnt necessarily the very last edition of Visio. Either an upgrade is coming for Windows 8 or the Visio functions will be available in another program which is W-8 compatible. Get in touch with Microsoft and see if Im not right</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351654767475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351654851698-187</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT will go past 30, Windows 8 selling very well.</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351626640429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 15:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, right. How much of that 8 million copies is Deferred Revenue from last quarter?</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351654851698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351654978968-188</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT is more like Rodney Dangerfield, gets no respect unfortunately!</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351647343369</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:35:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ballmer gets no respect. The day Ballmer was born, the doctor slapped his mother.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351654978968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351655059702-189</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL will lose a war of attrition with MSFT</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351622681936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:44:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ware of attrition will be lost by Windows 8. Lots of users will switch to other products after disliking the Metro tile interface.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351655059702</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351655079106-190</Id><Topic><Title>Why do we need a president ??</Title><Username>alias_4ever</Username><Timestamp>1351631879648</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you got it right- the RWNJs have now ceded so much power to the super rich oligarchs of this country that they soon will be able to run the country behind the scene (Charles and Dvid Koch, The Scaifs and Mellons, The Olins, Duponts etc) -- so Romeny will merely be a figurehead faking it and pretending to be president</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351655079106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351655390067-191</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL will lose a war of attrition with MSFT</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351622681936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:44:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lots of users will switch to other products</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1351655390067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351655568710-192</Id><Topic><Title>LOADED WINDOWS 8 GARBAGE, BACK TO WIN 7 WORSE THAN VISTA</Title><Username>ibrant57</Username><Timestamp>1351637556021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 18:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>watsa matta cant get it to install on your 386 dumpster computer??</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351655568710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:52:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351655963191-193</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT is more like Rodney Dangerfield, gets no respect unfortunately!</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351647343369</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:35:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rodney Dangerfield original joke (paraphrased): I was so ugly as a baby, every time my dad wanted to have sex, my mom would show my picture, he would simply walk away! Regarding Balmer, my guess is that the doctor slapped both his dad and mom and tried to choke Balmer!.</Msg><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1351655963191</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351655971051-194</Id><Topic><Title>Why a bidding war starts for Netflix below, 100-120 by friday out of aapl into NFLX cramer said sell aapl</Title><Username>namfong43</Username><Timestamp>1351645512736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 21:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have a question you end your head line with Cramer....</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1351655971051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>