<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-02"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346558705284-1</Id><Title>Obama/Biden = Dumb/Dumber</Title><Msg>Two buffoons!</Msg><Username>negrolover2012</Username><Timestamp>1346558705284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346558787256-2</Id><Title>How many buffoons to destroy country?</Title><Msg>Obama/Biden!!!!</Msg><Username>negrolover2012</Username><Timestamp>1346558787256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346558885371-3</Id><Title>Two stupid to lead Obama/Biden</Title><Msg>Too much!</Msg><Username>negrolover2012</Username><Timestamp>1346558885371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:08:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346558991105-4</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Admitted Killing Simpson Bowles Thru Ryan</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1346528491197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:41:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There have been some neuroscientists who have been mapping the way the minds of conservatives work and on the whole, they really don't work that well. That does not mean I am going to call them mental rejects, but there minds and way of thinking just ain't normal.</Msg><Username>repub_taliban</Username><Timestamp>1346558991105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:09:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346589646520-5</Id><Topic><Title>Norquist Admitted Killing Simpson Bowles Thru Ryan</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1346528491197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:41:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well we always knew that about the ole flat earth society</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346589646520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346589900839-6</Id><Title>just a reminder Obama does Not support infanticide</Title><Msg>in spite of that liar that we have to suffer on this board who calls himself reasonable but ought to change it to reasonless. Obama never has nor does he now support infanticide. Further more no Democrat has supported infanticide except for infanticide of republican children</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346589900839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346597989934-7</Id><Topic><Title>John Wayne and Clint Eastwood are true American Patriots</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1346595230288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:13:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And they both heroicly defended America on Iwo Jima in WWII and always wore white hats and rode white horses in their movies. With this sort of background they captured the undying loyalty of every ignorant american racist redneck for ever more and now we have to put up with these knuckle dragging neanderthals for ever more (I guess the neanderthals went extinct after about 25000 years tho)</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346597989934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:59:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346598278738-8</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle CIO: Linux is Fundamental</Title><Username>phands.theheretic3</Username><Timestamp>1346596515985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:35:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That CIO best have Larry's assent-trying to back 'sucks- else he is history--truth is Oracle has run fine on Windows for many years and the vast majority of applications run on Windows today with a small minority percentage running on 'sucks</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346598278738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346598615540-9</Id><Title>Oracle CIO mentions that Oracle runs on Linsux-</Title><Msg>It sure does but who cares- 75-80% of Oracle runs on Windows. That CIO best have Larry's assent-trying to back 'sucks- else he is history--truth is Oracle has run fine on Windows for many years and the vast majority of applications run on Windows today with a small minority percentage running on 'sucks....</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346598615540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346598669908-10</Id><Topic><Title>John Wayne and Clint Eastwood are true American Patriots</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1346595230288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:13:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Marion Morrison A.K.A John Wayne. No service of any kind to the United States, only to his screen image. Clinton Eastwood Jr. Swimming instructor and bouncer at NCO club at Fort Ord during Korean War. Carefully cultivated "tough guy" image onscreen. Former Mayor of Carmel CA (two years). Both fakes.</Msg><Username>nd1005</Username><Timestamp>1346598669908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346598860460-11</Id><Title>Dems = 8+% unemployment and rising after 4 years, 45% of Americans on Welfare, jobs, whats that???</Title><Msg>Dems = 8+% unemployment and rising after 4 years, 45% of Americans on Welfare, jobs, whats that??? all because the baggers and flat earthers in the house wont let any of Obamas jobs bills thru- they would rather destroy America than let Obama succede in his presidency</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346598860460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599436304-12</Id><Topic><Title>Dems = 8+% unemployment and rising after 4 years, 45% of Americans on Welfare, jobs, whats that???</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346598860460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:14:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone who believes there are flat landers in the House would also believe that when Obama had two years of House and Senate majority, he couldn't get any jobs bills through. I guess that is what they mean by brainwashing. You will believe anything those who brainwashed you say. Pretty sad for the young, but for your age, I wouldn't admit it.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1346599436304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346600049979-13</Id><Topic><Title>Dems = 8+% unemployment and rising after 4 years, 45% of Americans on Welfare, jobs, whats that???</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346598860460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:14:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all of those who havent been brainwashed by the Oligarch kazillions such as the Kochs own agree that big money is buying elections, buying votes, electing baggers and flatearthers who then repay their masters by blocking every iota of Obamas legislation even if it means the country slides into depression- Obamas first two years were spent overturning the past 100 years of republican efforts to block health care for Americans and passing the Health Care Reform Act and his next project was a vast program to increase imployment- but he lost his house majority and now these automatons of the right who have made their H.i.t.l.er oath to Grover Norquist to not raise taxes to fund any jobs programs have arisen to destroy america and they certainly wont allow Americans to have jobs</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346600049979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346600276988-14</Id><Topic><Title>John Wayne and Clint Eastwood are true American Patriots</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1346595230288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:13:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both fakes???????????? Oh my Gawd I will now have to end it all if I cant believe in the purity and heroism and and etc!!!!!</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346600276988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346600362703-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney loses cool with reporter that catches him in a lie</Title><Username>shapingtechnologies</Username><Timestamp>1346488864625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shapingtechnologies.. YOU POST THE same LIES ON GM BOARD. F$$ # YOU LIER. IGNORE</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1346600362703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346603117874-16</Id><Title>Gingrich, Huckabee and Me: Obama Supports Infanticide</Title><Msg>The fact that Obama voted for infanticide 4 times when he was in the Illinois Senate is now in the national political news. Gingrich spoke of it today on Meet the Press, Huckabee spoke of it several times on national TV. There is no more heinious crime than murdering living, born babies ... and that is exactly what Obama voted for when he was in the Illinois Senate and he now lies about it. Obama is a murderous ghoul and people who support him are either uninformed of this, misinformed or purposeful supporters of infanticide. Which are you?</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346603117874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346603183048-17</Id><Topic><Title>Gingrich, Huckabee and Me: Obama Supports Infanticide</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346603117874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:25:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America is slowly waking up to the bloody agenda of Obama and the Democrat Party.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346603183048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346603291078-18</Id><Topic><Title>just a reminder Obama does Not support infanticide</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346589900839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:45:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can deny it all you want ... but America is now learning that Obama voted for infanticide 4 times when he was in the Illinois Senate. It's now going national.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346603291078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:28:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346603511338-19</Id><Topic><Title>Just a Reminder: Obama Supports Infanticide</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346545494307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:24:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yes, now he supports same sex "smarriage". There is no pit so full of slime that Obama will not swim in it.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346603511338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346603646469-20</Id><Topic><Title>Gingrich, Huckabee and Me: Obama Supports Infanticide</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346603117874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:25:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speak up Obama supporters ... which are you? Do you also support infanticide?</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346603646469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346610475795-21</Id><Topic><Title>What we need is a neutral factchecker for factcheckers</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1346609438543</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love how when it was pointed out that the Fact Checkers were wrong, Donna Brazille didn't want "to get into the weeds with that". It is easier to just call Ryan a liar but when they can prove he isn't, theydon't want to go there.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1346610475795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:27:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346610515156-22</Id><Title>Let's Talk About Microsoft...Not this Political #$%$!!!</Title><Msg>MS will Shoot past IBM...this is my prediction looking at all the indicators....and P...I don't care to hear your thoughts so FO!</Msg><Username>jravera</Username><Timestamp>1346610515156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346610658280-23</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and Ryan trying to look like Ronald Reagan</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1346609428935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Desperate is Obama cracking jokes "while blacks are drowning".</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1346610658280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346611901049-24</Id><Topic><Title>Two stupid to lead Obama/Biden</Title><Username>negrolover2012</Username><Timestamp>1346558885371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:08:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, there may be truth to that. According to Kiplinger Mag., when looking at their financial discloure documents, they indicate that while Obama has investing and debt issues, Biden was the absolute pits. What disturbed the financial planner is how much debt the Biders, have,given their income and ages. Because they have numerous loans, the couple have just $215,000 in net worth. (that's pitiful) Hope Biden doesn't end up in charge. On the other hand, they say that Romnney's portfolio is sophisticated, complex and well diversified. Romney has a finger in virtually every pie.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1346611901049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346612253381-25</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and Ryan trying to look like Ronald Reagan</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1346609428935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't say Obama said that. I was saying it because I was repeating what the Yahoo guy said about Romney. Saying "while blacks are drowning" definately is not a joke. His speeches yesterday was all jokes about black and white TV's with rabbit ears. Get with it will ya?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1346612253381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346613505131-26</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and Ryan trying to look like Ronald Reagan</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1346609428935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was cracking jokes while blacks were drowning. Learn comprehenive reading idiot.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1346613505131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:18:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346613700886-27</Id><Title>The Liberal hate machine and Mia Love</Title><Msg>President Obama’s version of America is a divided one — pitting us against each other based on our income level, gender, and social status,” she said at the convention. “His policies have failed! We are not better off than we were 4 years ago, and no rhetoric, bumper sticker, or campaign ad can change that. The speech also inspired some animosity, as reflected in edits to her Wikipedia page. “Though the changes have since been removed, screen grabs posted to various websites show one section called her a “dirty, worthless whor” who sold out to big business,” Fox News observed. “Another section again called her a “sell-out” to the “right wing hate machine,” before accusing her of being exploited “like the House N—– she truly is.”</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1346613700886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346614413112-28</Id><Title>Paul Ryan Lies Like Richard Nixon</Title><Msg>“A downgraded America.” Ryan blamed the president for the nation’s credit downgrade in August 2011 after Republicans threatened to allow the government to default on its debt for the first time in history. But the ratings agency explicitly blamed “Republicans saying that they refuse to accept any tax increases as part of a larger deal.” . Obama “did exactly nothing” on Bowles-Simpson. Ryan said, “He created a bipartisan debt commission. They came back with an urgent report. He thanked them, sent them on their way, and then did exactly nothing.” In fact, Ryan was instrumental in sabotaging the commission, leading the other House Republicans in voting against the plan. “$716 billion, funneled out of Medicare by President Obama.” Ryan’s favorite lie is a deliberate distortion of Obamacare’s savings from eliminating inefficiencies. Furthermore, Ryan’s own plan for Medicare includes these savings. Romney has vowed to restore these cuts, which would render the trust fund insolvent 8 years ahead of schedule.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1346614413112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:33:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346614517936-29</Id><Title>Communist Obama's anti Romney ads are laughable</Title><Msg>The stupid POS Moslim and his moronic anti American ad says that Romney made big profits for his business ventures? Yep, that's something that the commie Libs don't want to see Romney doing for America!! Commies hate profits and success, they'd rather destroy and bleed America as their Kenyan messiah spends America into oblivion to bankrupt the nation.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1346614517936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346616357336-30</Id><Topic><Title>John Wayne and Clint Eastwood are true American Patriots</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1346595230288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:13:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW dumbbutt Austrian exists and its otherwise known as high German or Hochdeutsch- so if you are so stoooopid as to think Obama didnt know what Hochdeutsch was then you are one stooooopid SOB</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346616357336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 16:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346616904379-31</Id><Topic><Title>just a reminder Obama does Not support infanticide</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346589900839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:45:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yes we deny it- and you can consider yourself very fortunate to live in that insane asylum that lets you post in their library still. BTW if you would take your anti psychoses medication instead of spitting it out when nobody is looking you might be able to leave your institution. But if you did that you would have to get a job to support yourself and we know how shifless you are HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346616904379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 16:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346619592827-32</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Lies Like Richard Nixon</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1346614413112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:33:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan's speech was riddled with lies.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1346619592827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 16:59:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346622413713-33</Id><Title>The perfect bumper sticker will say</Title><Msg>"The Somalian Pirates, Osama Bin Laden are dead, General Motors is alive." That will win the election no matter how much the conservatives wring their hands over the demise of Bin Laden laden are dead</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1346622413713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346622501000-34</Id><Title>What happened?</Title><Msg>Good ol' MSFT board is deader than WindowsPhone sales!</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1346622501000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625206353-35</Id><Topic><Title>Google -Mother Of Fallen SEAL Rebukes Obama, Clinton-</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1346605281108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:01:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah the puke wimps couldnt get the job done- It took Obama HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346625206353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625621985-36</Id><Topic><Title>John Wayne and Clint Eastwood are true American Patriots</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1346595230288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:13:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blindboa eh- your real description is "criminal". You are nothing but an evil republican crook who doesnt know how to wipe his own a... Criminals like you have preyed on Democratic societies world wide thruout history and you have brought some of them down - and now you want to destroy America by bringing the government to a halt - anything to get Obama------- We used to hang traitors</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346625621985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346625897588-37</Id><Title>SOLYNDRA............</Title><Msg>YOUR TAX $$$ DOWN THE TUBE...... OBAMA'S GOOD BUSINESS SENSE.</Msg><Username>tunerads</Username><Timestamp>1346625897588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:44:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625905810-38</Id><Topic><Title>How many buffoons to destroy country?</Title><Username>negrolover2012</Username><Timestamp>1346558787256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:06:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its criminals like Ryun and Romney who want to destroy america along with such "patriots" as egrolover2012</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346625905810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346626087136-39</Id><Title>New bigger computer &amp; Vista SLOWER THAN EVER!</Title><Msg>Really disappointed! Older computer with Win2k &amp; FireFox was faster. Probably dump IE8 and get FireFox! I miss AdBlock on FireFox! New messageboard format sucks too.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346626087136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346630913894-40</Id><Topic><Title>John Wayne and Clint Eastwood are true American Patriots</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1346595230288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:13:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's GERMAN you stoooopid SOB. Its not either GERMAN you stooooopid SOB Its High German!! and the German word for it is Hochdeutsch or sometimes simply Austrian you stoooooooooooopid SOB</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1346630913894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346635618190-41</Id><Topic><Title>John Wayne and Clint Eastwood are true American Patriots</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1346595230288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:13:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Group says it found 30,000 dead North Carolinians registered to vote Democrat. Voter Integrity Project has no evidence of any ballots cast in their names. Posted: Sunday, Sep. 02, 2012 RALEIGH A Raleigh-based group devoted to reducing the potential for voter fraud presented the N.C. Board of Elections on Friday with a list of nearly 30,000 names of dead people statewide who are still registered to vote. The Voter Integrity Project compiled the list after obtaining death records from the state Department of Public Health from 2002 to March 31 and comparing them to the voter rolls. “Mainly, what we’re concerned about is the potential [for fraud],” said project director Jay DeLancy. “Since there is no voter ID law in North Carolina, anybody can walk in and claim to be anyone else.” DeLancy said his group has found evidence to suggest voter fraud in these numbers, but will not quantify how much until he is able to do more analysis. Most cases of what look like a dead person voting are likely just administrative errors, such as a son named Junior voting in his father’s name instead of his own.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1346635618190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346638401157-42</Id><Title>Let the Obamanure Convetion Begin</Title><Msg>Do they have the dump trucks lined up to shovel the amount of Obamanure that will be generated?</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346638401157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346638752741-43</Id><Title>DNC = Democrats Nurturing Communism</Title><Msg>Convention will be an Obamanure Communist love fest!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346638752741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346638908989-44</Id><Title>The perfect bumper sticker!</Title><Msg>"Two stupid to lead Obama/Biden" Thanks poster!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346638908989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346639062785-45</Id><Title>Paul Ryan Lies Like Obama/Biden</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346639062785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639231607-46</Id><Topic><Title>Two stupid to lead Obama/Biden</Title><Username>negrolover2012</Username><Timestamp>1346558885371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:08:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it only took less than four years to realize!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346639231607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639396242-47</Id><Topic><Title>How many buffoons to destroy country?</Title><Username>negrolover2012</Username><Timestamp>1346558787256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:06:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama, Biden, Pelosi, Reid, The Black Congressional Caucus, any Democrat in Congress, or as Governor or in a state legislature. Not to mention one despicable RINO in the Supreme Court, plus one lesbian (or maybe two.)</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346639396242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639428829-48</Id><Topic><Title>Two stupid to lead Obama/Biden</Title><Username>negrolover2012</Username><Timestamp>1346558885371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:08:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except that his portfolio is in a Blind Trust and he doesnt make any of the decisions much less have knowledge of what the Trustee does. But Biden truly is an idiot, Obama is just incompetent.</Msg><Username>k24chat</Username><Timestamp>1346639428829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:30:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346639518086-49</Id><Title>Two Empty Suits: Obama/Biden</Title><Msg>Clint should have had two empty seats! Plus another bumper sticker!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346639518086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346639684996-50</Id><Title>Mitt Romney gave 15% to charity...</Title><Msg>Obama and Biden gave 1%. They really care !</Msg><Username>tunerads</Username><Timestamp>1346639684996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:34:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346639806729-51</Id><Title>DNC CONVENTION....Sandra Fluke and Jimmy Carter ?</Title><Msg>HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAAHAHA!</Msg><Username>tunerads</Username><Timestamp>1346639806729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639810657-52</Id><Topic><Title>How many buffoons to destroy country?</Title><Username>negrolover2012</Username><Timestamp>1346558787256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:06:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget the Left Wing Funded Occupy Radical Communists fully supported by Obama/Biden!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346639810657</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346639888901-53</Id><Title>"Occupy Radical Communists for Obama/Biden", new bumper sticker!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346639888901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639969707-54</Id><Topic><Title>How many buffoons to destroy country?</Title><Username>negrolover2012</Username><Timestamp>1346558787256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:06:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346639969707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346640026099-55</Id><Title>Why does Sandra Fluke need.....</Title><Msg>birth control pills ? One ugly #$%$ !</Msg><Username>tunerads</Username><Timestamp>1346640026099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346640067875-56</Id><Title>How many Obamanurists to attend DNC Communist Convention this week?</Title><Msg>Any guesses?</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346640067875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346640117822-57</Id><Topic><Title>New bigger computer &amp; Vista SLOWER THAN EVER!</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346626087136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:48:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ IE8 just keeps taking up more memory and more memory and more memory. It's kind of like a virus all by itself! Is IE9 REALLY any better?</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346640117822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346640481396-58</Id><Title>"Leaderless/Rudderless - Obama/Biden" another bumper sticker</Title><Msg>Time to throw out the trash!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346640481396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346640838821-59</Id><Title>do you think that MFST will buy 10% of NOKIA?</Title><Msg>could that be for real? Cool</Msg><Username>coolzorro46</Username><Timestamp>1346640838821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346640925888-60</Id><Topic><Title>do you think that MFST will buy 10% of NOKIA?</Title><Username>coolzorro46</Username><Timestamp>1346640838821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ooouuups....sorry....it is MSFT....OK? Cool</Msg><Username>coolzorro46</Username><Timestamp>1346640925888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346641542333-61</Id><Topic><Title>Gingrich, Huckabee and Me: Obama Supports Infanticide</Title><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346603117874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:25:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama supporters know he voted for infanticide but they won't touch it because they know it is indefensible. Cowards.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346641542333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346641642822-62</Id><Topic><Title>The Liberal hate machine and Mia Love</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1346613700886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:21:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals are despicable. No bottom to their baseness.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1346641642822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:07:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>