<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351052146953-1</Id><Title>WHAT FUTURE DO YOU WANT FOR YOUR CHILDREN?</Title><Msg>Nanny president obama will give your children hand outs. president romney will get jobs for your children and make them independent. if they are smart they can even get rich. Imagine, rich.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351052146953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:15:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351061998126-2</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT FUTURE DO YOU WANT FOR YOUR CHILDREN?</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351052146953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 00:15:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBAMA POISONED YOUR MIND. I FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351061998126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 02:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351062158475-3</Id><Title>OBAMA, CLINTON,PRICE,BIDEN LIED ABOUT LIBYA TO AMERICAN PEOPLE.</Title><Msg>How can you trust them? Do they believe we are stupid?</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351062158475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 03:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351062344725-4</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA, CLINTON,PRICE,BIDEN LIED ABOUT LIBYA TO AMERICAN PEOPLE.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351062158475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 03:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They believe you are stupid, because you are stupid for electing them.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1351062344725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 03:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351063026007-5</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA, CLINTON,PRICE,BIDEN LIED ABOUT LIBYA TO AMERICAN PEOPLE.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351062158475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 03:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did not vote for obama and will not vote for obama. But i know of many people who voted for him in 2008 and are voting for romney in 2012. At least some people wised up.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351063026007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 03:17:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351069158937-6</Id><Title>Strong earnings preview from MPartners - Reporting a Milestone quarter today after market</Title><Msg>- Interdigital ( NASDAQ:IDCC ) is about to explode, check out the reasons for the $45 Price target from MPartners ( last night ) - This quarter IDCC recognized revenue from its first batch of patent assets sold to Intel for $375M (announced in June 2012) and also received positive ruling from the CAFC regarding its appeal of a 2009 ITC decision in favor of Nokia with respect to two 3G essential patents. - The recent good news has been undermined by underperformance of its core 3G licenses. Particularly revenue from per unit licensees continued to erode because handset vendors in Japan, along with RIM, and HTC continued to lose market share to Samsung and Apple. Samsung and Apple are both fixed-term licensees where revenue streams are unaffected by volumes. OUTLOOK SHOULD BE SOLID We believe that due to the timing of asset sales, as well as license renewals and outcomes of litigation, that quarterly results are difficult to forecast. However, we should continue to see an annualized trend towards growth through licensing, partnerships, and asset sales. This is reflected in our sum-of-the-parts analysis below. Our estimate of cash includes our estimate incremental cash that resulted from the sale of the patents to Intel. We reiterate our BUY recommendation and our 12-month share price target of $45.00. Our estimate excludes licensing revenue from Nokia, Huawei, ZTE, and LG, which are all involved in litigation with Interdigital currently. Yesterday's the stock closed with a gain of 5% in the after hours trading. Calls are also very active lately</Msg><Username>patentsaddicted</Username><Timestamp>1351069158937</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 04:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351073268569-7</Id><Title>FOCK GOERGE W BOUSH AND LIKE ILK</Title><Msg>Goerge Boush and Anglosaxon Republicans are dangerous killers, rapists, and genocidists. Real American People should FOCK these Anglosaxon Republican jerks.</Msg><Username>rozaliakott</Username><Timestamp>1351073268569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 06:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351074593121-8</Id><Title>EU regulators charge Microsoft over browser breach</Title><Msg>Oct 24 (Reuters) - EU antitrust regulators charged Microsoft on Wednesday for breaching a 2009 order to offer a choice of web browsers to consumers on its Windows 7 operating system, the first step to a possible hefty fine. _________________________________________ This is so typical. Microsoft does the right thing only with a gun to its head.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1351074593121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 06:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351076269992-9</Id><Title>2 black N.J. teens murder 12 year old white girl for her bike</Title><Msg>Their mother turned them into the police. Both of the racist pieces of blood thirsty entitlement minded white hating she it were wearing Obamma T-shirts too. No need to go figure either. The 2 pieces of she it murdered her in cold blood and then left her body in a recycling dumpster. Awwwww, how nice of the little thoughtful liberals. Now Al Sharpton will come out and defend them and say she wouldn't be dead if she would have just given them anything they wanted because she's white and they're black and they deserve whatever they want just because they're black and she's white. Obamma will probably have them to the white house and give them an award too. The Musllim P O S will protect them under his Sharia Law. He told them to say that it was an anti Isslam video that she made that made them do it. He told them it will work like a charm.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351076269992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 06:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351076968806-10</Id><Topic><Title>2 black N.J. teens murder 12 year old white girl for her bike</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351076269992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 06:57:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awwww the blood thirsty black nice young men lured the wittle 12 year old girl to their home by telling her that they wanted to trade some bike parts and then they strangled her to death. Their mother read her 17 year old son's Tweet saying that they were probably going to be moving and it made her suspicious. Al Sharton said that they should be allowed to keep the bike.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351076968806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351077295757-11</Id><Topic><Title>UH OH, just reported on FOX, the Musllim KNEW it was a terrorist attack IN REAL TIME</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351044547991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Turn off MSNBC and watch a real news channel and you'll see you fat old black broad. Your Musllim Messiah is a blood thirsty murderer trying to cover up his crimes and anti American maggot fat old racist black women like you try to protect the d min p o s. O'Musllim knew in REAL TIME it was a terrorist attack because he watched it on closed circuit tv along with Hill r e. Hussein is pure e vill and so is anyone that defends him and worships the vermin Musllim.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351077295757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351077569059-12</Id><Title>xkruushiatin is a commie maggot and a moooslim terrorist and a traitor to the USA</Title><Msg>aint that right maggot</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351077569059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:19:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351077693336-13</Id><Title>Romney and the Musllim TIED in Ohio at 48%</Title><Msg>The blood thirsty Musllim is toast. Especially after he gets the chair for all of his crimes. Maybe Obamma's Benghazi-Gate cover up of lying to the American people will help him out though. No, not really. The blood thirsty warmongering d min is done for.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351077693336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351077813460-14</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and the Musllim TIED in Ohio at 48%</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351077693336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:21:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmussen just reported those numbers this morning but you won't see them on MSNBC how much we lie to you.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351077813460</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:23:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351078350108-15</Id><Title>REPUB philosophy = SOCIALISM among Anglosaxons, but Rape and Kill and Capitalism for others</Title><Msg>Republican Anglosaxons are against health care reform because they cannot tolerate the concept of socialist health care being enjoyed by NON-ANGLOSAXONS. In their mind, good medical facilities and medicines should be made available only to White Anglosaxons, and that Non-Anglosaxons should get substandard medical care. The concept of socialist health care for all (like Canadian health care) sends shudders down REPUBLICAN ANGLOSAXON spines.</Msg><Username>repubs_r_crooks</Username><Timestamp>1351078350108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351078810914-16</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft stuck a deal with MIMV to further develope Azure and Bing for the latest Windows 8 push. I'm curious what the potential is here. After looking at what Azure can do I got interested. Right now MIMV is a saerch engine for Mobile apps. After hearing Larry Page talk last week about Search and Apps merging together, i thought MIMV would be a long shot, but is sitting in the sweet spot to make this happen.</Msg><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351078810914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351078831508-17</Id><Title>The U.S. Military has 176 horses and over 400,000 bayonets</Title><Msg>Thank God the Musllim is brain dead stoopid and wasn't allowed to have his tele prompter. Without it his true ignorance always shows. He knows nothing of the Military, other than it hates him with an American Patriotic PASSION. It would have been funny to watch the Kenyan's handlers cringe when their monkey lied about the military's weapons in the debate knowing that he's out there without his life line tele prompter or commie Crowley since he's so uneducated low IQ brain dead corpse man stoooopid. And blood thirsty too. This country has no president but it will when Mitt Romney takes over. Say bye bye to the Kenyan spy. "The Army said today it has 419,155 bayonets in its inventory. The Marine Corps has another 195,334 bayonets that it bought in 2004 and it plans on buying 175,061 more bayonets this year. A Marine official says it’s not accurate to add the two totals together as the new ones will include replacements for ones already in service as well as additional stocks. The Army also reported today that it has 176 horses. The horses kept at Fort Myer, Va., are used mainly for ceremonial duties at Arlington Cemetery and the Capital region. There are also some horses located at Fort Hood, Texas. The Marine Mountain Warfare Training Center in California trains Marines in using horses, mules and donkeys to carry supplies in mountainous regions." Yep, the Military has horses, mules and donkey's and one them is a Jihadisst Jackasss IN THE WHITE HOUSE.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351078831508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351078956460-18</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you obviously don't know what potential hosting SQL apps in the cloud can do. It would save hundreds of company's developement time to go to the cloud.</Msg><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351078956460</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:42:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351080016579-19</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. Military has 176 horses and over 400,000 bayonets</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351078831508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xcruyshiatn you traitor to your president and country get off this board go join your pals in Russia or in Iran</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351080016579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351080155543-20</Id><Title>WOW, even commie leftist night show host, Conan, rips on the Musllim</Title><Msg>He showed the Kenyan at one of his commie rally's trying to cheer up his worshipers by showing them his new 5 step plan in his pamphlet and when it's opened up to show the Kool-Aid drinkers it says, "Re-kill Bin Laden again." The commie Kenyan's radical racist blood thirsty regime is a huge joke and an even bigger tragedy for America. God Bless Stacey Dash for she is a true American patriot, she voted for President Romney. And the commies are coming unglued and savagely attacking her like the Kenyan did to President Romney.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351080155543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:02:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351080793063-21</Id><Title>Obamma's Pimp with a Limp</Title><Msg>How did Soros hurt his leg?</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351080793063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351082378539-22</Id><Title>Mossberg's Surface review in The Wall Street Journal</Title><Msg>Very positive. Plenty others are mixed but the WSJ is maybe the most important commentary vis a vis effect on the stock price. Looks like it wants to pop.</Msg><Username>rlb799</Username><Timestamp>1351082378539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351082584469-23</Id><Title>Unreal, even LENO is attacking the Musllim now!</Title><Msg>Youtube it, it's a howl but tragic for America. Obamma said Iran's economy is in shambles at the debate and Leno said if anyone knows about putting an economy in shambles it's OBAMMA. Leftist Leno attacks the commie. So you KNOW the Kenyan's done for. And HIS Benghazi-Gate will SEAL HIS FATE.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351082584469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351083269302-24</Id><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Msg>Search for "Who Is The Smallest Government Spender Since Eisenhower? Would You Believe It's Barack Obama" from Forbes</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351083599659-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can you possibly pump a president that sat and watched Ambassador Stevens being attacked without doing squat for him and then get up the next morning and go to Las Vegas for a fund raiser? Unbelievable!!!!!</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351083599659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084066882-26</Id><Topic><Title>Romney has balanced every budget he has come across</Title><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351001190197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 10:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes please document how he stole from employees and companies. Thats not even a democrap talking point because its so absurdly empty and false.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351084066882</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351084077655-27</Id><Title>Benghazi-Gate, Liberals couldn't care less that 4 Americans are dead</Title><Msg>They just live to give Obamma head.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351084077655</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:07:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084144303-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be an idiot. He spent more in 4 years than BUSH did in 8. Bush had 9/11 and 2 wars to pay for. Obama has had no 9/11 and 1 war to pay for.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351084144303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084184807-29</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" moderated huge spending is presented for the simple minded as a reduction." Looks like that worked for you.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351084184807</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084283746-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"a president that sat and watched Ambassador Stevens being attacked without doing squat for him" Specifically and in detail, what would you have done?</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351084283746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084396256-31</Id><Topic><Title>xkruushiatin is a commie maggot and a moooslim terrorist and a traitor to the USA</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351077569059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Inserting Obama is more to the truth.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351084396256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:13:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084479578-32</Id><Topic><Title>xkruushiatin is a commie maggot and a moooslim terrorist and a traitor to the USA</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351077569059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 07:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are either confused or delusional. Inserting Obama's name is more the truth and makes more sense.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351084479578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:14:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351084683747-33</Id><Topic><Title>Mossberg's Surface review in The Wall Street Journal</Title><Username>rlb799</Username><Timestamp>1351082378539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks.</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1351084683747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:18:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351084985951-34</Id><Title>MIMV: Mobile apps search play &amp; partners with MSFT on Windows 8....major play. A buyout likely...do your DD.</Title><Msg>..........................</Msg><Username>cashflow599</Username><Timestamp>1351084985951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:23:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085719006-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that would be stupid. No possibility of getting there in time IF the event was under way.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351085719006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085762454-36</Id><Topic><Title>Mossberg's Surface review in The Wall Street Journal</Title><Username>rlb799</Username><Timestamp>1351082378539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's the problem: If the Surface doesn't work as good as a tablet as the iPad then it might as well have the 3-watt Intel Atom processor and run Windows apps. Then why doesn't it have the 3-watt Intel Atom Processor ?</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1351085762454</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:36:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351085778227-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The spending was put in place by boosh. The graphic shows the spending increase put in place by Obama. Learn to read.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351085778227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086163114-38</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Lied About Using The Government To Help GM Going Through The Bankruptcy</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1351045813974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:30:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney Lied About Using The Government To Help GM Going Through The Bankruptcy. Miff's article released in 2009 said just the opposite.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351086163114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:42:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086184391-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Specifically, one thing I would not have done is lie for two weeks placing the blame on an obscure video.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351086184391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086333480-40</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Lied About Using The Government To Help GM Going Through The Bankruptcy</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1351045813974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:30:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One thing he would not have done, is stick it to guaranteed bond holders while paying off the unions.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351086333480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351086374307-41</Id><Title>The Deficit Is The Last Thing Romney &amp; The NeoCons/K0Ch Bros/Norquist Care About!</Title><Msg>The cynical attitude by the Romney/K0ch Bros/Norquist towards the debt is amusing. Explain how you decrease debt by spending $2 Trillion more on the militaryand cut taxes by 20%. The Romney Ryan budget is a cynical scam.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351086374307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086810489-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you believe that POTUS was not briefed on resources available at that time, including carriers and lead times to getting those choppers on site? Do you believe that anything and everything that he DID do or did NOT do was based on anything other than the intelligence available at the time from the agencies responsible for providing it gave to him? In light of communication capabilities at POTUS's disposal, regardless of his location or time of day, that continuing with his schedule actually hampered his ability in any conceivable fashion to react to situational changes and issue orders commensurate with intelligence available to him? Have you considered the possibility, or more accurately the probability, that due to the nature of the incident and its potential origins, that normal security rules in place regarding such attacks may prevent us from knowing with any precision exactly what POTUS did nor did not order in the way of additional security, investigative follow up on the issue of who was responsible for the attack, potential retaliatory measures or countermeasures? It's one thing for you to sit anonymously behind a computer screen, postulate and second guess without having the benefit of classified information not available to you. It's another thing entirely to wear a heavy burden of responsibility such as that worn by POTUS for the safety and security of three hundred million citizens when having to act on the available perceived facts in such fluid and unclear circumstances as those surrounding the Benghazi attack early in the incident.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351086810489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351086942521-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The spending was put in place by boosh? Reagan took over a much worse economy than Obama and never once blamed Carter! He did his job and got good times going again! Humanity is getting tired of you left wing whackos blaming boosh.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1351086942521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087075204-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it was the commie Kenyan, Hillary, Biden and Soros that were under attack I would have watched it on closed circuit tv like they did the 4 Americans and then gone to bed and then went to Vegas in the morning to go golfing and gambling and have a dandy time LIKE YOUR BLOOD THIRSTY WARMONGERING MUSLLIM MESSIAH DID INSTEAD OF HELPING THE 4 AMERICANS AS THEY FOUGHT FOR THEIR LIVES FOR WELL OVER 7 HOURS. The Kenyan killed them just as surely as if he put gun under their chins and blew their heads off AND then there is his subsequent COVER-UP of HIS crime that is being exposed as we watch. It's just as simple as that. But you won't see anything about it on the leftist propaganda spreading MSNBC how much we lie to you. Maybe you would care if it was one of YOUR family members that was murdered while THEY watched,................ but I doubt it because you are a slobbering fawning sycophant for your maniacal Musllim Messiah no matter what he does or who he kills.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351087075204</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 09:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351087339256-45</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your response is another attack on POTUS but is is not an answer to the question posed. The fact is that you have no earthly idea what you would or would not have done because, as I posted in reply to golfer, you weren't there and you did not have the info available to POTUS required to craft a response to the incident. You are quick to point out a perceived (by you) problem, but you haven't the tools or experience necessary to propose a solution appropriate to the task of resolving the perceived problem. Nonsensical uninformed criticism is all that you have to offer.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351087339256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351087445318-46</Id><Title>The Largest Deficit On Obama's Watch? It was the 2009 budget authored by GW Bush and handed off to Obama.</Title><Msg>The deficit has been decreasing ever since AFTER the Dubya Bush's budget of 2009 was handed off and inherited by Obama..</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351087445318</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:04:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351088381926-47</Id><Title>RWNJ news alert , Raype of a women is gawds will says bonified conservative RWNJ Richard Mourdock</Title><Msg>These type 1 thinking moe rons are who we want in office ?????</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351088381926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088417407-48</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Lied About Using The Government To Help GM Going Through The Bankruptcy</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1351045813974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 22:30:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, until the bailout proved successful, they were all over Obama day and night about using govt money. Government Motors remember that catch phrase? Now they say oh we wanted govt bailout money too. Totally the most lying to get votes propaganda machine in American history. Over what? Some of the rich, not all, can't stand to pay 5% more on income over 250k net? Like Romney has shown himself, paying a low tax rate is about all they live for.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351088417407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:20:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351088536641-49</Id><Title>The liberals know their Musllim Messiah watched the Benghazi terror attack in real time</Title><Msg>They, just, don't, care. Their Messiah can do no wrong in their anti American Musllim Messiah worshiping eyes. Liberals have no regard for life.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351088536641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:22:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351088885461-50</Id><Title>Obamacare leaves 30 million uninsured but cost $1.9 trillion</Title><Msg>and adds 16,000 IRS agents, and adds taxes to small businesses. We can't keep track of all the people (mostly Democrats) that don't pay their taxes but we will be able to find those that aren't paying for their health care. Yea right</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351088885461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351088982311-51</Id><Topic><Title>Syndicated columnist David Brooks spells out Obama's Green Energy. Romney had it right Obama can't pick one Winner but what</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1351087432854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:03:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Board messagist hawrcreek10 says romney had it wrong. Oh there are plenty of rich to make huge dents, and why you want them to save 5% on income over 250k net, and cut programs for the middle class and elderly, is unfathomable. They have already not paid a trillion because of the bush tax cuts. Even Bush set them to expire this year. But oh no, they like thm and want them. Chalk up another trillion over 10 yrs and the want to eliminate inheritance tax if they can get a majority. It isn't hard to understand romney's love of money.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351088982311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351089745395-52</Id><Title>In this corner Romney who is the most dishonest liar ever running for office, and in the other corner we have Obama</Title><Msg>the most honest and forthright man ever running for office. Now, why do people ignore romney's lies and accept his tax evasion tactics and don't ask for his birth certificate, but Obama they pick his words out of sentences and make false stories and call them lies, and he pays his taxes without evasion, and he shows his birth certificate three times and some people still say they haven't seen it? why?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1351089745395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351089755724-53</Id><Title>Obamma's War on America</Title><Msg>Now military personnel have to FIGHT for their rights against the anti American Musllim maggot in the white house who called his Musllim brother Nidal Hassan's terrorist attack at Fort Hood,... WORK PLACE VIOLENCE. Yep and so was the 9/11 WTC and the Benghazi massacre not to mention Pearl Harbor.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351089755724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351089757590-54</Id><Topic><Title>TADF BIG OCTOBER NEWS.TADF 2000% GAINS POSSIBLE ON ACQUISITIONS ANNOUNCED. Undervalued and CHEAP@ 0.0007.READ</Title><Username>dollarmultiplier</Username><Timestamp>1351009033139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 12:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Going to give this a try with 6 million shares at 0.0008. Don't think it Can go any lower, can only go up from here. 6 million shares X .20 cents = $1,200,000 profit. The profit potential on the upside is massive. This could help RECOVER all my losses for the YEAR. After purchase remember to Add TADF to your Watchlist to maximize gains to the upside on more news and to buy more on news.</Msg><Username>hugemargins</Username><Timestamp>1351089757590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351090433118-55</Id><Title>Commie Carney just came out lying like there's no tomorrow still trying to cover-up for Bennghazi!</Title><Msg>Doesn't the stoopid p o s commie know that the whole world knows now that they're LYING and that they watched it happen live AND DID NOTHING. Al Qaaeda is alive and well and their Musllim monkey faced blood thirsty leader IS IN THE WHITE HOUSE.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351090433118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351090976565-56</Id><Title>Windows 8 and Surface</Title><Msg>MSFT to release a product that is not only unfinished and defective, but one that people do not want or even cannot use. No laptops on the market have touchscreens. Nor do desktop PC displays. Who exactly would want this OS? What are its benefits? How is it better than Win 7 SP2? There is NO incentive to get this. The sales on Friday will be simply dreadful. MSFT will be smashed as a result.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351090976565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351091111219-57</Id><Title>The propaganda machine in the white house is in overdrive now trying to spin and lie</Title><Msg>.... to the AMERICAN PEOPLE. Commies need not worry because you're not Americans.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351091111219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351091141053-58</Id><Title>Grover Norquist's hand up Romney's #$%$ "Pick a Republican with enough working digits to handle a pen"</Title><Msg>Grover Norquist's hand up Romney's #$%$ "Pick a Republican with enough working digits to handle a pen" Cut taxes by 20%. Raise defense spending by $2Trillion!? Grover Norquist wrote the Romney/Ryan budget. They don't give a schitt about the debt. "Just don't raise my taxes".</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351091141053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:05:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351091142452-59</Id><Title>Grover Norquist's hand up Romney's #$%$ "Pick a Republican with enough working digits to handle a pen"</Title><Msg>Grover Norquist's hand up Romney's #$%$ "Pick a Republican with enough working digits to handle a pen" Cut taxes by 20%. Raise defense spending by $2Trillion!? Grover Norquist wrote the Romney/Ryan budget. They don't give a schitt about the debt. "Just don't raise my taxes".</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351091142452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091507115-60</Id><Topic><Title>Grover Norquist's hand up Romney's #$%$ "Pick a Republican with enough working digits to handle a pen"</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351091142452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:05:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stimulate the economy. Put people to work and you do not need to send them foodstamps and checks each month. Raising defense spending 2T is a lie, blatant, horrible lie. Its NOT cutting defense by 1T, which is coming in December. Even Obama said it will not happen, so HE is for NOT cutting defense by 1T over the next 10 years too. Their position is very similar. The debate showed us that. DO NOT LIE WITH YOUR FAKE TALKING POINTS!!!!</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351091507115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:11:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351091718708-61</Id><Title>Microsoft's best investment........AAPL</Title><Msg>They need to stop throwing money away on poorly designed tablet hardware. If they had any smarts in management they would take their cash hoard and buy Apple shares for big gains for their own stockholders.</Msg><Username>johnandtai</Username><Timestamp>1351091718708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351091938903-62</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft's best investment........AAPL</Title><Username>johnandtai</Username><Timestamp>1351091718708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:15:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What they need to do is come up with a killer app. Similar to SIRI, but better and fully wired into Win 8.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1351091938903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351092252457-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Disposableidiot, (Christ, how many names do you use craper?) What I would have or have not done is a mute point. As Obama pointed out about Bush, the buck stopped with him. Now, again, I believe Nixon had nothng to do with the Watergate break in, but he lost his job because he helped cover it up. (break in,nobody died) Now everyone knows that Obama was in charge of this cover-up, the mastermind. He deserves to the very least lose his job for misleading America for two weeks.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1351092252457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351092478231-64</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10/24/12: New Hampshire: Romney 50%, Obama 48% Rasmussen Ohio: Obama 48%, Romney 48% Daily Presidential Tracking Poll: Romney 50%, Obama 46% Swing State Tracking: Romney 50%, Obama 45% Minnesota: Obama 51%, Romney 46% Connecticut: Obama 52%, Romney 45%</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351092478231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351092891339-65</Id><Topic><Title>Grover Norquist's hand up Romney's #$%$ "Pick a Republican with enough working digits to handle a pen"</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351091142452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:05:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Stimulate the economy." I love it when one of the loudest "liar!" shrieking, least effective arguers puts his Achilles heel right up front of a "solution" for all to see. OK, you put it out there, "Stimulate the economy." Do you think that rather than redirect or trying to twist a question with what you *wouldn't* do that you could answer a direct query with a direct answer? What would you do, specifically and in detail, to accomplish the economic stimulation you propose to put people to work? Please refrain from substituting any of *your* "FAKE TALKING POINTS!!!!" while composing your answer and focus on the question.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351092891339</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351093058368-66</Id><Title>The Musllim spent over 6 TRILLION DOLLARS on pie in the sky</Title><Msg>And now the American tax payers will have to pay for HIS destruction. But what did anyone expect from a blood thirsty anti American community organizing commie Kenyan murderous Musllim p o s janitor who's so brain dead stupid he says CORPSE MAN.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351093058368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:37:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351093095973-67</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NewsmaxZogby Poll: Romney Surges Ahead Among Seniors in Virginia Wednesday, 24 Oct 2012 10:39 AM By David Alliot Mitt Romney is crushing Barack Obama among seniors 65 and over in Virginia — 58 percent to 39 percent — with 58 percent also saying it is time for someone new, versus 34 percent who said Obama deserves to be re-elected, according to the first of three NewsmaxZogby polls for the state. An overwhelming majority of seniors polled — 63 percent — said they “somewhat” or “strongly” disapprove of the job Obama’s doing as president, with only 36 percent “somewhat” or “strongly” approving. The president has a 3-percentage point advantage over his Republican challenger among all likely voters in Virginia, however: 49 percent to 46 percent, according to the poll. Yet more were against his re-election than were in favor of it: 47 percent to 44 percent. Among high-income earners ($100,00-plus), 52 percent said it was time for someone new in the White House versus 39 percent who said Obama should stay. It was the inverse for low-income earners ($25,000 or less) — 56 percent said he deserves to be re-elected, and 37 percent said it is time for someone new. Among those reporting a union member in the household, 50 percent said he deserves to be re-elected; 42 percent said he didn’t. In the youngest age group, 18- to 29-year-olds, the split favored his re-election: 45 percent to 38 percent. Obama had a slight edge over Romney among men for the presidency, 48 percent to 46 percent, and led substantially among women, 51 percent to 47 percent. The crucial independent vote favored Obama over Romney 47 percent to 40 percent. When asked about what kind of job the president is doing, 48 percent of those polled said they “strongly” or “somewhat” approve, with 50 percent “somewhat” or “strongly” disapproving. Independents expressed dissatisfaction with Obama: 49 percent said they somewhat or strongly disapprove, with 45 percent somewhat or strongly approving of the job he’s doing. Virginia’s role as a key battleground state leaves little wiggle room for Obama and Romney. “Both have some work to do to shore up their own bases,” said pollster John Zogby. “And the 7-point Obama lead among independents can be erased very quickly.” The online poll of 827 likely voters was conducted Sunday, Oct. 21, through Tuesday, Oct. 23, and has a margin-of-sampling error of plus or minus 3.5 percentage points. The joint venture between Newsmax and New York State-based pollster John Zogby has featured tracking polls in Ohio and Florida, with Virginia being the latest. National polls are featured right up to Election Day. All reported results include voters who have already voted and those voters initially undecided who indicated they are leaning toward a candidate. The NewsmaxZogby Poll of Virginia likely voters sampled 37 percent Democrats, 36 percent Republicans and 27 percent independents; 71 percent were white, 6 percent Hispanic, and 19 percent African-American; and 18 percent were ages 18-29, 38 percent ages 30-49, 32 percent ages 50-64, and 12 percent age 65 or older.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1351093095973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351093388713-68</Id><Title>Hillary just made a statement about Benghazi-Gate and the pig was actually laughing about it</Title><Msg>FOUR AMERICANS DEAD BECAUSE OF HER AND HER MUSLLIM MESSIAH AND ALL THAT PIECE OF SHE IT PIG CAN DO IS,....... laugh? Nothing funny here you f ing pig commie p o s. The only reason you're so uneasily laughing is because there's blood dripping from your hoar hands. The blood of 4 American Patriots. If you vote for the Kenyan U 2 R A P O S ps. Odd the hoar didn't say a word about their video scam? I wonder why?</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351093388713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351093782403-69</Id><Title>The Kenyan's reign of terror is about to come to an end</Title><Msg>.... when American Patriots throw him out and send him to the gallows for his crimes against humanity and America. Down with the anti American blood thirsty warmongering Musllm and onward and upwards with President Mitt Romney.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351093782403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351093890217-70</Id><Topic><Title>The Kenyan's reign of terror is about to come to an end</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351093782403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:49:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STOP THE BLOOD THIRSTY MUSLLIM NOW. Don't be an anti American commie p o s and be an American Patriot and vote for President Mitt Romney, he's an American and a Christian, not a p o s Musllim from Kenya.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351093890217</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094037248-71</Id><Topic><Title>The Musllim spent over 6 TRILLION DOLLARS on pie in the sky</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351093058368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:37:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop the madman Musllim before he finishes destroying what's left of America. All he needs is another 4 years to do it too. But Americans won't let the e vill p o s do it, they will vote patriot, they will vote Romney.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351094037248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351094302473-72</Id><Title>Obamma is trying to buy another election with his lies and blood money</Title><Msg>Americans must unite and stop the e vill d min from succeeding in his criminal commie quest.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351094302473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094498616-73</Id><Topic><Title>Game changing report</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351087332860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for this guys!</Msg><Username>libbylicyr356003</Username><Timestamp>1351094498616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094895279-74</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Azure is FUD. No one uses it except a few clients paid off by MS to act as poster boys.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351094895279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094906140-75</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Azure is FUD. No one uses it except a few clients paid off by MS to act as poster boys.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351094906140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:08:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094915616-76</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Azure is FUD. No one uses it except a few clients paid off by MS to act as poster boys.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351094915616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:08:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351094984057-77</Id><Topic><Title>Grover Norquist's hand up Romney's #$%$ "Pick a Republican with enough working digits to handle a pen"</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1351091142452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:05:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*BUMP*</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351094984057</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095198202-78</Id><Topic><Title>Obamma is trying to buy another election with his lies and blood money</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351094302473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's imperative for the strength, future, prosperity and freedom of America. The Musllim MUST be defeated and sent back to Kenya after he's sent to the gallows.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351095198202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351095422678-79</Id><Title>The reason Hillary and Hussein used the video as cover for their Benghazi Cover-Up is</Title><Msg>.... because that they figured that the American people were stoopid and would believe anything they said. After all, they did vote the Musllim Monkey into office. And you would have to be brain dead stoopid to do that, so why not lie to them some more.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351095422678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095671245-80</Id><Topic><Title>Game changing report</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351087332860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>libbylicyr356003</Username><Timestamp>1351095671245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095856957-81</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"you obviously don't know what potential hosting SQL apps in the cloud can do." Uhhh... Excuse me. Didn't you just ask about Azure pretending you didn't know anything about it and by extension, the cloud. You just exposed yourself. Doesn't matter though, you pretty much did that when you asked the question about touch screen apps for Lose 8. If you paid anything for your shill classes you need to demand your money back. Final exam grade? Epic Fail...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351095856957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:24:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351095982961-82</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I hear that penguins like to cover the ground with their manure" While *you* on the other hand, like to deposit your turds directly into the tub while bathing and conferring with Paul Allen and call them "yachts".</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351095982961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351096028124-83</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are desperate MS employees doing "marketing" as a hobby to make their pathetic stock grants go up.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1351096028124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351096207316-84</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Highly plausible assertion, ghos.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351096207316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:30:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351097038024-85</Id><Title>Pig Hillary was LAUGHING this morning talking about Benghazi-Gate</Title><Msg>I wonder what the commie pig finds so f'ing funny about FOUR DEAD AMERICANS. She is a piece of lying anti American she it, her and her Messiah watched the men die live and they laughed about it, let's see how much the vermin maggots laugh while they're holding hands walking to the gallows,... now THAT will be funny. And the Musllim is pure e vill.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351097038024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097503893-86</Id><Topic><Title>Game changing report</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351087332860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very informative. Thank you</Msg><Username>quianabbalf331833</Username><Timestamp>1351097503893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351097510549-87</Id><Title>EU Antitrust suit will hurt MSFT this is very Bad timing NOW</Title><Msg>Msft need to hit a home run and this will kill thier sales prospect Crazy stupid by msft</Msg><Username>neffrocker</Username><Timestamp>1351097510549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351097957097-88</Id><Topic><Title>Pig Hillary was LAUGHING this morning talking about Benghazi-Gate</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351097038024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:43:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NEW YORK | Wed Oct 24, 2012 12:46pm EDT (Reuters) - Donald Trump offered to pay $5 million to the charity of President Barack Obama's choice if Obama releases his college and passport records, the real estate mogul and television personality said on Wednesday. "Frankly, it's a check that I very much want to write," Trump said in a YouTube video released via his Twitter and Facebook pages. Trump has questioned whether Obama's birth certificate issued by the state of Hawaii is legitimate, suggesting Obama was not born in the United States, which could have made him ineligible for the White House. The White House released the long-form copy of Obama's birth certificate in 2011. Trump did not say what he expected the college and passports records to reveal but was specific in saying he wanted to see all of Obama's college applications and records and his passport applications and records. "President Obama is the least transparent president in the history of this country," Trump said in the video. "If he releases these records it will end the question and indeed the anger of many Americans."</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351097957097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098070565-89</Id><Topic><Title>EU Antitrust suit will hurt MSFT this is very Bad timing NOW</Title><Username>neffrocker</Username><Timestamp>1351097510549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:51:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fines are the cost of doing buisness no big deal.</Msg><Username>bucks0501</Username><Timestamp>1351098070565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351098565273-90</Id><Topic><Title>Game changing report</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351087332860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure thing. Been receiving good alerts from them</Msg><Username>quianabbalf331833</Username><Timestamp>1351098565273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351100106168-91</Id><Topic><Title>Pig Hillary was LAUGHING this morning talking about Benghazi-Gate</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351097038024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:43:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White House knew 2 hours after Libya attack that Ansar al-Sharia claimed responsibility, emails show By Larry Margasak Associated Press Posted: 10/24/2012 10:08:19 AM PDT Updated: 10/24/2012 10:08:20 AM PDT WASHINGTON -- Two hours after the U.S. Consulate came under attack in Benghazi, Libya, the White House was told that a militant group was claiming responsibility for the violence that killed the U.S. ambassador and three other Americans. A State Department email sent to intelligence officials and the White House situation room said the Islamist group Ansar al-Sharia claimed responsibility on Facebook and Twitter, and also called for an attack on the U.S. Embassy in Tripoli. The document may fuel Republican efforts to show that the White House knew it was a terrorist attack, even as the U.S. ambassador to the United Nations was saying -- five days afterward -- that it appeared to be a protest gone awry. The Obama administration's account of the Benghazi events has become a campaign issue, with Republican challenger Mitt Romney and GOP lawmakers accusing the White House of misleading Americans about the nature of the attack. The Associated Press and other news organizations obtained the unclassified email and two related emails from government officials who requested anonymity because they were not authorized to speak about them publicly. White House press secretary Jay Carney said the emails represented just one piece of information the administration was receiving at the time. "There were emails about all sorts of information that was becoming available in the aftermath of the attack," Carney said. "The whole point of an Advertisement intelligence community and what they do is to #$%$ strands of information and make judgments about what happened and who is responsible." Carney, traveling with President Barack Obama Wednesday on Air Force One, said the emails were unclassified and referred to assertions made on a social media site. There were a series of three emails sent by State Department officials in Washington as events unfolded on Sept. 11. Among the recipients was the White House situation room. The first email said that the State Department's regional security officer reported the mission in Benghazi was under attack, and that "20 armed people fired shots." It said that Ambassador Chris Stevens, who was killed in the attack, was in Benghazi, and that Stevens and four others were in the compound's safe haven. Forty-nine minutes later, an email said that the firing at the consulate "has stopped and the compound has been cleared," while a response team was attempting to locate people. The next message, one hour and 13 minutes after the second and some two hours after the attack began, a message reported that Ansar-al-Sharia claimed responsibility for the attack. "Embassy Tripoli reports the group claimed responsibility on Faceboook and Twitter and has called for an attack on Embassy Tripoli," it said. Ansar al-Sharia bragged to members of al-Qaida in the Islamic Maghreb that it was responsible for the attack, according to recordings of phone calls intercepted by U.S. intelligence. But the group has publicly denied having anything to do with the attack. Secretary of State Hillary Rodham Clinton, speaking to reporters at the State Department, said, "You know, posting something on Facebook is not in and of itself evidence and I think it just underscores how fluid the reporting was at the time and continued some time to be." Clinton said the Accountability Review Board she appointed to investigate the attack is "looking at everything," rather than "cherry picking one story here or one document there." She added, "What I keep in mind is that four brave Americans were killed and we will find out what happened, we will take whatever measures are necessary to fix anything that needs to be fixed and we will bring those to justice who committed these murders."</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1351100106168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351100321456-92</Id><Topic><Title>Game changing report</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351087332860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this here.</Msg><Username>luanarbhoj06666</Username><Timestamp>1351100321456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351100712825-93</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Microsoft stuck a deal with MIMV" "Stuck" a deal *with* MIMV. No. Stuck it *to* MIMV. "After looking at what Azure can do I got interested." So, after looking at what Azure can do, you show up here and ask "What do you know of this thing called Azure??"? HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA!!! You *are* really bad at this. Even worse, you choose to tag team shill with wally, the piece of squirrel bait that spends all day insulting people on a message board but still claims to own a yacht and purports to confer with MS co founder, Paul Allen? You've already outed yourself and thoroughly undermined your own credibility here so I guess it's time for you to go change your nym and come back as another transparent fanboi. Good luck.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351100712825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351100821985-94</Id><Title>Politics: BIG PICTURE</Title><Msg>Democrats are Republicans in training. Some Democrats never grow up and graduate. However, sometimes I feel as though some Republicans and even Democrats don't want them to graduate. That's the BIG QUESTION.</Msg><Username>minicurt</Username><Timestamp>1351100821985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351101030307-95</Id><Title>Unlocked W8 Phones</Title><Msg>Does anyone know if any the handset makers will be makeing a unlocked version of the W8 phone?</Msg><Username>minicurt</Username><Timestamp>1351101030307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351101182624-96</Id><Topic><Title>Game changing report</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351087332860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>luanarbhoj06666</Username><Timestamp>1351101182624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351101264670-97</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but what about da children ??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351101264670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351101327668-98</Id><Topic><Title>RWNJ news alert , Raype of a women is gawds will says bonified conservative RWNJ Richard Mourdock</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351088381926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:19:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The same people behind intellectual takeout.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351101327668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:55:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351103162095-99</Id><Title>They unloading VXX</Title><Msg>Will the bid dump come after 2:30 ?</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1351103162095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:26:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351103729509-100</Id><Title>golfer booger</Title><Msg>You didn't have to go far nor expend a great deal of energy in proving the points I raised beyond a shadow of a doubt. For example: "Disposableidiot, (Christ, how many names do you use craper?)" As always when you have nothing to contribute or can't answer a simple question, you resort to insulting and attacking the poster that posed the question. If you can't tell the difference between me (predisposable is my ONLY nym), and craper by writing style and word selection, general overall sentence construction, grammar and punctuation, then you are indeed too perceptually challenged to be making any judgements about anyone, particularly a duly elected sitting POTUS. "What I would have or have not done is a mute point. As Obama pointed out about Bush, the buck stopped with him." The word is "moot" not "mute", though it would be a blessing if you were the latter. The point is not moot. You couldn't answer the question because you are a blind hypocrite and any attempt at a cogent answer would have further exposed you as a complete and utter fool, which is not to say that your haven't done that already. "Now, again, I believe Nixon had nothng to do with the Watergate break in, but he lost his job because he helped cover it up." Nixon resigned from his job in disgrace to avoid the public spectacle and humiliation of impeachment for high crimes and misdemeanors. When you produce the missing 18 minutes from the tape of his meeting with Bob Haldeman you might be able to say for certain one way or another what Nixon instructed or condoned as action by his staff. Otherwise it's just more of your unsubstantiated bloviation of which there is already more than a surplus. "Now everyone knows that Obama was in charge of this cover-up, the mastermind. He deserves to the very least lose his job for misleading America for two weeks." You are neither qualified nor empowered to speak for "everyone". There is no evidence or proof of any coverup, much less POTUS involvement in such. Without proof or evidence it's just another of your pipe dreams, another, falsehood, another smear. Stuff it in your snood.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351103729509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351103859275-101</Id><Topic><Title>Unlocked W8 Phones</Title><Username>minicurt</Username><Timestamp>1351101030307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 13:50:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure, there are thousands of knock off W8 phones in China. Nobody is buying them though. They're buying knock off iPhones instead.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1351103859275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351104141510-102</Id><Title>ROMNEY ENDORSED SEN. MOURDOCK, AND NOW ROMNEY IS HIDING, JUST LIKE BUSH?</Title><Msg>Romney, where are you hiding?</Msg><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351104141510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351104304077-103</Id><Title>MOURDOCK SAID: GOD AT WORK IF RAPE CAUSES PREGNANCY</Title><Msg>And guess what, Mitt Romney had just endorsed him. And Romney is nowhere to be found. He is hiding out.</Msg><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351104304077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104373312-104</Id><Topic><Title>Obama restrained spending growth the most of any president since Eisenhower</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351083269302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 08:54:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Colorado finds 300 more suspected noncitizens on voter rolls Published October 23, 2012 Associated Press DENVER – There are 300 more suspected noncitizens on Colorado's voter rolls, Secretary of State Gessler announced Tuesday in the latest chapter of a contentious national debate over what Republicans say is vulnerability in the voting system. The latest figures are from the 3,903 people who received letters from Gessler's office questioning their citizenship in August. During a first round of checks, Gessler said 141 others were found to be possible noncitizens based on a federal immigration database.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351104373312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351104418860-105</Id><Title>Obamma Bin Laden bin murder'in AMERICANS!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>WHO IN THE MOTHER F HUCK PUT THAT E VILL PIECE OF GODLESS MUSLLIM SHE IT IN THE WHITE HOUSE. Who could hate America THAT much. You would have to be an anti American pagan piece of she it to worship that blood thirsty psychotic Kenyan and then vote for it. ps. Now the leftist maggots in Hussein's regime are on tv trying to say thst their blood thirsty Messiah knew the Americans were being murdered because HE WATCHED it but they said that there was nothing he could do so why NOT go to Vegas, after all, it was the OPTIMAL thing to do.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351104418860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:46:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104449842-106</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY ENDORSED SEN. MOURDOCK, AND NOW ROMNEY IS HIDING, JUST LIKE BUSH?</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351104141510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:42:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We're all going to have to accept their religion like it or not. This is the fringe right wing who less than a 100 years ago fought hard to prevent a women's right to vote, now their making a comeback.</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1351104449842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104672119-107</Id><Topic><Title>Obamma Bin Laden bin murder'in AMERICANS!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351104418860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:46:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jim Jones the Christian killed almost a thousand in Guyana, that doesn't seem to have lessened the popularity of Christianity...</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1351104672119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:51:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351104707860-108</Id><Topic><Title>golfer booger</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351103729509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:35:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may be right about that. It would certainly seem as if their comments are scripted if for no other reason than most real humans, expressing themselves independently, appear to have the ability to learn and thereby modify their stance or opinion based on new information or proof of the factual nature of opposing argument. They seem to have none of that ability. By the way, I did not mean to imply that my "writing style" is in any way better or superior to your own, just that it is different and observably so. Regards, Gary</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351104707860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351104936617-109</Id><Title>What would have happened if Bush would have went to Vegas after watching the attack?</Title><Msg>After all, the leftist commie Libs came apart at the seams for him sitting with some school children for 3 minutes on 9/11 before leaving. Bush = 3 minutes then left to deal with the terrorist attack O'Bloodthirsty = 7 HOUR TERRORIST ATTACK then left for Vegas after WATCHING IT LIVE for the FIRST HOUR and did NOTHING TO HELP THE 4 AMERICANS.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351104936617</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351105590825-110</Id><Topic><Title>Obamma Bin Laden bin murder'in AMERICANS!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351104418860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:46:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, pin head, Jim Jones was a Marxist like your Musllim Messiah and both of the pagan pieces of arrogant elitist she it suffer from delusions of grandeur and fancy themselves demigods. Obamma massacred thousands upon thousands of innocent women and children in Libya in his blood thirsty illegal war and murdered Americans then sealed all the evidence incriminating him and THAT doesn't seem to have lessened the way you and your commie cohorts worship and glorify the d min as your Messiah which can only mean that YOU are a brain dead anti American liberal.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351105590825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351105798461-111</Id><Title>MSFT below 28</Title><Msg>Ballmer bites the big one!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1351105798461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351105886168-112</Id><Title>DO MORMONS ENDORSE RAPE?</Title><Msg>What rights do women have in a Mormon society?</Msg><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351105886168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351106068325-113</Id><Title>Hog Wad Hillary said that there needs to be an investigation before jumping to conclusions?</Title><Msg>Gee, I wonder why her and her Musllim Messiah didn't do that BEFORE THEY RAN AROUND THE COUNTRY LYING SAYING IT WAS A VIDEO THAT INCITED SOME PEACEFUL MUSLLIMS TO MURDER AMERICANS! We all know why. Hillary, like Hussein, thinks that ALL the American people are as stoopid as THEIR simple minded uneducated commie constituents. Guess what Hillary,............ WRONG, not EVERYONE is as brain dead stoopid as you and your e vill Kenayan CORPSE MAN. Hey hog Hillary, don't cover up your crimes, cover up your fat PIG mouth.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351106068325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106101829-114</Id><Topic><Title>DO MORMONS ENDORSE RAPE?</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351105886168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It may depend on what regional or local prophet/profit center they belong to.</Msg><Username>celtic70737</Username><Timestamp>1351106101829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106366947-115</Id><Topic><Title>DO MORMONS ENDORSE RAPE?</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351105886168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have more rights than in your Musllim society. Why do you want to know if they endorse rape, are you tired of being raped and want to leave Isslam and become a Mormon because your gristle ring is getting sore? Or is it your mouth.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351106366947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:19:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106470504-116</Id><Topic><Title>Question about Azure??</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1351038844263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>predisposable eh- for a section 8 you are a bit too uppitty- What Paul Allen and Craig McCaw and Bill Gates and I do is none of your business- and try to stop picking sh.t for the goodies for a change eh</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1351106470504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351106840846-117</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY ENDORSED SEN. MOURDOCK, AND NOW ROMNEY IS HIDING, JUST LIKE BUSH?</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351104141510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:42:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney will not win</Msg><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351106840846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107249719-118</Id><Topic><Title>MOURDOCK SAID: GOD AT WORK IF RAPE CAUSES PREGNANCY</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351104304077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 14:45:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't believe in murder even if it is in Benghazi? Shouldn't lie to your people Mr President.</Msg><Username>free2491</Username><Timestamp>1351107249719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351107309337-119</Id><Title>Romney stands behind Mourdock even after rape is gods will comment. Now you see what you are</Title><Msg>voting against. Conservatives are stupid and they prove it frequently.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351107309337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351107408991-120</Id><Title>RWNJ move on from the Benghazi thing. The sizzle is gone and you sound stewpid.</Title><Msg>Unless that is how you RWNJ want to sound.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351107408991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107697997-121</Id><Topic><Title>DO MORMONS ENDORSE RAPE?</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351105886168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Our lib President doesn't seem to recognize the need for more battle ships" Please provide your expert analysis of our current naval battle readiness and capabilities with specificity and full detail. You *are* privy to the information contained in all the current reports being submitted on these subjects by the JCS, the Secretary of Defense, the CIA, DHS and their functional area experts, right? You do have these assessments at your privileged disposal, there at your finger tips, right, Harry? It occurs to me that you do NOT have that information and that in fact you have no idea what you're talking about nor what ANY of our military forces need in order to maintain combat readiness in the current geopolitical climate. Talking out of your fecal matter exit pathway again, Harry?</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1351107697997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:41:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107752774-122</Id><Topic><Title>Hog Wad Hillary said that there needs to be an investigation before jumping to conclusions?</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351106068325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:14:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ you stoopid old fat black broad and stop trying to cover up for your blood thirsty Musllim Messiah from Kenya, after all, YOU live in Cuba ya commie ho. And don't forget, ROMNEY was RIGHT. You see, he told the truth and you don't have to worry when you tell the truth, but your lying e vill P O S Musllim Messiah lies all the time and now he's in a world of she it because of it. He is pure e vill and still, you worship him as your god, Allah Barack. Even when the investigation is complete when President Romney is in power because a real investigation can't be done with the ENEMY OBAMMA in the white house, but when President Romney does sentence your blood thirsty psycho Kenyan and he's walking to the gallows you will still be trying to defend them as your Mullah Messiah while you're trying to clean up all the blood dripping from his hands.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351107752774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351107910374-123</Id><Topic><Title>DO MORMONS ENDORSE RAPE?</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351105886168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do expect from a brain dead corpse man janitor from Kenya, he knows nothing of our country or her military but he knows everything about his Musllim countries.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351107910374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351107979012-124</Id><Title>Creationist+vote=child+matches</Title><Msg>Bin Laden escapes over the Bora Bora mountains into Pakistan....Bush attacks Iraq. Bush re-elected. Hunt for non-existent WMD's to cost America over $1 trillion. Brilliant!</Msg><Username>celtic70737</Username><Timestamp>1351107979012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351108227834-125</Id><Title>Go to Youtube and type in, president obamma on Zakat</Title><Msg>The Musllim piece of she it promises his Musllim people to help them pay Zakat. He's no more a Christian than Muhammmed. And then for fun, while you're in Youtube mode, type in, Obamma attacks Christian Bible. And listen to the blood thirsty Musllim attack Christianity. But don't bother typing in, Obamma attacks his Qu'rran, because you'll NEVER hear him do THAT since he's an exteeeeemely DEVOUT MUSLLIM JUST LIKE HIS P O S FATHER.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351108227834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108711270-126</Id><Topic><Title>DO MORMONS ENDORSE RAPE?</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351105886168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Our lib President doesn't seem to recognize the need for more battle ships" Who the H said something as stupid as that. Is this from the debate where the President schooled romney on naval ships now aren't comparable to naval ships in 1917? That is one far leap from what he said, to say he doesn't recognize the need for more ships. This President recognizes everything we need, and lower taxes on rich folks, the trillion dollar Bush tax cuts for them, isn't one of them.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351108711270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351108742219-127</Id><Topic><Title>Romney stands behind Mourdock even after rape is gods will comment. Now you see what you are</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351107309337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:35:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree Romney is in full hiding Mode.</Msg><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351108742219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351109320563-128</Id><Topic><Title>DO MORMONS ENDORSE RAPE?</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351105886168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, nor cover up &amp; lie.</Msg><Username>free2491</Username><Timestamp>1351109320563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351109484393-129</Id><Title>Bush had pockets full of Clinton money to burn</Title><Msg>so he, like most shopaholics, burned through it. In the meantime he thought it best to cut the upper income tax rates and add along regular people so they feel good too. After all, the pockets had some left.Then the bills came due and Bush said bye bye so sorry. Now Obama is in there swinging for us, and what do the previous Bushaholics do, they diss Obama day and night and say everything is his fault, he spends too much, and they won't vote for anything he wants, even if it is their own plan, they won't vote for it. The solution to this is put all the republicans in the back seats to watch for a dozen years or so while the Dems get us back on track just like Clinton did.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1351109484393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351110207477-130</Id><Title>MSFT launch window 8 this Friday</Title><Msg>MSFT goes to $30 again</Msg><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1351110207477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351110346603-131</Id><Title>so much bashing on msft they may just buy it up tomorrow to $30</Title><Msg>uuu never know how much inst $$$$ like mr softy. a bounce is coming in the Nasq and appl &amp; msft may just blow it out tomorrow :-))</Msg><Username>neffrocker</Username><Timestamp>1351110346603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:25:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351110603011-132</Id><Topic><Title>so much bashing on msft they may just buy it up tomorrow to $30</Title><Username>neffrocker</Username><Timestamp>1351110346603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:25:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL jumped from $609 to $634 the day before I-Pad mini launch same will happen with MSFT the day before WINDOW 8 Launch plus WINDOW 8 is much much significant than I-PAD mini</Msg><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1351110603011</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 16:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113202165-133</Id><Topic><Title>Game changing report</Title><Username>jaunitaapuz94729</Username><Timestamp>1351087332860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 10:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great share. Many thanks</Msg><Username>clairvnrh52236</Username><Timestamp>1351113202165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351113727891-134</Id><Topic><Title>Hog Wad Hillary said that there needs to be an investigation before jumping to conclusions?</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351106068325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:14:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About your lying p o s Musllim Messiah being a lying p o s Musllim Messiah. Like me and the rest of the world, Romney said it was a terrorist attack, just as soon as it happened but YOUR lying p o s Musllim Messiah said it was just a Sunday afternoon Ice Cream Social Mullah rally walk in the park at Benghazi gone wrong because of some fairy tale story he made up about some who cares video attacking HIS precious prophet, Mu'ham head. And THEN the e vill P O S TRIED TO COVER IT ALL UP when he was inevitably caught with the fresh blood still dripping from his hands. Now we know he watched it all happen on closed circuit tv,.... and DID NOTHING, other than run off to Vegas, again, leaving a trail of blood that was dripping from his hands. And the only way you would care is if it was one of YOUR family members that Hussein'bo murdered in Benghazi then tried to cover up and then run off to Vegas. Or at least I'd like to believe you would. But alas,....</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351113727891</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:22:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351114037170-135</Id><Topic><Title>DO MORMONS ENDORSE RAPE?</Title><Username>c.luke44</Username><Timestamp>1351105886168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are still two battleships in existence that are in operable states, US Navy is not requesting any new battleships to be built, doesnt have anything to do with who the President is, battleships had their day, the world is a far different place today, one where older technology doesnt seem to have a fit in. Ship needed today require the US to have sea superiorty, support special operations, rapid global mobility, agile combat support. You are not going to get this from battleships from the days of old. Building new battleships would be a waste of tax payer dollars. Presidents come and go, and hopefully Congress doesnt decide there is no longer a sovereign neeed to have a military and have the United Nations protect us all - God Help Us if that should ever happen.</Msg><Username>skeetz1234</Username><Timestamp>1351114037170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351115006973-136</Id><Title>Binders and Big Bird ROMNESIA OH MY!</Title><Msg>Whatever you, don't vote for the e vill P O S Musllim, ..... cause he LIE.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351115006973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:43:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351115572392-137</Id><Title>Obamma's campaign song by the Edgar Winter Group</Title><Msg>C'mon and take a "Free Ride" Listen to the monkey Obamma sing it on Youtube Well the free rides over commie parasites, time to get one of those shovel ready jobs your Marxist commie slob told you about. Oops, wait a minute, the blood thirsty Kenyan LIED about that. But then again, what doesn't the d min Musllim Monkey lie about.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351115572392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351115726402-138</Id><Title>worst case is $23 on bottom of 2013 correction</Title><Msg>until then we drift</Msg><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1351115726402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351115866844-139</Id><Topic><Title>worst case is $23 on bottom of 2013 correction</Title><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1351115726402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:55:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fund managers are going to be afraid of being the last one holding the bag on MSFT, at least for a while. Probably we see some strong selling still for at least 3 more points.</Msg><Username>ohvirtuousone1</Username><Timestamp>1351115866844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:57:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351115876521-140</Id><Title>CNN, NBC, CBC, ABC, MSNBC, PBS all quiet on Libya!</Title><Msg>Only Fox and Rush busting the greatest story of the year thus far!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351115876521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:57:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351116613615-141</Id><Topic><Title>CNN, NBC, CBC, ABC, MSNBC, PBS all quiet on Libya!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351115876521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surge in Women Voting for Mitt Romney for President of USA and Their Reasons By ladies_4_romney . Oct 24, 2012 2:37 PM Women Democrat Voters and Others are Switching to Mitt Romney in Ohio Michigan Florida Virginia Pennsylvania Wisconsin New York- New Jersey ( East Coast to West Coast ) The Democrat Ladies for Romney in all 50 States Ladies are Switching from Obama very Fast. Read this and you too will Change and become a "Romney Democrat" for a Stronger USA Economy and honest leadership. Women, Jewish Democrats and others are Switching to Mitt Romney for President. Women Review Debate 3 : First, Governor Mitt Romney Pasted the President Test, Ready to Lead USA. By USA_Jewish_Women 10 22 2012 Great Impression: Mitt Romney's Stunning Turnaround in Past 3 Debates after Huge Negative Ads. The Reasons for Change is Obama has Lost the Support and Respect with Women Voters and Others. People Notice: Most Men and Women are Turned Off Against Barack Obama most everywhere and Across All 50 States, Here is the the Review of Debate 3 on October 22, 2012 By a Jewish Women Focus Group of 7,890 Women Connecticut Across America Our Strong Plea for Change in the White House, Why? The following reasons listed bellow. Note: This review is a agreement amongst a Group of almost 8000 Women watching debates. During the Debate 3, President Barack Obama was Arrogant, Disrespectfully, Angry, Rude and Condescending to Governor Mitt Romney. Obama did not Act or Look Presidential. We Feel Governor Mitt Romney Pasted the Presidential Test and is Ready to Lead USA We Support Mitt Romney, found him to be a Smart, Respectable and Decent Gentleman. Governor Mitt Romney Looked Much More Presidential, Ready to be Commander-in-Chief. Mitt Romney said America Needs a Strong Economy in order to have a Strong Military for our National Security right now and the Future. ...... We All Agree. Women came away from this Debate with a Very Good Impression of Governor Mitt Romney, in that he would be a “ A Safe Pair of Hands.” in Foreign Policy and a Strong Economy. We Trust Him More. Obama lied about Libya on 9 11 ( a 8 hour fire fight, Obama watched did nothing) In Foreign Policy We feel Mitt Romney is Tough Enough to do what’s necessary, but laid-back enough not to do too much and get us into another war. Miit Romney Did Not attack President Obama's Policies, he Simply Pointed Out a Few Needed Improvements in a Very Respectable Way. During the debate Governor Mitt Romney Seemed More Like a Leader, Smart, Respectable, Thoughtful and Considerate. He looked and Acted more Like the New American President that our Nation and the rest of the World Needs so Disparately in These Troubling Economic Times. Governor Mitt Romney was Calm, Thoughtful, Relaxed, Steady, Looked Like A Smart Gentleman and More Presidential. Romney Looked and Acted as if he was Ready to Take the Job as Commander-in-Chief ASAP. President Barack Obama Looked more like a Very Disparate Candidate and Challenger, very Negative, Acted like a Disrespectful Attack Dog Instead of the President of the United States. Mitt Romney Expressed his Concern about Iran's Nuclear Threat that is 4 Years Closer and the USA Support of Israel, our Good Friend and Middle East Ally. The strained relationship with the Obama Administration. Tonight Romney Impressed the Ladies Very much, in that a Vote for Him is a Vote for American Security, Peace and Safety, a Strong Economy, a Strong Military, Millions of Higher Paying Jobs, Prosperity for the Middle Class and Others. and a Quiet Peaceful Life for USA and all People. The World is Much to Scary these days, Americans Aren’t Looking For a Scary Arrogant, Angry. Rude, Disrespectfully and Weak President. Barack Obama is Not the One to Lead us Any Longer Tonight we Came Away with the Feeling that President Barack Obama is extremely a more Scary Candidate then the President of USA. We are Concerned about America's Weaken Relationship with Israel, a Nuclear Iran, our Weaken Economy and the Huge 16 Trillion Dollars Debt, that in itself Threatens our National Security. Americans, Black, White, Latinos, Wake Up, USA Debt is Bigger than our Gross National Product. We Can Not Afford Four More Years of President Obama's Spending, Borrowing and lies. We Can Not Afford Another 5 or 6 Trillion Dollars in More Debt From China or Other Countries. Our Jewish Women's Focus Group of almost 8000 Democrats Therefore Proudly Endorse Governor Mitt Romney as the Next President of the United States of America. Vote for Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan Before It's to Late. Do it Now ....ASAP Public Notice: We Feel Strongly that President Barack Obama is No Longer Fit to Lead USA.</Msg><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351116613615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:10:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351116660620-142</Id><Topic><Title>Binders and Big Bird ROMNESIA OH MY!</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351115006973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surge in Women Voting for Mitt Romney for President of USA and Their Reasons By ladies_4_romney . Oct 24, 2012 2:37 PM Women Democrat Voters and Others are Switching to Mitt Romney in Ohio Michigan Florida Virginia Pennsylvania Wisconsin New York- New Jersey ( East Coast to West Coast ) The Democrat Ladies for Romney in all 50 States Ladies are Switching from Obama very Fast. Read this and you too will Change and become a "Romney Democrat" for a Stronger USA Economy and honest leadership. Women, Jewish Democrats and others are Switching to Mitt Romney for President. Women Review Debate 3 : First, Governor Mitt Romney Pasted the President Test, Ready to Lead USA. By USA_Jewish_Women 10 22 2012 Great Impression: Mitt Romney's Stunning Turnaround in Past 3 Debates after Huge Negative Ads. The Reasons for Change is Obama has Lost the Support and Respect with Women Voters and Others. People Notice: Most Men and Women are Turned Off Against Barack Obama most everywhere and Across All 50 States, Here is the the Review of Debate 3 on October 22, 2012 By a Jewish Women Focus Group of 7,890 Women Connecticut Across America Our Strong Plea for Change in the White House, Why? The following reasons listed bellow. Note: This review is a agreement amongst a Group of almost 8000 Women watching debates. During the Debate 3, President Barack Obama was Arrogant, Disrespectfully, Angry, Rude and Condescending to Governor Mitt Romney. Obama did not Act or Look Presidential. We Feel Governor Mitt Romney Pasted the Presidential Test and is Ready to Lead USA We Support Mitt Romney, found him to be a Smart, Respectable and Decent Gentleman. Governor Mitt Romney Looked Much More Presidential, Ready to be Commander-in-Chief. Mitt Romney said America Needs a Strong Economy in order to have a Strong Military for our National Security right now and the Future. ...... We All Agree. Women came away from this Debate with a Very Good Impression of Governor Mitt Romney, in that he would be a “ A Safe Pair of Hands.” in Foreign Policy and a Strong Economy. We Trust Him More. Obama lied about Libya on 9 11 ( a 8 hour fire fight, Obama watched did nothing) In Foreign Policy We feel Mitt Romney is Tough Enough to do what’s necessary, but laid-back enough not to do too much and get us into another war. Miit Romney Did Not attack President Obama's Policies, he Simply Pointed Out a Few Needed Improvements in a Very Respectable Way. During the debate Governor Mitt Romney Seemed More Like a Leader, Smart, Respectable, Thoughtful and Considerate. He looked and Acted more Like the New American President that our Nation and the rest of the World Needs so Disparately in These Troubling Economic Times. Governor Mitt Romney was Calm, Thoughtful, Relaxed, Steady, Looked Like A Smart Gentleman and More Presidential. Romney Looked and Acted as if he was Ready to Take the Job as Commander-in-Chief ASAP. President Barack Obama Looked more like a Very Disparate Candidate and Challenger, very Negative, Acted like a Disrespectful Attack Dog Instead of the President of the United States. Mitt Romney Expressed his Concern about Iran's Nuclear Threat that is 4 Years Closer and the USA Support of Israel, our Good Friend and Middle East Ally. The strained relationship with the Obama Administration. Tonight Romney Impressed the Ladies Very much, in that a Vote for Him is a Vote for American Security, Peace and Safety, a Strong Economy, a Strong Military, Millions of Higher Paying Jobs, Prosperity for the Middle Class and Others. and a Quiet Peaceful Life for USA and all People. The World is Much to Scary these days, Americans Aren’t Looking For a Scary Arrogant, Angry. Rude, Disrespectfully and Weak President. Barack Obama is Not the One to Lead us Any Longer Tonight we Came Away with the Feeling that President Barack Obama is extremely a more Scary Candidate then the President of USA. We are Concerned about America's Weaken Relationship with Israel, a Nuclear Iran, our Weaken Economy and the Huge 16 Trillion Dollars Debt, that in itself Threatens our National Security. Americans, Black, White, Latinos, Wake Up, USA Debt is Bigger than our Gross National Product. We Can Not Afford Four More Years of President Obama's Spending, Borrowing and lies. We Can Not Afford Another 5 or 6 Trillion Dollars in More Debt From China or Other Countries. Our Jewish Women's Focus Group of almost 8000 Democrats Therefore Proudly Endorse Governor Mitt Romney as the Next President of the United States of America. Vote for Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan Before It's to Late. Do it Now ....ASAP Public Notice: We Feel Strongly that President Barack Obama is No Longer Fit to Lead USA.</Msg><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351116660620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351116882781-143</Id><Title>Obama another Nixon but Much Worse - Romney is the man, The Only Choice - CNBC Chris Mathews - Hard Ball Racist BoyCott</Title><Msg>Surge in Women Voting for Mitt Romney for President of USA and Their Reasons By ladies_4_romney . Oct 24, 2012 2:37 PM Women Democrat Voters and Others are Switching to Mitt Romney in Ohio Michigan Florida Virginia Pennsylvania Wisconsin New York- New Jersey ( East Coast to West Coast ) The Democrat Ladies for Romney in all 50 States Ladies are Switching from Obama very Fast. Read this and you too will Change and become a "Romney Democrat" for a Stronger USA Economy and honest leadership. Women, Jewish Democrats and others are Switching to Mitt Romney for President. Women Review Debate 3 : First, Governor Mitt Romney Pasted the President Test, Ready to Lead USA. By USA_Jewish_Women 10 22 2012 Great Impression: Mitt Romney's Stunning Turnaround in Past 3 Debates after Huge Negative Ads. The Reasons for Change is Obama has Lost the Support and Respect with Women Voters and Others. People Notice: Most Men and Women are Turned Off Against Barack Obama most everywhere and Across All 50 States, Here is the the Review of Debate 3 on October 22, 2012 By a Jewish Women Focus Group of 7,890 Women Connecticut Across America Our Strong Plea for Change in the White House, Why? The following reasons listed bellow. Note: This review is a agreement amongst a Group of almost 8000 Women watching debates. During the Debate 3, President Barack Obama was Arrogant, Disrespectfully, Angry, Rude and Condescending to Governor Mitt Romney. Obama did not Act or Look Presidential. We Feel Governor Mitt Romney Pasted the Presidential Test and is Ready to Lead USA We Support Mitt Romney, found him to be a Smart, Respectable and Decent Gentleman. Governor Mitt Romney Looked Much More Presidential, Ready to be Commander-in-Chief. Mitt Romney said America Needs a Strong Economy in order to have a Strong Military for our National Security right now and the Future. ...... We All Agree. Women came away from this Debate with a Very Good Impression of Governor Mitt Romney, in that he would be a “ A Safe Pair of Hands.” in Foreign Policy and a Strong Economy. We Trust Him More. Obama lied about Libya on 9 11 ( a 8 hour fire fight, Obama watched did nothing) In Foreign Policy We feel Mitt Romney is Tough Enough to do what’s necessary, but laid-back enough not to do too much and get us into another war. Miit Romney Did Not attack President Obama's Policies, he Simply Pointed Out a Few Needed Improvements in a Very Respectable Way. During the debate Governor Mitt Romney Seemed More Like a Leader, Smart, Respectable, Thoughtful and Considerate. He looked and Acted more Like the New American President that our Nation and the rest of the World Needs so Disparately in These Troubling Economic Times. Governor Mitt Romney was Calm, Thoughtful, Relaxed, Steady, Looked Like A Smart Gentleman and More Presidential. Romney Looked and Acted as if he was Ready to Take the Job as Commander-in-Chief ASAP. President Barack Obama Looked more like a Very Disparate Candidate and Challenger, very Negative, Acted like a Disrespectful Attack Dog Instead of the President of the United States. Mitt Romney Expressed his Concern about Iran's Nuclear Threat that is 4 Years Closer and the USA Support of Israel, our Good Friend and Middle East Ally. The strained relationship with the Obama Administration. Tonight Romney Impressed the Ladies Very much, in that a Vote for Him is a Vote for American Security, Peace and Safety, a Strong Economy, a Strong Military, Millions of Higher Paying Jobs, Prosperity for the Middle Class and Others. and a Quiet Peaceful Life for USA and all People. The World is Much to Scary these days, Americans Aren’t Looking For a Scary Arrogant, Angry. Rude, Disrespectfully and Weak President. Barack Obama is Not the One to Lead us Any Longer Tonight we Came Away with the Feeling that President Barack Obama is extremely a more Scary Candidate then the President of USA. We are Concerned about America's Weaken Relationship with Israel, a Nuclear Iran, our Weaken Economy and the Huge 16 Trillion Dollars Debt, that in itself Threatens our National Security. Americans, Black, White, Latinos, Wake Up, USA Debt is Bigger than our Gross National Product. We Can Not Afford Four More Years of President Obama's Spending, Borrowing and lies. We Can Not Afford Another 5 or 6 Trillion Dollars in More Debt From China or Other Countries. Our Jewish Women's Focus Group of almost 8000 Democrats Therefore Proudly Endorse Governor Mitt Romney as the Next President of the United States of America. Vote for Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan Before It's to Late. Do it Now ....ASAP Public Notice: We Feel Strongly that President Barack Obama is No Longer Fit to Lead USA.</Msg><Username>political_gangsters</Username><Timestamp>1351116882781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351118479221-144</Id><Title>Romney wins with landslide between 304 to 334 electoral votes</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351118479221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351118669985-145</Id><Title>Surface POS surfaced a belch, nice try Dinosoft</Title><Msg>roflmao</Msg><Username>lumpycei</Username><Timestamp>1351118669985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351119626315-146</Id><Topic><Title>Surface POS surfaced a belch, nice try Dinosoft</Title><Username>lumpycei</Username><Timestamp>1351118669985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:44:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We're not there yet. Surface is a fantastic promise, and holds fantastic potential. But while potential is worth your attention, it's not worth your paycheck. Surface RT gets so many things right, and pulls so many good things together into one package. But it is undercooked. For all Microsoft's claims to hardware perfection and software revolution, Surface RT is undone by too many little annoyances, cracks, and flaws. After the initial delight of an evolved tablet wears off, you'll groan—because Surface brings the appearance of unity, but it's really just the worst of both worlds. Instead of trading in your laptop and tablet for Surface, a cocktail of compromises that fracture the whole endeavor, you'll miss them both urgently. Want to use Surface RT as a laptop? Sorry, the Touch Cover is a letdown. It's a phenomenal engineering effort, and the most terrifically-integrated mobile keyboard ever. It doesn't compare to the junky Bluetooth options you can slap against your iPad. Microsoft's keyboard cover is perfectly integrated with the device, and touch typing on it is actually possible. You can't say the same for the iPad's glass. But it only approximates a real keyboard—the buttons are pressure activated, barely buttons at all, and spaced in such a way that typos are inevitable and constant. Unlike the first time you pinched an iPhone or gazed at E-ink, there's zero that's instantly intuitive about the Touch Cover. And in order for this to be a brave new computer, Touch Cover had to be instantly intuitive, an immediately responsive thing to touch and work with. But rather than feeling like you've instantly grown an extra brain lobe just by using it, Surface's mega-hyped keyboard cover feels like it requires one. You'll feel clumsy. You'll write slowly. I tried writing this review on the Surface, but I would've missed my deadline by a week. You'll get better—it will probably take weeks to hit a stride—but this thing was supposed to be a breakthrough. A perfect interface. Instead, it's just a half-broken death march up the learning curve. The trackpad, sludge-like and jerky, is even worse—particularly galling compared to the super-smooth touchscreen—and unlike the keyboard, will never get better with practice. The Touch Cover also approximates, dismally, the sturdiness of a laptop: thanks to the cloth-like floppiness of the thing that's necessary for making it easy to open and close, it can't support itself on anything but a flat, rigid (apologies) surface. You can't type on your lap, like laptop. It's hard to imagine what a design solution out of this would have been, but that's Microsoft's job, not ours. Perhaps most galling is the Touch Cover's $100 addition to the Surface's already pricy $400 base MSRP—akin to selling your windshield wipers separate from the car. Microsoft also offers a Type Cover, that promises actual physical keys instead of the flattened solution, but that will add critical bulk to your Surface experience—along with an extra $130. Another letdown—and a pretty outrageous one. But it's Windows on Surface RT that's the greatest letdown of all, the lethal letdown, because it's not Windows 8, but Windows RT. You can't tell the difference by looking at them, but you certainly will once you use it. Windows RT is underpowered (everything opens and syncs slightly too slowly), under-functional (you cannot install a single app that's not available through the Windows RT app store, which offers a paltry selection), and under-planned (the built-in apps can't feel like Lite versions of something better). You'd be right to note that many of those limitations apply to the iPad as well, but no one could mistake iOS for OS X the way RT apes Windows 8. And even if it's a plight common to tablets, Microsoft—for better or worse—has hyped Surface RT as being so much more. In the end though, this is nothing more than Microsoft's tablet. And a buggy, at times broken one, at that, whose "ecosystem" feels more like a tundra. There's no Twitter or Facebook app, and the most popular 3rd party client breaks often. The Kindle app is completely unusable. There's no image editing software. A People app is supposed to give you all the social media access you'd ever need, but It's impossible to write on someone's Facebook wall through the People app, Surface's social hub; the only workaround is to load Internet Explorer. Blech. Something as simple as loading a video requires a jumbled process of USB importing, dipping in and out of the stripped-down desktop mode, opening a Video app, importing, going back into the Video app, and then playing. What. The app selection, overall, is worse than the already pathetic Windows Phone app fare, looking like the software equivalent to a barren Soviet grocery store. The difference is that Windows Phone, used in quick, informative bursts, skates by on the strength of its excellent with integrated features. At the moment, there's just not that much to do with Microsoft's über-tablet. Surface is weak because Windows RT is weak; a tepid tablet OS pretending to be a computer's. You can do work, yes. But productivity is limited to a "preview" (beta) version of Microsoft Office. It also hurts that Office requires plunging into Windows RT's Desktop mode, where users of actual Windows 8 are able to install a decade's worth of legacy software. Normally, this would compensate. But RT users can't install any of this older software. None of it. Desktop mode is entirely worthless in RT, a cruel tease of non-functionality. It'll only remind you of how much you can't do with your Surface, and is going to confuse the living hell out of most people who buy one—especially when Surface Pro, built on x86 architecture and perfectly compatible with all of those legacy programs, steps in a few months from now. I pity Microsoft's retail staff. Should you buy it? No. The Surface, with an obligatory Touch Cover, is $600. That's a lot of money. Especially given that it's no laptop replacement, no matter how it looks or what Microsoft says. It's a tablet-plus, priced right alongside the iPad and in most ways inferior. That could change. Maybe there will be a new Touch Cover that retains the original's terrific physical qualities while actually allowing good typing. Maybe the quasi-vaporware Surface Pro, which eschews Windows RT in favor of the real-deal Win 8, will make all the difference, opening itself up to the open seas of PC software (for several hundred dollars more). Maybe the app store will look different in a month, or a year, and have anything to offer. Maybe. But remember that Windows Phone—which has swelled from mere hundreds, to tens of thousands, to over a hundred thousand app offerings over the past two years—is still a wasteland compared to iOS and Android. Poor precedent. Maybe Windows RT will be different. Maybe.</Msg><Username>applesplits</Username><Timestamp>1351119626315</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351119791119-147</Id><Topic><Title>Surface POS surfaced a belch, nice try Dinosoft</Title><Username>lumpycei</Username><Timestamp>1351118669985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:44:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU MUST WORK FOR DINOSOFT ROFLMAO</Msg><Username>lumpycei</Username><Timestamp>1351119791119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351121031505-148</Id><Title>Windoze RT is a clusterphuck: will not run any desktop applications beyond the applications that are bundled with the operating system: NO OUTLOOK!!</Title><Msg>wwwDOTwinsupersiteDOTcom/article/windows8/windows-rt-redmond-problem-144554 Straight for winsupersite...the fanboi place....WaRT is a #$%$ disaster.... ===================================== Fact is, Microsoft has decided to launch a Windows RT version of its Surface three months before a Windows 8 version. And to do so without effectively communicating what, exactly, it is selling. Put another way, on the day that Microsoft launches Windows 8 to the world—a day that is the most eagerly awaited Microsoft product launch since Windows 95—Microsoft will also launch a device that runs Windows RT, and not Windows 8. Think about that for a minute. And consider this: When Microsoft finally announced the pricing and availability of that (Windows RT, not Windows 8) product this week, it left out crucial technical specifications as always, even as it allowed customers to actually pre-order the thing. Cue onslaught of questions. Cue deer in the headlamp response. This was avoidable. Based on my email, I have to think that most of these first customers have absolutely no idea what they’re buying. That some have still made an amazingly expensive purchase regardless, well, it boggles the mind. Regular readers of this site already know that I’ve written about this stuff. A lot. I mean, just this week, I wrote Microsoft Surface: RT Vs. Pro, A Specifications Comparison, a way to pick between the current RT-only versions of Surface and the coming Windows 8-based versions. I published Mailbag: Microsoft Surface Special Edition, a collection of the most frequent (and reasonable) Windows RT and Surface RT questions I’ve received since the product pre-order announcement. Most important, I published How To Choose: Windows 8 Vs. Windows RT, a guide to choosing between Windows RT and Windows 8. But people still don’t understand Windows RT. Because of the amazing amount of email I’ve received this week, I kept my Windows Phone nearby while watching TV last night and answered dozens of emails during commercial breaks. I went to sleep with not a single email left unread. And yet I woke up to 154 non-spam emails, most about Surface and Windows RT, this morning. 154. Just from overnight. Some of the questions I’m getting are absolutely amazing to me. And these emails, which are almost child-like in their lack of awareness, speaking volumes about the job that Microsoft simply is not doing communicating this product—and its differences with Windows 8—to customers. With the understanding that I have communicated all of this stuff dozens of times, if not more, a few basics: Windows RT is a limited version of Windows 8 that runs on ARM-based devices, not on traditional PCs. Yes, Windows RT is compatible with most, but not all, of the Metro-style apps that also run on Windows 8. That is one advantage of this new Metro environment that graces both systems. But. Windows RT will not run any desktop Windows applications beyond the applications that are bundled with the operating system. Bundled applications include virtually every single desktop application found in Windows 8—Paint, WordPad, etc.—except for Windows Media Player. It also includes a fully-functional and full-featured version of Office 2013 called Office Home &amp; Student 2013 RT. This suite includes Word, Excel, OneNote, and PowerPoint. For the umpteenth time, it does not include Outlook. Let me stress that point again. Windows RT will not run any desktop applications beyond the applications that are bundled with the operating system. This means it will not run Windows Essentials 2012, Microsoft Outlook (any version), Microsoft Office (any version, beyond what’s included with RT), Adobe Photoshop or Photoshop Elements, or any other Adobe desktop application. It will not run the SkyDrive desktop application (which is part of Essentials 2012, yes, I know), meaning you cannot sync SkyDrive data to your RT device’s storage. You can only use the SkyDrive Metro app, which lets you access SkyDrive only when connected … just as with any other mobile device. It will not run iTunes. It will not run any desktop Windows application beyond what’s bundled with the OS. Windows RT is not a computer operating system. Windows RT is an operating system for mobile devices. Surface with Windows RT is not a computer. It is mobile computing device, like an iPad. It is a tablet, a hybrid device that bridges the gap between real PCs and media tablets, where you can work and play. =====================================</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1351121031505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351121567080-149</Id><Title>Get this, the Lying Conniving King of Cover-Ups Commie Kenyan...</Title><Msg>.... wants YOU to TRUST HIM!!!!!!!!!! Now THAT'S funny, the lying piece of e vill blood thirsty she it wants someone to, TRUST "HIM!" You can't make this stuff up,.... unless of course you're a lying loser anti American blood thirsty liberal making up some far fetched fairy tale story about some obscure video being the cause of a MASSACRE WHERE 5 AMERICANS WERE MURDERED and then trying to cover-up what really happened. Now THAT can be made up, by a certain piece of e vill d mon ick anti American lying commie Kenyan she it. And the Musllim monkey want's YOU to BELIEVE his LIE because HE thinks that YOU are as STUPID as HE IS and YOU say corpse man TOO. Never EVER trust a lying anti American blood thirsty d mon ick Musllim from Kenya with big ears and a bigger nose and as black as the ace of spades that stutters and stammers like the blithering blood thirsty p o s it e it he is. The only time the warmongering psychotic Kenyan lies, is when he's breathing. No one trusts the Musllim, no one. Except for anti American commies and Musllims.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351121567080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:32:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351122054798-150</Id><Title>Tagg</Title><Msg>anyone know if MSFT would be looking at Tagg :?: Thanks</Msg><Username>whoppo142002</Username><Timestamp>1351122054798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351123183617-151</Id><Topic><Title>Windoze RT is a clusterphuck: will not run any desktop applications beyond the applications that are bundled with the operating system: NO OUTLOOK!!</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1351121031505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:23:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol, you are simply showing how much you fear this great new device from MSFT.</Msg><Username>jackdee45</Username><Timestamp>1351123183617</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351123306535-152</Id><Title>Comedian, Paul Rodriguez, endorses Mitt Romney and says Latinos don't really like the Kenyan</Title><Msg>But then again, who does, he's blood thirsty d mon ickally e vill.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351123306535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:01:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351124727602-153</Id><Topic><Title>Obamma's campaign song by the Edgar Winter Group</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351115572392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 17:52:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice! There's hope for you yet.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351124727602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351124945265-154</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins with landslide between 304 to 334 electoral votes</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351118479221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually 340 for Romney!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351124945265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351125155314-155</Id><Topic><Title>Likeability poll</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351117382597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, Barney Frank, Dodd, Hillary, Billary, Obamma, Soros, Cloward, Pivens and ACORN et. al caused the financial meltdown by lending money to people who couldn't afford a snow cone let alone a hundred thousand dollar home and after they collapsed it they had to blame it on someone other than themselves so the blamed on Bush as usual. But no one really believes it was Bush other than the anti American commies who hate the country because that's why caused the meltdown in the first place, it was quite intentional by the aforementioned financial leftist commie terrorists. Pay attention old fat black lady and stop being Kool-Aid drinking commie for a change.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351125155314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351126087155-156</Id><Title>Polls show: Legal Latinos to vote for Romney, illegals to vote for Obamanure!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351126087155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351126699636-157</Id><Topic><Title>Likeability poll</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351117382597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Video snags Dem boss plotting vote fraud Congressman's son advises forging ID, relying on party lawyers Published: 8 hours ago author-image by Art MooreEmail | Archive Art Moore entered the media world as a public relations assistant for the Seattle Mariners and a correspondent covering pro and college sports for Associated Press Radio. He reported for a daily newspaper and served as senior news writer for Christianity Today magazine before joining WND shortly after 9/11. He holds a master's degree in communications from Wheaton College Graduate School.More ↓ The son of Rep. Jim Moran, D-Va. – who serves as the field director for his father’s campaign – has been caught on video advising an undercover reporter how to fraudulently cast ballots in the name of registered voters by forging utility bills and relying on the assistance of Democrat lawyers. James O’Keefe’s Project Veritas, known for its hidden-camera probe of the controversial national community organizing group tied to Obama, ACORN, carried out the investigation and provided the video exclusively to WND. UPDATE: After this story was published today, Patrick Moran announced his immediate resignation from the Moran for Congress campaign. Click here for details. Jim Moran, 67, a controversial figure in Congress, has been criticized for his collaboration with Islamic leaders with ties to terrorism. In 2003, Moran, then a regional whip in the House of Representatives, was punished by House Democratic Leader Nancy Pelosi after he suggested Jews were responsible for the push for war against Iraq. His son, Patrick Moran, was videoed by the undercover reporter Oct. 8 at the Cosi Restaurant in Arlington, Va., just across the Potomac River from the nation’s capital. The Project Veritas video shows the undercover reporter posing as a citizen concerned that the Democratic Party might lose power in the upcoming Nov. 6 elections. The reporter explains to Moran that he had been apolitical but got his girlfriend pregnant and was concerned about the political threat to the funding of “reproductive services.” The reporter, who approaches Moran at the restaurant, says he has a friend who found the names of 100 Virginia residents who have been registered the past three elections but have not voted. Moran initially thinks the reporter’s intent is to offer the registered voters a ride to the polling place on Election Day to ensure they cast their ballots. But the reporter states he and his friend actually want to vote in the name of the Virginia residents.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351126699636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351126865832-158</Id><Topic><Title>Likeability poll</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351117382597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba got caught in a lie about libya and will be impeached and jailed.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351126865832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:01:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351126976873-159</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins with landslide between 304 to 334 electoral votes</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351118479221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba will have less now that their is proof that he lied about libya. Impeached and jail is going to meet him.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351126976873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351127204043-160</Id><Topic><Title>Romney wins with landslide between 304 to 334 electoral votes</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351118479221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney sign burning in Leesburg considered arson Wednesday - 10/24/2012, 12:02pm ET LEESBURG, Va. - It's not unusual for campaign signs to be stolen or even destroyed during the course of a political campaign. But an incident early Monday morning, involving a sign burning, is now being called arson. Libby Stevens put up her 4-foot-by-8-foot blue and white Mitt Romney sign when the candidate himself came to Leesburg last week. It was on her front lawn, inside her white picket fence. About 2 a.m. Monday someone set the plastic sign on fire. Stevens says it was scary to look out the window to see flames leaping into the night. "To come into someone's gated fenced front yard and set something on fire? Something could have happened," she says. The Loudoun County Fire Department has classified the sign burning as arson, which in this case would be a misdemeanor. If a suspect is convicted he or she could face a year in jail and a big fine. Stevens' home is on South King Street, or route 15, which is a major commuter route into Leesburg. Stevens says signs have been stolen from her fence before. She's replaced her smaller signs on the fence three times, even using plastic fasteners to keep them from being stolen again. Two doors down, her neighbor also has signs up. But they are for President Obama. Her message to whoever burned the sign: "Shame on you!" On her lawn now, next to the scorch mark from the fire, and two empty aluminum poles, she has placed a smaller Romney sign and an American flag.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1351127204043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:06:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351127317728-161</Id><Topic><Title>Likeability poll</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351117382597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congressman's son resigns after voter fraud video The field director for Virginia Democratic Rep. Jim Moran - his son Patrick Moran - has resigned after being secretly recorded seemingly advising an conservative journalist masquerading as a supporter that utility bills could be used to aid in voter fraud. "Patrick is well liked and was a well-respected member of the campaign team. This incident, however, was clearly an error in judgment," said a statement from Moran for Congress. "The campaign has accepted Patrick's resignation, effective immediately." The undercover video comes from Project Veritas, which is led by group James O'Keefe - the activist whose undercover videos have caused serious headaches for ACORN, NPR and other groups. It shows a Project Veritas "investigator" telling Patrick Moran that he has a friend who is seeking to "get in a van" and vote on behalf of about 100 people. Patrick Moran responds with skepticism, but is later shown saying the person voting on behalf of others could potentially use "utility bills or something like that." "He'll need bills," says Moran. "He'll need something with the name and their address on it." He adds, "they can fake a utility bill with ease, you know?" Moran later says the person would be better off participating in traditional get-out-the-vote efforts, but he goes on to have a conversation about how to forge documents. In a press release, O'Keefe called the video "the most damning evidence to date of the scope of voter fraud in this country." Many states have passed laws in recent years, largely pushed by Republicans, designed to reduce voter fraud. Democrats note that there have been very few documented cases of voter fraud and say the laws are designed to suppress the vote among groups that traditionally support Democrats.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1351127317728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351127509020-162</Id><Topic><Title>Likeability poll</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351117382597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a question for Team Commie,.... what part don't you understand, poor old fat black lady living on assistance and food stamps? Your Musllim Messiah spearheaded the efforts to implement the sub-prime meltdown by forcing countless bogus loans to people that couldn't afford a sno-cone let alone a mobil home that led to the Great Recession and just because you're too obtuse to understand that don't get your big fat old lady granny panties in a bunch. He, your e vill anti American destructive Musllim Messiah, was key in bringing down the financial institutions because he followed his 2 commie pieces of socialistic she it's mentor's plan to bring it down, their names are Cloward and Pivens, they were commie professors in 1964 and the old commie p o s Frances Fox Pivens still attends the Marxist Musllims fund raisers today to help him finish off America. Oh, I almost forgot,.... Bush made Obamma, Cloward, Pivens, Frank, Dodd and Soros do it. No wait, it was the anti Isllam video. Or better yet, blame it on Rio. In any case you communists will blame it on everyone but the guilty party, the communist party, the DNC.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351127509020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351127740357-163</Id><Topic><Title>Likeability poll</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1351117382597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 18:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one really like the blood thirsty Musllim, they just like the free stuff he gives them then they drool and mindlessly vote for the corpse man p o s. It's a Pavlovian thing.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351127740357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351127767714-164</Id><Title>MSFT is at the launching pad</Title><Msg>3 days in a low, MSFT found the bottom and refused to go lower. It's on the launching pad right now. look for 5% to 10% appreciation with official WINDOW 8 rollout MSFT goes to $29.25-$30.75</Msg><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1351127767714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351127806284-165</Id><Title>Squueze play in CGUD!!</Title><Msg>Confirmed NoLimitStocks and ThePennystockProfiler are teaming up on CGUD for tommorow mornings low float sub penny play.</Msg><Username>robbiequy262</Username><Timestamp>1351127806284</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351128269228-166</Id><Title>Obamma said Bush made the video</Title><Msg>And Bush told him to use it as an excuse. And that it was Bush that went to Vegas, not him. Don't worry about Big Bird, it's the Big Lying Turd Obamma that you have to beware of, for it is e vill.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351128269228</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351128864910-167</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Media Still Spouting Libya....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351096700238</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 12:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo will not let me post anything that isn't positive for the pres. Just keep pounding</Msg><Username>free2491</Username><Timestamp>1351128864910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351130005984-168</Id><Title>Type in, 12 year old girl shoots intruder</Title><Msg>An Oklahoma girl shot an intruder in her home after calling 911. She is a hero and SHE is alive because if she waited for the police to arrive she would be DEAD. Maybe if she asked the intruder nicely to hold on before he killed her cause she called 911 and the police were caught in traffic maybe he would give her more time. The intruder broke into her home and was shot in the arm through the door of the closet she was hiding in and police found the 32 year old man and arrested him down the road as he tried to flee. She shot the intruder with a GUN that saved her life, if she didn't have a GUN to protect her life she would have probably been raped, beaten and had her throat cut from ear to ear and the criminal would be alive and THAT would make the anti American anti Freedom commie liberals quite happy because they think she probably deserved it and shouldn't have had a gun and that he was really a nice guy and didn't deserve to be shot because he probably just wanted to have s e x with her and some milk and cookies.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351130005984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351130679257-169</Id><Topic><Title>Type in, 12 year old girl shoots intruder</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351130005984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 21:53:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy more as long as the Kenyan is in our white house.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351130679257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351130865718-170</Id><Topic><Title>Hog Wad Hillary said that there needs to be an investigation before jumping to conclusions?</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351106068325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 15:14:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hog Wad Hillary Dog is a lying anti American communist piece of she it. Like her hubby and Hussein.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351130865718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:07:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351132154254-171</Id><Topic><Title>Windoze RT is a clusterphuck: will not run any desktop applications beyond the applications that are bundled with the operating system: NO OUTLOOK!!</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1351121031505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 19:23:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, #$%$ - I'm pointing out how #$%$ it is.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1351132154254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 22:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351134971641-172</Id><Title>Brain dead Bozo Biden stumping in Ohio spreading his commie propaganda said to the crowd,...</Title><Msg>.... 'I'm glad to be here in Iowa!' The mindless more on doesn't even know where he's at let alone what time it is, but at least he's not so stupid he says corpse man. But then again, NO ONE, could be THAT stupid.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351134971641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351135386943-173</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show: Legal Latinos to vote for Romney, illegals to vote for Obamanure!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351126087155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 20:48:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama gets all cartoon character votes by 100%.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351135386943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:23:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351135439685-174</Id><Title>Obama is ahead in dead people vote!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351135439685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351135553394-175</Id><Title>Obama ahead in the all voters 17 and younger!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351135553394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351135779752-176</Id><Title>Romney wins with 340 electoral votes!!!!!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1351135779752</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351136338680-177</Id><Title>PBS is reflective of America's parasitical decaying entitlement draining society</Title><Msg>Big Bird's worth over $400,000,000.00 and THEY DON'T NEED THE MONEY. Just like one too many parasites that are 'making money' under the table quite nicely getting big bucks and STILL, like PBS, getting money from the government, hence putting the burden on the shrinking tax base and soon it will all go boom if you reelect the commie....... The looney leftist are giving money to the 'mega wealthy' people that they hate so much. So in essence and in fact, liberals LOVE to hate or else they wouldn't hypocritically do that. They are all truly mentally disturbed and would cut off their noses to spite their fascist faces. i.e. they're killing the host goose that laid the golden egg and they will be itch the loudest when it dies. Even though THEY killed it. Again, they are truly mentally disturbed and extremely self loathing stoopid.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351136338680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351136556074-178</Id><Topic><Title>PBS is reflective of America's parasitical decaying entitlement draining society</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351136338680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:38:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The commies must be stopped at any and ALL costs.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1351136556074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 23:42:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>