<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348129303234-1</Id><Topic><Title>Volume has drastically reduced to wait for the big Windows 8 launch</Title><Username>topinvestgun1</Username><Timestamp>1348111072499</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:17:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>w8 and wp8 are clusterphucks in the making. They will be wrose than vista and kin.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1348129303234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 04:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348135924152-2</Id><Title>msft in hottest stocks</Title><Msg>Good time buy on the dip as recommended here #######investmentviews.net#######</Msg><Username>garymott211</Username><Timestamp>1348135924152</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348136020901-3</Id><Title>GMO Corn Is Lethal</Title><Msg>Eating genetically modified corn (GM corn) and consuming trace levels of Monsanto’s Roundup chemical fertilizer caused rats to develop horrifying tumors, widespread organ damage, and premature death. That’s the conclusion of a shocking new study that looked at the long-term effects of consuming Monsanto’s genetically modified corn. The study has been deemed “the most thorough research ever published into the health effects of GM food crops and the herbicide Roundup on rats.” News of the horrifying findings is spreading like wildfire across the internet, with even the mainstream media seemingly in shock over the photos of rats with multiple grotesque tumors… tumors so large the rats even had difficulty breathing in some cases. GMOs may be the new thalidomide. “Monsanto Roundup weedkiller and GM maize implicated in ‘shocking’ new cancer study” wrote The Grocery, a popular UK publication. It reported, “Scientists found that rats exposed to even the smallest amounts, developed mammary tumors and severe liver and kidney damage as early as four months in males, and seven months for females.” The Daily Mail reported, “Fresh row over GM foods as French study claims rats fed the controversial crops suffered tumors.” It goes on to say: “The animals on the GM diet suffered mammary tumors, as well as severe liver and kidney damage. The researchers said 50 percent of males and 70 percent of females died prematurely, compared with only 30 percent and 20 percent in the control group.”</Msg><Username>bankerbuster</Username><Timestamp>1348136020901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348136202388-4</Id><Topic><Title>GMO Corn Is Lethal</Title><Username>bankerbuster</Username><Timestamp>1348136020901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:13:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GMO Tumor Death brought to you by MONSANTO, manufacturer of Agent Orange(the defoliant) morphed into ROUND-UP(Weed Killer). *0% of corn on the consumer shelf here in the good old USA is GMO. Bill Gates you idiot! You are killing us.</Msg><Username>bankerbuster</Username><Timestamp>1348136202388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:16:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348136305671-5</Id><Topic><Title>GMO Corn Is Lethal</Title><Username>bankerbuster</Username><Timestamp>1348136020901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:13:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>80 % of the Corn on the grocery store shelf is GMO. Thank your FDA GUbermint GUBERS!</Msg><Username>bankerbuster</Username><Timestamp>1348136305671</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:18:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348136769244-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama "Redistribution" is Communism 101</Title><Username>paulrand18</Username><Timestamp>1348108629301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:37:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really #$%$ I hope you didn't just figure this out.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348136769244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:26:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348137414646-7</Id><Topic><Title>GMO Corn Is Lethal</Title><Username>bankerbuster</Username><Timestamp>1348136020901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:13:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where was the FDA? In the backroom of MONSANTO, stuffing CASH into their TRAITOR pockets.</Msg><Username>bankerbuster</Username><Timestamp>1348137414646</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348140938500-8</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says a "tape released a coupla days ago"</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1348094900053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Posted at 03:39 PM ET, 09/19/2012 Champagne tower hidden at Jay-Z and Beyonce’s fundraiser for Obama By The Reliable Source The famous champagne tower at Jay-Z’s 40/40 Club — shown on a night when the president wasn’t there. (Theo Wargo/Getty Images) Hey, where’s the bubbly? The landmark feature at Jay-Z’s 40/40 Club in Manhattan is a dazzling, 18-foot champagne tower — 350 gold bottles in all, from what’s said to be his favorite brand, Armand de Brignac — a highlight of the nightspot’s $10 million renovation earlier this year. But at the hip-hop mogul’s fundraiser for President Obama Tuesday night, the wall of glitz was discreetly covered up under a dark dropcloth, reports our colleague Amy Gardner. Hmmm — an optics thing, you think? Only a few gleaming bottles near the top were visible. Guests, who paid $40K each for the privilege of attending, did however enjoy champers served in flutes. Obligatory VIP banter aimed at co-hostess Beyonce: “Jay-Z now knows, you know, what my life is like,” joked POTUS. “We both have daughters. And our wives are more popular than we are.”</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1348140938500</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348142583638-9</Id><Topic><Title>Be wary</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1348064777914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:26:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jim Jones the Christian gave the Muslims the idea for using terrorism in the name of their respective deities.</Msg><Username>therwnjneedhelp</Username><Timestamp>1348142583638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348146083193-10</Id><Title>Windows Update</Title><Msg>Anyone having trouble getting updates for windows 7 ?</Msg><Username>einho330</Username><Timestamp>1348146083193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348146190936-11</Id><Title>PAUL RYAN JILLED BOWLES-SIMPSON: Judd Gregg, said he believes the House Republicans who rejected it were beholden to an argument by anti-tax advocate Grover Norquist that the measure was tantamount to a tax increase.</Title><Msg>Bloomberg News Ryan Helped Derail Simpson-Bowles Plan Romney Now Sees as Model By Heidi Przybyla on August 13, 2012 Representative Paul Ryan was a pivotal figure in killing the 2010 Bowles-Simpson agreement, which Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney now holds out as a model for putting America’s fiscal house in order. The 18-member panel needed 14 votes to send a 10-year plan to trim the debt to Congress for a vote. As his party’s then- ranking member on the House Budget Committee, Ryan led a bloc of three House Republicans who denied the additional votes needed. All three Senate Republicans on the panel backed the plan and one of them, former New Hampshire Senator Judd Gregg, said he believes the House Republicans who rejected it were beholden to an argument by anti-tax advocate Grover Norquist that the measure was tantamount to a tax increase. “All of the House Republicans were disproportionately affected by the Norquist group on the issue of tax reform,” said Gregg, now a senior adviser at New Mountain Capital LLC. Ryan “clearly was the leader” of House Republicans in setting the terms of a grand debt bargain, said Andy Stern, a panel member and Democrat</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1348146190936</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:03:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348146661702-12</Id><Title>NTWK $6.04….Breakout Alert…....Up Every day following record 4Q and FY 2012 Revenues. .....Guidance for 2013 is strong with 30 - 40% revenue growth and $1/share net income.....Cloud Divisions growing exponentially....Analysts increase their average target price to $16 and max to $21/share after September FY 2012 earnings report…..Short-term (about a month) Target: $10++.....Significant institutional and insider buying.…3M share float.</Title><Msg>Check Out NTWK’s Magnificent Chart. Can’t Post Here….. NTWK is poised to stage a significant breakout any day now Most Recent Analyst Research (last week): We project 13% annual growth to FY14 from FY10 reflecting 80 significant legacy NFS customers in FY14, up from 52, 37, and 28 in FY12, FY11, and FY10, respectively. The great majority of them in China and the rest of Asia where NTWK is the undisputed preferred software provider of every major public and state-owned car company in the region. It's global alliance with Mercedes Benz has resulted in over a dozen multi-million implementations in the region and many more in the pipeline Globally The new Vroozi Cloud Division contributed $1.3 million in FY12. We expect at least $4 million in FY13 and $6 million to FY14 Our price target is based on the average forward 2013 P/E multiple of 13.2X (up from 12.8X in August 2012). NTWK is trading at 6.4X our FY13 net income projections. EPS forecast of $0.85 per share. We applied an 11X multiple to our FY13 EPS forecast. We anticipate a richer multiple as earnings momentum builds in FY13. . NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. In August 2011, NetSol launched its Cloud Vroozi Division, an e-procurement search tool for SAP supplier relationship management (SRM) users. SAP AG is a global vendor of enterprise management systems that has the largest market share (24%) based on a worldwide Gartner survey. Vroozi should provide sales diversification and a higher margin recurring revenue stream. The Vroozi division contributed $1.3 million in FY12 sales and is expected to grow to $4 million in revenues in 2013 NTWK announced its 2nd Cloud Division last week offering an array of products and services to capture a greater % of the cloud applications in North America. The company is implementing this division using their significant software development capabilities and infrastructure. MORE NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide and Riyadh.</Msg><Username>john.kenell</Username><Timestamp>1348146661702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348146734327-13</Id><Topic><Title>Investigation finds no evidence AG Eric Holder knew of 'Fast and Furious' gun-running sting</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1348095751750</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:02:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course there was no evidence. One by one the bogus talking points from the radical right are being destroyed.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1348146734327</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348147703370-14</Id><Topic><Title>Investigation finds no evidence AG Eric Holder knew of 'Fast and Furious' gun-running sting</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1348095751750</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:02:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no evidence all was fabricated made up right wing lies. correction: the most honest and moral administration of all time, Obama's.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1348147703370</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348147760336-15</Id><Title>The Clueless Will All Vote For Obama</Title><Msg>they have NO clue how bad the economy is and how incompetent Obama is. They will vote for him just because he's Black and talks well. It's called the dumbing down of America. I feel sorry for Romney. He has the right message and plan, but has no chance with the legions of uniformed out there who look at Obama as a God.</Msg><Username>citamar</Username><Timestamp>1348147760336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348147924044-16</Id><Title>paurand is a communist and traitor to his country</Title><Msg>every time crap rolls out of his mouth like a bunch of maggots</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348147924044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348147965039-17</Id><Topic><Title>PAUL RYAN JILLED BOWLES-SIMPSON: Judd Gregg, said he believes the House Republicans who rejected it were beholden to an argument by anti-tax advocate Grover Norquist that the measure was tantamount to a tax increase.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1348146190936</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:03:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, Paul Ryan PAUL RYAN KILLED BOWLES-SIMPSON as commanded by Grover Norquist.</Msg><Username>mongo_the_puffball</Username><Timestamp>1348147965039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:32:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348147996088-18</Id><Title>correction paulrand is a communist and traitor to his country</Title><Msg>every time crap rolls out of his mouth like a bunch of maggots</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348147996088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348148743786-19</Id><Title>The K0*ch Bros have the House Republicans by the short hairs. THE k0*CH Bros use their lobbyist Grover Norquist to control the Republican House. Grover Norquist is the arm-twister of their whacky libertarian agenda. Norquist is the enforcer.</Title><Msg>Paul Ryan is a desciple of whacky Ayn Rand. These fanatical people should scare the be-jebus out of you.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1348148743786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149083349-20</Id><Topic><Title>The Clueless Will All Vote For Obama</Title><Username>citamar</Username><Timestamp>1348147760336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama voters don't need clues they already know who's best. Besides you caling nursing home patients, soldiers, hard working low income famiies,children, those on social security, clueless? Robme you know, said they all, all vote for Obama. They pay no taxes and want everything for free, food, housing, you name it. Yes a presidential candidate said that. Get a clue from that?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1348149083349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149611072-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama "Redistribution" is Communism 101</Title><Username>paulrand18</Username><Timestamp>1348108629301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:37:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a closet communist only to those dummies who vote for him; he is actually a full blown openly communist commisar type. I figured Obama out as a disaster long before he was elected. Now we have to get together and dump him.</Msg><Username>paulrand18</Username><Timestamp>1348149611072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149664638-22</Id><Topic><Title>Koch Bros.</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348149413097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>directly to those in need what a joke- the Kochs wouldnt give the sweat off their #$%$ to someone really in need- they wouldnt be able to get all the money in the world that way- BTW fairydumb... is a communist and a traitor to his country</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348149664638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:01:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149802889-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama "Redistribution" is Communism 101</Title><Username>paulrand18</Username><Timestamp>1348108629301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:37:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>paulrand is a communist and a socialist as well as a marxist- time to prosecute him and deport him</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348149802889</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348149859077-24</Id><Title>An Empty Chair Would be Far Better than Obama</Title><Msg>An empty chair can't borrow money from China. An empty cair can't wreck the economy. An empty chair can't go golfing instead of doing its job. An empty chair isn't married to a wife who spends your money like water.. An empty chair doesn't support infanticide of small babies. An empty chair isn't a pathological liar. etc, etc. etc.</Msg><Username>paulrand18</Username><Timestamp>1348149859077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149978430-25</Id><Topic><Title>An Empty Chair Would be Far Better than Obama</Title><Username>paulrand18</Username><Timestamp>1348149859077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only communists are against Roe Wade and pro life</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348149978430</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348150406565-26</Id><Title>The AlQaeda connection</Title><Msg>Could it be that the republicans are directly responsible for 9/11?? look at the person who is leading them around by the nose now- none other than the mysterious Grover Norquist with his mysterious connections to the Middle East. Is it possible that GN is an AlQaeda operative?? if not he is at least a communist</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348150406565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348150469502-27</Id><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Msg>BOSTON (Reuters) - Microsoft Corp said it has fixed a security bug in Internet Explorer that hackers exploited to attack some customers. The attacks prompted the German government and security experts to urge people to temporarily stop using the browser. The software maker said late Wednesday that the permanent repair to the software, used by hundreds of millions of people, would be released on Friday. A majority of Microsoft Windows users have their computers set to automatically download that update. Microsoft spokeswoman Yunsun Wee said in a statement that "the vast majority" of Internet Explorer users had not been attacked as a result of the security flaw.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348150824576-28</Id><Title>CERP, adding BIG, this has a TON of room to run, AND WILL</Title><Msg>Target .50 by tomorrow or Monday.</Msg><Username>dealerschoice10</Username><Timestamp>1348150824576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348151454337-29</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once again the screaming and hollering of the Microsoft haters and bashers is shown to be little more than chicken little shouting that the sky is falling- its amazing how the news media never ceases to fall for this crap and echoes the squawks of these psuedo IT experts- likely because their readership is in seemingly continual decline</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348151454337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152168178-30</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The rest of the story: "The vulnerability in Internet Explorer was identified on Friday by a Luxembourg-based security researcher. His computer was infected while analyzing a computer server used last year to launch a cyber industrial espionage campaign on dozens of chemical makers and defense contractors. "Network security firm AlienVault said on Tuesday that it had discovered three other servers that hosted malicious websites that exploited the Internet Explorer flaw. It said the latest round of attacks targeted defense contractors, not the general public. "Internet Explorer was the world's second-most widely used browser last month, with about a 33 percent market share, according to StatCounter. It was close behind Chrome, which had 34 percent of the market."</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1348152168178</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:42:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348152355594-31</Id><Topic><Title>The AlQaeda connection</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348150406565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>something is going on to subvert America for sure, why do so many republicans swear allegiance to him and have secret meetings? why do they talk in code and laugh under their breath and give each other winks?</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1348152355594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348154038078-32</Id><Topic><Title>The World is on Fire</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1348152551200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>News to U.. The USA is not the world. Let the Middle East deal with its own problems, they are not our problems. Nice little emotional hatchet job though. Either you are a disingenuous $&amp;$##% or you are too stupid to grasp the scale of things.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1348154038078</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348154291499-33</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at nearly 60% market share of desktops and laptops Microsoft IE easily bests feebleflop and chrome neither of which has even 20% share anymore</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348154291499</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348154314677-34</Id><Title>PLmartin craps himself in girlish hissy fit over protests. Take it easy Martian and turn off the Limbaugh.</Title><Msg>Poor little PL is just fit to be tied. Maybe the only thing he needs is an old white guy in the presidency to make it all better.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1348154314677</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348154651289-35</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see the wally bot has added something. Too bad it (not he) is permanently on Ignore, so I can't read it or reply.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1348154651289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348155170171-36</Id><Title>Romney now wants to be Latino</Title><Msg>when speaking to Latino groups, that is. He references his grandparents, who "were Ameican". If they were Americans why did they move to Mexico to avoid obeying American laws on marriage? Hey this is entertaining.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1348155170171</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348155870584-37</Id><Title>Senate Tax dodging report may hurt MSFT &amp; Hewlett</Title><Msg>once again Washington, trying to divert attention from their own failures to simplify the tax paying process, is looking for a scapegoat to pick on. Claims MSFT dodged about $40 billion in taxes by using legal means to avoid paying taxes.</Msg><Username>jspsaki</Username><Timestamp>1348155870584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:44:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348156189244-38</Id><Topic><Title>The World is on Fire</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1348152551200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your little flag waving opinion is at odds with the Tea Party. Better check your script. Every empire ends by ignoring its limitations. You seem to want the USA to jump in over its head and fail. Are you a commie. Do you really not understand the transient nature of this "support" the USA gives to the world economy. Apparently you do not as you also bring up our floundering currency. Put those two things together and stir em up and see if you can understand. You get your group together and talk of how gud it wuz in the gud ole dayz when the USA was White and women knew their place and vast swaths of the world were underdeveloped and we could do as we pleased and we were a capitalist run utopia.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1348156189244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157176280-39</Id><Topic><Title>PLmartin craps himself in girlish hissy fit over protests. Take it easy Martian and turn off the Limbaugh.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1348154314677</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:18:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe there is no problem with America today. I know you reject this in the purpose of partisan politics and would be as happy as a brain dead redneck could be with our current status if a repub were in charge. Just remember Obama did not start any useless wars. Compare that to the trivial things you whine about.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1348157176280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348157298651-40</Id><Title>FFI, loading huge here on tiny dip, this is heading to $1 and more. Check news</Title><Msg>CANNOT PASS THIS UP</Msg><Username>dealerschoice10</Username><Timestamp>1348157298651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157322838-41</Id><Topic><Title>The World is on Fire</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1348152551200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While you idiots discuss politics on this Board Microsoft is taking off like gang busters.....Very strong buy.....</Msg><Username>jravera</Username><Timestamp>1348157322838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:08:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158509061-42</Id><Topic><Title>The K0*ch Bros have the House Republicans by the short hairs. THE k0*CH Bros use their lobbyist Grover Norquist to control the Republican House. Grover Norquist is the arm-twister of their whacky libertarian agenda. Norquist is the enforcer.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1348148743786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul Ryan is a desciple of whacky Ayn Rand. These fanatical people should scare the be-jebus out of you. Ryan is another wealthy dik that inherited well from daddy.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1348158509061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:28:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348158882075-43</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not worth reading anyway...just wally spewing his usual crap.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1348158882075</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348160557777-44</Id><Title>TAXES</Title><Msg>I'm not buying ANYTHING form Corps that are avoiding taxes. Small start; one person; star none-the-less.</Msg><Username>datacounts</Username><Timestamp>1348160557777</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161183765-45</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT TO GET HIT WITH $4.6 BIL. TAX FOR STEALING FROM TAXPAYERS IN US</Title><Username>dexter.anastacio</Username><Timestamp>1348160739519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:05:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was all perfectly legal....politicians can moan and groan all they want, but the bottom-line is...YOU are the legislators....CHANGE THE LAW!!!!</Msg><Username>fattymcbutterpants2001</Username><Timestamp>1348161183765</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348161775308-46</Id><Topic><Title>TAXES</Title><Username>datacounts</Username><Timestamp>1348160557777</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:02:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who then? GE? FEES - FEES</Msg><Username>free2491</Username><Timestamp>1348161775308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348163394481-47</Id><Topic><Title>TAXES</Title><Username>datacounts</Username><Timestamp>1348160557777</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:02:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft structured the Skype deal to keep its taxes as low as possible. As the Wall Street Journal’s Ronald Barusch notes, Microsoft and Skype saved billions of dollars in taxes because Microsoft used its foreign profits to purchase Skype, which also happens to base its corporate headquarters in a major tax haven itself, Luxembourg. • Every employee at Microsoft has the same aim: to give Microsoft 100% market share in every market that it is involved in – Total World Domination • Hire type A people who are driven by conquest, not by security • Go after a market with the view to dominate it because owning a strategic market gives you a cash cow. In his 1996 book, Type A Behavior: Its Diagnosis and Treatment, Friedman suggests that Type A behavior is expressed in three major symptoms: free-floating hostility, which can be triggered by even minor incidents; time urgency and impatience, which causes irritation and exasperation usually described as being "short-fused"; and a competitive drive, which causes stress and a achievement-driven mentality. The first of these symptoms is believed to be covert and therefore less observable, while the other two are more overt.</Msg><Username>der_schpountz</Username><Timestamp>1348163394481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348164832367-48</Id><Title>Stock Alerts Microsoft MSFT, Facebook FB, Groupon GRPN</Title><Msg>Stock Alerts Microsoft MSFT, Facebook FB, Groupon GRPN</Msg><Username>wworld933</Username><Timestamp>1348164832367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348165169080-49</Id><Topic><Title>Real Scientists know polar ice levels neither support or debunk warming</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1348162982564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:43:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So due to melting Antarctic glaciers are pushing more and more ice into the Antarctic seas? And in the mean time Arctic ice is less and less every year?</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1348165169080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:19:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348165419918-50</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just as I thought.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1348165419918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348166760831-51</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT can be the next ten bagger!</Title><Username>reed_cranford</Username><Timestamp>1348151983830</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:39:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks good</Msg><Username>patrickowens182</Username><Timestamp>1348166760831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:46:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348167209040-52</Id><Title>Westinghouse Solar, Inc. (WEST) Google it 10 X's the money @ current .20 pps</Title><Msg>Westinghouse Solar, Inc. (WEST) Google them and your see why 10 X's the money in the making</Msg><Username>serenityloveh69</Username><Timestamp>1348167209040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348167423376-53</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcreek Team and Obama's So-Called Redistribution....Debunked Again.</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1348164311794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:05:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The hawcreek team is much more interested in power , and partisan politics than they are for the welfare of their country....</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1348167423376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348167879989-54</Id><Title>NTWK $6.2 Up 3%....Hottest NASDAQ stock up every day.....Just the start of a prolonged rally to double digits.....Fundamentals can support $16 per analysts......Technicals looking better each day......Cloud Division is growing exponentially.....only 6 PE and 1 times sales is 30% of sector average......3 million share float almost gone after record earnings and strong guidance of over 30% revenue growth and $1/share net income in 2013 and doubling/tripling revenues to 2015.</Title><Msg>EASY DOUBLE AS FUNDAMENTALS EASILY SUPPORT $16……WEEKLY CHART SHOWS REPLICA OF 2010 WHEN THE STOCK WENT FROM $8 TO $24 IN A FEW WEEKS WITH FAR LESS POTENTIAL FYI….This Week’s Analysts Comments o Upgrade: We project 13% annual growth to FY14 from FY10 reflecting 80 significant customers in FY14, up from 52, 37, and 28 in FY12, FY11, and FY10, respectively...ÃƒÂ¢Ã¢â€šÂ¬Ã‚Â¦The Vroozi Cloud Division contributed $1.3 million in FY12. We expect at least $4 million in FY13 and $6 million to FY14 Our price target is based on the average forward 2013 P/E multiple of 13.2X (up from 12.8X in August 2012). NTWK is trading at 6.4X our FY13ÃƒÂ¢Ã¢â€šÂ¬Ã‚Â¦.. EPS forecast of $0.85 per share. We applied an 11X multiple to our FY13 EPS forecast. We anticipate a richer multiple as earnings momentum builds in FY13. . NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. In August 2011, NetSol launched its Cloud Vroozi Division, an e-procurement search tool for SAP supplier relationship management (SRM) users. SAP AG is a global vendor of enterprise management systems that has the largest market share (24%) based on a worldwide Gartner survey. Vroozi should provide sales diversification and a higher margin recurring revenue stream. The Vroozi division contributed $1.3 million in FY12 sales and is expected to grow to $4 million in revenues in 2013 NTWK announced its 2nd Cloud Division last week offering an array of products and services to capture a greater % of the cloud applications in North America. The company is implementing this division using their significant software development capabilities and infrastructure. === MORE NTWWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide and Riyadh.</Msg><Username>joeyggrecco</Username><Timestamp>1348167879989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348168417361-55</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Pulling Ahead Of Romney</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1348158816850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt proved himself right: we do have a problem with people who see themselves as victims even as they benefit from loopholes in the IRS code. One of them is running for President.</Msg><Username>murrymom</Username><Timestamp>1348168417361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348168792378-56</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once again MSFT proves it has an excellent good team in place to backup it's products.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348168792378</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348170911405-57</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcreek Team and Obama's So-Called Redistribution....Debunked Again.</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1348164311794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:05:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>taking from some to give to others You aren't taking anything, and not getting it from someone who is paying less tax rate than others, like Romney does. The govt isn't receiving anything but what you owe tham, or if Romney, less than you owe cause you're rich and hire attorneys to game the system. You still haven't figured it out. No one is taking your money and giving it to poor people. You owe it, due to your income in this case, the govt receives it, then they use it according to how ALL the people decide. Sorry, money doesn't get you more than one vote.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1348170911405</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171012557-58</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcreek Team and Obama's So-Called Redistribution....Debunked Again.</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1348164311794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:05:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They aren't "taking"</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1348171012557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171609284-59</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once again, despite being a dying product, Internet Explorer proves to be an inviting target for exploits.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1348171609284</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171770769-60</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which is why many places are advising people to abandon IE for ever.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1348171770769</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348172088224-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama makes a good decision, he is reportedly looking for a retirement home in Hawaii</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1348164481355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in KENYA</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348172088224</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:14:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348172190765-62</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why MSFT is the DE FACTO browser &amp; OS &amp; why linux is the dismal failure that it is.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348172190765</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:16:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348174311078-63</Id><Topic><Title>Terrorist attacks against Americans</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348174159963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yes, Like Romney has so much damn experience....get real, although Obama is not that good he is still more experienced that Romney......</Msg><Username>jravera</Username><Timestamp>1348174311078</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348174343916-64</Id><Topic><Title>Terrorist attacks against Americans</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348174159963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White House Press Secretary Jay Carney, after insisting for more than a week that the White House had no evidence to suggest the deadly attack on the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi was anything but a 'spontaneous' act, concedes that it was an act of terror.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348174343916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348174406796-65</Id><Topic><Title>If you make less than $250K you won't see ANY tax rise a dime? No much more</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1348162332756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:32:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our Family of four earns $35,000 anually. We are one of the Families included in Romneys Speel which basicly Labeled us as Mooches.The funny thing is until Romneys Elitist Speech labeling us as Loosers we had always Voted Republican. So now we have traded sides and will vote for Obama. At leasthe only thinks the 47% are Losers and Trash,but is NOT DUMB ENOUGH TO VERBALIZE IT. I wonder how many Republican Voters he lost with that one speech. We can`t be the only ones.</Msg><Username>bhenning32</Username><Timestamp>1348174406796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348174769452-66</Id><Topic><Title>Terrorist attacks against Americans</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348174159963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libya attack directly tied to al Qaeda, involved former Gitmo detainee: Intelligence sources Last Updated: 1:21 PM, September 20, 2012 Posted: 8:41 AM, September 20, 2012 Intelligence sources say they are convinced the deadly attack on the US Consulate in Benghazi, Libya, was directly tied to al Qaeda -- with a former Guantanamo detainee released by the Obama Administration. That revelation comes on the same day a top Obama administration admitted last week's deadly assault a "terrorist attack" -- the first time the attack has been described that way by the administration after claims it had been a "spontaneous" act. "Yes, they were killed in the course of a terrorist attack on our embassy," Matt Olsen, director of the National Counterterrorism Center, said during a Senate hearing Wednesday. Olsen echoed administration colleagues in saying US officials have no specific intelligence about "significant advanced planning or coordination" for the attack. However, his statement goes beyond White House Press Secretary Jay Carney and Susan Rice, the US ambassador to the United Nations, saying the Sept. 11 attack on the consulate was spontaneous. He is the first top administration official to call the strike an act of terrorism.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1348174769452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:59:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348175981634-67</Id><Title>HairyDoakes likely a marxist communist in drag</Title><Msg>generally speaking these people who rage against something are usually guilty of that transgression themselves. The drunk who screams and howls against liquor is of course one of the worst offenders- thats ole Hairy when it comes to marxism and communism</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348175981634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348176499440-68</Id><Topic><Title>Terrorist attacks against Americans</Title><Username>harrydokes</Username><Timestamp>1348174159963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Americans like you deserve it.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1348176499440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348178926037-69</Id><Topic><Title>Why is it so difficult for some to see something so clear?</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1348177804899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The old saw is as true as ever: There is none so blind as he who WILL not see. Socialism is favored almost exclusively by those who have good reason to expect nothing in life but failure. They rationalize it in every way imaginable and hope against hope that others will be unable to see what they themselves refuse to see.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1348178926037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348179289228-70</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your information is about a dozen years out of date.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1348179289228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:14:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348182224992-71</Id><Topic><Title>Why is it so difficult for some to see something so clear?</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1348177804899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well tell us of ANY modern societies that don't incorporate some socialism?? Since your ideal gov does not exist in the real world do you think there might be a problem??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1348182224992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348183069649-72</Id><Topic><Title>Warming - Hawcreek Team Debunked By Pictures....</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1348161855011</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:24:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>James Taylor is a senior member of the Heartland Institute...i.e. a K0*ch Bros shill.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1348183069649</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348187469576-73</Id><Title>"Make no mistake...", I lied about the terrorist attacks!</Title><Msg>Lier, lier pants on fire. What a Obamanure buffoon!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1348187469576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348187626472-74</Id><Title>Must see: "The obama you don't know, the Washington Examiner." 10 part series</Title><Msg>The anti American commie left's Musllim Messiah was a lawyer for his favorite slum lord pastor and not only helped him illegally evict many, many black, white and hispanic tenants he got him off with a paltry $50.00 fine. The Kenyan is out for money and power, nothing more, and NOTHING less. His stupid followers are just too stupid to figure it out. Go and read the Washington Examiner and see just how devious and evill your Musllim Messiah really is. Find out what the rest of America already knew about the spawn of darkness Musllim. It also reveals that the Musllim was no more a "professor" than a june bug. The babbling stuttering moe ron was a "lecturer" which is tantamount to nothing more than being the big mouth brain dead corpse man speaking idiot that he is. And he NEVER published even ONE legal article while other legal eagles around him published hundreds upon hundreds and that's because they are intelligent while the Kenyan is a dope smoking blood thirsty dolt who feeds off of others as he's done his whole parasitical Musllim magggot life.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1348187626472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:33:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348187633868-75</Id><Title>"Make no mistake...", Obamanure is all I got!</Title><Msg>No solutions to anything, and got ambassador killed by terrorists.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1348187633868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348188382993-76</Id><Title>"Make no mistake...", all the liberal rags got my back so I can say anything I want.</Title><Msg>And with no repercussions.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1348188382993</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348192356850-77</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT IE security flaw is fixed!</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1348150469502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After almost 2 decades, Microsoft STILL can't get it right!</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1348192356850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348192433154-78</Id><Topic><Title>Why is it so difficult for some to see something so clear?</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1348177804899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with the possible exception of Cuba there are no total socialist states on this planet wotopmp's bogeyman is nonexistant- the product of ignorance and apparant inability to learn the simplest things- look around you - almost every country on the planet is a capitalist socialist hybrid with the socialist part covering only things like infrastructure, medical programs, pension programs and military. The makebelieve bogey man doesnt exist</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348192433154</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348192878759-79</Id><Topic><Title>Why is it so difficult for some to see something so clear?</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1348177804899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Name a society where the socialism part of the economy is failing- no countrys are giving up their pensions, medical programs, military, infrastructure- instead we do have the rumble of the super rich and the super capitalists rageing against this little splinter of socialism and magnifying the size of this part of the economy and telling horror stories how its all bad for the character of good citizens to have medical care and pensions(God might punish them)- such an evil- and ignorant people like hawfaeces have fallen for it hook line and sinker</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348192878759</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:01:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348193208279-80</Id><Title>"Make no mistake...", Obamanure is not responsible, its the video guy!</Title><Msg>Its not the obamanure fault!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1348193208279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:06:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348193770300-81</Id><Title>"Make no mistake...", Redistribution Obamanure is policy!</Title><Msg>You didn't make that!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1348193770300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348194176847-82</Id><Title>Neegroes, Welfare &amp; Redistribution: Perfect together!</Title><Msg>A perfect balance!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1348194176847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348194831526-83</Id><Title>Strength in WIndows 8 launch</Title><Msg>Now, iPHONE is out of the way, MSFT is going to rocket to new highs. The giant has so much in the war chest that it can fight and win any war. It can through in feebies, lower license fee, provide supports and free software, skpye on mobile phone, free Office, Outlook, CRM, Finance and content. Plus, eco system is lining up, MS music store, app store, at &amp; t , Verison, Nokia, HTC, Samsung, and more more, the army is having strong alliance from gamers, business, developer, even government!. The Microsoft era is coming, Microsoft store is flourishing, with Surface, multimedia gadget, who knows what else in their sleeves, but I know the current forward P/E 9 will have lots of room to grow while you collecting ever increasing dividend that will be paid soon, With the wining of the patent war against Android, Andrioid is handicapped! iPHONE is for kids and consumers. Microsoft phone is for business, RIMM will surrender or get bought out using the round error in Microsoft balance sheet. .</Msg><Username>topinvestgun1</Username><Timestamp>1348194831526</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348195017856-84</Id><Topic><Title>Real Scientists know polar ice levels neither support or debunk warming</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1348162982564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:43:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Antarctic is the south pole Arctic is the north pole, the record ice you speak of is at the south pole where the extra ice could be coming from the land mass. And the mean time up north in the Arctic Seas we have less and less ice where no land mass is feeding the system.</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1348195017856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:36:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>