<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353822330405-1</Id><Topic><Title>Surface V IPAD</Title><Username>meadows_field</Username><Timestamp>1353694877912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:21:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you are stuck in a rut.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1353822330405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 00:45:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353822379076-2</Id><Topic><Title>Surface V IPAD</Title><Username>meadows_field</Username><Timestamp>1353694877912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:21:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no reason to lie; why would I bother to.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1353822379076</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 00:46:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353830523525-3</Id><Topic><Title>Expand Your Universe</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353770254026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:17:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oct 15, 2012 at 10:25am ET by Stephanie Hobbs While attending BIA/Kelsey’s SMB Digital Marketing 2012 Conference in Chicago last month, I was surprised by the results of a recent LCM study, which showed that only 20 percent of local businesses said they have experience with mobile marketing. Small businesses today operate in a time when smartphone adoption is growing rapidly (eMarketer predicts there will be 116 million U.S. smartphone users, representing 37% of the population, by the end of this year</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353830523525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 03:02:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353831167663-4</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT is the new RIMM for next decade!</Title><Username>dogeater2008</Username><Timestamp>1353812459485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:00:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a dip chit</Msg><Username>nzar669</Username><Timestamp>1353831167663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 03:12:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353831512294-5</Id><Topic><Title>Bush/Republican Tax Cuts For The Wealthy Created This Debt</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1353681868900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 09:44:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you that stupid to believe that liberal Bull chit. Stupid #$%$!!!!!</Msg><Username>nzar669</Username><Timestamp>1353831512294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 03:18:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353831588230-6</Id><Topic><Title>When is MSFT going to get its mojo back?</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1353693512304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 12:58:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Soon</Msg><Username>nzar669</Username><Timestamp>1353831588230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 03:19:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353837277720-7</Id><Topic><Title>Expand Your Universe</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353770254026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:17:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Washington Post: A digital marketing guide to prepare for Small Business Saturday A digital marketing guide to prepare for Small Business Saturday 11/13/2012 - The Washington Post Last year, American Express estimated that 103 million Americans shopped at a small business on Small Business Saturday. This is 15% higher than pre-Thanksgiving projections. With the year’s most popular local business shopping day less than a month away, it’s important to include digital media in your marketing mix. Customers are expected to “shop small” on Nov. 24. But how do you lure them into your store, not your competitors’? (Sarah L. Voisin - Post) To get the full exposure and awareness that your small business needs and deserves, here are some digital marketing tips to help you prepare for this year’s Small Business Saturday, coming up on Nov. 24.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353837277720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 04:54:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353838356553-8</Id><Title>So much for Open Source</Title><Msg>No one should use open source software without a USB Token since anybody can write to the source code which means "security" is non existent and open source does not necessarily mean "free" since software can be developed as a consulting project for one or more customers. The customers pay to direct the developers' efforts: to have bugs prioritized and fixed or features added. Companies or independent consultants can also charge for training, installation, technical support, or customization of the software.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1353838356553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 05:12:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353838834508-9</Id><Topic><Title>Expand Your Universe</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353770254026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:17:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- URL-Acquisition - Web-Hosting - Site Design - Mobile - Social Media - Content - Listings - SEO - Display - Offers - Calls - Leads Propel gets you everything you need to launch your business to new heights so that you can get found by customers looking for you when they’re ready to buy. The best part about it? Our package offers an unbeatable value at one low price. Sign up today and we’ll do all the work to get you started. Price Comparison</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353838834508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 05:20:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353845762454-10</Id><Topic><Title>Which stocks Billionaires Love?</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905639453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 04:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Total Black Friday revenue may have fallen, but online sales jumped 20.7%, IBM estimates. That followed an increase of 17.4% on Thanksgiving day. Shoppers are increasingly using their mobile devices to compare prices, with 24% of consumers accessing a retailer's site with a phone or tablet vs 14.3% last year.</Msg><Username>cris.chest</Username><Timestamp>1353845762454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 07:16:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353851648634-11</Id><Title>What is the next MSFT - Motley Fool</Title><Msg>The next MSFT is Micro Soft - MF you have identified a lot of winners in the past, but did you identify AAPL when it was around 35 just before it shot-up?......I did</Msg><Username>sseharan</Username><Timestamp>1353851648634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 08:54:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353853779170-12</Id><Title>CBO: Taxes are at their lowest level in more than 60 years</Title><Msg>Are Taxes in the U.S. High or Low? By BRUCE BARTLETT Historically, the term “tax rate” has meant the average or effective tax rate — that is, taxes as a share of income. The broadest measure of the tax rate is total federal revenues divided by the gross domestic product. By this measure, federal taxes are at their lowest level in more than 60 years. The Congressional Budget Office estimated that federal taxes would consume just 14.8 percent of G.D.P. this year. The last year in which revenues were lower was 1950, according to the Office of Management and Budget. The many adjustments to income permitted by the tax code, plus alternative tax rates on the largest sources of income of the wealthy, explain why the average federal income tax rate on the 400 richest people in America was 18.11 percent in 2008, according to the Internal Revenue Service, down from 26.38 percent when these data were first calculated in 1992. Among the top 400, 7.5 percent had an average tax rate of less than 10 percent, 25 percent paid between 10 and 15 percent, and 28 percent paid between 15 and 20 percent. The truth of the matter is that federal taxes in the United States are very low. There is no reason to believe that reducing them further will do anything to raise growth or reduce unemployment.</Msg><Username>your_lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1353853779170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 09:29:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353856719439-13</Id><Title>Taxes on the rich are lower than they have been for 80 years.</Title><Msg>The Long Run History of Taxes on the Rich We know that taxes on the very rich are at a historic low right now, which will go even lower if Mitt Romney wins. But how low, exactly? All the detailed studies I know of go back only to 1960. I’ve written about Piketty-Saez; the 2010 Economic Report of the President (pdf) also provided estimates, not taking into account corporate taxes: All these estimates show that taxes on the rich are the lowest they have been in half a century. But what about before 1960? Well, we know that the top marginal tax rate was even higher in the 40s and 50s than in the 60s; and it was very high by modern standards through much of the 30s too. So I think it’s safe to say that taxes on the rich are currently lower than they have been for not 50 but 80 years.</Msg><Username>your_lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1353856719439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:18:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353857027577-14</Id><Title>Congressional Research Service Study: Tax Cuts for the Rich Don't Spur Growth</Title><Msg>By Robert Frank Cutting taxes for the wealthy does not generate faster economic growth, according to a new report. But those cuts may widen the income gap between the rich and the rest, according to a new report. A study from the Congressional Research Service -- the non-partisan research office for Congress -- shows that "there is little evidence over the past 65 years that tax cuts for the highest earners are associated with savings, investment or productivity growth." In fact, the study found that higher tax rates for the wealthy are statistically associated with higher levels of growth. The finding is likely to fuel to the already bitter political fight over taxing the rich, with President Obama and the Democrats calling for higher taxes on the wealthy to reduce the deficit and fund spending. Mitt Romney and the GOP advocate lower marginal tax rates for top earners, saying they fuel investment and job creation</Msg><Username>your_lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1353857027577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:23:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353857419243-15</Id><Topic><Title>Congressional Research Service Study: Tax Cuts for the Rich Don't Spur Growth</Title><Username>your_lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1353857027577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:23:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely true at this point. Back decades ago when there was pent up demand for new production that would be certainly consumed giving the rich a cut would spur investment and hiring to make the goods. Now we have an impoverished middle class and no slam dunk areas for business to invest in that would improve middle class earning. So no tax cuts cannot do anything now.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857419243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:30:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353857723047-16</Id><Title>Serial liar and business idiot creek claims business costs are up in a recession and profits to be low</Title><Msg>Despite the available evidence of corporate profits. So the usual question which is he. 1 Completely ignorant without knowing so. 2 A deceptive partisan shill who cares nothing about the country only his cohorts. Or a linear combination of the two.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857723047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:35:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353858249130-17</Id><Topic><Title>Serial liar and business idiot creek claims business costs are up in a recession and profits to be low</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857723047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet he fails to explain how costs rise in a recession.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353858249130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:44:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353858921041-18</Id><Title>The Same Tea Party Birther Liars Are Now The Tax Liars!!!</Title><Msg>Remember the 'Birther' lie. Obama is not a US citizen? Remember the Tea Party liars that promoted the 'Birther' lie? Those are the same liars that are now lying about taxes. Birther Liars are now Tax Lairs.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1353858921041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:55:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353859271631-19</Id><Topic><Title>Surface V IPAD</Title><Username>meadows_field</Username><Timestamp>1353694877912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:21:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"why would I bother to" Because you are directly or indirectly paid to. That is the reason for your entire existence here. Been posting here a long time and have seen many many shills like you pop up around product launches. The work you do is a line item on MS marketing budget, or you are a volunteer who benefits in some way by posting your MS-boosting lies. Either way....</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1353859271631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 11:01:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353861963476-20</Id><Topic><Title>Serial liar and business idiot creek claims business costs are up in a recession and profits to be low</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857723047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Is corn up?" Was there a drought due to human induced climate change? " Is wheat up?" Was there a drought due to human induced climate change? "Why has gold doubled?" People are stupid. Not as stupid as you in most cases, but, more often than not, stupid. Speaking of making a donkey of yourself, how have y'all been doing since your team dug themselves farther into a hole? How was your THanksgiving crow? A lonely meal?</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1353861963476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 11:46:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353862007313-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Same Tea Party Birther Liars Are Now The Tax Liars!!!</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1353858921041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:55:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are those Looney's, and they are not that many anymore as they think, against people like romney paying 4% more in income tax? Like it was under Clinton. When asked why does romney need the extra money we give him, they even say he doesn't need it. He just likes it and wants it, real bad. So it appears their, the Looney's, ony true stance is "I'm obsessed with a black man being in charge , say it ain't so." Grover has done quite a number on their fried little brains thse past four years.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1353862007313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 11:46:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353862161666-22</Id><Topic><Title>Serial liar and business idiot creek claims business costs are up in a recession and profits to be low</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857723047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weak and lame excuses. You indicated costs rise generally in recessions then can only back this up with tangent factors of only the current recession. Try again dummie</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353862161666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 11:49:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353862247378-23</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Hawcrapers, he says to me "...you sound Loony" because I asked who caused the Benghazi screw up</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1353849946993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 08:25:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still won't admit that his idol Bush the Lesser decided that Saddam Hussein was responsable for the attack on 9/11/2001 that he was warned of and did nothing to prevent. Wingnuts don't seem to get the lack of poutrage that sane people have when the Bengoozle Bamboozle gets farted out of their moronic mouths. How can that be?</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1353862247378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 11:50:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353863839371-24</Id><Topic><Title>The Same Tea Party Birther Liars Are Now The Tax Liars!!!</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1353858921041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:55:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll be happy when he is long out of office and all the records are finally opened up. We are going to learn mind-blowing things about this pretender.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1353863839371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:17:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353864498768-25</Id><Title>Confronting the Reality of a Rapidly Warming World</Title><Msg>Bloomberg: The reality of a world with more extreme weather events, rising seas, and longer droughts is becoming clearer by the day. Even more troubling is that we are on course for still greater changes to our planet in the years ahead. That’s the key takeaway from a major new report from the World Bank, which examines the impact of a 4 degree Celsius (7.2 degree Fahrenheit) warmer world. At the same time, a new analysis by World Resources Institute (WRI) finds there are nearly 1,200 proposed coal plants worldwide. If these plants come online, our chances of staying within 2 degrees of warming—the level recommended to prevent the worst consequences of climate change—would be nil. The World Bank is not prone to hyperbole. Its warning that we could be heading to 4 degrees of rising global temperatures should be taken extremely seriously by leaders around the world. The World Bank’s assessment reaffirms what many of us already understand: scientific evidence of human-caused global warming is unequivocal. Given that it took little more than 4 degrees of cooling to create the last Ice Age, it would be hard to overstate how 4 degrees of warming could reshape our world by the end of this century.</Msg><Username>your_lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1353864498768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:28:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353865101610-26</Id><Topic><Title>Serial liar and business idiot creek claims business costs are up in a recession and profits to be low</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857723047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without having to give it a thought, one easy answer that I can't believe you overlooked is the health care costs have already gone up. Oh and energy costs. That's without even trying. Give it up. Hawk is always right.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1353865101610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:38:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353866165708-27</Id><Topic><Title>Surface V IPAD</Title><Username>meadows_field</Username><Timestamp>1353694877912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:21:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>trolls can'thandle the truth, Surface is kicking ipad's #$%$.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1353866165708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 12:56:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353866410146-28</Id><Topic><Title>Serial liar and business idiot creek claims business costs are up in a recession and profits to be low</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857723047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has sat in his chair all holiday weekend, constantly posting. Let's analyze what that means, it's more interesting than what he actually says bad about Obama. Business, climate change, politics, "you name it" he has been debunked and shown wrong on all. He doesn't care, he goes back to the same ol' same ol' statements. One thing it means is he has nothing else to do. What posseses someone to spend their entire life at posting political mesages on a finance board is more interesting. He says he has a wife and some kind of farm. He constantly calls others liars and "moes." Let's get out the psychology books on this guy, because it is quite "looney", as someone has said. His southern racist roots growing up in segregation in the 50's and 60's are quite apparent, and I think is why he doesn't like Obama and degrades him. Especially Obama being from a white mother and African father, that's a big one to many still.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1353866410146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:00:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353869077329-29</Id><Topic><Title>Win 8 will bomb big time</Title><Username>creephhi</Username><Timestamp>1353639027868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 21:50:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another dissatisfied customer. Microsoft does it again! Another Vista/Kin/Zune product that will fail.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1353869077329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:44:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353869191462-30</Id><Topic><Title>Surface V IPAD</Title><Username>meadows_field</Username><Timestamp>1353694877912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:21:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ipad is 90% hype. No productivity there. shorts paid shills can't handle that Surface is better so the only option they have to is blame you working for microsoft. lol Surface is the bets table. WIN8 is the best and mostly used (98%) o.s. just facts!</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1353869191462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:46:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353869191943-31</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT Surface on top of holiday gift wish list</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1353718760814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:59:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not on my holiday gift wish list, but a 13 inch MacBook Air is.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1353869191943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:46:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353869296568-32</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT Surface on top of holiday gift wish list</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1353718760814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:59:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WSJ --- Surface on top of holiday gift wish list FACT !</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1353869296568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:48:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353869318922-33</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT is the new RIMM for next decade!</Title><Username>dogeater2008</Username><Timestamp>1353812459485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:00:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw a store at the mall with a Lumina 900 poster in the window. There weren't any customers in that store.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1353869318922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 13:48:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353870059595-34</Id><Topic><Title>Serial liar and business idiot creek claims business costs are up in a recession and profits to be low</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857723047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How convenient of you to 'forget' that dufuscreek claimed a general feature of recessions which no one has yet to even try to support. He claimed costs go up in recessions.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353870059595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:00:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353872831486-35</Id><Topic><Title>Serial liar and business idiot creek claims business costs are up in a recession and profits to be low</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857723047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah the ole creek imply and deny scheme. You said ""Taxes are low as a percentage of GDP profit margins on domestic product are at lows in a recession. You pay taxes on profits not GDP"" So if sales are high (GDP) how can profits be low other than costs?? So explain how profits are low in a general recession when sales are still high.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353872831486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 14:47:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353873905050-36</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT Surface on top of holiday gift wish list</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1353718760814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:59:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Adios fool! I can hardly wait to buy an INTC based all in one Surface device.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1353873905050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:05:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353874464215-37</Id><Topic><Title>Win 8 will bomb big time</Title><Username>creephhi</Username><Timestamp>1353639027868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 21:50:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since mobile computing is displacing the desktop, and Android (i.e. Linux) is dominating mobile computing, it will make much more sense to standardize on Linux. That said, I don't necessarily expect Ubuntu Linux to become dominant. It appears to be aping Windows in some respects, and that is a losing strategy. For example, in some utilities it has translucent windows ( that is, the content of hidden portions of windows is visible but dimmed and blurred).</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1353874464215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:14:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353876668045-38</Id><Topic><Title>Serial liar and business idiot creek claims business costs are up in a recession and profits to be low</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857723047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""Taxes are low as a percentage of GDP profit margins on domestic product are at lows in a recession. You pay taxes on profits not GDP"" So if sales are high (GDP) how can profits be low other than costs?? So explain how profits are low in a general recession when sales are still high.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353876668045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 15:51:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353879333461-39</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung Tablets</Title><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1353714331499</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 18:45:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So-called leaked slides from Intel show a quad-core Atom processor running at half the power of the current dual-core Atom processor and that for the year 2014. Then announcement is expected in the fist half of 2013. This could make Atom the correct processor to support and favor for tablets. In the meantime, if you run programs like Photoshop, I would just go with Intel Ivy Bridge for 2012 and early 2013 and with Intel Haswell for mid-2013. The Samsung ATIV 700T tablet has the Intel Ivy Bridge processor. If the programs run are simpler than Photoshop then there is the Samsung ATIV 500T tablet.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1353879333461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:35:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353880597574-40</Id><Title>And why not, the super rich are the natural constituency of the Republican party...</Title><Msg>Many in the market agree there will be some sort of agreement that will fuel a rally, but the road there will be full of political landmines as Democrats and Republicans dig in on positions defended during the recent election. Liberals want tax increases on the wealthiest Americans while protecting progressive advances in healthcare, while conservatives make a case for deep cuts in programs for the poor and a widening of the tax base to raise revenues without lifting tax rates.</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1353880597574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:56:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353881466670-41</Id><Topic><Title>And why not, the super rich are the natural constituency of the Republican party...</Title><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1353880597574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"while conservatives make a case for deep cuts in programs for the poor " Isn't that a good thing? Why should poverty be programmed by the government? Oh yeah, it's a voting constituency for the left. Never mind.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1353881466670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:11:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353882036736-42</Id><Topic><Title>The Same Tea Party Birther Liars Are Now The Tax Liars!!!</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1353858921041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:55:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's an interesting point now that I think about it more. Unfortunately I got used to, and liked, segregation. Whatever the reasons are for tax revenues, as long as this President is in power, I will make up anything and everything to put him in a bad light. He just doesn't belong where he is, he should be a janitor at the white house using the back door, not fouling up the white areas. That over rules everything now.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1353882036736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:20:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353882945871-43</Id><Title>Google Search: Intertial Mass Suspension</Title><Msg>Paul Allen Needs to see this? Send him the info if you have any contact with him..</Msg><Username>dotcomsale</Username><Timestamp>1353882945871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:35:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353883471531-44</Id><Topic><Title>And why not, the super rich are the natural constituency of the Republican party...</Title><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1353880597574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you noticed? When the AMT was designed, its good point was that it prevented some people from using tax breaks to avoid paying taxes... and now that the AMT will prevent lower income people from using tax breaks from from payng taxes, the AMT is evil and needs to be changed to apply to some people, but not all people... The expression "equal before the law" is history...</Msg><Username>mcmsbm</Username><Timestamp>1353883471531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 17:44:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353885168064-45</Id><Topic><Title>Win 8 will bomb big time</Title><Username>creephhi</Username><Timestamp>1353639027868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 21:50:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>penguin if you don't like it go cry over on an open sore forum &amp; get the H off this board because plenty of people like myself happen to like &amp; use M$FT products.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1353885168064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 18:12:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353886773516-46</Id><Topic><Title>Serial liar and business idiot creek claims business costs are up in a recession and profits to be low</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353857723047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 10:35:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""Taxes are low as a percentage of GDP profit margins on domestic product are at lows in a recession. You pay taxes on profits not GDP"" Well trying to read this sentence with its incorrect English language, one could get the wrong idea of your intent. Is that intentional?? I notice that most of your posts contain grammatical errors even as you belittle others for their inability to read your incorrectly structured sentences. It seems to imply that GDP is high but profits are low?? Which leads us back to the question of why if sales are steady, are profits necessarily lower in a recession. You have dodged this question for a dozen posts as usual. I assume you are just posting nonsense about the Amazon thing as that is not at all relative to the question.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1353886773516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 18:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353886807080-47</Id><Title>The Confederacy Is An Example Of Redneck Extremism And Slavery/Wage Slavery</Title><Msg>Do you really believe the rightwing Norquist Schutzstaffel from the Bible Belt will negotiate before the Fiscal Cliff? Look at their stance on slavery and the economy based on the Plantation model! Did they compromise in 1861? What makes you think those advocates of the Plantation Economy will compromise on the emancipation of the wage slaves of 2013?</Msg><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1353886807080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 18:40:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353886873055-48</Id><Topic><Title>Win 8 will bomb big time</Title><Username>creephhi</Username><Timestamp>1353639027868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 21:50:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i bought and love it. 10 sec boot time. the whole screen comes to life.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1353886873055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 18:41:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353889081144-49</Id><Topic><Title>And why not, the super rich are the natural constituency of the Republican party...</Title><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1353880597574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lughead, I see you have been sold a bill of goods. The rich are the Wall St, Hollywood, Gates, Oprah, Buffett, Rockerfella, Heinz etc. All liberals. The Republicans are the party of personal responsibility.The middle class that goes to work everyday, pays their bills, taxes, healthcare etc and are being taxed to pay for the Democrat's vote buying programs. The increase in taxes for the top 1% won't even pay the interest on the 16 trillion dollar debt. Where do think we are going to get the money to pay down this debt? Or do you care. Obama says it doesn't matter in the short or mid term. And you liberals buy that? Not very smart are you?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1353889081144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 19:18:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353889297215-50</Id><Topic><Title>The Confederacy Is An Example Of Redneck Extremism And Slavery/Wage Slavery</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1353886807080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 18:40:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never compromise when it is God's will that teachs each to his own. Slavery was good for the black children, as has been said this election cycle. Taught them respect, how to work, and their place in the world. Now look how they behave. Segregation kept us apart according to God's will, and we were fine. We had no problems, everything ran smoothly. Now look what we have going on. How can we compromise with a so called President, who isn't one of us, and doesn't belong in that job? It's not his place. Worse he isn't even a legally born person according to my good old school thinking. Used to be we had laws against interracial marriage. Now look at the mess we have coming up in the world. Sincerley, Soul imposter, the truth shower</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1353889297215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 19:21:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353890776654-51</Id><Topic><Title>And why not, the super rich are the natural constituency of the Republican party...</Title><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1353880597574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 16:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>++The rich are the Wall St, Hollywood, Gates, Oprah, Buffett, Rockerfella, Heinz etc. All liberals.++ Yes, and all being realistic in saying that taxes on the super wealthy are too low considering the budget deficit...</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1353890776654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 19:46:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353893377618-52</Id><Title>The REAL Speaker Of The House Is A Lobbyist</Title><Msg>Billionaires Charley &amp; Dave K0ch pay Grover Norquist million$ to keep their taxes low. It's a good investment for them with a huge payback. Grover Norquist is the de facto Speaker Of The House.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1353893377618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:29:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353904590848-53</Id><Topic><Title>Win 8 will bomb big time</Title><Username>creephhi</Username><Timestamp>1353639027868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 21:50:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt Microsoft can develop a patch to fix that.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1353904590848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 23:36:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>