<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345263179000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest disgrace to Afro-Americans: Obamanure!</Title><Username>obadidoss</Username><Timestamp>1345262293000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 23:58:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Put a cork in it pal &amp; give everyone a break.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1345263179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345263472000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Even More Stunning Obama Corruption....</Title><Username>general_squalor</Username><Timestamp>1345215055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:50:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>media matters cut and pasted OPIC's description of itself from it's .GOV website. This program is self sustaining only when loans are paid back. I think we have a good glimpse of the government's ability to pick winners lately. If you look further into OPIC's objective, one guy pushing Lexus and Jag cars doesn't seem in tune with their mission statement. Nice try Media Matters. Good thing the majority of your readers are not into critical thinking. Forgive any typos as I could type with one hand only. I had to hold my nose from the stench of corruption.</Msg><Username>truescoundrel</Username><Timestamp>1345263472000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:17:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345286144000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Special Ops troups speak out against the President</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345265232000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama should never have singled out which unit did the deed, he should have just said US Military Operation. That camel hat is leaking info to his camel hat buddies, and you voted for him?</Msg><Username>tookzgain</Username><Timestamp>1345286144000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 06:35:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345286910000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Special Ops troups speak out against the President</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345265232000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you know anything about that? Were the "operatives" who are now working on behalf of the Republican party's political interests involved in any way? Can you point out any specific "leaks" damaging to the national security originating from the Executive? Just asking.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345286910000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 06:48:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345287190000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Special Ops troups speak out against the President</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345265232000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you know anything about that? I know the commander in chief's middle name is hussian, you don't need to be a rocket scienist to deduct from there.</Msg><Username>tookzgain</Username><Timestamp>1345287190000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 06:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345287661000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Special Ops troups speak out against the President</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345265232000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're just an idiot. Just checking. Carry on.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345287661000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:01:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345288256000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Special Ops troups speak out against the President</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345265232000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're just an idiot. To say "He" has a shady background would be a understatement and the turmoil the world is in is caused by a lot of hussians and there is the possibility "he" is trying to bust the USA financially. Trust is the key word here, can you trust anyone with that name?</Msg><Username>tookzgain</Username><Timestamp>1345288256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:10:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345288443000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting find of the Obama liar cartel here</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345288257000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the IRS passed romney taxes, they are OK. "they can't talk issues like jobs, economy. hussian must of read mein kampf, tell a lie loud enough long enough it becomes fact.</Msg><Username>tookzgain</Username><Timestamp>1345288443000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:14:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345288625000-9</Id><Title>Leaky Prime Minister.</Title><Msg>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/middleeast/israel/8326387/Israel-video-shows-Stuxnet-as-one-of-its-successes.html http://www.nytimes.com/2011/01/16/world/middleeast/16stuxnet.html?pagewanted=all</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345288625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345288977000-10</Id><Title>W. Mitt Romney paid ZERO Federal income and capital gains taxes</Title><Msg>For the ten years beginning in 1999 and extending to 2009. He's been shown to have been dishonest about his Bain Capital involvements during the years from 1999 to 2002 (and beyond) and his residence in the Commonwealth of Massachusetts during those years, along with the evasion of state and local taxes associated with his "retroactive" residency. There's absolutely no reason to believe anything he says, no matter how much his political supporters want to gloss over his record of dishonesty.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345288977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345289328000-11</Id><Topic><Title>W. Mitt Romney paid ZERO Federal income and capital gains taxes</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345288977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So painfully desperate you are. Will Bibi get you off the Kibbutz and into a nice settlement high-rise this year?</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345289328000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345291143000-12</Id><Title>Was Bush a secret Moozlim?</Title><Msg>Why else would he publish -IN ARABIC- atomic bomb designs on the internet? http://www.nytimes.com/2006/11/03/world/middleeast/03documents.html?pagewanted=print What wonderful things would Mitt the dimwit accomplish if given the ability to abuse the office of the Presidency? Secretary of the Treasury Meg Whitman would at least have auctioned those off on EBay.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345291143000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345295377000-13</Id><Title>Paul Ryan begging for TARP money.</Title><Msg>To paper over the economic disaster he and his Bushite teabagger buddies fostered: http://reason.com/blog/2012/08/13/watch-paul-ryans-speech-in-support-of-ta Maybe he should wander off into Galt's Gulch and starve.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345295377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345296131000-14</Id><Title>Voter fraud?</Title><Msg>http://www.forbes.com/sites/brendancoffey/2011/06/15/did-mitt-romney-live-in-his-sons-unfinished-basement-last-year/ I'm sure that that's only part of it. The roads are a wreck, the scumballs living there are too cheap to pay any taxes.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345296131000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345297972000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney/Ryan not perfect, just light years ahead of Obama</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297686000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:48:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A white collar criminal tax evader and a grandstanding welfare recipient who blames Obama for the failures of the Bush administration he played ballwasher for. Hawfreak has a real mancrush on these two. Perhaps if he gives them the "millions" he and his golferbogie alias made from their "successful construction business" he van get a few minutes in a "quiet room" with them.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345297972000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345298031000-16</Id><Topic><Title>W. Mitt Romney paid ZERO Federal income and capital gains taxes</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345288977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yur right, WMR cannot show his taxes now because it would very likely prove him a liar, one more time. Ann was so entitled and outraged about the taxes, like a "typical rich person" having it their way too much, it was throw up time. Whad'ya do with 20-40 million income per year? Is it too much to ask to not hire a bevy of tax attorneys to make sure you've gamed the govt to the max, offshore, swiss acts etc? 13% claim, even that was stupid to say. Show the cancelled check paid to the IRS.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345298031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345298063000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Guess What I saw?</Title><Username>ebentxw773</Username><Timestamp>1345295024000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:03:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1345298063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345298406000-18</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who made sure that the "haves and have mores" didn't have to shoulder any financial burden for his jolly little Iraq adventure or the neglected "hunt for bin Laden" that he gave up on after Rumsfeld let his former asset find sanctuary with his other asset Musharraf. Who made sure that Randian nutcase Greenspan was kept on to blow an even bigger asset inflation bubble to paper over the rip-off of the middle class he undertook to fill the coffers of flim-flam men like Romney and worse. It was poor black people who caused the third wave of the Clinton recession at the end of the Bush 43 reign of error, take it from Hawfreak, he's a "financial wizard" with all the "facts" that Rush Limbaugh and the Fox News bobleheads feed him.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345298406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345298734000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Special Ops troups speak out against the President</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345265232000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A rwnj offshoot group who were thoroughly debunked and made fools of on TV yesterday. The President was shown first off saying thank you thank you thank you to them. He must have thanked them a hundered times since then, and even thanked GWWB at the picture ceremony. What a guy. His grievous credit taking mistake was to say I ordered the attack. Of course that's what he did. He said absolutely nothing, except to a rwnj, that would lead one to believe he was taking credit. The RWNJ's jusrt can't stand the fact he was a success. Never have I seen a more humble, less credit taking guy.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345298734000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345298984000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Special Ops troups speak out against the President</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345265232000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some message board bigot who can't spell is talking about trust? Good luck with that, jamook.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345298984000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345299702000-21</Id><Title>Today on "Substantive Issues":</Title><Msg>Paul Ryan discusses noodling for catfish while on one of his 180 day a year absences from congress. Tomorrow: Cheese, is it good to have "running in your veins"? with Paul Ryan. In the archives: Yesterday's show discussing with Paul Ryan Obama's responsibility for the Janesville plant shutdown that occurred during the Bush administration. Thursday's show with Paul Ryan discussing how he was forced, Chicago thug style, to mooch stimulus funds for pet projects in his district. Wedensday's show on how to stretch your trust fund dollar by not reporting income on your 2011 tax returns with Paul Ryan, financial adviser to the stars.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345299702000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345300017000-22</Id><Title>Windows Ph 8 features and specs</Title><Msg>Windows Phone 8 is what Windows Phone 7 should have been from the get go: a fully feature modern OS without any restriction. This is now the case thanks to the new shared core with it’ desktop/tablet big brother Windows 8. The fact that WP8 will run on the same NT Kernel Windows 8 isn’t really a surprise if you have been following me given that I had uncovered some subtle hints quite a while ago and even shared my concern that if this was going to be the case then current WP7 handsets probably won’t have the HW guts to run the future OS. http://www.mobiletechworld.com/2012/06/20/windows-phone-8-unveiled-features-and-specs/</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345300017000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:26:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345300374000-23</Id><Title>Windows Ph 8 time to make the switch to WP-8</Title><Msg>http://www.inc.com/christina-desmarais/microsoft-windows-8-phone-should-you-make-the-switch.html</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345300374000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301062000-24</Id><Topic><Title>W. Mitt Romney paid ZERO Federal income and capital gains taxes</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345288977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did he do any work for it or was it like his BYU BS in English, a privilege that sons of rich Mormon Governors and foreign born candidates for the Presidency deserve? What about Paul Ryans "academic credentials", such as they are? Does a Batchelor's degree with a minor in Economics from a state University make for a plausible budget director? Is that why he estimates that revenues of 16% of GDP will provide for expenditures of 20% of GDP? http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/08/14/fact-check-ryan-budget-plan-doesnt-actually-slash-budget/ "Fact Check: Ryan budget plan doesn't actually slash the budget Under the latest Ryan plan, the budget would grow from $3.6 trillion this year to $4.9 trillion in 2022. .... While claims that Ryan is slashing the budget are questionable, there are studies to back up claims that the Republicans' tax plans benefit the wealthy more than others." &lt;terrorist_fist_bump&gt; FOX News, soshulists, totally in the tank for the Moozlim Kenyan usurper! &lt;/terrorist_fist_bump&gt;</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345301062000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301173000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Ph 8 time to make the switch to WP-8</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345300374000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On Monday Microsoft announced the Microsoft Surface, its latest foray into the tablet hardware market. Now the software giant has unveiled Windows Phone 8, the new version of its smartphone operating system. The new OS looks impressive on several levels: •It borrows much of its code base from Windows 8. •WP8, which will support multi-core chipsets, a range of screen resolutions and removable MicroSD, also includes better support for native near-field communication (NFC) between phones, laptops, tablets, and PCs, meaning we could soon see more usable applications for NFC and a real mobile wallet. •WP8 will get Internet Explorer 10, complete with malware blocking, from Windows 8. IE10 provides significantly faster JavaScript performance and full HTML5 support. •Nokia's turn-by-turn navigation and offline maps is built into WP8, which means all phones running the OS, not just Nokia Lumia handsets, will have access to these very popular features. •Microsoft also talked about its renewed focus on its business users. The updated OS, which includes Office apps, will support BitLocker encryption, a secure boot mode, and deployment of Line-of-Business apps such as point-of-sale apps, product catalogs, dashboards, in-field or sales apps, workflow management apps, and monitoring and response apps. Admins will like features that let them manage WP8 devices using the same tools they use to manage the desktop, as well as the ability they'll have to set up apps for users without having to go through the Marketplace. Is Windows Phone on Your Radar? While BlackBerry used to be the smartphone of choice for business users, it's no secret that its maker, Research in Motion, has been in trouble for a while. In fact, a recent Nielson report indicates that the BlackBerry has only a 6% market share among recent smartphone buyers. But what about Windows Phone? Are the phones that run it even on your radar? If not, maybe they should be. The UI is Great for Business Users I recently tested the 4G Nokia Lumia 900 (running Windows Phone 7.5 Mango) and in many ways preferred it to my Samsung Galaxy Nexus running Android 4.0. While the Lumia 900 and other current Windows Phones won't be able to upgrade to Windows 8, the Metro user interface it employs remains at the core of WP8. So if you haven't played around with Metro, there are a couple things you should know. Unlike the iPhone and Android phones which show you screens and screens of small app icons, the Metro UI in Windows Phone features bright and colorful "live" tiles that morph as your phone is synced with real time information. You can also organize your contacts into Groups so you can email, text, or chat with a whole group at once. By pinning a group to the home screen, you'll see missed calls, new messages, and social networking updates from members of the group anytime you launch your phone. You can also pin documents and spreadsheets to your start screen so as to easily view and edit them. For instance, while at a conference you could pin the event itinerary so as to quickly see what's coming up next or where you need to go. That's true, but Microsoft is working hard to get developers more invested in coding for the platform. In fact, the company gives developers free phones and promises to prominently locate them in its app store and advertising</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345301173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345301285000-26</Id><Title>Arab Spring run amok: 'Brotherhood' starts crucifixions</Title><Msg>Where's the human rights zealots and obama????</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301322000-27</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to the Hawfreak brigade, it most certainly was. And ACORN! Don't forget about ACORN! And he's got some bogus chopped-up hash from a fellow wingnut to link to! Isn't that so important. (probably not a good idea to click on his link to the Ogrish spin-off)</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345301322000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301335000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Arab Spring run amok: 'Brotherhood' starts crucifixions</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LINK: http://www.wnd.com/2012/08/arab-spring-run-amok-brotherhood-starts-crucifixions/</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301335000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301845000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Arab Spring run amok: 'Brotherhood' starts crucifixions</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wingnut Daily, it must be all true. Any hot news about Hillary's run for the presidency as a stealth Green party candidate? Will she "tap" Janet Napolitanto as her mate? Running mate I mean. That's what Jerry Corsi told me when we had lunch at the Felafel wagon in Central Square. He paid in Ameros.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345301845000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301994000-30</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no idea who this "bogie" individual you're referring to might be. Perhaps you'd rather watch some Saddam hanging shock video.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345301994000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345302614000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Arab Spring run amok: 'Brotherhood' starts crucifixions</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THIS IS REAL TERROR!!!!</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1345302614000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345305102000-32</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're just a bankrupt wingnut posting crap sixteen to twenty hours a day now that it's campaign season. You'll be back down to your usual twelve to sixteen hour stints after the silly season has run its course. All of that will be irrelevant garbage too. Perhaps you should take advantage of Romneycare to spend some time with a mental health clinician, your mood swings are becoming more and more troubling lately.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345305102000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345307810000-33</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: update</Title><Username>rhodyssj460</Username><Timestamp>1345302862000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:14:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From a boiler room trying to influence the market</Msg><Username>thekindaguyiyam</Username><Timestamp>1345307810000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345308215000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan is a Follower and Talks about Milking Cows.</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1345306043000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:07:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Craper starting a conversation about someone talking about milking cows shows what a dim bulb she is. Sooooooo stupid. How about a real adult, meaningful, subject for a change?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345308215000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345308279000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcraper, did the debt go up $5.35T on</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345308230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Craper, are you satisfied with the "hope and change"?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345308279000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345308504000-36</Id><Topic><Title>What's the fixtion with Ryan, Romney will be President</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345306262000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:11:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The talk is Biden may have early dementia. After all he didn't even know what state he was end the other day.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345308504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345309851000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcraper, did the debt go up $5.35T on</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345308230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Craper, you do realize, hawc or I would have had to post two messages and change our computer ID in 60 seconds. Let's see you do that.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345309851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345309985000-38</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barack Obama served as the Illinois executive director of the ACORN partner Project Vote in 1992. His campaign paid more than $800,000 to an ACORN organization to help "get out the vote" in his successful primary campaign against then-Sen. Hillary Clinton in 2008. In November 2007, then-Senator Obama addressed ACORN and thanked the organization for its work: "I’ve been fighting alongside ACORN on issues you care about my entire career. "Even before I was an elected official, when I ran Project Vote voter registration drives in Illinois, ACORN was smack dab in the middle of it, and we appreciate your work."</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345309985000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345310488000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Arab Spring run amok: 'Brotherhood' starts crucifixions</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, dumbingovernment, you don't believe the Mus brotherhoods has taken over in Egypt and people are being murdered in Syria and because there haven't been any bodies of soliers shown coming back on MSNBC, you don't think any of that is happening.? I guess it is all right to not know wtf is going on but maybe you shouldn't be showing your stupidity by making uninformed remarks on a public message board.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345310488000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345311089000-40</Id><Topic><Title>W. Mitt Romney paid ZERO Federal income and capital gains taxes</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345288977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yu work, yu make $100, pay tax on it, yu then put it in a cd, yu get taxed on the interest. yu pay tax on the money twice? No, false, yu get taxed on income. If romney wants to be pres, he needs to adapt his entitled thinking to the real world, which he is out of touch with.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345311089000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:31:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345311388000-41</Id><Topic><Title>W. Mitt Romney paid ZERO Federal income and capital gains taxes</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345288977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HO hum. Once again. We don't care about Romney's taxes, we who work care about our taxes. When was the last time or ever did you pay fed income taxes, dead beat? I bet never....dead beat....</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345311388000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345311838000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Arab Spring run amok: 'Brotherhood' starts crucifixions</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are asking everyone to say a prayer for "Darkhorse" 3rd Battalion 5th Marines and their families. They are fighting it out in Afghanistan &amp; they have lost 12 marines in 4 days. IT WOULD BE NICE TO SEE the message spread if more people could pass it on. Nothing has been in the media about these guys because no one seems to care. They are: Justin Allen, 23 Brett Linley, 29 Matthew Weikert, 29 Justus Bartett, 27 Dave Santos, 21 Chase Stanley, 21 Jesse Reed, 26 Matthew Johnson, 21 Zachary Fisher, 24 Brandon King, 23 Christopher Goeke 23 Sheldon Tate, 27 All are Marines that gave their lives for YOU this week. &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; Dumbingovernment. Did you know this? Did you see their caskets on MSNBC or CNN?? You hypocrite</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345311838000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345312590000-43</Id><Title>The Romney plan:</Title><Msg>Make people who don't have any money pay for everything. Mitt and his country club buddies get more stuff.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345312590000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:56:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345312590000-44</Id><Topic><Title>2011 Bust or Bargain</Title><Username>justine_emmanuel53</Username><Timestamp>1345306749000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:19:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am glad I am in the right stocks.</Msg><Username>sophia_isaiah45</Username><Timestamp>1345312590000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:56:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345312646000-45</Id><Title>Daddy,</Title><Msg>why does Grandma have to go without her medicine so that Mitt Romney can have a tax break?</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345312646000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:57:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345312799000-46</Id><Title>Mommy,</Title><Msg>why are the Republicans so mad at the President for killing that nasty Mr. bin Laden?</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345312799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345312910000-47</Id><Topic><Title>Mommy,</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345312799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:59:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seals to Obama "You didn't do that".</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345312910000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:01:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345314345000-48</Id><Topic><Title>Guess What I saw?</Title><Username>ebentxw773</Username><Timestamp>1345295024000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:03:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>brilliant analysis</Msg><Username>diannwfa254</Username><Timestamp>1345314345000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345314487000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Mommy,</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345312799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:59:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama to rwnj Seals faction: "I told you already you did the deed,I gave the orders, do you need to be told again?"</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345314487000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345315069000-50</Id><Topic><Title>Mommy,</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345312799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:59:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who didn't do that. Perhaps when they figure out whether bin Laden is dead or not (maybe someone "in the know" could leak that information to them) they can get back to us. http://www.cnn.com/2012/08/17/opinion/bergen-obama-swift-boat/index.html The opinions of the producers of the propaganda film are noted, but they haven't any reason or need to know anything.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345315069000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:37:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345315276000-51</Id><Title>Daddy,</Title><Msg>after I've profited from bankrupting a company and stolen it's pension fund so that its employees are left without health care benefits they were owed, can I evade responsibility by "retroactively retiring" like Mitt Romney did?</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345315276000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345316134000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Hawcraper, did the debt go up $5.35T on</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345308230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>while you neglected your "construction business" to spend sixteen hours every day posting the garbage you copy from wingnut puke funnels here? Weren't there ongoing obligations that led to your bankruptcy as you became totally obsessed with "sharing your financial insights" and"rebutting the multi-nymed European soshulistic hydra"? Gee, how does that kind of thing happen.... Are you suggesting we all follow your example and hole up in some tin shack in the swamp posting lies about how our downfall was caused by poor black people instead of idiotic warmongering spendthrift Republican douchenozzles? That's an interesting perscription for the country's ills. Perhaps the chiggers are carrying some kind of brain rotting disease.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345316134000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345316265000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Arab Spring run amok: 'Brotherhood' starts crucifixions</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Horrible situation but it's election time and Obama is not going to do anything. He's going to protect his election chances no matter how many lives it costs</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1345316265000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345316844000-54</Id><Topic><Title>Arab Spring run amok: 'Brotherhood' starts crucifixions</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like Obama miscalculated big time!</Msg><Username>cable_monkey</Username><Timestamp>1345316844000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345316961000-55</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even the Fox News chumpmaster Murdoch supports that analysis! ___________________________________ January 9, 2009, 12:04 PM ET. Bush On Jobs: The Worst Track Record On Record. By WSJ Staff President George W. Bush entered office in 2001 just as a recession was starting, and is preparing to leave in the middle of a long one. That’s almost 22 months of recession during his 96 months in office. His job-creation record won’t look much better. The Bush administration created about three million jobs (net) over its eight years, a fraction of the 23 million jobs created under President Bill Clinton‘s administration and only slightly better than President George H.W. Bush did in his four years in office. Here’s a look at job creation under each president since the Labor Department started keeping payroll records in 1939. The counts are based on total payrolls between the start of the month the president took office (using the final payroll count for the end of the prior December) and his final December in office. Because the size of the economy and labor force varies, we also calculate in percentage terms how much the total payroll count expanded under each president. The current President Bush, once taking account how long he’s been in office, shows the worst track record for job creation since the government began keeping records. –Sudeep Reddy ________________________________________ Letting the Chapter 11 cokehead Bush steal the 2000 election was a $10 Trillion step backwards for this country.</Msg><Username>luckypaws20</Username><Timestamp>1345316961000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345317235000-56</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sure can? ************************************ ...if you own something, you have a vital stake in the future of our country. The more ownership there is in America, the more vitality there is in America, and the more people have a vital stake in the future of this country. - President George W. Bush, June 17, 2004 We're creating... an ownership society in this country, where more Americans than ever will be able to open up their door where they live and say, welcome to my house, welcome to my piece of property. - President George W. Bush, October 2004 ************************************** (Insofar as crack-dealing slimeball Reagan did the exact same thing to commercial real estate 20 years earlier?) Running two bad faith wars for oil off the books, Enron-style? That sleazy stunt sure didn't help either?</Msg><Username>luckypaws20</Username><Timestamp>1345317235000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345317843000-57</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah. THAT'S the ticket...... "On February 14, a Florida Appeals court ruled there is absolutely nothing illegal about lying, concealing or distorting information by a major press organization. The court reversed the $425,000 jury verdict in favor of journalist Jane Akre who charged she was pressured by Fox Television management and lawyers to air what she knew and documented to be false information. The ruling basically declares it is technically not against any law, rule, or regulation to deliberately lie or distort the news on a television broadcast." Here in the REAL world by the time the drunk-driving coward Bush even KNEW that there was a housing crash, he had already handed the Treasury over to the Goldman Sachs dirtbag. He honestly thought that his own incredibly limp 2007 Stimulus would push the country back from the brink.</Msg><Username>paidtopump2001</Username><Timestamp>1345317843000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345318602000-58</Id><Title>Mommy,</Title><Msg>why does Mr. Ryan have to hide behind his mom when he's telling old people he'll take their children's Medicare away?</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345318602000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:36:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345319584000-59</Id><Topic><Title>Bush tried to stop wholesale lending to unqualified</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345318484000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:34:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Under the plan, disclosed at a Congressional hearing today, a new agency would be created within the Treasury Department to assume supervision of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, the government-sponsored companies that are the two largest players in the mortgage lending industry. The new agency would have the authority, which now rests with Congress, to set one of the two capital-reserve requirements for the companies. It would exercise authority over any new lines of business. And it would determine whether the two are adequately managing the risks of their ballooning portfolios." The New York Times, 2003 "The truth is when President Bush took office, and the Republicans controlled both houses of Congress, he did not make any progress on comprehensive legislation to reform the regulation of the Government Sponsored Enterprises. It was not until 2005, when the House, on a bipartisan basis, and over the President's objections finally passed a reform bill. It died in the Senate in part because the White House's failure to make it a priority." -Barney Frank 2005 ********* Hawfreak's POLITICAL posturing aside (along with his nonsensical Bush-worship): "This Article posits a new explanation for the housing bubble. First, it demonstrates that the bubble was a supply-side phenomenon attributable to an excess of mispriced mortgage finance: mortgage-finance spreads declined and volume increased, even as risk increased — a confluence attributable only to an oversupply of mortgage finance. Second, it explains the mortgage-finance supply glut as resulting from the failure of markets to price risk correctly due to the complexity, opacity, and heterogeneity of the unregulated private-label mortgage-backed securities (PLS) that began to dominate the market in 2004. The rise of PLS exacerbated informational asymmetries between the financial institutions that intermediate mortgage finance and PLS investors. These intermediation agents exploited informational asymmetries to encourage overinvestment in PLS that boosted the financial intermediaries’ volume-based profits and enabled borrowers to bid up housing prices." http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=1669401 So the banksters stole the money, wasted it and when it all went wrong wanted us to bail them out. Hawfreak, as a self-interested part-time "successful construction businessman" and part-time swampland salesman uses his primary occupation (posting endlessly on backwater financial message boards) to promote the POLITICAL campaigns of swindlers who he thinks will blow another nice big bubble (what he calls the "boom-boom" years) that he can syphon some money out of before it all goes bust again.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345319584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345320367000-60</Id><Topic><Title>Arab Spring run amok: 'Brotherhood' starts crucifixions</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep!!</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1345320367000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345320674000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Bush tried to stop wholesale lending to unqualified</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345318484000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:34:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>floated by his corrupt bankster "have more" buddies to inflate the housing bubble. http://www.fhfa.gov/webfiles/2708/FHFA_Director%27s_Testimony_Final.pdf **** As of March 31, 2009, seriously delinquent loans accounted for 2.3% of single-family mortgages owned or guaranteed for Freddie Mac and 3.2% for Fannie Mae. While those are historically high levels, they compare favorably to industry averages of 4.7% for all prime loans, 7.2% for all single-family mortgages, 24.9% for all subprime mortgages, and 36.5% for subprime adjustable rate mortgages The report provides background on the origins of PLS and the risk they present. PLS loans represent only 15% of mortgages but 50% of serious delinquencies. In contrast at year-end 2008, the loans the Enterprises held or guaranteed represented 56% of the U.S. single family mortgages outstanding, but only 20% of serious delinquencies. The credit quality of investments in PLS has proven to be much worse than the initial AAA credit ratings of those securities would have suggested. The ongoing uncertainty surrounding the true economic value of PLS will continue to raise safety and soundness concerns. The report notes the for-profit structure of the GSEs worked counter to prudent risk management as competition reduced both marketshare and profits, thus eroding the GSEs credit requirements. To maintain profitability, each Enterprise increased purchases of PLS backed by alternative mortgages and of high-risk whole loans. And while many had criticized the OFHEO and sought to replace it: Purchases of PLS ultimately proved disastrous for the Enterprises. Credit and market-value losses would have been even larger had the Office of Federal Housing Enterprise Oversight (OFHEO), one of FHFA’s predecessor agencies, not increased the Enterprises’ capital requirement by 30% and capped their asset portfolios because of accounting and control problems. ****** http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Federal_takeover_of_Fannie_Mae_and_Freddie_Mac</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345320674000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345320955000-62</Id><Topic><Title>Mommy,</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345312799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:59:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You knew the worthless cokehead coward Bush backed off TWICE when we had Bin Laden in our sights? Not just Tora Bora? (Some say that Bush's Saudi Masters had told him "hands off Osama" before sunset on 9/13/2001...naturally he obeyed! After all Bush had shafted two other members of the Bin Laden family when he folded his first stock con.) WASHINGTON — Before Sunday, the last time an American president thought he had Osama bin Laden in his sights was the late summer of 2007. Al Qaeda and Taliban commanders, terrorist volunteers and insurgent foot soldiers would be meeting in the Tora Bora region of Afghanistan, a stream of intelligence reports showed. And there were hints that Bin Laden himself might travel from his hiding place in Pakistan to rally militants training for large-scale suicide attacks in Europe or the United States. “We thought we had ‘No. 1’ on this side of the border,” said a senior American military officer involved in planning the operation. “It was the best intelligence we’d had on him in a long time.” The military set into motion one of the largest strike missions of its kind, with long-range bombers, attack helicopters, artillery and commandos all ready to pummel the rugged mountain valley along Afghanistan’s border with Pakistan, according to military officers and former government officials. But just as the half dozen B-2 Stealth bombers were halfway on the 3,000-mile flight to their target, commanders ordered them to return to their secret base in the Indian Ocean, because of doubts about the intelligence on Bin Laden and concerns about civilian casualties from the bombs.</Msg><Username>luckypaws20</Username><Timestamp>1345320955000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345323589000-63</Id><Topic><Title>Bush tried to stop wholesale lending to unqualified</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345318484000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:34:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in 2006. Throughout 2007 he was "adjusting" Fannie and Freddie's lending standards to ensure that they took on more subprime PLSs as it was becoming clear that the bubble was inflating a to dangerous proportions: http://www.nytimes.com/2008/10/05/business/05fannie.html?pagewanted=3&amp;_r=3&amp;sq=mozilo In the end, Bawney Fwank's trust in Fannie and Freddie will probably pay off quite a bit better than Hawfreak's trust in Bushonomics. The "free market" resulted in the AIG bailout at 180 billion and counting. The "socialistic" GSEs are a much better bet.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345323589000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:59:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345325177000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Arab Spring run amok: 'Brotherhood' starts crucifixions</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345301285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:48:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad but true!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345325177000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345334383000-65</Id><Topic><Title>W. Mitt Romney paid ZERO Federal income and capital gains taxes</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345288977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney can reiterate that he has fully complied with the law, including the payment of all taxes he owed. Would his critics prefer he pay more than his legal obligation?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345334383000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345338461000-66</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Loves him some Karl Rove. http://online.wsj.com/article/SB123137220550562585.html Unfortunately for KKKarl's history rewrite, James B Lockheart was Bush's point man in B.S.ing Congress about the ability to launder all the bad paper the private mortgage bankers were flooding the market with. www.fhfa.gov/webfiles/1417/12606SMConf.pdf www.fhfa.gov/webfiles/1421/NEC92806.pdf February 27, 2008 "OFHEO will remove the portfolio growth caps for both companies on March 1, 2008.” And he made the GSEs a dumping ground for the junk that was issued by private mortgage lenders. online.wsj.com/public/resources/documents/fannietimeline0506.pdf All in an attempt to cover up the "free market paradise" created by the Bush43 brain trust. Now all the Bushies have are Rovian op-eds that only serve to highlight that the Republiscums are trying to pin the blame for their screw-ups on anyone and everyone else.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345338461000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345342556000-67</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: update</Title><Username>rhodyssj460</Username><Timestamp>1345302862000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:14:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very good record</Msg><Username>biddieidu926</Username><Timestamp>1345342556000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345347538000-68</Id><Title>recommendation</Title><Msg>put romney in office I strongly recommend this</Msg><Username>kureisema</Username><Timestamp>1345347538000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 23:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>