<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345350601000-1</Id><Title>Surface Tablet</Title><Msg>Any word on pricing for the Surface Tablet? I can buy an iPad 2 for $399 and Apple's new Mini iPad will cost around $299. If the Surface Tablet costs more than $400 it won't be competitive. http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-08-17/apple-rises-to-intraday-record-on-ipad-mini-research-note.html?cmpid=yhoo Here is why Windows 8 Tablets will fail. First of all, the 'Metro' graphical interface sucks. Second, how many apps are available for Windows 8 RT? iPad has millions of apps in comparison. Third, a growing number of people think Windows 8 will be the next Vista Fiasco. And last but not least, pricing. Windows Tablets will be overpriced, just like Zune.</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345350601000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:30:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345351101000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Alert! Actual Stock Message Here!</Title><Username>gijason21</Username><Timestamp>1345328748000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows XP was one of Microsoft's most successful products ever, and Microsoft stopped supporting it. Why? Because they're greedy bass turds. Instead, they tried to force Vista on the world. The Vista Fiasco caused many users to switch to alternatives like Mac, iPhone, Android and Linux. That's why I'm using a Dell Ubuntu Linux Laptop right now instead of a Vista machine. As of July, Windows Vista has only 3.4% market share while Mac OSX has more than double that. http://www.w3schools.com/browsers/browsers_os.asp Will Windows 8 be another Vista? You bet your @$$!!!</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345351101000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:38:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345352072000-3</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Linux Rules! Not as bloated at Windows. Linux is faster and more efficient than Windows. It uses less disk space and memory. Linux does not require hardware upgredes. Unlike Vista or Windows 8, Linux offers you a choice of graphical interfaces. Thousands of FREE apps. Linux is FREE and you get FREE upgrades too! Make the switch to Linux today. I recommend Linux Mint. http://www.linuxmint.com/</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345352072000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:54:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345352253000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and paying money, in this case taxes</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345344776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and Unemployment are why the federal government are short on cash. Unemployed people don't pay taxes. Where is Obama's Change? Only 3 months til the election and Unemployment is still over 8%. I'm voting for Change again this November, but this time it won't be Obama!</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345352253000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345352323000-5</Id><Title>Hope and Change</Title><Msg>I hope we change Presidents this November. Obama lost my vote!</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345352323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345352936000-6</Id><Title>Global Warming</Title><Msg>The NOAA has located 2 causes of Global Warming caused by man made sources of hot air. The first one is located near Redmond Washington, caused by speculation about Microsoft's new Surface Tablet. Lots of hot air in Redmond, but no product or sales numbers to back it up. The second cause of Global Warming is located in Charlotte NC, near the Democratic National Convention. Both sources of man made Global Warming are expected to increase over the next month.</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345352936000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 01:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345353019000-7</Id><Topic><Title>W. Mitt Romney paid ZERO Federal income and capital gains taxes</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345288977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 07:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unemployed people don't pay taxes either. Unemployment is still over 8% after 3 years of Obama's "Hope and Change".</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345353019000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 01:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345353307000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Market Fear index hits 5 year low</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345317838000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:23:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about Microsoft investor fear? What will happen when Microsoft stops supporting Windows 7 and XP, then forces Windows 8 and Metro on the world? It will be even worse than the Vista Fiasco of 2009. Windows 8 will crash and burn, just like the Hindenberg in 1937. Oh, the Humanity! http://www.fiascoawards.com/continguts/general/fitxa.php?id=13</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345353307000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 01:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345353710000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Tablet</Title><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345350601000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:30:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iPad is a piece of junk. What does it do? Movies and browsing? oh I forgot email. Big deal. Surface Pro is better. Forget RT. But wait no one has really tried out the the suface products. So lets wait till they come out. If the jaded iPad interface and it's useless bunch of Apps wins the day then we are no better off then before we had the iPad. The iPad is not light weight. Sorry but it's heavy and needs a stand. So reading on the couch is uncomfortable after the first 5 minutes. it does not work. Using MS Surface Pro is going to be cool when it's a productivity tool.</Msg><Username>barrylam2000</Username><Timestamp>1345353710000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 01:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345357672000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Tablet</Title><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345350601000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:30:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mini =/= Surface which is larger. iPad 2 is also out dated.</Msg><Username>kabraxisx64</Username><Timestamp>1345357672000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 02:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345370531000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and paying money, in this case taxes</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345344776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a liar who stole their livelihoods from honest citizens and hid it from lawful taxation, or the person who brought the country back from the economic catastrophe caused by warmongering, torturing, lying, jingoistic false "patriots"? "Corporate America" is a B.S. construct of nasty, greedy, stupid little slime like you. We're the People of the United States, not some quasi-person that in this devolved state of society serves only the purpose of carrying out economic crimes that no reasonable individual would be insane enough to expect to get away with.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345370531000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 06:02:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345371392000-12</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Squeal like a little piggie, crap in your adult diaper kind of on target, isn't it you Bush worshipping little scumsucker.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345371392000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 06:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345373631000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and paying money, in this case taxes</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345344776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba is going to jail soon.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345373631000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 06:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345373704000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Hope and Change</Title><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345352323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you would have to be an commie idiot to vote for this 2 bit clown commie.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345373704000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 06:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345373842000-15</Id><Topic><Title>The biggest Obama lie is Romney is a felon and murderer</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345316968000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:09:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba going to jail after election. Dem. voters will have to pay an extra 25% tax for being stupid.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345373842000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 06:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345373963000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Corzine goes free, he works for Obama and Holder once</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345316800000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take all of corzines assets away and give to the victims. Just cause he is a dumbocrap he can not legaly steal despite what nobumba tells him.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345373963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 06:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345374373000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Corzine goes free, he works for Obama and Holder once</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345316800000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;Take all of corzines assets away and give to the victims. Just cause he is a dumbocrap he can not legaly steal despite what nobumba tells him&gt;&gt; can I get you an appointment with the Bankruptcy judge - you two can work out the distribution of assets together</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345374373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:06:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345374477000-18</Id><Topic><Title>The biggest Obama lie is Romney is a felon and murderer</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345316968000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:09:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;nobumba going to jail after election. Dem. voters will have to pay an extra 25% tax for being stupid&gt;&gt; did you make that stuff you are drinking or did you buy it</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345374477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:07:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345375499000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming</Title><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345352936000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 01:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>largest source of MMGW is b2boomer who wont keep his polluting k-sucker closed long enough for any dissapation of the hot air</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345375499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345377215000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and paying money, in this case taxes</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345344776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you swamp dwelling bankrupt liar with a Bush fetish and a broken crystal ball.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345377215000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345380607000-21</Id><Title>Going Higher!</Title><Msg>Amazing !!! I am extremely pleased to have become a member of this service earlier this year (2012)! We are up over 36%, and my retirement savings have never looked better. I was thrilled with the nimble movement they made when they had us go to cash in the morning and then back to long in the afternoon just ahead of the big market move on the following Monday. That was brilliant! I also appreciate there comments they made about pullbacks which helped me to not panic and to be patient when my position in these stocks temporarily loses money. I suggest you check this out, there daily video is FREE! WWW.EXPERT-ANALYST.INFO</Msg><Username>phyllishenry6488</Username><Timestamp>1345380607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 08:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345381609000-22</Id><Topic><Title>The biggest Obama lie is Romney is a felon and murderer</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345316968000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 15:09:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STFU commie POS traitor.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345381609000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 09:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345386175000-23</Id><Title>Mitt made tremendous sacrifices...</Title><Msg>for his career in public service. "You people" couldn't possibly appreciate how expensive it is to replace the staff of multiple estates with documented workers. Of course he was going to siphon off a few million tax dollars into his own pockets. $360,000 boat houses aren't free, my friends. You should be thankful for the benefit of his job destroying expertise.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345386175000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345388111000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and paying money, in this case taxes</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345344776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that the reason Corzine got off scott free because he is a politician with connections? How come you are more concerned with Romney's legally filed taxes than Obama bundler who screwed clients out of millions?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345388111000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345388815000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt made tremendous sacrifices...</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345386175000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:22:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Careful, your class envy is showing. As far as jobs he destroyed, what is the difference in his using private money and taking a company that is losing money and laying people off and obama taking taxpayer money and throwing it into GM and laying off a lot of non union people? Explain please.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345388815000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345394610000-26</Id><Title>CLINTON TO REPLACE BIDEN?</Title><Msg>Ed Klein has previously discovered that Chelsea Clinton was conceived via Bill Clinton's rape of Hillary Clinton and that Hillary is a secret lesbian, so on all things Clinton, he is the go-to guy for groundbreaking scoops. Today he has another one about the Rumor That Will Never Die, a.k.a. the Great Switcheroo, in which Joe Biden is locked in the White House basement and replaced by Hillary Clinton on President Obama's reelection ticket. Everyone else is in the political-media world is just speculating, but Klein? Klein is reporting: "As recently as a couple of weeks ago, the White House was putting out feelers to see if Hillary Clinton was interested in replacing Joe Biden on the ticket," Klein told Secrets. "Bill Clinton, I'm told, was urging his wife to accept the number two spot if it was formally offered. Bill sees the vice presidency as the perfect launching pad for Hillary to run for president in 2016." ... Klein, whose book is No. 2 on the NYT bestseller list, quoted unnamed sources who revealed that top Obama aide Valerie Jarrett put the vice presidency on the table during a lunch with the secretary of state. "The lunch was ostensibly about policy issues, but the subject of the vice presidency came up," he said. "Hillary told Valerie Jarrett that she was not interested in running as Obama's vice president." http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2012/05/22/michael-tomasky-on-obama-s-hillary-clinton-joe-biden-switcheroo.html</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345394610000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345396237000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and paying money, in this case taxes</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345344776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should choose the guy that is directly lining YOUR pockets. That is what the game has evolved into, as you have pointed out. Money is no longer passed under the table, the fraud and outright stealling goes on right under our noses as we debate philosophical differences that neither party cares about. The politicos have done the math and realize that at 16 TRILLION, the ponzi scheme is about to dry up. Mathematically, there is now way to recover, even if they could rig inflation back to it's highest levels, there isn't enough time to absorb the spread. So what is left? Ask greece. They are the model for what is about to happen. They have kept the rest of europe in the game because their is still enough money to be stolen from the average municipalities bond fund. So what is next? - Not sure of the exact order,but watch for China to hit the wall HARD. Italy and Spain to call it quits and Germany to cut the rest of europe off. The next seperation of you and your money will be when gold plummets as China and india start dumping their reserves to get their hamds on anything that is liquid. I know you all were told that gold will skyrocket - it did,in case you haven't been paying attention. JUST LIKE THE HOUSING MARKET. Now the government owns your car companies, your banks, and your house. What do you call it when the government controls the means of production? The only difference is the full faith and trust of the US government doesn't mean anything anymore and your future value has been auctioned off to the likes of John Corzine and the rest of your insider tradin congress thugs. They have all shown up at the masqurade party, and the american voters debate who has the cutest costume as these guys loot your house of.its last piece of silverware. The question is, will you be getting your envelope at the end of the party? Maybe,but it will probably have a postage due stamp attached.</Msg><Username>dorianpc</Username><Timestamp>1345396237000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 13:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345398292000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt made tremendous sacrifices...</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345386175000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:22:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You think that Mitt is a different "class" of person and that he should be "envied" because of his ability to defraud people of money. You're also dripping with Union worker envy. Explain it to yourself, tool.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345398292000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 13:44:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345398340000-29</Id><Title>harry dokes</Title><Msg>reminds me of the uncle to the boy who chooses winning picks at the racetrack. The film about the boy and the rocking horse. The uncle, or whoever he is, sees value in the boy's abilities.</Msg><Username>neutered_bloodhound</Username><Timestamp>1345398340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 13:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345400038000-30</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON TO REPLACE BIDEN?</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345394610000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:43:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTERESTING!</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1345400038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345403494000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming</Title><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345352936000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 01:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet you didn't type that on a Nokia Lumina phone or a Windows Tablet.</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345403494000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345403672000-32</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from Obama: "Bush caused this problem"</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345297302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seriously, do you think either Obama or Romney give a crap about YOU? They both have their agendas to make special interest groups happy. Guess what? You aren't special.</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345403672000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345403819000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Tablet</Title><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345350601000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:30:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface Pro? Sounds like it will cost over $500. No Thanks!</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345403819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345403864000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Going Higher!</Title><Username>phyllishenry6488</Username><Timestamp>1345380607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 08:50:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I want some of what this guy is smokin!</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345403864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345404379000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt made tremendous sacrifices...</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345386175000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:22:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are all obsessed with money, even though it's easy for moronic wastes of skin like Mitt Romney to steal however much of the stuff they want. They all think that there are "classes" of people, those undeserving of the riches they've gotten in life just as deserving of their fanboy envy as those who deserve what they have and more (even if it's vastly less than Mitt Romney has accumulated through his leveraged buyout mismanagement schemes). They don't particularly care that as Governor of the state of Massachusetts, Mitt retained interests in a number of corporations that he directed our tax money into to the tune of millions of dollars. They think that's "classy" and envy Mitt his ability to steal money, just like they would if they had the chance.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345404379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345405261000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt made tremendous sacrifices...</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345386175000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:22:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, because I am obsessed with money, I don't have to depend on the government for anything. You liberals on the other hand, are obsessed with my money too. That you can't get your hand on the 50% that is left just drives your class envy. And just wtf does "moronic wastes of skin" mean? You are so filled with envy, you don't even make sense.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345405261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345405801000-37</Id><Title>Heym when are you liberals going to hold the White House accountable</Title><Msg>for the leaking of all those state secrets.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345405801000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345405979000-38</Id><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Msg>They blame the credit crisis on one of their favorite punching bags, fannie and freddie. There are soooooo many things wrong with this. 1 No credible economists agree that fan and fred were primary. 2 Fan and fred were miniscule compared to the loans issued, and to believe that wall street believed they had a way out through selling to fan and fred is like believing exxon mobil could always sell its gas to fred down the street if the world market tanked. 3 The financial wizardry being employed on wall street to value the loans relied on mathematical modeling that worked well as long as nobody blinked, their thinking is well documented in numerous books. 4 There was an illusion in place that real estate never declined and the cost of risky loans would be covered by asset appreciation. 5 The credit problems extended far beyond housing. 6 Other countries suffering under the same illusions had credit crashes without a fan or fred rescue even possible. 7 Massive inflows of money from China and trade imbalances together with classic synchronized speculation is the primary cause. But it is easier to blab out the talking points and augment the feeling 'I'm inteligunt' than to actually think. Type one thinking again.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345406046000-39</Id><Title>Humongous Truism: Bush Fcuked Us But Good!</Title><Msg>On 9/11/2001, the Bush/Cheney Administration along with the Republican controlled Congress got caught flatfooted when Al Qaeda slipped it to them, killing thousands of Americans. To cover for their criminal negligence the Republican Party Boys started two unfunded, unpaid-for, wars on the credit card. The unfunded, unpaid-for,wars continue to create debt to this day. Then there were the Bush Tax cuts that threw gasoline on the deficit fire. To cap off their list of accomplishments the Republican Party Boys deregulated the banks and refused to enforce strict loan adminstration standards which created a bank failure, a housing collapse, and a global financial melt-down. Say "thank you" to the Republican Party Boys. Now we got the R &amp; R Republican Party Boy Replacemnt squad. God help this country if they get in.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345406046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345407403000-40</Id><Topic><Title>NBC losing money Jay Leno took a big cut in pay</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345401240000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:34:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, FAUX News and Rush Limpballs Radio, now that's more your speed. Oh yeah, we can add the Blaze and NewsMax as well to your information sources.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1345407403000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345408269000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt made tremendous sacrifices...</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345386175000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:22:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't have to depend on the government for anything" Not roads or schools or bridges or a Navy, Air Force or Army. Not clean water, clean air, safe food, a police force to keep others from stealing back what you stole from them, not a Fire Department to put out the piles of burning garbage because there's no more DPW since you decided your tax rate should be ZERO just like Mitt Romney's. If you want to see a moronic waste of skin look in the mirror, or at the poster of Mitt Romney you salivate over thinking he'll give you free money.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345408269000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345409339000-42</Id><Title>All Planned Parenthood Charges Dropped After Sebelius Document Shredding</Title><Msg>All of the charges against a Planned Parenthood abortion business have been dropped after one of the most politically biased cases pro-life groups say they can remember. The case was embroiled in controversy after it was found documents critical to it were destroyed during the administration of former Gov. Kathleen Sebelius. http://www.lifenews.com/2012/08/17/all-planned-parenthood-charges-dropped-after-sebelius-document-shredding/</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345409339000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:48:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345410473000-43</Id><Title>The current monetary system will start to collapse in 2013 .......</Title><Msg>Most of the developed countries, US, UK, and Europe have carried so much debtload that the continued positive response cycle between economic growth and asset appreciation become almost impossible. US has about $16 trillion sovereign debt right not but it has more than $50 trillion liabilities on entitlement programs. I will show you that it is only Bernanke's pipe-dream to expect 3-4% real GDP growth over the next decade: (1) Based on the official fiscal deficit project up to 2020, the total US debtload is expected to reach $19-20 trillion. Given a 3% average interest rate on the debt, the total annual interest expense would be about $600 billion. This figure can goes to $1 trillion, if the average interest rate reaches 5%, which is not an likely scenario. ( This means that Federal Reserve will not boost the growth to much, assuming they still can, since 5% interest rate would mean almost immediate insolvent for the entire fiscal system.) (2) The most likely case is that we could see zero to negative average GDP growth over the next decades, with interest rate hovering around 1-2%. Why? Because Firstly, the healthcare industry would likely shrink 20%-30% given the much-needed reform. Currently, the most younger workers are enrolled in private health insurance program so that private providers could reap billions of profit; but the elders are kicked into the MediCare program, funded by the Tax Payers. Remember, 70% of average person's total life-time health cost is typically incurred during the last year of his/her life, i.e. when he/she is in MediCare program, funded by all the tax payers. Such system is no longer sustainable. Secondly, the traditional energy sector would likely shrink 30-70% over the next decade if the world government decide to adopt new technologies which can generate electricity from the vibration of particle from our ambient environment. If you do not believe me, search for kapanadze on the Internet. Such technologies and knowledge are hidden from us by the Elite for hundreds of years. That is why you have not heard about a inventor called Nikola Tesla, who have created many of things our life depend on nowadays. I understand that some groups' financial interest will be badly hurt by the wide application of such technologies. But I wonder how long the embargo against humanity would last. When the embargo is finally lifted, you might find your investment in tradition energy sector lose 50% of value immediately. These developments will lead to zero or negative GDP growth in the first decade as the economy realign itself. Unfortunately, it means that the current PONZI global monetary system will be essentially insolvent and could no longer sustainable. I do not how things will work out, but it would be very painful for many. However, the human kinds need such massive "reset" to embark on the neo-wave of sustainable development and prosperity. All you can do is to make yourself be prepared for the impact, since there will be many unknown unknowns.</Msg><Username>sky_walker618</Username><Timestamp>1345410473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345414691000-44</Id><Topic><Title>CFury's repeated problem on this board</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345409423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:50:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[[The key question is: WOULD ANY OF THOSE LOANS HAVE EVEN EXISTED WITHOUT FREDDIE AND FANNIE MAKING A MARKET? Also NO!! Bankers held many loans because they were making money and they had a place to sell them if need be.]] You must not think wall street very smart if they kept buying and holding assets based on a buyer of last resort who could not possibly buy the assets. Nope, all the analysis of the credit crises is much closer to my post than your singular ridiculous talking point. I don't have a repeated problem as i don't repeat myself. YOU on the other hand say exactly the same thing over and over and over and over.... Always without any justification.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345414691000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345414806000-45</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's go find some economic papers or seriously credible analysis and report back with links, what do you say??? I guess anything not supporting your view will be 'soshulist' ????</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345414806000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345418417000-46</Id><Topic><Title>NBC losing money Jay Leno took a big cut in pay</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345401240000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:34:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be sure to see 2016.</Msg><Username>fajitawagon1</Username><Timestamp>1345418417000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:20:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345419696000-47</Id><Topic><Title>Economist confirms: Freddie and Fannie the "fuel" for financial crisis</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345417815000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the paper is a hack pile of crap. Calomiris is a Wall Street Journal favorite since he reliably poops out "scholarly research" that ignores fact and recorded history to spin a tale that the nasty federal government was entirely the cause of every bad credit instrument issued by the Mortgage and Private Banking "industries". He's also a prolific and reliable source of bilge for the Politico puke funnel and an AEI hack. And you wouldn't know a Brit from someone who would hang a Tory.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345419696000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345420802000-48</Id><Topic><Title>THe Obamanure Covention</Title><Username>obadidoss</Username><Timestamp>1345417078000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:57:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all the commie rat bast--- losers.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345420802000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345420852000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Humongous Truism: Bush Fcuked Us But Good!</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345406046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:54:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STFU commie rat traitor.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345420852000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:00:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345420998000-50</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON TO REPLACE BIDEN?</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1345394610000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:43:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whoa I didn't know that!</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1345420998000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345422033000-51</Id><Title>AKIN TO REPLACE RYAN?</Title><Msg>Rush Limbaugh, working with a recently formed Arpaio cold-case posse has discovered that Paul Ryan is the secret love child of Ayn Rand in an illicit three-way affair with Ron Paul and Alan Greenspan during the filming of The Fountainhead. Today, the confirmation of the longstanding rumor the great switcheroo, is nearly at hand. Paul Ryan will declare Democrat, becoming Obama's running mate while Todd Akin will team up with Romney to run a barrage of negative ads about how Ryan's birth couldn't have been caused by the "forcible" rape of Greenspan by Rand, since "natural secretions" would otherwise have prevented Greenspan from becoming pregnant (sparing him a rather painful labor, by all accounts). Meanwhile, Hillary will finally dump that old philanderer Bill and elope with Janet Napolitano and Joe Biden to become the first family of Lichtenstein after seizing the $1.23Billion in undisclosed assets Mitt Romney stashed there thinking it was safe from them infernal revenooers.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345422033000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345422408000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Humongous Truism: Bush Fcuked Us But Good!</Title><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345406046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:54:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On 9/11/2001, the Bush/Cheney Administration along with the Republican controlled Congress got caught flatfooted when Al Qaeda slipped it to them, killing thousands of Americans.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1345422408000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345423145000-53</Id><Title>Obama promised you women birth control</Title><Msg>Romney promised you jobs. You gave hope and change a chance. It's OK to fire someone when even he said if he didn't get it solved in his first term he should be held accountable. So nows your chance to do what he said.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345423145000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:39:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345423287000-54</Id><Topic><Title>AKIN TO REPLACE RYAN?</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345422033000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:20:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see you finally admit how really screwed up the Democratic/socialist party really is.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345423287000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345423706000-55</Id><Title>Why Obama has to go - Newsweek</Title><Msg>Why does Paul Ryan scare the president so much? Because Obama has broken his promises, and it’s clear that the GOP ticket’s path to prosperity is our only hope. I was a good loser four years ago. “In the grand scheme of history,” I wrote the day after Barack Obama’s election as president, “four decades is not an especially long time. Yet in that brief period America has gone from the assassination of Martin Luther King Jr. to the apotheosis of Barack Obama. You would not be human if you failed to acknowledge this as a cause for great rejoicing.” Despite having been—full disclosure—an adviser to John McCain, I acknowledged his opponent’s remarkable qualities: his soaring oratory, his cool, hard-to-ruffle temperament, and his near faultless campaign organization. Yet the question confronting the country nearly four years later is not who was the better candidate four years ago. It is whether the winner has delivered on his promises. And the sad truth is that he has not. Neal Ferguson</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345423706000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345423724000-56</Id><Topic><Title>Economist confirms: Freddie and Fannie the "fuel" for financial crisis</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345417815000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you'd read the paper, which I have, instead of quoting a Barron's hack quoting an AEI and Hoover institution hack you'd have a better chance of arguing that it's not an exquisitely polished turd pooped out by a prolific peddler of pabulum to the plebes for the promotion of the plutocracy. If you'd look at something other than my colourful and incisive prose you might be able to guess why I might know who Pablo's compadre was and the "Mass liberal gal" you've hallucinated in your swamp fever and diaper stench induced altered states wouldn't. And crap is crap, no matter what degree the Sunshine State Asylum for the Criminally Insane awarded your little voodoo man has or what sinecures he's obtained from the wingnut welfare rolls for his services.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345423724000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:48:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345424128000-57</Id><Topic><Title>AKIN TO REPLACE RYAN?</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345422033000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:20:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see you finally admit that you're a wackjob with at best a split personality and a sad inability to distinguish reality from the internet. Welcome to the twenty-first century, pilgrim.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345424128000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345424723000-58</Id><Topic><Title>AKIN TO REPLACE RYAN?</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345422033000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:20:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden said it was the 20th century. Which one of you is the idiot? You or the guy next in line to be president.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345424723000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345424972000-59</Id><Topic><Title>AKIN TO REPLACE RYAN?</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345422033000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:20:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read more: http://newsbusters.org/blogs/noel-sheppard/2012/08/19/peggy-noonan-if-biden-were-republican-meet-press-subject-would-be-how#ixzz242jXUrjc</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1345424972000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345426026000-60</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama has to go - Newsweek</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345423706000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:48:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the Afghani's are still killing foreign invaders...and this time it's US. Thanks Barak...good going.</Msg><Username>samsonp65</Username><Timestamp>1345426026000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:27:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345426155000-61</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone alone Bigger than all of MSFT</Title><Username>obadidoss</Username><Timestamp>1345419713000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hardware cost more than software!</Msg><Username>Don_Cornwell</Username><Timestamp>1345426155000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345426393000-62</Id><Topic><Title>I can't lose</Title><Username>laviniatmj289</Username><Timestamp>1345392199000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:03:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>brilliant analysis</Msg><Username>goraudyeq718</Username><Timestamp>1345426393000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345427147000-63</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone alone Bigger than all of MSFT</Title><Username>obadidoss</Username><Timestamp>1345419713000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why is MSFT making less money than the iPhone hardware?</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345427147000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345432750000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Obama promised you women birth control</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345423145000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:39:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney promised you jobs.&gt;&gt; in Romania for 50 cents/hr hey hes going to save us if we move to Bucharest</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345432750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345432855000-65</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone alone Bigger than all of MSFT</Title><Username>obadidoss</Username><Timestamp>1345419713000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamanure looks like that manure you have been taking is fcukin up your haid!!</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345432855000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345433585000-66</Id><Topic><Title>The largest lie from the right is the housing issue.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345405979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I brought down the world economies, not just the US economy with the most destructive puke Republican bagger economic policy the world has ever witnessed...the sub-prime loan debacle, I think I would want to divert the blame as well. there I fixed it for you fairy</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345433585000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>