<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352004144186-1</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P.S. In case you do not like what you heard from Romney, you got nothing to worry either. All you need to do is wait a day or two and he will change what he say.</Msg><Username>bushiname</Username><Timestamp>1352004144186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 00:42:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352004382750-2</Id><Title>Is there any possibilities that MSFT will hire John Browett?</Title><Msg>Steve Bal.mer will definitely be manly enough to hire him.</Msg><Username>bushiname</Username><Timestamp>1352004382750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 00:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352005145548-3</Id><Topic><Title>Which stocks Billionaires Love?</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905639453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 04:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First it built the Surface, and now Microsoft is said to be working on another new hardware product, this time a smartphone. That’s according to a new report from the Wall Street Journal, which says Microsoft is currently working with Asian component suppliers on its own handset design, though it isn’t yet clear whether or not the device will ever go into mass production.</Msg><Username>tomson.antony</Username><Timestamp>1352005145548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 00:59:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352009047973-4</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wing Talking Heads Retraction ??? - Continued</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1351958018325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Did the CIA lie then, or were they called on the carpet to lie now?" "Did the CIA lie then, (NO) or were they called on the carpet to lie now?(NO)"</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1352009047973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 01:04:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352016671947-5</Id><Topic><Title>Which stocks Billionaires Love?</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905639453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 04:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gmail is now the world's most popular PC e-mail service, per comScore: the research firm estimates Gmail saw 287.9M monthly unique visitors in October, putting it ahead of Hotmail's 286.2M. Once-dominant Yahoo Mail came in third with 281.7M visitors, though it still leads in the U.S. Back in June, Google claimed it had 425M total monthly active Gmail users (includes mobile-only users).</Msg><Username>cris.chest</Username><Timestamp>1352016671947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 03:11:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352029696333-6</Id><Title>Mitt's "change".</Title><Msg>Change his already preposterous 10% tax rate to zero. Change your tax rate to take up the slack. Change a government of, by and for the people of the United States into a government of, by and for Mitt and his cronies and dedicated to their greater profit independent of the consequences for anyone else.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1352029696333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 06:48:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352030216908-7</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's "change".</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1352029696333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 06:48:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's either Mitt or let the low life #$%$ rule another four years.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1352030216908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 06:56:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352030672528-8</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's "change".</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1352029696333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 06:48:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is what you are. Thanks for making that obvious.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1352030672528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:04:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352033009962-9</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama was qualified enough to take care of Bin Laden, and other high profile terrorists, he has kept the American homeland safe.....</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1352033009962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:43:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352033278325-10</Id><Title>Vote for REVENGE</Title><Msg>Get REVENGE for putting up with the dog eater for four years, vote ROMNEY.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1352033278325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:47:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352034737982-11</Id><Topic><Title>Creek slips, reveals his true feelings about minorities, especially politically active blacks</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1351986540269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:49:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The best solution would be to have mutually consenting adults do what ever they want in the privacy of their own homes, and have big Government stay out of it. Less than one hundred years ago, conservatives worked hard to keep women from voting. Since that time, they have been pretty much against any economic, or social reform that was of benefit the country, and they haven't improved much on that over the years..</Msg><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1352034737982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 08:12:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352035662627-12</Id><Title>Bing or Google "Microsoft Smart Glass demo" this could be next Big Thing</Title><Msg>Looks great on paper, hope it works as good as advertised.</Msg><Username>samcastle100</Username><Timestamp>1352035662627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 08:27:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352037543100-13</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's "change".</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1352029696333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 06:48:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Extricated us from the debacle in Iraq in which lives and treasure were expended on the basis of false and deliberately fearmongering claims of immanent threats of destruction from non-existent "WMDs" Extracted the financial "industry" from the catastrophe they brought about on themselves and the public worldwide with the false "economic boom" they created through fraud and manipulation to mask the dissipation of wealth and industry that occurred through the eight years of "conservative" misrule. Worked to ensure that emergency rooms are the only option for the care necessary for the ailing and infirm due to the greed and overweening self-interest of pure profit driven "insurance" providers reluctant to provide the coverage they claim they would provide lest their profit margins and the astronomical compensation of their CxOs be impacted, and legislated against the same profit obsessed agenda of private hospital chains, drug companies and Medicare providers. Worked to reestablish employment opportunities lost due to the greed and negligent self interest of alleged "job creators" more concerned with their quest for inordinate wealth and power than with any concern for those who labor to ensure that their "business" interests are ensured and serve as the only actual market for their goods and services. Turned away from a hostile, overbearing and militant attitude toward our fellow nations and worked toward the ability to trade, travel and interact without the atmosphere of fear and hatred that dominated the discourse during the ascendency of the band of jingoist pseudo-patriots who damaged out international reputation and our ability to make our way as an example of freedom peace and enlightenment to the world. I know you advocate the return to the "Bush boom" policies that led to a false security and a transient enrichment for you. I disagree heartily that those policies are anything other than a path to another, even bigger, "bust" of the kind we haven't yet recovered from and from which we never will under the misguided and incoherent "policies", such as they are, advanced by Romney and his coterie. You've never really given me any reason to change my mind about that and your incessant parroting of irrelevant, inane talking points manufactured by an extremist, regressive right wing within the Republican party and its hyper-radical splinter groups has confirmed that you never will. No matter the outcome of the upcoming election you'll remain in your swamp of misery and discontent, doing nothing other than incessantly posting your nonsensical drivel to the delight of the even more depraved and hate-filled blatherers who spend their entire lives posting off-topic drivel on this irrelevant message board. Have a good time of it.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1352037543100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 08:59:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352039371373-14</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT headed to 35 to 45 soon</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1351778602665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without a mouse on the Surface, on step e just touch the top edge of the web page (make sure you are not clicking a link). This is equivalent to right clicking and the (show) Menu option will appear. Click Menu so it is selected. Then a Menu bar appears where the Import/Export Favorites is.</Msg><Username>jaceanne_gibson</Username><Timestamp>1352039371373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 09:29:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352040311247-15</Id><Title>Romney's economic advisors are the same as Bush's economic advisors. Romney's foreign policy advisors are the same as Bush's</Title><Msg>Romney's economic advisors are the same as Bush's economic advisors. Romney's foreign policy advisors are the same as Bush's. Romney's tax plan is the Bush tax plan on crack! Cut taxes for the wealthy by 20% and increase military spending by $2Trillion? That's Bush on crystal meth! Both Romney and Bush are in the pockets of Grover Norquist and the Koch Bros. Romney is George Dubya Bush on acid. Romney will accelerate the deficits and kill the economy.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352040311247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 09:45:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352041189065-16</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's "change".</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1352029696333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 06:48:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1.) The debacle in Iraq never had to occur in the first place and, as Mitt Romney has stated on many occasions, it would be the preference of the corporatist wing of the regressive Republican party that military presence be reestablished no matter the cost in order to further the profitability of the U.S. segment of the extractive energy industry. Romney's inarticulate quasi-justification for a continuing occupation of a country initially invaded under false pretexts: "Yeah. A couple of things. One, you probably know that it is my view that the withdrawal of all of our troops from Iraq by the end of this year is an enormous mistake and a failing by the Obama administration. Secretary Panetta and others had indicated they were working to put in place a Status of Forces Agreement to maintain our presence there, so that we could most effectively transition to the Iraqi military and Iraqi security forces providing security for their country. "The precipitous withdrawal is unfortunate. It's more than unfortunate. I think it's tragic. It puts at risk many of the victories that were hard-won by the men and women who have served there. I hope the risk is not realized. I hope instead that the Iraqis are able to pick up the baton, and despite the fact that we will have walked away on a too-rapid basis." 2.) Neither Barney Frank nor Barack Obama were President in 2007 and neither set fiscal or monetary policy. You continue to promote the fallacy that the failure of the private mortgage industry was magically the fault of Barney Frank or whatever scapegoat you've been fed misinformation you eagerly parrot, Repetition of falsehoods don't make them true. 3.) The failure to effect the closure of Guantanimo is due to the intransigence of the House of Representatives and their bowing to a fear campaign promoted by right wing propaganda outlets implying that the "Kenyan Muslim Blackamoor" to put it as your more despicable followers on this board would and do, was intending to release hoards of Islamic extremists into the local Walmart. 4.) Foreign nations understand the false bravado of a cowardly bully. They may be concerned when that bully wields nuclear weapons and doesn't exhibit the ability to restrain itself from unprovoked agression on the basis of at best unfounded rumor and at worst a deliberate campaign of inflammatory falsehoods. Once again you've tried fear, lies and trickery in the attempt to promote your backward agenda and failed miserably. Only the most disgusting of your fans would begin to be swayed by your canards.</Msg><Username>nd1005</Username><Timestamp>1352041189065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 09:59:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352043218392-17</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's "change".</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1352029696333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 06:48:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Change a government of, by and for the people of the United States into a government of, by and for Mitt and his cronies and dedicated to their greater profit independent of the consequences for anyone else." I think you give too much intellect to Mitt. He is just a hand to sign the docs from Norquist's office. When I learned this, I went back to my Democrat roots and when I get in the booth I will vote Obama. I hate to, because he's black, but I think Norquist should be at least an elected official to change the country. Good post btw. Later.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1352043218392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 10:33:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352044172003-18</Id><Topic><Title>Vote for REVENGE</Title><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1352033278325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:47:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i can do that-bring jobs and less #$%$</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1352044172003</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 10:49:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352045325702-19</Id><Title>Bloomberg's ringing endorsement of Obama</Title><Msg>Even in his endorsement, the mayor continued to express criticism of the president. He said Mr. Obama had fallen short of his 2008 campaign promise to be a problem solver and consensus builder, noting that Mr. Obama had “devoted little time” to creating a coalition of centrists in Washington who could find common ground on important issues like illegal guns, immigration, tax reform and deficit reduction. “Rather than uniting the country around a message of shared sacrifice,” Mr. Bloomberg said of Mr. Obama, “he engaged in partisan attacks and has embraced a divisive populist agenda focused more on redistributing income than creating it.” ...Makes me want to go right out and vote for him myself. LOL</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352045325702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:08:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352045344881-20</Id><Title>I've seen countless Romney/Ryan yard signs but only one Obamma/Binden sign</Title><Msg>And that one was sticking out of the business end of a garbage truck on it's way to the city dump. Now THAT'S a GOOD sign.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1352045344881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:09:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352046036079-21</Id><Title>Finally, newspapers finding a story in Benghazi</Title><Msg>Piece it all together, and there you have it: a narrative that provides context to the administration's rapidly-falling-apart storyline on Benghazi. Some in the mainstream media have attempted to minimize the administration's Benghazi missteps as the product of understandable confusion given the "fog of war." Others see a Fox News hatchet job on a vulnerable Democratic incumbent president. Hopefully, most will at least ask themselves why a now-discredited explanation about a video few have ever seen was so feverishly peddled to the American public — and the world. An American ambassador and three other Americans are dead. Inexplicably, one of the most dangerous consulates (and most vulnerable ambassadors) in the world lacked a Marine detail. A no-name amateur filmmaker is still being held in the Los Angeles Metropolitan Detention Center without bond. Hillary Clinton and Susan Rice remain silent. The American people deserve the truth, Vegas fundraisers and important elections notwithstanding. Copyright © 2012, The Baltimore Sun</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352046036079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:20:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352046310166-22</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg's ringing endorsement of Obama</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352045325702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:08:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah but even the pecksniffian putz Mayor is vacillating like the blooming it e it he is by condoning the death and destruction the Ken'yan has caused to the country by endorsing the D min spawn.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1352046310166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:25:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352046923064-23</Id><Topic><Title>Finally, newspapers finding a story in Benghazi</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352046036079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:20:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UPDATE: CBS reports that, as the attack on the U.S. mission unfolded over the course of hours, the president “did not convene its top interagency counterterrorism resource: the Counterterrorism Security Group, (CSG).” A source, a “high-ranking government official,” explained to the network that “the CSG is the one group that’s supposed to know what resources every agency has. They know of multiple options and have the ability to coordinate counterterrorism assets across all the agencies . . . They were not allowed to do their job. They were not called upon.” This seems to call into question the president’s claim that he acted in response to the attack by issung “three clear directives,” including “securing our personnel and doing whatever we need to” and “find[ing] out exactly who did this so we can bring him to justice.”</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352046923064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:35:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352047037542-24</Id><Topic><Title>I've seen countless Romney/Ryan yard signs but only one Obamma/Binden sign</Title><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1352045344881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:09:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Must really suck to have to live in the sh.t hole ignorant redneck racist defeated Confederacy in a gator swamp in your tin shack eh</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1352047037542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:37:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352047091677-25</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama failed middle class. No jobs, no future. It would not be any better if he stays in. He has to be voted out. He is not qualified for the president's position.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352047091677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:38:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352047357388-26</Id><Topic><Title>Finally, newspapers finding a story in Benghazi</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352046036079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:20:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He did what his hero Hittller did and D mon ized someone else, in this case, the film maker, in order to divert the blame from HIM, where it belongs. We now know for a fact that Hussein and his henchmen watched those men die from the situation room and DID NOTHING other than call out for pizza so that they could enjoy their bird's eye view of everything going on over there before heading off to campaign in Sin City.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1352047357388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:42:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352047543076-27</Id><Topic><Title>Finally, newspapers finding a story in Benghazi</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352046036079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:20:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There may have been confusion in the first 7 or 70 minutes,.... BUT NOT 7 FKCUING HOURS. The only confusion was what tie the D min Mu'slim had to pick out for his Vegas tour.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1352047543076</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:45:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352048291080-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's economic advisors are the same as Bush's economic advisors. Romney's foreign policy advisors are the same as Bush's</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352040311247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 09:45:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney's tax plan is the Bush tax plan on crack! Cut taxes for the wealthy by 20% and increase military spending by $2Trillion? That's Bush on crystal meth! Both Romney and Bush are in the pockets of Grover Norquist and the Koch Bros</Msg><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1352048291080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:58:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352048420273-29</Id><Title>From the People Who Brought You Economic Collapse and Iraq</Title><Msg>Because the truth is that Romney's economic advisers, led by Glenn Hubbard, were also George W Bush's economic advisers. Not surprisingly, they have the same plan: tax cuts for the wealthy, de-regulation, subsidies for oil companies, ending subsidies for alternative energy, tax breaks for shipping jobs overseas and skyrocketing defense spending. Lurking not too deep behind the surface are plans to hand Social Security to Wall Street. But, this time the collapse will be worse. We start from a far less secure position than when President Clinton handed the Republicans surpluses "as far as the eye could see," and, this time, there is no stomach in the Republican party to do anything but let it all fall.</Msg><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1352048420273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:00:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352048919248-30</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT up on very heavy volume for 2 days straight</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1351792531576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:55:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like WIn 8 and Surface both are doing well. plus, MSFt issues more than 2 billions of debt. next week, we shall start to see Windoews 8 Phones coming out. Lots of new products are on out or coming out. Let us not forget thaat we have got almost 2 billions of top line that wre deferred from the last 2 quaters that will have to be realized. So, we shall start to see top line possibly up big time over the coming 2 quaters. Share price will go up possibly by 10-20% over coming months.</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1352048919248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:08:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352049188486-31</Id><Title>The Democarts caused the financial collapse by giving sub prime loans to penniless paupers</Title><Msg>.... who couldn't afford a snow-cone let alone new homes. And then after the vermin leftists managed to intentionally collapse it all, they did just what their eve ill leader is doing right now in HIS cover up,.... BLAME SOMEONE ELSE.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1352049188486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:13:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352049755212-32</Id><Topic><Title>Finally, newspapers finding a story in Benghazi</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352046036079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 11:20:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only meeting the Kenyan convened is the one where they planned the cover-up.</Msg><Username>xcrewshe8n</Username><Timestamp>1352049755212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:22:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352054643228-33</Id><Topic><Title>From the People Who Brought You Economic Collapse and Iraq</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1352048420273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:00:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From February 2001 until March 2003, Hubbard was chairman of the Council of Economic Advisors under President George W. Bush. A supply-side economist, he was instrumental in the design of the 2003 Bush Tax cuts[</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352054643228</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 13:44:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352056453460-34</Id><Topic><Title>From the People Who Brought You Economic Collapse and Iraq</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1352048420273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:00:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"let it all fall." That's right Moe, no more free lunch, you pay to play. I'm amazed at all the liberal Moes who can't think straight. When you go to buy a gallon of milk do you get it free, Moe? 47% get everything free, Obama voters all of them. Obama told Benghazi to give up, and everyone was killed, Obama didn't get Bin Laden, the Seals did, and Obama just stood around shuffling his feet with his head down, Moe, and Obama stole 20 Billion of my money and gave it to the UAW to spend on themselves. Moe you are right, let it all fall.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1352056453460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:14:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352056536070-35</Id><Title>Poor balz, despite all her alias on this board and others</Title><Msg>doesn't get to vote but once. Rembrantjohn/amogine etc don't count.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352056536070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:15:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352057222234-36</Id><Topic><Title>Poor balz, despite all her alias on this board and others</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352056536070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:15:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>does'nt get to vote but once.amogine and others don't count.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352057222234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:27:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352057673421-37</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS NO SHAME TO VOTE FOR ROMNEY. YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY VOTING FOR OBAMA IN 2008.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1351924108656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To some people looking for the truth if ever they do is like a blind man looking for a black gnat on a black night under a black rock. They don't know it is dark much less.</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1352057673421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:34:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352057778833-38</Id><Topic><Title>Which stocks Billionaires Love?</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905639453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 04:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft is reinventing itself. Google and Apple have a head start in the mobile sector for tablets and smartphones, but the change Microsoft is undergoing is impressive. It is responding to the challenge of its rivals, and it will include the first window machines capable of running on chips with technology from ARM Holdings, instead of Intel.</Msg><Username>cris.chest</Username><Timestamp>1352057778833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:36:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352058063805-39</Id><Topic><Title>From the People Who Brought You Economic Collapse and Iraq</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1352048420273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:00:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a major victory for the White House, the Senate early Friday voted 77-23 to authorize President Bush to attack Iraq if Saddam Hussein refuses to give up weapons of mass destruction as required by U.N. resolutions. 10/11/2002 Hours earlier, the House approved an identical resolution, 296-133.</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1352058063805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 14:41:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352059628223-40</Id><Topic><Title>From the People Who Brought You Economic Collapse and Iraq</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1352048420273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:00:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"if Saddam Hussein refuses to give up weapons of mass destruction as required by U.N. resolutions" And Saddam Hussein disclosed clearly that he already had given up weapons of mass destruction and was blustering to keep the Iranians off guard. Inspectors were in the process of fully verifying that when Bush decided to invade without U.N. backing: "U.N. weapons inspectors climbed aboard a plane and pulled out of Iraq on Tuesday after President Bush issued a final ultimatum for Saddam Hussein to step down or face war. U.N. Secretary-General Kofi Annan on Monday ordered all U.N. inspectors and support staff, humanitarian workers and U.N. observers along the Iraq-Kuwait border to evacuate Iraq after U.S. threats to launch war. After failing to secure U.N. authorization to use force to disarm Iraq, Bush gave Saddam 48 hours to step down or face war in a speech Monday night. A plane carrying the inspectors took off Tuesday morning from Saddam International Airport and later landed in Laranca, Cyprus, where the inspectors have a base. U.N. officials said about 150 inspectors, support staff, humanitarian workers and observers would be evacuated. "We left Iraq with a sense of sadness," U.N. spokesman Hiro Ueki said in Cyprus. "We have done our job to the extent that we could. All the staff did this the best possible way, both objectively and professionally."" Read more: http://www.foxnews.com/story/0,2933,81343,00.html#ixzz2BHoX2h95</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1352059628223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:07:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352061554318-41</Id><Topic><Title>Vote for REVENGE</Title><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1352033278325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:47:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already did, and enjoyed every second, for Obama/Biden of course.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1352061554318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:39:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352061765087-42</Id><Title>American Enterprise Institute Senior Fellow Kevin Hassett was Bush's Now Romney's Econmic Advisor</Title><Msg>American Enterprise Institute Senior Fellow Kevin Hassett was Senator John McCain’s chief economic adviser during his 2000 presidential run, and also served as an economic adviser to George W. Bush in 2004 and to McCain again in 2008. A National Review columnist, Hassett has argued in favor of privatizing Social Security, whined over Democratic attempts to have hedge fund managers pay a larger tax on carried interest, and called Warren Buffett an “ignorant rube” for proposing a higher tax on the top 1 percent. AMERICAN ENTERPRISE INST = K0CH BROS/GROVER NORQUIST</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352061765087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:42:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352062547952-43</Id><Title>VOTE FOR UNIFIER, VOTE FOR FUTURE, VOTE FOR BETTER LIFE - VOTE FOR ROMNEY.</Title><Msg>We can never get the above with obama. He already proved it to us.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352062547952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:55:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352062569349-44</Id><Topic><Title>From the People Who Brought You Economic Collapse and Iraq</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1352048420273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:00:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$................................</Msg><Username>opinionsarelike33</Username><Timestamp>1352062569349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:56:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352062941592-45</Id><Topic><Title>From the People Who Brought You Economic Collapse and Iraq</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1352048420273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:00:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes it was wrong (hindsight) but not like this (BO) does without senate or congress. Two wrongs don't make a right. This man is a failure &amp; disgrace. One example - From Audacity of Hope: "I will stand with the Muslims should the political winds shift in an ugly direction."</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1352062941592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:02:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352063227682-46</Id><Title>NTEK Next Weeks #1 Stock Gainer</Title><Msg>NTEK Will be next weeks number 1 stock gainer stock is going to explode monday morning</Msg><Username>ta_k1ng_expert_pro</Username><Timestamp>1352063227682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:07:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352063370884-47</Id><Topic><Title>Vote for REVENGE</Title><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1352033278325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:47:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Voting for obama is voting against america. America is our country. America supports romney.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352063370884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:09:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352063719251-48</Id><Title>VOTE FOR a UNIFIER, VOTE FOR the FUTURE, VOTE FOR a BETTER LIFE - VOTE FOR OBAMA</Title><Msg>"VOTE FOR UNIFIER, VOTE FOR FUTURE, VOTE FOR BETTER LIFE" What country are you living in? From someone who is an American, lives in America, works in America, loves America, and writes the language better: Obama is a great man, highly qualified, highly educated, super intelligent, and has earned, the hard way, every thing he has gotten. He is the greatest unifier and peacemaker of all time. If the teas think they can get away with blocking his every move, then saying "oh look he can"t get along, but we can", they have another think coming. The Party is over. I voted Obama/Biden, and it was the right thing to do for America.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1352063719251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:15:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352063790198-49</Id><Title>The Nonpartisan Study On High-Income Tax Cuts The GOP Doesn’t Want You To Read</Title><Msg>The Nonpartisan Study On High-Income Tax Cuts The GOP Doesn’t Want You To Read The nonpartisan Congressional Research Service (CRS) issued a report in September that showed that cutting tax rates for the wealthiest Americans did not spur economic or job growth, refuting a key Republican justification for the party’s continued obsession with maintaining the tax cuts for the wealthy they passed in 2003. But when Senate Republicans aired seemingly minor complaints about it, the agency quietly withdrew the report, even as its economic team advised it to stand firm. The report, as ThinkProgress reported in September, found that tax cuts for the rich spurred income inequality, not economic growth. “There is not conclusive evidence, however, to substantiate a clear relationship between the 65-year steady reduction in the top tax rates and economic growth,” the report stated. “However, the top tax rate reductions appear to be associated with the increasing concentration of income at the top of the income distribution.”</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352063790198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:16:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352063880166-50</Id><Title>idiotic xkkkrushi8n, ghosanon, gooferboooger hawfaeces dont know that backing the super rich who will keep them in poverty and virtual slavery</Title><Msg>The problem ignorant racist rednecks always have is they are so stooopid they always vote against their own interest</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1352063880166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:18:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352063892949-51</Id><Topic><Title>VOTE FOR UNIFIER, VOTE FOR FUTURE, VOTE FOR BETTER LIFE - VOTE FOR ROMNEY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352062547952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:55:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"VOTE FOR UNIFIER, VOTE FOR FUTURE, VOTE FOR BETTER LIFE " Uh huh</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1352063892949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:18:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352064044246-52</Id><Topic><Title>VOTE FOR UNIFIER, VOTE FOR FUTURE, VOTE FOR BETTER LIFE - VOTE FOR ROMNEY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1352062547952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 15:55:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup lets give the super rich the tax cut they have been lobbying for for years. To helll with the middle class</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1352064044246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:20:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352064134078-53</Id><Topic><Title>VOTE FOR a UNIFIER, VOTE FOR the FUTURE, VOTE FOR a BETTER LIFE - VOTE FOR OBAMA</Title><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1352063719251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:15:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GooG - Justice with judge Jeanie sat 9PM et</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1352064134078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:22:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352064139030-54</Id><Topic><Title>Vote for REVENGE</Title><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1352033278325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 07:47:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America supports Obama, romney is a liar, cheater, and con man extraordinaire</Msg><Username>hawrcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1352064139030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:22:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352064401869-55</Id><Title>Payroll Growth Shows U.S. Labor Market Healing Before Election</Title><Msg>BLOOMBERG: Payroll Growth Shows U.S. Labor Market Healing Before Election American employers hired more workers than forecast in October while an influx of people joining the labor force pushed the jobless rate higher, according to the last job market report before the presidential election. Payrolls expanded by 171,000 workers following a 148,000 gain in September that was bigger than first estimated, figures from the Labor Department showed yesterday. October’s increase exceeded the highest forecast in a Bloomberg survey with a median projection of 125,000. Unemployment rose to 7.9 percent.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352064401869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:26:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352065444149-56</Id><Title>Romney Promises To Create 12 Million Jobs In China</Title><Msg>More on Bain/Romney and Outsourcing U.S. Jobs to China By SEIU Research Bain Capital, while still under the leadership of Mitt Romney, invested in a Chinese outsourcing company that profited at the expense of some 520 workers at a Sunbeam appliance factory in Coushatta, Louisiana. The Louisiana plant - which made domestic appliances like irons and toaster ovens - was shuttered in December 1996; one month after Sunbeam CEO "Chainsaw" Al Dunlap announced a corporate restructuring plan including the "rationalization of manufacturing." Dunlap was an early and vocal proponent of shipping jobs overseas to low-wage countries in the interest of maximizing shareholder value. The GAO highlighted the job losses in Coushatta as part of an August 2001 report on the impact of global trade on a handful of six American communities. The GAO wrote: The closure, effective December 31, 1996, was part of a nationwide downsizing by Sunbeam that cut more than 6,000 jobs due to increased imports. With the closure of the Sunbeam plant, a major employer in Coushatta, the unemployment rate for Red River Parish rose to 23.7 percent in 1997. A total of approximately 520 workers lost their jobs. Just six months after the Coushatta factory was shut down, on June 27, 1997 the Chinese manufacturer Global-Tech signed a formal outsourcing agreement with Sunbeam "to be its sole outside supplier of certain models of bread makers, air cleaners, coffeemakers, irons, rotisseries, toaster ovens, food steamers, deep fryers and other products." The timing of this agreement leaves little doubt that work being performed by American workers was headed to China. The impact of this shift on Coushatta, a town of just 2,000, was devastating, particularly on women, who comprised the majority of workers at the plant, said the Washington Post. The plant also employed 43 mentally handicapped workers, said the Times-Picayune.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352065444149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:44:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352065778470-57</Id><Topic><Title>idiotic xkkkrushi8n, ghosanon, gooferboooger hawfaeces dont know that backing the super rich who will keep them in poverty and virtual slavery</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1352063880166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:18:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better to be around rich than poor low life like you, four more years and everybody will be poor.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1352065778470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:49:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352066325043-58</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Promises To Create 12 Million Jobs In China</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352065444149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SHHHH, not supposed to be told quite yet. The other quick note is the 12 million jobs are expected to be created anyway, under Obama. SHHHH, when they are, it will be us that did it, the Romney Norquist Team. Just hold back on that awhile, OK?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1352066325043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:58:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352066848473-59</Id><Topic><Title>The Nonpartisan Study On High-Income Tax Cuts The GOP Doesn’t Want You To Read</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352063790198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:16:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flat Tax - No exemptions there are none in washington who will talk about it, why? It means if they buy a jet or 40 million house- they would have to pay 20-30% flat tax . Would be great for this country, EVERYTHING from China or any other country would get the same value added tax. Jobs would come home.</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1352066848473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 17:07:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352066870963-60</Id><Title>Romney has used car salesman skill not president</Title><Msg>4 years ago we had to hear the name of this lady Sara Palin(possible the most idiot lady in planet earth)and today that replace by a man name Romney (used car salesman skill)out of touch with americam people.sometimes I see these young(all male)kids biking and promoting their parents religion.he did for two years ,believe in France.united state rapresent planet earth population with their color of skin/religion/culture but all under ONE name americans....Romney out of touch with 90% of them.I'm american free of my parents religion and in love with america since my birth country run by religouse so called kigdom leader(BTW they ssuukk).my love in america tell me to follow a leader that his religous believe rapresent all american as equal as possible so my kids grow up as free as their father.I understand 95% of african/american vote for Obama but why 100% of mormons will vote for Romney ? I learn to be free from religion of my parents then why not one mormon out of what ever mil of them in US will follow me to be free of their religion.....just one ....are they free ? look at jewish faith,I call them free people atleast in politics...how many jews will vote for Romney or Obama ? good % for either one.I bet if candidate was jewish still some jews vote for other none jew candidate and that's beauty of being equal.....is there one mormon critic of Romney ? just one mormon.. the answer is no if I'm wrong then pardon my ignorance...GO OBAMA . ... .. . .</Msg><Username>momokamas</Username><Timestamp>1352066870963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 17:07:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352066997371-61</Id><Topic><Title>Payroll Growth Shows U.S. Labor Market Healing Before Election</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352064401869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:26:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then why are we now printing 40 billion a month?</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1352066997371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 17:09:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352070825205-62</Id><Title>MSFT, Rodney Dangerfield of stocks!!!</Title><Msg>With Windows 8 selling well, tablet Surface (we know MSFT is a bland company but can't they chose a better name?) about to be launched, one would think the stock would exhibit a bit mojo. Nope, unfortunately it is for ever stuck at 30 range. MSFT badly needs a new leadership but I don't see it happening with Bill Gates loyal to his buddy (over the long suffering stock holders). In addition, billionaire Balmer owns lot of MSFT stock and has board in his pocket.</Msg><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1352070825205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 18:13:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352071574797-63</Id><Title>I say good riddance ...</Title><Msg>I say good riddance to these detrimental socialist-welfare-state mongers - the affirmative-action-president and affirmative-action-secretary-of-state. I think that this is the end-of-the-line for Barry-the-Marxist - the first affirmative-action-president. He thought that because he's a nice looking, cool-black-dude with a "good rap" that he could get away with just about anything, including telling direct lies. Even though the news media (democrat propaganda agency) is in the bag for him, I think many of those with their head in the sand are finally waking up to Barry's ineptitude and compulsive fibbing. And, this giggling, affirmative-action-secretary-of-state is no bargain either. This ditz has no idea of what the hell she's doing, and that has been tragically underscored by the disaster in Libya that she has helped orchestrate. She's just political opportunist who has used her husband's power and fame to get where she is today. She's the darling of radical-Marxist-feminists who have helped to destroy the family structure in this nation, and for her to advance would be very bad news in a multitude of ways. A Realist.</Msg><Username>clyde54</Username><Timestamp>1352071574797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 18:26:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352071772692-64</Id><Title>After The Bush Depression Do You Want Another Romney Depression?</Title><Msg>Supply side economics and deregulation and tax cuts caused the Bush Depression. Romney wants to double down on Dubya. Guess where that's going to lead?</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352071772692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 18:29:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352075147228-65</Id><Topic><Title>From the People Who Brought You Economic Collapse and Iraq</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1352048420273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:00:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if such fickle winds as those of politics should shift to cause them harm. Political winds shifted against people of the Jewish faith at one point and many were found not standing with them for a distorted sense of self-interest. In the end we're all just people, whatever our spiritual beliefs if any. Political "movements" can often cause harm for the gain of manipulators with a fundamental disregard for anything but their own transient "glory". Barack Obama does things under the law. There are others who come to mind readily who think the law is something to be twisted to their own purposes or worse.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1352075147228</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:25:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352075249827-66</Id><Topic><Title>idiotic xkkkrushi8n, ghosanon, gooferboooger hawfaeces dont know that backing the super rich who will keep them in poverty and virtual slavery</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1352063880166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:18:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot, I am not in poverty and plan to vote for Romney to make sure I don't end up in there. The poor does nothing for anyone. Never have given anyone a job and suck off the government. It used to be an embarassment to be on welfare, now it is a badge of honor that they know how to scam the system and not work.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352075249827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:27:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352075363814-67</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Promises To Create 12 Million Jobs In China</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352065444149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 16:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that in addition to all the jobs GM is sending to China.? Why don't you learn something besides liberal talking points?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352075363814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:29:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352075478768-68</Id><Title>How many bigots here will not vote for redneck knee grow?</Title><Msg>???????</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352075478768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:31:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352076237448-69</Id><Title>Romney has used car salesman skills, the president has no skills!!!</Title><Msg>Obamanure has the skill of gab!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352076237448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:43:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352076381670-70</Id><Title>The Waste Management trucks are heading to DC to remove 4 years of Obamanure .</Title><Msg>It will begin on Wednesday.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352076381670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:46:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352078192834-71</Id><Topic><Title>From the People Who Brought You Economic Collapse and Iraq</Title><Username>the_lord_balzy_project</Username><Timestamp>1352048420273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 12:00:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because the truth is that Romney's economic advisers, led by Glenn Hubbard, were also George W Bush's economic advisers. Not surprisingly, they have the same plan: tax cuts for the wealthy, de-regulation, subsidies for oil companies, ending subsidies for alternative energy, tax breaks for shipping jobs overseas and skyrocketing defense spending. Lurking not too deep behind the surface are plans to hand Social Security to Wall Street. But, this time the collapse will be worse. We start from a far less secure position than when President Clinton handed the Republicans surpluses "as far as the eye could see," and, this time, there is no stomach in the Republican party to do anything but let it all fall.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352078192834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:16:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352078712896-72</Id><Title>Ordinary people acturally like WIn 8, based on HSN review</Title><Msg>Well, this kind of have put to rest much of all those uncessary worries about Win 8. Win 8 machines with all those touch based interface will be a great success for MSFT. expect great things from MSFT and much higher share price!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1352078712896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:25:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352078722256-73</Id><Topic><Title>After The Bush Depression Do You Want Another Romney Depression?</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352071772692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 18:29:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will be better than the current Obamanure depression!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352078722256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:25:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352078795708-74</Id><Title>How many here will vote for the redneck knee grow?</Title><Msg>??????????</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352078795708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:26:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352078918078-75</Id><Title>Romney wins Pennsylvania, despite Philly knee grows!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352078918078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:28:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352079013440-76</Id><Title>Election is referendum on expanded knee grow welfare state.</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352079013440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:30:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352079377166-77</Id><Topic><Title>Romney has used car salesman skills, the president has no skills!!!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352076237448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:43:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did sell it to liberal knee grow!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352079377166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:36:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352079493468-78</Id><Title>How many knee grows does it take to build a bridge?</Title><Msg>They are all on welfare. They create nothing!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352079493468</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:38:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352079885830-79</Id><Title>Tuesday vote results: Romney 344, Obamanure 194!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352079885830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:44:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352083376090-80</Id><Topic><Title>More than 20 major newspaper switch endorsements from Obama in 2008 to Romney 2012</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1352082777979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 21:32:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're going to need to prepare yourself for Obama winning.</Msg><Username>michaelborneman</Username><Timestamp>1352083376090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 21:42:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352083580782-81</Id><Title>Obamanure may win if he gets votes from: all 57 states, all dead, all children under 18, all cartoon characters, and a vast majority of illegals.</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352083580782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 21:46:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352083582000-82</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing Bush did caused a worldwide meltdown like the Obama moes want you to believe.</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1352075130990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:25:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was under Bush that investment banks were allowed to go over 40 times leverage? You really think that helped?</Msg><Username>michaelborneman</Username><Timestamp>1352083582000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 21:46:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352084016424-83</Id><Topic><Title>Obamanure may win if he gets votes from: all 57 states, all dead, all children under 18, all cartoon characters, and a vast majority of illegals.</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352083580782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 21:46:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I fall under Illegal on welfare! Obamanure is the best thing that ever happened to me! I will vote as many times as Acorn will get me new IDs.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352084016424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 21:53:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352084393870-84</Id><Topic><Title>How many here will vote for the redneck knee grow?</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352078795708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:26:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I probably will just to #$%$ you off.</Msg><Username>mcmillanryan1981</Username><Timestamp>1352084393870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 21:59:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352085683946-85</Id><Title>Why is Karl Rove &amp; Grover Norquist hiding Dubya Bush &amp; Cheney?</Title><Msg>Karl Rove and Grover Norquist created the Dubya tax/economic policies. Karl Rove and Grover Norquist created Dubya's foreign policy as well. When those policies failed, crashed the economy and created 2 unfunded wars, Karl Rove decided to hide Duby &amp; Cheney and create new zombies, Romney/ Ryan. Norquist said it. All we need is a president with working digits.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352085683946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:21:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352086170439-86</Id><Topic><Title>How many here will vote for the redneck knee grow?</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352078795708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:26:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which half do you support, the redneck side, or the knee grow side?</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352086170439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:29:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352086240340-87</Id><Topic><Title>How many here will vote for the redneck knee grow?</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352078795708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:26:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I forgot to ask about how much Obamanure you consume each day?</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352086240340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:30:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352086658742-88</Id><Topic><Title>Obamanure may win if he gets votes from: all 57 states, all dead, all children under 18, all cartoon characters, and a vast majority of illegals.</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352083580782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 21:46:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "corpse-men" certainly won't vote for him.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1352086658742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:37:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352086862737-89</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Karl Rove &amp; Grover Norquist hiding Dubya Bush &amp; Cheney?</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1352085683946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:21:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush spent too much 4 trillion in 8 years, but now this guy 6 trillion in 4 years. And wants to spend 6 trillion more? WHOA BOY</Msg><Username>tomuch2491</Username><Timestamp>1352086862737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:41:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352087221566-90</Id><Title>Visited my local Best Buy, found many Win 8 computers there</Title><Msg>Do not know if any on the board have visited any Best Buy Stores. I did this weekend, there were 4-5 poeple checking otu the new Win 8 models. To my surprise, most of the computers there were acturally Win 8 systems. I think this looks to be a good start for WIn 8. As a compariusion, the tables showing the Apple products, I noticed just one single person there checking it out.</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1352087221566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:47:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352088504810-91</Id><Title>JAG is Oversold, RSI 29.2, Ready to Run...</Title><Msg>Check it out....</Msg><Username>cantfigureitout4thelifeofme</Username><Timestamp>1352088504810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 23:08:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352088653710-92</Id><Topic><Title>Visited my local Best Buy, found many Win 8 computers there</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1352087221566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 22:47:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many were sold silly boy????</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352088653710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 23:10:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352088764962-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obamanure may win if he gets votes from: all 57 states, all dead, all children under 18, all cartoon characters, and a vast majority of illegals.</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352083580782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 21:46:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With all due respect, I thinks a lot of corpses will cast their vote for Obamanure!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352088764962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 23:12:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352088904060-94</Id><Topic><Title>Tuesday vote results: Romney 344, Obamanure 194!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352079885830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:44:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Landslide victory Tuesday for Romney!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352088904060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 23:15:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352089799668-95</Id><Title>Obamanure will carry the votes form Russia, Venezuela, Mexico, Cuba, Iran, Libya, Egypt, Iraq, Somalia, Kenya!</Title><Msg>Romney will lose by landslide!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352089799668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 23:29:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352089938819-96</Id><Topic><Title>Obamanure will carry the votes form Russia, Venezuela, Mexico, Cuba, Iran, Libya, Egypt, Iraq, Somalia, Kenya!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352089799668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 23:29:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamanure has spent a great deal of USA money and has and advantage because Romney has not spent a dime in these key electoral countries!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352089938819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 23:32:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352090035049-97</Id><Topic><Title>Tuesday vote results: Romney 344, Obamanure 194!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352079885830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 20:44:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets pray. If people without a job think the last 4 years was bad then they will find out how bad it can really get if obama gets back in. Severe depression, double gas prices and food prices thru the roof. Not to mention this same sex marriage shyte. IT CAN ONLY GET WORSE AND DEFICITS I predict will soar past 20 trillion under another Obama.</Msg><Username>richeydouglas</Username><Timestamp>1352090035049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 23:33:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352091427800-98</Id><Topic><Title>Romney has used car salesman skills, the president has no skills!!!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352076237448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 19:43:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The redneck knee grow does have a skill, a propensity to generate Obamanure!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1352091427800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-04 23:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>