<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354425673667-1</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT announcing a special div in December?</Title><Username>qzeck71</Username><Timestamp>1354282567353</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 08:36:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WIn 8 will be helping MSFt to get into the game of tablets and more smartphones. Win 8 busuiness will surely build up over time. The good thing is, Windows control pretty mcuh 90% of all computers, so, when popel do not buy WIn 8, they will be buying Win 8. SO, eith way, MSFT makes money. In fact, when someone buys Win7 systems, MSFT makes more money for the short term. However, MSFT wants to make less now with Win 8, in order to make more and way more in the long future. s for this quater and many quaters to come, regarless of what WIn 8 will do in the market, MSFT will still ba making clsoe to 5-8 billionsof dollaars each quater. MSFt is a money printing machine, and all long sharehooder shall be pleased to own a small piece of it!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354425673667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 00:21:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354425936406-2</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface is a piece of JUNK!!!</Title><Username>nxpx2c</Username><Timestamp>1354380983089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:56:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Win 8 interface is the way of future, may be you are not used to it now. But, infomation and most common web links at the start screen is the future. As civilization advances, we all must learn more and Win 8 is the3 way to help most popell in th world to get there. Since Win 8 is the future, one may be way best served to get on with it and do not be left behind. Donot be lazy amd learn.</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354425936406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 00:25:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354426364761-3</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Softie is becoming irrelevant</Title><Username>jdolby32</Username><Timestamp>1354402356906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 17:52:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jdolby, garbage!!!! MSFt serves the needs of 90% of all computers inthe world, and much of our human society advances depend on computers. Ask anyone who has computers and many opther things - what he or she will keep if he or she had to have one thing, i am pretyt sure he or she will say, I want my computer!!!! MSft advances each and every year, along with each human imporvments. MSFt will unify all comuter devices from desktops to leptops , to tablets , then to martphones and X-boxes. Productivity across all devices is the way to go over the medium and long term. Regardless what MSFt WIN 8 will do over the short term, MSFT will still be making $5-8 billions of each quater going foward. Anybody believing otherwise just do not have a clue what he is talkign about!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354426364761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 00:32:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354427112781-4</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS CRAZY. JUST LOOK AT HIM AND LISTEN TO HIM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354329719887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 21:41:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, his best qualification as a leader was to lead a community." The election is over, don't vote for Obama. He is the best leader we have had in manyy a year. He was President of the United States for four years, that's more than 50. He was elected by the people for four more years. He is campaigning for the middle class, to end the tea party hostage taking of America, us. Anyone saying he is campaigning as in for election is wacko beyond wacko. Even those here from Camp Wakko can't be that wacky.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354427112781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 00:45:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354427259208-5</Id><Topic><Title>Any chance for a special dividend by MSFT</Title><Username>dramdram</Username><Timestamp>1354299833336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:23:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thing it will all depend on if COngress and the White House can reach an agrement or not by late December. There is still 3 weeks to go. the key point will be around Dec 25. If by Dec. 5, there is still no agreement, MSFt may get jum,py and issue a special devidend. Since the chance of having an agreement is high, so MSFt will at this point wait for perhaps a couple of more weeks. I personally believe having $70 billions of cash in US treasuries do nto make any sense. best thing for MSFt to do now is to aggrasively buying MSFt shares from the open market. I think MSFt can easily buying close to 10 billions of $ each of the following 4 quaters. Buying shares now is the most attrcative since the share price has come down to so low, and it is just so smart to buy these shares here for cancellation. MSFt in 2009 bought back some 20 billions $ of shares, and this resulted in total share count down some 15%. This boasted earning per share by the same %. The reason MSFT bought back aggrassively is because MSFt shares were so cheap then. But, in terms of p/e, exclusing cash , no, p/e is even lower. cash at hand $70 billions, this is almost $9 per share of cash. share price now 26$, this leave a net share price of just 17$. since earning over coming year is $3.3, so we have a p/e now just: p/ e = 18/3.3 = cheap 5 That is right, effective p/e now just 5. This is the very reason, MSFT BOD should lanch a super sized buy back program in the area of some $40 billions!!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354427259208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 00:47:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354427521338-6</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft should buy back its own stock</Title><Username>geosmart668</Username><Timestamp>1354407333690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:15:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>please see myother post, best teim for MSFt to buy back some $40 billions. cash at hand some $70 billions, this is abotu $9 per share. earnign per share over coming year is $3.3. So, we got this effective p/e (26-9) = $17/3.3 = 5 p/e. For one of the most prifitable companies in the wodl, getting a piece of it at a p/e 5. This does not happen once in a few life times, so MSFT itself shold get into action, and own a large piece of it itselfright now!!!! takign advantage of stupid wall street is the best revange and best reward here!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354427521338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 00:52:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354427588151-7</Id><Title>Hello Mudda, Hello Fadda, here I am at, Camp Wackoa</Title><Msg>When I come here to Obama whiney, they spank me on my hiney.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1354427588151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 00:53:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354427727537-8</Id><Topic><Title>Is Windows 8 the catalyst for growth? hat about DIv?</Title><Username>investtxs</Username><Timestamp>1354378694366</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:18:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>effective p/e now at 5. time ot load up the boat, and you will not regert it!!!! You cannot make the 1st million $ with Bill Gates, but I want to make my next millions along with the richest man on earth!!!! so, load up and hold till at least $36 (p/e 11). this is what i am doing!!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354427727537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 00:55:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354428317875-9</Id><Topic><Title>Kill Off The Windows RT Tablet - Nobody Is Buying Anway</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1354318260937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 18:31:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for those peole who buys Ipad and andriods, these peoel do not mindd their machines that do not run old windows programs, so Surface RT is perfect for these people. many people like kids, they do not care windows things, so Surface RT is cheap and work fine for them. Ipads and andriods do nto run windows, but people want these and do nto complain. for those who want their machiens to run old windows programs, then Surface Pro is the answer. MSFT is building two surfaces to satify both groups of customers. The 1st generation is pretty good, and MSft will launch future Surface machiens that will have different sized and that have different price points, and they will all become better and better as future models are designed and biuld and sold. Do not just look at the 5 inches ahead, the focus is on the 5 years down the road, and 50 years down th road. corporations have many trillions invested in windows. as a society, it is only to everyones advantages to have as many things as possible unified and higher prodcutivity is good for each and everyone.</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354428317875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:05:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354428496474-10</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Tablet Sales Almost Non-existent</Title><Username>sanddollars586</Username><Timestamp>1354309786897</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:09:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a coupld month ago, MSFt tablets were zero. But, now, we are looking at at least a douzen WIn 8 tablets , both RT and Pro, are coming out. Go to Expansyst web site, you can easily see pre orders for many WIn 8 tablets are high, especially for Samsang tablets. WIn 8 is just out a month ago, of course, WIN 8 tablets are amost zero. The key is, with Win 8, MSFT is gettgin into the game!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354428496474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:08:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354428769478-11</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro: Non Starter at any price</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1354309706077</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:08:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pre order for Samsang WIn 8 tablets are looing good Syrface Pro orders is also pretty high. Check Expansyst web site. regardless what the near future is, the long term future is great with WIn 8 RT and Win 8 pro tablets. YOu want sometig cheap, you get RT. You want somting to run old windows programs, get Win 8 Pro. Easy as pie!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354428769478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:12:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354428918262-12</Id><Topic><Title>3.5% Dividend, 60+ Billion in Current Assets</Title><Username>b3keyboard</Username><Timestamp>1354295323290</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:08:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree. in fact, cash shold be more than $70 billions now, since 4th quater is the most profitable of the year, and it was 67$ billions the end of last quater. effect p/e now is just 5. If Peter Launch looks at MSFT now, I am sure he will say BUY!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354428918262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:15:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354429004474-13</Id><Topic><Title>It's scary that MSFT is being heavily shorted at..</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354296653652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:30:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anyone who is shorting MSFt here will most likely be devastitated shortly. MSFT now has p/e 5, excluding $9 cash per share.</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354429004474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:16:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354429232025-14</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro: Non Starter at any price</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1354309706077</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:08:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My son was telling me the Win-8 upgrade from Win-7 is only $39.95. Hard to beat that price when you get a real professional made O/S. A friend has Surface and it looks good. Should pretty much replace laptops of all kinds. And the advantage is its 100% compatible with your Win desk top and Win Phone. Same MS-Office and same all other Win compatible software. So you're getting a REAL O/S with REAL software! For $39.95 too!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1354429232025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:20:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354429607027-15</Id><Title>Look out MSFT! The Penguins 1/2% Market Share MIGHT be come significant!</Title><Msg>Some day in the distant future.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1354429607027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:26:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354437213324-16</Id><Title>reason Micrsofot sold 40m of Windows 8 license although Win8 PCs report sluggshish at the satart</Title><Msg>it could be because of Windows 7 PCs still depleting from on retailers shelfs/inventory and with it Windows 8 upgrade license selling. also i believe as we heading to the Holidays more Windows 8 PCs/Tablets will sell and CES 2013, 8 January will be the Show that most Vendors comes up with their latest Windows 8 related products as their Windows 7 products inventory depleted by then</Msg><Username>swisslakes</Username><Timestamp>1354437213324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 03:33:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354456381330-17</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS CRAZY. JUST LOOK AT HIM AND LISTEN TO HIM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354329719887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 21:41:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what you do when you are a socialist, and speak to the majority of ignorants that trust you are looking out for them. Chavez does the same thing, and his people wallow in abject poverty...just what is going to happen here in the USA when successful folks pull their money out of the USA. Libtards won't change until they feel lots of pain, and it is coming to your community if it hasn't been there already.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354456381330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 08:53:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354459066039-18</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS CRAZY. JUST LOOK AT HIM AND LISTEN TO HIM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354329719887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 21:41:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course the election is over. We responsible, commonsense conservatives are just telling you what is coming down the pike. Look at the background on our fascist President that constantly wants to circumvent the constitution, and use exec. order...no background. He hid the bad background that he had. Any wonder why George Soros, and his billionaire socialist friends bought the democrat party?</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354459066039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:37:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354459093513-19</Id><Topic><Title>Will the real Obama please stand up. Talk about flip floppers</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1354380965662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:56:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK sybil, maybe he is not a flip flopper. He is just a habitual liar. I was being kind calling him a flip flopper. So for once in your life admit the truth. HE LIES!!!!! In his own words. HE LIES!!!!</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1354459093513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:38:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354460375130-20</Id><Title>Craper/'Sybil, is Marixsm what you really want?</Title><Msg>. Obama knows exactly what he is doing. He wants to weaken the economy for a reason. He is a marxist. This is what marxist dictators do, in every country, so the federal government can take over every facet of our life. It is maddening that it has been done so many times before, without good results, and you do not recognize and acknowledge it.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1354460375130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:59:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354460873481-21</Id><Topic><Title>Look out MSFT! The Penguins 1/2% Market Share MIGHT be come significant!</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1354429607027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:26:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After more than 21/2 decades the linux tsunami has achieved .1% market share, a milestone Congrats! LOL.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354460873481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:07:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354461010454-22</Id><Topic><Title>Look out MSFT! The Penguins 1/2% Market Share MIGHT be come significant!</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1354429607027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:26:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make that .1% after 2 1/2 decades my bad LOL.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354461010454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:10:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354461181762-23</Id><Topic><Title>It's scary that MSFT is being heavily shorted at..</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354296653652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:30:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seen so many short chumps come &amp; go over the years it's not funny.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354461181762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:13:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354461960150-24</Id><Topic><Title>It's scary that MSFT is being heavily shorted at..</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354296653652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:30:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can be sure the mikergo character &amp; his fantasy trade position will soon disappear they always do.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354461960150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:26:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354462659018-25</Id><Topic><Title>Will the real Obama please stand up. Talk about flip floppers</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1354380965662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:56:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cyber is a #$%$ POS</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354462659018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:37:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354462735828-26</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS CRAZY. JUST LOOK AT HIM AND LISTEN TO HIM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354329719887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 21:41:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is not a socialist, fascist, nor has hid any background. His background is superb. If anything he is a little too conservative for many. If the election is over, what's the point of making up degrading phrases about Obama, except you can't take losing, and are full of hatred for some unknown reason. Obama is a good man and patriotic American. His actions and words say so.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354462735828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 10:38:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354464211149-27</Id><Topic><Title>CFury asks: 'And what is it that Obama is doing to play chicken with the economy?'</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1354380254960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:44:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U said some time back the tax hikes would not be that important and certainly the cuts in spending would not upset a republican, As for tactics the public is going to blame the republicans if we go over the cliff, that puts the ball in Obamas court. Are U dumb enough to think hardball politics was invented this month.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1354464211149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:03:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354464453181-28</Id><Title>Such drama spewed from the keyboards of these right wingnuts.</Title><Msg>Much ado about nothing really. Both parties want us over the fiscal cliff. The best way to protect the ultra wealthy is to convince the average guy he will lose out equally badly.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1354464453181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:07:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354464596544-29</Id><Topic><Title>CFury asks: 'And what is it that Obama is doing to play chicken with the economy?'</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1354380254960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:44:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get real workin stiff. Obama wants to further socialism, and it depends on extracting the workin stiff's money. That is our tax system. Only the workin stiff gets taxed. Obama, and the left will attempt, in everyway possible to increase taxes on the workin stiff rather than cutback spending on socialism. That is a fact, and smart money is not going to let it happen. They will pull money out of the USA, cutback on labor costs, rathole money using all kinds of loopholes to prevent that from happening. Obama is already talking about circumventing congress, and going after retirement funds.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354464596544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:09:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354464617764-30</Id><Title>stupid yahoo</Title><Msg>can I post anything stupid yahoo</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1354464617764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:10:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354464657301-31</Id><Title>msft msft</Title><Msg>msft msft msft</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1354464657301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:10:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354464758888-32</Id><Topic><Title>msft msft</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1354464657301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:10:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dang cant post anything here</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1354464758888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:12:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354464851241-33</Id><Topic><Title>msft msft</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1354464657301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:10:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i guess ya yahoos are beginning to clamp down on off topic stuff or is it just for these five minutes.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1354464851241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:14:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354466404171-34</Id><Title>Grover Sat There In His Armani Suit Paid For By The K0ch Bros And Whined About Their Taxes</Title><Msg>It's estimated Grove takes in at least $50 mil annually. Oh, woe is the Walton Family! Oh, woe are the K0ch Bros says Grover! He's sincere too! Tax rates on the 1% are the lowest in 60 years!!! But they pay too much in taxes says Grover. Wages &amp; benefits have tanked due to off-shore out-sourcing. But they pay too much in taxes. We also have to cut working families' social benifits. (Here's a fact. Walmart wages are so low and lacking benefits that their employees with kids have to collect State and Local health insurance benefits. Deficits continue to mount. But they pay too much in taxes. Yeah, the K0ch Brosare real patriots. Here's a message from We The People to Grover. Eat rat schitt and die.</Msg><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1354466404171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:40:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354466584601-35</Id><Topic><Title>CFury asks: 'And what is it that Obama is doing to play chicken with the economy?'</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1354380254960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:44:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The revenue stream that Obama needs to fuel his socialism is over. Way too much debt, and way to much expense on the private sector increasing their costs to continue to support socialism. The ave. workin stiff, and the poor will feel the pain, and the dems will blame the GOP, but the pain will continue.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354466584601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:43:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354466717100-36</Id><Topic><Title>Such drama spewed from the keyboards of these right wingnuts.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1354464453181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We The People aren't buying Grover's propaganda. High incomes pay more taxes or take us off the cliff. Let the rates go up for everyone, thanks Grover. Let the economy tank, thanks Grover. Let 'er go over, thanks Grover!! We The People know who to blame.</Msg><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1354466717100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:45:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354468148238-37</Id><Topic><Title>Grover Sat There In His Armani Suit Paid For By The K0ch Bros And Whined About Their Taxes</Title><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1354466404171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 11:40:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I'm sure We The People are sympathetic to the plight of the K0ch Bros. Here's a message from We The People to Grover. Eat rat schitt and die.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1354468148238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:09:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354469250278-38</Id><Topic><Title>reason Micrsofot sold 40m of Windows 8 license although Win8 PCs report sluggshish at the satart</Title><Username>swisslakes</Username><Timestamp>1354437213324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 03:33:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the pc vendors besides lenovo did a terrible job. they just slapped win 8 on win 7 machines. win 8 really needs the touchscreen to shine. this is why msft needs to make own hardware or store.</Msg><Username>bill3442li</Username><Timestamp>1354469250278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:27:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354470493819-39</Id><Topic><Title>Look out MSFT! The Penguins 1/2% Market Share MIGHT be come significant!</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1354429607027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 01:26:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Android is Linux. The Internet runs on Linux. A huge portion of commercial business runs Linux. Windows is a dying anachronism of the 90's, fading fast. MS is dead in mobile. Mobile is the trend in computing. You lose.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1354470493819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:48:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354470959638-40</Id><Topic><Title>Craper/'Sybil, is Marixsm what you really want?</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1354460375130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:59:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey boooger how can you bash the Marxists when you are one yourself-- What kind of person lives off the dole like you do- you certainly appear to be at the receiving end of Marxist philosophy by being a welfare bum don't you</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1354470959638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:55:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354471147756-41</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro: Non Starter at any price</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1354309706077</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:08:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on-- it means the AAPL and GOOG boys are going to get crushed in the long run</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1354471147756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:59:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354471349606-42</Id><Topic><Title>Surface Pro: Non Starter at any price</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1354309706077</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:08:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a non starter at $499. I can buy an iPad Mini for $329.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1354471349606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:02:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354471500072-43</Id><Title>Gay Marriage</Title><Msg>It all makes sense now. Gay marriage &amp; marijuana being legalized on the same day in Washington state. Leviticus 20:13- "If a man lays with another man he should be stoned." We were just interpreting it wrong.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1354471500072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:05:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354471638114-44</Id><Title>No intercourse before marriage?</Title><Msg>Conservatives say not to have intercourse before marriage. Why not? There's no guarantee of intercourse AFTER marriage!</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1354471638114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:07:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354472006210-45</Id><Topic><Title>reason Micrsofot sold 40m of Windows 8 license although Win8 PCs report sluggshish at the satart</Title><Username>swisslakes</Username><Timestamp>1354437213324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 03:33:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ultrathin Ultrabooks with SSD Storage are WOW, as price drops and touchscreen included will hurt tablets i believe at a point people will find tablets unproductive, nice reader and media player while Windows 8 will have a wider range of price points starting with entry point Notebooks and slim desktops with non touch, i have many devices including Sony Android tablet, Samsung Note II, also Windows 8 touch notebooks, Windows 7 Notebooks at work and home i use touch only when i hold a device in hand other than that is unergonomic</Msg><Username>swisslakes</Username><Timestamp>1354472006210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:13:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354472065192-46</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface is a piece of JUNK!!!</Title><Username>nxpx2c</Username><Timestamp>1354380983089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:56:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The way of the future for me will be Mac OSX, iOS, Android and Linux. No way I'm buying anything that runs Windows 8. Do not be left behind? Tell that to MSFT shareholders! This stock is already down 10% since Windows 8 was released. How much lower does this stock have to go before Ballmer admits Windows 8 is another Vista?</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1354472065192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:14:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354472346888-47</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface is a piece of JUNK!!!</Title><Username>nxpx2c</Username><Timestamp>1354380983089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:56:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I LOVE SURFACE AND I LOVE MICROSOFT..!!</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1354472346888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:19:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354472981503-48</Id><Topic><Title>It's scary that MSFT is being heavily shorted at..</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354296653652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:30:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've seen them come and go with fists full of cash while your 100 share long position has gained you nothing for 12 years running - you're right - it's not funny for longs you fool.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354472981503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:29:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354473672015-49</Id><Title>Break Out comig!</Title><Msg>Could be fueled by a special dividend..........$3.00 my guess......stock breaks out of the $35 range never looks back!</Msg><Username>don.roberts86</Username><Timestamp>1354473672015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:41:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354473900763-50</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wing Wackos Claim Obama Is a Socialist....</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1354469115937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:25:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Churches get to pay no taxes, and the goers get to deduct their tithes. A double whammy of wealth redistribution based on favoring religious beliefs.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354473900763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:45:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354474248930-51</Id><Topic><Title>CFury asks: 'And what is it that Obama is doing to play chicken with the economy?'</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1354380254960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:44:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama campaigned on $800B in tax increases for the wealthy" before, haven't you been on the soap box saying the tax cuts on the wealthy were insignificant? remember GWB himself designed the tax cuts to expire this year? Obama want to keep the cut for us, not them, what's your problem?</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1354474248930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:50:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354474316370-52</Id><Title>Conservatives Say Anal Intercourse Is Wrong</Title><Msg>Unless it's performed by Grover Norquist and the Koch Bros on working people.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1354474316370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:51:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354474560130-53</Id><Topic><Title>CFury asks: 'And what is it that Obama is doing to play chicken with the economy?'</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1354380254960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:44:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Standing up solidly for the majority and not giving in to special interests, is not "playing chicken." Another made up term for the uneducated segregationist crown to latch on to. The election is over, the election is over......</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354474560130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:56:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354474611532-54</Id><Topic><Title>CFury asks: 'And what is it that Obama is doing to play chicken with the economy?'</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1354380254960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:44:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"playing chicken." Another made up term for the uneducated segregationist crowd to latch on to.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354474611532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:56:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354475358934-55</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wing Wackos Claim Obama Is a Socialist....</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1354469115937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:25:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A bunch of #$%$ POS mouths.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354475358934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 14:09:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354480328439-56</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wing Wackos Claim Obama Is a Socialist....</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1354469115937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:25:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course he is. Lots of too rated CEO's have been asked that question, and I know of none of them that says he is not. He can accurately be described as an anti-capitalist that goes along with his being a socialist.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354480328439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:32:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354480654355-57</Id><Topic><Title>Break Out comig!</Title><Username>don.roberts86</Username><Timestamp>1354473672015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:41:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You keep pumping the "special" dividend. I have heard nothing about it. Stick to the facts. I sold all my MSFT at $28.00. This stock will rebound; but not anytime soon.</Msg><Username>stok1mom</Username><Timestamp>1354480654355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 15:37:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354483445331-58</Id><Topic><Title>Surface's first success.</Title><Username>dogeater2008</Username><Timestamp>1354236535482</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 19:48:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's wonder about possible problems with the Surface. Who wants a tablet with two pieces ? Now, since the Surface comes with Word and Excel then it requires a keyboard, But who wants a keyboard and screen that can't be used on a lap-top but requires a table-top ? Those who want Word and Excel should just buy a laptop. Now, does Word and Excel on RT require an internet connection ?</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1354483445331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:24:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354483477290-59</Id><Topic><Title>It's scary that MSFT is being heavily shorted at..</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1354296653652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:30:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be careful what you wish for. That's a bit like hoping for an iceberg so the captain of the Titanic will be fired.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1354483477290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:24:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354483763195-60</Id><Topic><Title>Surface's first success.</Title><Username>dogeater2008</Username><Timestamp>1354236535482</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 19:48:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And consider the Samsung ATIV 500T form factor. The keyboard and tablet connect to each other in such a way that the computer can be used like a lap-top.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1354483763195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:29:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354484641292-61</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wing Wackos Claim Obama Is a Socialist....</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1354469115937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 12:25:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Redistribution is redistribution. Allowing religious groups not to pay tax, and giving a govt rebate, or refund, for church donations is redistribution. The money they should have paid has to be taken from somewhere else to make up for it. Don't like to have it shown to you, do you. Your position, and I have heard many nut cases like you over the years, is any tax on you is stealing. You can read about them being arrested for tax evasion "in the newspapers" from time to time. All the while you sit in your govt protected and enabled "Camp Wacko" chair.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354484641292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 16:44:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354486130302-62</Id><Title>DID YOU ENJOY BUSH'S TAX CUT? IT WILL BE OVER FOR EVERYBODY. HIGHER TAXES ARE ON THE WAY.</Title><Msg>Good. Everybody should be paying for obama's takers. Obama is the party of takers, gop and independents are the party of makers. There are no democrats or republicans. Get it thru your head.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354486130302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:08:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354486288698-63</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS CRAZY. JUST LOOK AT HIM AND LISTEN TO HIM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354329719887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 21:41:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is after ruining america. He does not like the america's power.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354486288698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:11:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354486800808-64</Id><Title>You walk away from Shareholder Meeting friday thinking...............</Title><Msg>This stock is about to take off!........after a lost decade of waiting it sounds like Microsoft is about to make a run at apple and google.....if not now when..........if not them.....who? ...</Msg><Username>don.roberts86</Username><Timestamp>1354486800808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:20:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354488366044-65</Id><Topic><Title>Craper/'Sybil, is Marixsm what you really want?</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1354460375130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 09:59:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Craper, no one in my familoy has ever been on welfare. My mother used to say "I'd rather pick shet with the chickens than get on welfare. " I bet that's not what your mother said. I bet she said "Let's take her for all she's worth. Screw America" The acorn never falls far from it's tree.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1354488366044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:46:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354488478697-66</Id><Title>Hey crapercritiqer, quit redirecting and answer the question</Title><Msg>Do you really want Marxism???????</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1354488478697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:47:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354488760111-67</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS CRAZY. JUST LOOK AT HIM AND LISTEN TO HIM.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354329719887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 21:41:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama is after ruining america. He does not like the america's power." He sure is after America was (almost) ruined. You got that right. What kind of car is that america, that he doesn't like the power of? I had a Gremlin once by american motors, it was pretty quick. The AMX with a 401 was plenty powerful, he should look for one of those on the collector's market. If he gets an AMX 401, he will like the power.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1354488760111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:52:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354489026614-68</Id><Topic><Title>You walk away from Shareholder Meeting friday thinking...............</Title><Username>don.roberts86</Username><Timestamp>1354486800808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:20:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A new race a new era"......".a sea of upside".......that sounds like a company that is going for it......and may I say it is about time!</Msg><Username>don.roberts86</Username><Timestamp>1354489026614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:57:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354490224091-69</Id><Title>SURPRISE!!!! Grover Norquist Is A Koch Bros Lobbyist</Title><Msg>Why would House Republicans swear allegiance to Grover Norquist instead of the Constitution? Follow the money. That's right. Follow the Koch Bros money and to whom it goes to, Boehner, Cantor, Ryan, etc. Koch Bros money is buying favorable tax policy for the billionaire Koch Bros.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1354490224091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 18:17:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354495795687-70</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU ENJOY BUSH'S TAX CUT? IT WILL BE OVER FOR EVERYBODY. HIGHER TAXES ARE ON THE WAY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354486130302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:08:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see how you can sit on your fat can all day &amp; post political vomit on a financial board,the election is over &amp; you lost got that? go away TY.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1354495795687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:49:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354496188895-71</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU ENJOY BUSH'S TAX CUT? IT WILL BE OVER FOR EVERYBODY. HIGHER TAXES ARE ON THE WAY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354486130302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:08:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ #$%$ rat boy.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354496188895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:56:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354496351635-72</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU ENJOY BUSH'S TAX CUT? IT WILL BE OVER FOR EVERYBODY. HIGHER TAXES ARE ON THE WAY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354486130302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:08:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Higher taxes mean more layoffs and higher unemployment. The tax receipts will never be what the libdems anticipate meaning taxes then get raised on the middle class. Cut the masssive socailist spending, or the middle class will continue to enter the poor class.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1354496351635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 19:59:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354498241047-73</Id><Title>With Win 8 hybrids like Surface Pro, you get a laptop and a free tablet</Title><Msg>advice to MSFT to put out ads reading like this "How do you get a free tablet, go buy a Win 8 hybrids!!!!"" This is exactly the advantage of Win 8 hybrids like Surface Pro. It is a laptop and a tablet, all in one!!! In other words, you get a full funtion tablet for free!!!! Those peopel doing Win 8 ads shold be fired!!! a minute ad shold put out the most value to the potnetial customer, the shut up. Apple things sell for cool. MSft stuss sell for value. Which parents donot want to get a free tabnlets for their kid? You want to save the money for a free full funtion tablet, buy Surafec Pro!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354498241047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:30:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354498992645-74</Id><Topic><Title>With Win 8 hybrids like Surface Pro, you get a laptop and a free tablet</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1354498241047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:30:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one wants a toaster duct taped to a shaver. MS is dead meat.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1354498992645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 20:43:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354500007149-75</Id><Topic><Title>You walk away from Shareholder Meeting friday thinking...............</Title><Username>don.roberts86</Username><Timestamp>1354486800808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:20:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>M$ is garbage...a dying dinosaur.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1354500007149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 21:00:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354500473041-76</Id><Topic><Title>You walk away from Shareholder Meeting friday thinking...............</Title><Username>don.roberts86</Username><Timestamp>1354486800808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:20:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"make a run at apple and google.....if not now when........." Never. MS had their chance. They blew it.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1354500473041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 21:07:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354504245255-77</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU ENJOY BUSH'S TAX CUT? IT WILL BE OVER FOR EVERYBODY. HIGHER TAXES ARE ON THE WAY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354486130302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:08:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems to be the plan.</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1354504245255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:10:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354507194479-78</Id><Title>Turn our subject to special dividend</Title><Msg>Any thoughts.......</Msg><Username>don.roberts86</Username><Timestamp>1354507194479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 22:59:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354508356613-79</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU ENJOY BUSH'S TAX CUT? IT WILL BE OVER FOR EVERYBODY. HIGHER TAXES ARE ON THE WAY.</Title><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354486130302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 17:08:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds good to me. Everybody should be paying for obama's takers.</Msg><Username>penma1</Username><Timestamp>1354508356613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:19:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>