<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356760268713-1</Id><Topic><Title>Congressional Republicans Are About To Get A Good Arsewailing In Obama's Woodshed</Title><Username>click_to_see_lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1356737014807</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:23:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama is probably the best negotiator of all Presidents. " Now, that is truly hilarious. Thanks for the laugh.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1356760268713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 00:51:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356761259349-2</Id><Topic><Title>You see, C-Fury</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1356747305890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:15:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of which might very well be true, but doesn't count as evidence because none of it is verifiable. You might as well have said, This is true because God whispered it in my ear.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1356761259349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 01:07:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356767303584-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Spent All The Money In His Piggy Bank!</Title><Username>don_cornwell</Username><Timestamp>1356748753312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:39:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congress controls the pursestrings #$%$</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356767303584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 02:48:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356767334142-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Spent All The Money In His Piggy Bank!</Title><Username>don_cornwell</Username><Timestamp>1356748753312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:39:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>learn how government works stupid</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356767334142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 02:48:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356767423638-5</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8, Surface and WIndows phones are really selling well</Title><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1356722588095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:23:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>surface isn't selling worth a damn</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356767423638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 02:50:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356768058897-6</Id><Topic><Title>Why is the enterprise dumping Windows and moving to iOS?</Title><Username>dogeater20088</Username><Timestamp>1356665164599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 22:26:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously you cannot read what has been printed for the last several months but then Stupid is as Stupid does</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356768058897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 03:00:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356781639021-7</Id><Topic><Title>Why is the enterprise dumping Windows and moving to iOS?</Title><Username>dogeater20088</Username><Timestamp>1356665164599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 22:26:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would have said ten years, but the Windows 8 trainwreck may force me to change my mind, Maybe 7 or 8 years.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1356781639021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 06:47:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356784911147-8</Id><Topic><Title>You see, C-Fury</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1356747305890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:15:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your "career" consists entirely of posting inane twaddle on this godforsaken message board sixteen to twenty hours a day, every day, for at least the past twelve years. Incompetent CxOs are a dime a dozen, as are message board trolls with delusions of adequacy. Resolve in the upcoming year to extract yourself from bankruptcy (and your soiled adult diaper), charge up your Medicaid financed Hoveround and trundle your smelly butt out of the swamp. Perhaps you'll find a prestigious CEO position replacing the eminent and brilliant Baldie Balmer or Nutmeg Witless to complete the destruction of once-viable companies for excessive compensation.</Msg><Username>nd1005</Username><Timestamp>1356784911147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 07:41:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356787615471-9</Id><Topic><Title>Watch For Potential Topping</Title><Username>ptekqxg1983</Username><Timestamp>1338836753000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-06-04 15:05:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this site.</Msg><Username>stevensherry131</Username><Timestamp>1356787615471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 08:26:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356794945691-10</Id><Topic><Title>'Splain something lefty loonies, if the Bush era tax cuts were a bad idea and do not create jobs</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1356737816516</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:36:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The point is you libs say that the Bush taxes are the cause of the debt and then you say we will go off the cliff if they aren't extending for 98% of tax payers. This is a 12/4 quote from one of you: "Tax cuts under Dubya Bush did nothing to create jobs, increase wages but added $5T to the debt" Is it because you can't make up your minds which it is or do you just not get it??? Actually I know which it is.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1356794945691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:29:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356795581197-11</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft making strong progress in Phones and Tablets</Title><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1356721852142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:10:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The iPad Domination Research firm Chitika measured ad impressions from various manufacturers’ devices in the pre-Christmas week and found that 87 percent of the tablet web traffic in North America was generated by an iPad somewhere. That effectively means that for every 100 iPad impressions, all other tablets combined only have 14.75. Putting it further into context, Venture Beat postulated that for every 100 web page views on an iPad, an Amazon (NASDAQ:AMZN) Kindle Fire gets 4.88, a Samsung (SSNLF.PK) Galaxy gets 3.04, the Google (NASDAQ:GOOG) Nexus gets 1.22, and a Microsoft (NASDAQ:MSFT) Surface gets 0.22.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356795581197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:39:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356795714298-12</Id><Title>We Had A Balanced Budget And Booming Economy With Prez Clinton. When The Wealthy Pay More The Economy Works.</Title><Msg>Obama is doing exactly the right thing for the budget and the economy, the rich MUST pay more. The Grover Norquist snotty brats need to get their buttocks wailed by Obama....INDEED!</Msg><Username>syncophants_suck_koch</Username><Timestamp>1356795714298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:41:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356796691101-13</Id><Title>Windows 8- microsoft's self destruct program</Title><Msg>this bad desktop program needs to be discarded Microsoft doesn't realise it can no longer muscle consumers into using another inferior software product Bill Gates saw this coming and walked away from managingt years ago IMHO</Msg><Username>goaway_hank</Username><Timestamp>1356796691101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:58:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356797995810-14</Id><Title>Windows Surface "PRO"</Title><Msg>will use 3G; does the Windows Surface RT only use dial-up? Sad way to launch your "best" effort.</Msg><Username>twitbum</Username><Timestamp>1356797995810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:19:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356798347043-15</Id><Title>Reality check</Title><Msg>Occasionally it is worthwhile to put something here of substance to refresh the truth in the RWNJ mind so that a touch of doubt about their programmed messages remains. The economy is where it is today due to decades of labor outsourcing to China with the middlemen pocketing the difference between low production costs and slightly low sales prices. Prices set just low enough to run out domestic businesses. This led to the imbalances in wealth that have our economy tied up. The consumers have little money and have lost purchasing power. Business is sitting on record cash but they don't know what to do with it because the public can't afford to buy very much now. The credit fueled boom that some RWNJ seem to believe is the normal state of the economy was a transient event and will not repeat for quite a while. Inflation is a non existent threat because inflation is always due to excess demand setting up wage increases and cannot happen now. The cliff is something both sides want, told ya this months ago.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356798347043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:25:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356798475424-16</Id><Title>i didn't think they could make the message board worse but they did.</Title><Msg>do away with the more,less #$%$ and show the full text.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356798475424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:27:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356800297168-17</Id><Topic><Title>We Had A Balanced Budget And Booming Economy With Prez Clinton. When The Wealthy Pay More The Economy Works.</Title><Username>syncophants_suck_koch</Username><Timestamp>1356795714298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:41:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree! Totally! Let's go over the Fiscal Cliff and 100% do away with Bush Tax Cuts. 100% gone for 100% of everybody! Do away with so called "Payroll Tax Cut which only weakens Social Security! Keep spemding rampatly! Americz will soon be a liberal utopia, just like Detroit!</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1356800297168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:58:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356800380907-18</Id><Topic><Title>We Had A Balanced Budget And Booming Economy With Prez Clinton. When The Wealthy Pay More The Economy Works.</Title><Username>syncophants_suck_koch</Username><Timestamp>1356795714298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:41:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, syncopant! What's wrong with Ed Koch? Good Democrat &amp; long time Mayor of NYC!</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1356800380907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:59:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356800439395-19</Id><Topic><Title>i didn't think they could make the message board worse but they did.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356798475424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hard work can accomplish anyting!</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1356800439395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:00:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356800656222-20</Id><Title>I just ordered a Kindle Fire HD!</Title><Msg>Much less expensive than an iPad or Surface. I read reviews and people who owned both talked about taking thier Kindle Fire HD with them on vacations and such a leaving their iPads, Surfaces &amp; other tablets at home. 90% of the function. Less than 50% the price. Handy mobile size.</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1356800656222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:04:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356801595221-21</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8- microsoft's self destruct program</Title><Username>goaway_hank</Username><Timestamp>1356796691101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:58:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it kills M$.......soon.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1356801595221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:19:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356801986819-22</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8- microsoft's self destruct program</Title><Username>goaway_hank</Username><Timestamp>1356796691101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:58:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forget about Microsoft. I've been using Linux ever since the Vista Fiasco. I'll never pay a penny for another piece of lousy bloated incompatible crapware from Microsoft.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356801986819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:26:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356802146808-23</Id><Topic><Title>I just ordered a Kindle Fire HD!</Title><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1356800656222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, no way I'm paying $499 for a Surface tablet with Windows RT. I won't pay $699 for a Surface Pro with Windows 8 either. The Kindle Fire is the most bang for the buck.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356802146808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:29:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356802215160-24</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Surface "PRO"</Title><Username>twitbum</Username><Timestamp>1356797995810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface Pro is already too late for the holiday season and too late for this quarter's sales numbers.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356802215160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:30:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356802263233-25</Id><Title>Most popular end-user systems of all: Linux</Title><Msg>wwwDOTzdnetDOTcom/2012s-top-five-linux-stories-with-one-big-conclusion-7000009190/ Linux won..... ======================================== 2012 didn't see any single large Linux news story. Instead, we saw many small Linux stories that, when added together, led to Linux becoming the single most important operating system of all. Here's the count-down to the top of the operating system stack. 5) Raspberry Pi is as popular as apple pie People love their polished hardware devices such as the Apple iPad, but some still love do-it-yourself *DIY) gear and nothing says DIY quite so much as the Raspberry Pi. This Linux-powered credit-card sized computer is as bare-bones as it comes, but it still had over 250,000 people on its buyers waiting list before its launch. Months later it's still insanely popular. 4) Gaming moves to Linux People always used to complain about Linux's lack of games. In the next few years they may start complaining about Windows' lack of games. Valve, maker of the popular Steam gaming platform, has announced that since "Windows 8 is a "catastrophe" for PCs, they're moving their games to Linux. Their long-term plan? Make a Linux-powered PC/game device to compete with Xbox 360 and the Sony PlayStation 3. 3) Google puts Chromebook and Google Docs up against Windows 8 and MS Office We used to think that Microsoft would always own the desktop. Then, along came richer Web applications, cloud services, and the dysfunctional Windows 8. Google is taking advantage of all these factors with its partners' ever-cheaper line of Chromebooks and positioning Quickoffice and Google Docs against Microsoft Office. For many people, a Chromebook is all the laptop they need. Google's goal is to give users a cheaper Linux-based solution to Windows and Office. Getting users off legacy Windows systems wont' be easy. On the other hand, Windows 8 requires users to learn a new way to do the same old things, and Google's offerings let them keep using the good old Windows, Icon, Menu, and Pointer (WIMP) interface. I foresee users shifting away from desktop Windows to Chromebook and from Microsoft Office to Google Docs as they retire their Windows XP and 7 PCs. 2) Nexus 7: Linux finally gets a top tablet Many good Linux/Android-powered tablets showed up in 2012, but the best of them all was the Asus/Google Nexus 7. How good was it? While Apple will never admit it, but the only reason we have iPad Minis today is because 7" Android tablets, led by the Nexus 7, forced Apple's to enter the small tablet market. 1) Most popular end-user systems of all: Linux On top of all these other changes, add in the simple fact that the old PC is no longer the heart of computing and what you end up with is a world where the most popular end-user computing devices aren't running Windows, instead they're running Android. Oh, and, this isn't a prediction. It's already happened. According to Goldman Sachs, the "consumer compute market (1.07bn devices) is led by Android at 42% share, followed by Apple at 24%, Microsoft at 20% and other vendors at 14%." It's not just Goldman Sachs, according to Mary Meeker, one of the top analysts around, Apple iOS and Google Android already have 45% of the market to Windows' 35%. So, without an earth-shattering kaboom, but quietly and in hundreds of millions of smartphones, tablets, and, increasingly PCs, Linux has become the top operating system of all. ========================================</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1356802263233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:31:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356802263441-26</Id><Topic><Title>We Had A Balanced Budget And Booming Economy With Prez Clinton. When The Wealthy Pay More The Economy Works.</Title><Username>syncophants_suck_koch</Username><Timestamp>1356795714298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:41:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Clinton had a Surplus in his Pants!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356802263441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:31:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356802413832-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Spent All The Money In His Piggy Bank!</Title><Username>don_cornwell</Username><Timestamp>1356748753312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:39:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is also spending the money in federal employee's piggy banks too, by robbing the Thrift Savings Plan! Where do you think he got the money to run the government for the last 4 years?</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356802413832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:33:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356802538425-28</Id><Topic><Title>Pennies from a new 52 week low...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1356729617719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 16:20:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft will sink even lower as long as Ballmer is running the show. Watch what happens when Microsoft discontinues Windows 7 sales and ends support for XP. It's gonna get even uglier!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356802538425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:35:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356802701822-29</Id><Topic><Title>Congressional Republicans Are About To Get A Good Arsewailing In Obama's Woodshed</Title><Username>click_to_see_lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1356737014807</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 18:23:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope he keeps it up. Truly comical.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1356802701822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:38:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356802851537-30</Id><Topic><Title>fijitsu president disappointed with PC sales</Title><Username>idbtc</Username><Timestamp>1356726350286</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 15:25:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not just Fujitsu. HP, Dell, Asus and Acer are all reporting weak sales. It looks like nobody wants Windows 8 Metro. I sure don't want it. Instead of buying a new Windows 8 PC, I custom built my own PC with an AMD processor, 8gb of RAM, a 128gb SSD and Linux with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356802851537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:40:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356803719974-31</Id><Topic><Title>Most popular end-user systems of all: Linux</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1356802263233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:31:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody has to get stuck with Windows 8 and Metro. Linux is a great alternative Microsoft's crapware. Hundreds of Linux distros are available for FREE. Most distros let you try the 'Live' CD or DVD without installing it first. All you need to do is download the ISO file, burn the disc and boot from the Live OS. Install it if you like or try another if you don't. All you have to lose is a couple of blank discs. Here is a list of the top 15 Linux distros. 1. Linux Mint 2. Mageia 3. Ubuntu 4. Fedora 5. OpenSUSE 6. Debian 7. Arch 8. PCLinuxOS 9. Zorin 10. CentOS 11. Slackware 12. Puppy 13. Snowlinux 14. OS4 15. Lubuntu I recommend Linux Mint. I'm using it right now on my AMD system with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356803719974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:55:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356803851437-32</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8, Surface and WIndows phones are really selling well</Title><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1356722588095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:23:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barely 0.22% market share.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356803851437</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 12:57:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356804148189-33</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8, Surface and WIndows phones are really selling well</Title><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1356722588095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:23:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get #$%$ dead, wally.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1356804148189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:02:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356805721378-34</Id><Title>TO ALL THOSE THAT VOTE REPUBLICANS: A GOOD REASON NOT TO VOTE THEM ANYMORE</Title><Msg>If you earn less than 250.000 dollars a year YOU SHOULD NOT VOTE REPUBLICANS since they do not care about you. If you have your money in the stock market they prefer that we go into the fiscal cliff and you lose a big amount of money. Simply republicans DO NOT CARE ABOUT YOU if your salary is less than 250.000. If you earn more than 1 milion then you should also not vote republicans because they will cause your shares to have a brutal drop. In conclusion, if republicans do not go into an agreement before Monday they should lose most of the power in the next elections. REMIND THIS: NEXT TIME DO NOT VOTE REPUBLICANS.</Msg><Username>newfundinv</Username><Timestamp>1356805721378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:28:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356813367180-35</Id><Topic><Title>TO ALL THOSE THAT VOTE REPUBLICANS: A GOOD REASON NOT TO VOTE THEM ANYMORE</Title><Username>newfundinv</Username><Timestamp>1356805721378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:28:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL Actually if you are concerned about your kids and your grand kids, you shouldn't vote for Democrats who have sold America's prosperity down the drink for votes. What plan do they have for moving the economy? That's right. None. Tax the rich has been their ONLY mantra. To quote someone else: "It is easier to pursue a politial policy of sneaking inAmerica's back door, swiping a laptop,going around to the front door, and announcing. "Free computer equipment for all school children."</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1356813367180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 15:36:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356815105170-36</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8, Surface and WIndows phones are really selling well</Title><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1356722588095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 14:23:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IT wouldn't have jobs if Apple was the OS</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356815105170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 16:05:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356815276428-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Spent All The Money In His Piggy Bank!</Title><Username>don_cornwell</Username><Timestamp>1356748753312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 21:39:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a moronic post considering how the republicans use big business, the Koch brothers etc to fund their races</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1356815276428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 16:07:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356818864974-38</Id><Topic><Title>We Had A Balanced Budget And Booming Economy With Prez Clinton. When The Wealthy Pay More The Economy Works.</Title><Username>syncophants_suck_koch</Username><Timestamp>1356795714298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 10:41:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have a deficit between your ears.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1356818864974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 17:07:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356819229867-39</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Surface "PRO"</Title><Username>twitbum</Username><Timestamp>1356797995810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are either ignorant or a paid shorty. Both are worthless and should be discarded.</Msg><Username>jjking516</Username><Timestamp>1356819229867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 17:13:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356819431192-40</Id><Topic><Title>Reality check</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356798347043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:25:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would ask how printing money makes things more expensive but i don't want to embarrass you. Can you explain it</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356819431192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 17:17:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356820228356-41</Id><Title>reminder of reality check</Title><Msg>Occasionally it is worthwhile to put something here of substance to refresh the truth in the RWNJ mind so that a touch of doubt about their programmed messages remains. The economy is where it is today due to decades of labor outsourcing to China with the middlemen pocketing the difference between low production costs and slightly low sales prices. Prices set just low enough to run out domestic businesses. This led to the imbalances in wealth that have our economy tied up. The consumers have little money and have lost purchasing power. Business is sitting on record cash but they don't know what to do with it because the public can't afford to buy very much now. The credit fueled boom that some RWNJ seem to believe is the normal state of the economy was a transient event and will not repeat for quite a while. Inflation is a non existent threat because inflation is always due to excess demand setting up wage increases and cannot happen now. The cliff is something both sides want, told ya this months ago.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356820228356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 17:30:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356821672138-42</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer needs to come out and Mention Apps Situation</Title><Username>ossweekly</Username><Timestamp>1356675922148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 01:25:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They need to come out with something that is easy to use, not confusing and not so daunting at first sight !!! As a shareholder i am injecting my 2 cents and I sincerely hope they use more common sense rather than technical logic. After all, those that are purchasing products are the average people that have jobs and need to be practical. Apple products garnered alot of audience because of their simplicity, and style and their Apple Store logistics.</Msg><Username>ossweekly</Username><Timestamp>1356821672138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 17:54:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356822590564-43</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Surface "PRO"</Title><Username>twitbum</Username><Timestamp>1356797995810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface RT uses Wi-Fi. Hello, nobody uses dial-up anymore.</Msg><Username>jaceanne_gibson</Username><Timestamp>1356822590564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 18:09:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356823854999-44</Id><Title>LET THEM SAY WHAT THEY WANT....</Title><Msg>Everyone is just waiting on the surface pro.......blah blah blah failure is not even in the cards....</Msg><Username>richeydouglas</Username><Timestamp>1356823854999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 18:30:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356823994750-45</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Surface "PRO"</Title><Username>twitbum</Username><Timestamp>1356797995810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A tablet should be WiFi and also have an ethernet plug-in. It should only be cellular if it's going to be used as a mobile phone. The Samsung ATIV 500T and 700T have both WiFi and ethernet. For instance, a hotel room might have WiFi off the cable TV box but for connection to financial websites go looking for the internet room.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1356823994750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 18:33:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356824433961-46</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Surface "PRO"</Title><Username>twitbum</Username><Timestamp>1356797995810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, the correct price for the Samsung ATIV 500T is $750 including optional keyboard. The correct price for the 700T is $1200 including optional keyboard.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1356824433961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 18:40:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356824788730-47</Id><Topic><Title>Reality check</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356798347043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:25:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You neglected to explain how the money would get to the public after it was printed. I assume you don't really think it would be placed on the street for pick up. Can you elaborate your idea a little further.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356824788730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 18:46:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356826810353-48</Id><Topic><Title>Reality check</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356798347043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:25:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you don't understand how adding more money doesn't make it worth less therefore makiing things more expensive,then there is no hope for you. Too bad Do you really not understand that just printing money adnaseum does'nt cause a problem?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1356826810353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 19:20:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356829141331-49</Id><Topic><Title>Reality check</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356798347043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:25:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did i say that it didn't cause a problem??? good of you to help out your boi</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1356829141331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 19:59:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356831424324-50</Id><Title>Markets may move up 5% on Monday on Fiscal cliff agreement</Title><Msg>Will be interesting. If it falls that i great opportunity to load up. The S&amp;P500 trades at 13 PE vs 16.9 average and based on 105dollars EPS, should be at 1775. Considering 10 year T-bond is at 1.7% the PE could expand to 24 (as it was at prior similar rate periods). i.e. S&amp;P could go up to 2450 but on extreme bullishness when the cliff clears and investors focus on the brightening US recovery. As to Microsoft. It is the best among the lot with 62Billion cash, growing Office and Server business that makes up 80% of profits. Despite some popular press, CEOs of Dell and Lenovo have said Windows 8 demand is strong for touchscreens and in the Enterprise as well. Surface RT (according to Microsoft is beating their own estimates.. all of RT is additional gravy). WIndows phone as we know is growing 300% year over year. MSFT is a $34 to $40 stock</Msg><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1356831424324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 20:37:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356831951588-51</Id><Topic><Title>Markets may move up 5% on Monday on Fiscal cliff agreement</Title><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1356831424324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 20:37:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice pack of pumping lies, shill. MS is sucking wind in mobile, Office is crumbling, and Windows 8 is a dud. MS is going down hard.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1356831951588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 20:45:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356833522549-52</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Surface "PRO"</Title><Username>twitbum</Username><Timestamp>1356797995810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dial-up? WTH are you talking about more-on?</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1356833522549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 21:12:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356837201402-53</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer needs to come out and Mention Apps Situation</Title><Username>ossweekly</Username><Timestamp>1356675922148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 01:25:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ballmer will never admit that Windows 8 is D.O.A.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356837201402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 22:13:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356837449698-54</Id><Topic><Title>Why is the enterprise dumping Windows and moving to iOS?</Title><Username>dogeater20088</Username><Timestamp>1356665164599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 22:26:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft ain't the ONLY game in town! iOS, OS X, Android and Linux are all viable alternatives to Windows 8 Metro.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1356837449698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 22:17:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356838549252-55</Id><Topic><Title>Will Whitebread Mitch McConnell Filibuster?</Title><Username>rush_limpballs_warning</Username><Timestamp>1356743535965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 20:12:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawfaeces ever the ignorant redneck racist has swallowed the koolaide hook line and sinker- sometimes he gives me the eerie feeling he actually is Charles Koch instead of just Charles Koch's a....kisser- anyway with the nations ignorant rednecks all acting like a...kissing serfs like hawfaeces Charlses Koch will be able to take over at long last as the United States' oligarch</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1356838549252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 22:35:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356839846963-56</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Surface "PRO"</Title><Username>twitbum</Username><Timestamp>1356797995810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 11:19:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We don't no stinking penguins.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1356839846963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 22:57:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356839920563-57</Id><Title>Still no links allowed here</Title><Msg>is it a tv consiracy against youtube. I will head back on my own and watch Pet Shop Boys - West End Girls video.</Msg><Username>just_1_more_bing</Username><Timestamp>1356839920563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 22:58:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>