<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345177648000-1</Id><Title>How much market lost to Apple in 2013?</Title><Msg>About 30%!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345177648000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 00:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345180583000-2</Id><Topic><Title>How much market lost to Apple in 2013?</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345177648000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 00:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much market lost due to Windows 8 and 'Metro'? It's gonna get Ugly!</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345180583000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 01:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345181309000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Vista better success than Windows 8?</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345169510000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 22:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5 1/2 years after Vista's release, it barely has 3.4% market share. Vista still sucks! It reached a peak of 18.6% market share in Oct 2009, but NEVER had more market share than XP http://www.w3schools.com/browsers/browsers_os.asp Why? Nobody likes the 'Metro' graphical interface. Users don't like it. Developers don't like it. Manufacturers don't like it. They should really change the name to Windows WTF! Plus, there are plenty of alternatives to Microsoft Windows these days: iPhone, iPad, MacBook, Linux, Android phones and tablets. In fact, Windows alternatives have almost 15% market share as of July 2012. I predict Windows loses even more market share in 2013, thanks to Windows 8 and Metro.</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345181309000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 01:28:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345182307000-4</Id><Title>Top 500 sites on the web</Title><Msg>did you know Bing made it to the first page? http://www.alexa.com/topsites</Msg><Username>just_1_more_bing</Username><Timestamp>1345182307000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 01:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345198127000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8: not doing well</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345160346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 wouldn't be so bad if you could disable 'Metro' graphical interface. Metro will be the deal breaker.</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1345198127000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 06:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345199912000-6</Id><Title>"If you add in what I wrote off..."</Title><Msg>as "charitable deductions" (setting aside for the moment whether or not the amount meets the demands of his cult for 10% of Mitt's accumulating wealth) you could conceive of my tax rate on "reported earned income" as being almost infinite. --W. Mitt Romney; latest B.S. about his tax dodging schemes. Somehow, our favorite "financial wizard" and "economic guru" seems to think that his deductions add to his taxable income. Although he won't actually produce records of his personal finances (probably since they'd necessarily lead to further "retroactive revisions" to his financial disclosures to the FEC) he "assures us" that he thinks that his tax rate was something like 13% of whatever he alleges to have been "income". Since he immediately went to his Glenn Beck approved whiteboard to lie about the Federal implementation of Romneycare, it's easy to chalk up the "13% minimum" claim as being just another Romney lie. Just like his backdated exit from Bain Capital and its various shell corporations specifically constructed for the evasion of taxes, or his "retroactive residency" in the state of Massachusetts that became effective when his prior declarations of residency became an inconveniently disqualifying for the office he sought to abuse.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345199912000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 06:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345200190000-7</Id><Topic><Title>conservative voters by IQ level</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345164745000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 20:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hawfreak weighs in. The "conservative" choice is Wallace / LeMay. Just because you write that in every election (and shell out $3K in precious Confederate scrip to stuff the Floridian ballot box for them) doesn't make a "50%" out of the 24% of the Bushite dead-enders who vote "wastrel" and think they're going to "conserve" something. As a "registered Demoncrate" you should know that, but you fake a misunderstanding under your current alias.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345200190000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 06:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345200205000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Top 500 sites on the web</Title><Username>just_1_more_bing</Username><Timestamp>1345182307000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 01:45:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I notice Google is two of the first three. (Google owns YouTube.) By another ranking, which I was looking at yesterday, the order was: 1. Google 2. Facebook 3. YouTube</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345200205000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 06:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345203607000-9</Id><Title>Does Microsoft Have A Master Plan?</Title><Msg>The first words out of his mouth tell me this is a snow job; the Surface announcement was anything but perfectly executed, as everyone knows. So the rest of the article, by frankly laying out the difficulties Microsoft finds itself in, ends up being negative overall, because we are forewarned that the included positive remarks are not to be relied upon. http://seekingalpha.com/article/813602-does-microsoft-have-a-master-plan?source=yahoo "Does Microsoft Have A Master Plan? August 17, 2012 | about: MSFT, includes: AAPL, DELL, GOOG, HP, NOK Jared Sleeper "The perfectly executed Surface announcement earlier this summer marked a clear inflection point for Microsoft (MSFT). Most prominently, Microsoft abandoned its long held strategy of producing software and leaving the hardware to a diverse ecosystem of OEMs, including industry titans like Dell (DELL) and HP (HPQ) who built major businesses on hardware side of this model. With the Surface's design work performed in house and its Windows branding, Microsoft couldn't have more clearly redefined the paradigm in which its software is consumed, and if it thought OEMs would buy its lip service to the contrary it is now learning the hard way that they see the writing on the wall. Apple (AAPL) has single handedly shown the value of an integrated hardware and software product ecosystem (to the tune of hundreds of billions of dollars) and Microsoft now appears set to create its own version, with Windows 8 integrating the full spectrum of devices from phones to tablets to PCs in an environment of increasing Microsoft hardware control. (The new laptops released by Vizio are another manifestation of this trend.) "Though the hardware element was surprising to many, integrating people's lives into a tight, self contained Microsoft ecosystem has been a goal of the company for most of the past decade, from its ill-fated Live social network to it's failed attempt to force Bing down the throats of internet users who are quite content with Google (GOOG). The thing is, it's never worked. Windows Phones and Tablets (the two fastest growing device categories by far) are footnotes, with market shares of less than 3.5%. The Zune, recently discontinued (along with the rest of its device category, another victim of smartphones), never caught traction despite its shared heritage with what is still the world's dominant operating system. Overall, the general public seems to have bought into a view of Microsoft as old, stodgy, and incapable of doing almost anything right. A decade of cheap plastic hardware, compared with Apple's rigidly controlled (and, well, rigid) lines of beautifully designed gadgets has cemented this perception, and Apple's brutally effective "I'm a Mac" advertising campaign nailed the message home like the best of political attack ads. Many observers, myself included, saw a dim future for Microsoft ahead, built around its still wildly profitable enterprise solutions and with declining or stagnant market share in almost everything consumer. ... "... There are barriers, to be sure, including heavily cast perceptions about Microsoft and somewhat lackluster early reviews of the OS at the core of it all, but there are also billions of dollars, a great product and a company with lots of strengths that should never be counted out. They also know better than anyone that if Surface fails from a sales perspective their future in the consumer space is effectively decided. I'm not certain it'll all work, but I have a strong feeling that Microsoft is about to successfully shake things up across the entire tech space, and I'm impressed enough by what I've seen so far to bet on it. "Disclosure: I am long MSFT."</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345203607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345203944000-10</Id><Topic><Title>conservative voters by IQ level</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345164745000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 20:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny thing is to ask him what he likes or ever did like about the democratic platform and wait for an answer.. and wait ... and wait...</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345203944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:45:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345204407000-11</Id><Topic><Title>"Windows 8 review: Yes, it's that bad"</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1345076696000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 20:24:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;suck&lt; Ahhhh... Walleye's favorite subject and the only one he's qualified to post about from firsthand personal experience.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1345204407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345206579000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Does Microsoft Have A Master Plan?</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345203607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wotopimp where do you find these crap propaganda pieces They are always the same and may even be the same author under a psuedonym doing his best to bash Microsoft even tho his sophomoric observations are so transparant that every one recognizes he is simply pumping out crap to get readers by attacking the dominant IT vendor-never mind the quality of the articles Its probably time for you to find a high paying used car lot to go work for and give up bashing</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345206579000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 08:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345206720000-13</Id><Topic><Title>"Windows 8 review: Yes, it's that bad"</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1345076696000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 20:24:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>phands it would appear that you hold the honors as the most experienced Windows 8 user what with your pronouncements - to the effect that W-8 will bring about the end of civilization kind of like the fall of the Roman Empire eh?</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345206720000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 08:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345206805000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8: not doing well</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345160346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt; &gt;&gt;grok&gt;&gt; the most asinine excuse for a word that has been invented in all of recorded history- I guess its sort of an inside word that the suxers used to use&gt; As usual, the wally bot has nothing to say on topic. You guessed wrong. The word comes from "Stranger in a Strange Land" by Robert Heinlein.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345206805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 08:33:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345207248000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8: not doing well</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345160346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like I said wotop grok has to be the most asinine word ever invented in all of recorded history....</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345207248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 08:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345207669000-16</Id><Topic><Title>"Windows 8 review: Yes, it's that bad"</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1345076696000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 20:24:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rough night on the waterfront last night there phands maybe you should give up the sailor bois and stick with Father Murphy - you could still be his own precious alter boi</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345207669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 08:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345207777000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Does Microsoft Have A Master Plan?</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345203607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does Microsoft Have A Master Plan? Definately! A whistle blower told me W8 will emit sound waves or oscillations that will kill penquins on contact.</Msg><Username>mr_graymatter</Username><Timestamp>1345207777000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 08:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345207822000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Does Microsoft Have A Master Plan?</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345203607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you dont qualify phands with your 70 IQ...oh thats minus 70 IQ</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345207822000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 08:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345208742000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8: not doing well</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345160346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I said, you guessed wrong. If you weren't illiterate, you would have known where it came from.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345208742000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345209427000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Does Microsoft Have A Master Plan?</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345203607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I found this article on the Seeking Alpha site, as you would know if you weren't illiterate. It was among the articles cited by Yahoo in the Headlines section of the Microsoft Finance pages.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345209427000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345209500000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Does Microsoft Have A Master Plan?</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345203607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;Definately&gt; A misspelling favored by trailer trash...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345209500000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345209757000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Does Microsoft Have A Master Plan?</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345203607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so pimp when you going to take me up on my suggestion eh</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345209757000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345209944000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8: not doing well</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345160346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in the end its source and use is only a little more honorable than the crooks who utilized it in their project to abet the thief Torvalds</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345209944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 09:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345212186000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8: not doing well</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345160346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You insist on demonstrating your illiteracy over and over and over. Not to mention that you are not capable of learning anything at all, because you didn't learn anything from SCO's utter failure to prove ANY of its claims after trying for many years, or even bring forth any evidence at all supporting them, and its eventual ignominious bankruptcy.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345212186000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:03:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345212313000-25</Id><Title>Windows 8 tablets to be lots cheaper than Ipads or droids</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/theres-really-good-chance-windows-133400880.html</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345212313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345212356000-26</Id><Title>Hi folks, is Apple up. Taking over TV industry like it did the mobile industry, 1000 soom</Title><Msg>.......</Msg><Username>koubaro_dimitrios</Username><Timestamp>1345212356000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345212441000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8: not doing well</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345160346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Torvalds belongs in prison wotopimp- and that makes you an aider and abettor</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345212441000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345212528000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Hi folks, is Apple up. Taking over TV industry like it did the mobile industry, 1000 soom</Title><Username>koubaro_dimitrios</Username><Timestamp>1345212356000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>koubaro it would be a good day to get your shorts on AAPL and GOOG in dont get caught with your pants down again like you did last year</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345212528000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345212748000-29</Id><Title>Apple to 1000 before MSFT holds 30. LOLOLOL</Title><Msg>This will happen especially if the Apple TV and content agreement are analogous to the mobile music industry</Msg><Username>koubaro_dimitrios</Username><Timestamp>1345212748000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:12:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345212797000-30</Id><Topic><Title>The fastest way to make money trading has arrived!</Title><Username>gorihfna1118</Username><Timestamp>1345204025000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:47:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FREE SPAM - GOODBY MONEY</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1345212797000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345212895000-31</Id><Topic><Title>stock indicators</Title><Username>grenvillekak243</Username><Timestamp>1345179155000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 00:52:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UGLY SPAM - FROM YOUR SPAMMER GANG OF THEIVES.</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1345212895000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345215075000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 tablets to be lots cheaper than Ipads or droids</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345212313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:05:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cheaper than dirt, I hear.</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345215075000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345215592000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 tablets to be lots cheaper than Ipads or droids</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345212313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:05:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have to be, otherwise they won't sell.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345215592000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:59:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345216128000-34</Id><Title>Quick and easy money trading Microsoft Corporation! Find out how!</Title><Msg>How do I know which stocks to buy and when to sell? Find out more here. HTTP://WWW.TRADINGPENNYSTOCKSPROFITS.INFO</Msg><Username>munsellepiib6934</Username><Timestamp>1345216128000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345216185000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Help for Trading</Title><Username>curciofki633</Username><Timestamp>1345214350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:39:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THIS SPAMMER IS BEYOND HELP -</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1345216185000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345216603000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Quick and easy money trading Microsoft Corporation! Find out how!</Title><Username>munsellepiib6934</Username><Timestamp>1345216128000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:08:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IGNORE - SPAMMER MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1345216603000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345218007000-37</Id><Topic><Title>conservative voters by IQ level</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345164745000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 20:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at Romney, he looks like a President should look. That's why I will vote for Romney.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345218007000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 11:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345219543000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Even More Stunning Obama Corruption....</Title><Username>general_squalor</Username><Timestamp>1345215055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:50:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't get any reaction because people expect this from our incumbent gangland administration.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1345219543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345219661000-39</Id><Title>Apple at all time highs, MSFT at early 2000s level .LOLOLOLO</Title><Msg>.................</Msg><Username>koubaro_dimitrios</Username><Timestamp>1345219661000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345219775000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8: not doing well</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345160346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>b52boomer hey man you are really skillful at parroting basher bullsh.t arent you</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345219775000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:09:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345219903000-41</Id><Title>Apple: Cloud-baded DVR-TV. Wow. Time to dominate the TV industry next..</Title><Msg>...............</Msg><Username>koubaro_dimitrios</Username><Timestamp>1345219903000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345220955000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 tablets to be lots cheaper than Ipads or droids</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345212313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:05:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt; Windows 8 tablets to be lots cheaper than Ipads or droids &lt; That will be directly proportional to the degree of inferiority of the MS product compared to the Apple and Android offerings. ...it's to be expected...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1345220955000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345221178000-43</Id><Title>After all these years</Title><Msg>of using IE browsers, I finally gave up trying to fix slow and glitchy website loading through IE fixes and switched over to Firefox. The loading problems vanished! Just like buying a new computer with double the RAM. Dumbly resisted for so long but now see the light everyone told me about. Will go all Apple next. Finished with Mr. Softie and its crummy products forever. Am I the last one to switch?</Msg><Username>bobbobwhite</Username><Timestamp>1345221178000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345221464000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 tablets to be lots cheaper than Ipads or droids</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345212313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:05:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares, people will buy iPads and Androids, its all about the name folks. Iphones are very pricey but still selling like hot cakes.</Msg><Username>ventral_medial_man</Username><Timestamp>1345221464000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:37:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345221826000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Check it out, Microsoft: best of both worlds</Title><Username>flytrysk</Username><Timestamp>1345132063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:47:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now would be a good time to consider strong Europe-based companies.</Msg><Username>maine.man57</Username><Timestamp>1345221826000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345221921000-46</Id><Topic><Title>conservative voters by IQ level</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345164745000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 20:52:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So ur a DINO. Nice ....</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1345221921000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345224479000-47</Id><Topic><Title>Chart Video Analysis</Title><Username>lacy_moises65</Username><Timestamp>1345221134000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:32:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IGNORE - SPAMMER MALWAR SPAM VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1345224479000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345227395000-48</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;Onward and upward to 1000 posts!&gt; We're already well over 1/3 of the way there...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345227395000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345227808000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Market up 700+ points in 3 weeks</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345225412000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:43:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our Stimulus $$ - Tax $$ GS knows when to run up the MKT.</Msg><Username>free2491</Username><Timestamp>1345227808000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345230665000-50</Id><Title>New Analysis on Microsoft Corporation Suggests Drop</Title><Msg>Wow! Microsoft Corporation is not looking good right now. MUST READ! http://WWW.FREESTOCKPICKINGSOFTWARE.INFO</Msg><Username>dennatalaska</Username><Timestamp>1345230665000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:11:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345231554000-51</Id><Title>Ryan's spending votes get a second look</Title><Msg>Ryan in his 14 years in Congress has voted for pricey intiatives, as Politico notes, like the Bush-era tax cuts, the $700 billion bank bailout, the expansion of Medicare and the highway bill that included the notorious "Bridge to Nowhere." http://www.cbsnews.com/8301-503544_162-57495402-503544/paul-ryans-spending-votes-get-a-second-look/?tag=cbsContent;cbsCarousel</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1345231554000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345231681000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla Model S Relies On Linux</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345044259000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:24:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must mean the one by Fucik, not Khachaturian. Thanks for the tip. Tracking down the source of things has always been a passion of mine, it didn't start with software, though that's where it ended up. Never knew where the circus march came from.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345231681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345231884000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8: not doing well</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345160346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Gates is, in a manner of speaking, flushing his money down the toilet. His charitable organisation, the Bill &amp; Melinda Gates Foundation, is looking for future loos that can improve sanitation around the world. At the Reinvent the Toilet fair, hosted at its Seattle campus this week, designs included a lavatory that used microwave energy to turn poo into electricity. It will convert Windows Software into methane and dust which has the potential to save trillions of dollars worldwide.</Msg><Username>der_schpountz</Username><Timestamp>1345231884000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:31:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345232418000-54</Id><Title>More skunks to ignore</Title><Msg>More skunks: phands.theapostate58 phands.yourheretic phands.theheretical phandstheheretic deep.buttthrust phands.theheretic hands_theheretic phands_heretical2 paulh.heretic phands_is_a_heretic predisposable_nym_01 henkepek phands.apostate58 phands.theheretic2 phands.theheretical4</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1345232418000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 15:40:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345234299000-55</Id><Title>university bubble will burst</Title><Msg>not enough balance.</Msg><Username>swingingparrot_llllllll</Username><Timestamp>1345234299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345234404000-56</Id><Title>Apple is ON FIRE! $606 Billion Market Cap is Here</Title><Msg>That's about what MSFT market cap was, at its peak in 1999. http://wallstcheatsheet.com/stocks/apple-is-off-the-charts.html/?ref=YF Apple is ON FIRE! $606 Billion Market Cap is Here By Aabha Rathee | More Articles August 17, 2012 Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) touched a record stock price high of $648.19 on Friday afternoon after an analyst note to investors said the company had put the rumored iPad Mini tablet as well as a new full-fledged television set into production. The previous high for Apple shares was $644, which came on April 10.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1345234404000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:13:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345235873000-57</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8: not doing well</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345160346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:39:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey -- es ist der Scheiskopf mit sein Bill Gatesisches verhasst villeicht?</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345235873000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345236622000-58</Id><Topic><Title>Even More Stunning Obama Corruption....</Title><Username>general_squalor</Username><Timestamp>1345215055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:50:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In late July, John Hynansky — a longtime friend of Vice President Joe Biden, and a major donor to Biden’s campaigns as well as President Barack Obama’s — was awarded a $20 million taxpayer loan to build a foreign-car dealership in Ukraine. According to a public summary document, the loan, from the federal government’s Overseas Private Investment Corporation, is for “[u]p to $20.0 million,” and is designed to “expand Winner Import Ukraine’s automobile business, [and] construct and operate ‘Winner Autocity,’ which will have two new, state-of-the-art dealership facilities for Porsche and Land Rover/Jaguar automobiles.” Porsche is a German-made luxury and sports car, and Jaguar Land Rover is a British luxury and sports car company owned by an Indian subsidiary. Under “U.S. Economic Impact,” the summary document says, “This project will have a positive developmental impact on the host country, Ukraine. The project will generate a significant number of new local jobs. Running a dealership for premium automobile brands requires a highly trained sales force, mechanics, accountants, communications and advertising specialists, IT specialists, service personnel, warehouse managers, and customer relations specialists.” Along with his family, Hynansky also owns car dealerships in Pennsylvania and Biden’s home state of Delaware. Since at least 1999, Hynansky and his family have been regular donors to Biden’s campaigns, and, later, Obama’s. John Hynansky has donated $7,690 to a combination of Biden’s Senate campaigns and failed presidential campaign; Michael Hynansky donated $7,690; Alexandra Hynansky donated $7,280; Deanne Hynansky donated $4,645; and Susan Hynansky donated $1,000 — coming to a total family donation of $28,715. During Obama’s 2008 run for president, John Hynansky gave $30,800 to the Obama Victory Fund; Alexandra Hynansky gave $2,550; and Deanne Hynansky gave $2,000 — totaling $35,350 to that campaign. Read more: http://dailycaller.com/2012/08/17/bidens-good-friend-donor-receives-20m-federal-loan/#ixzz23q3matPV</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345236622000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345236881000-59</Id><Topic><Title>Even More Stunning Obama Corruption....</Title><Username>general_squalor</Username><Timestamp>1345215055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:50:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how does it feel to a Gdam liar there golfer?? because thats what you are- so what if a guy gets a loan to start a business using the OPIC? It is 100% legal Looks to me like you are guilty of criminal libel there golfer-- scumbucket</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1345236881000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345242542000-60</Id><Title>Obamacare health care redistribution</Title><Msg>Take money paid into Medicare for seniors, then redistribute the initial $700 Billion to young welfare folks.</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345242542000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 18:29:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345243456000-61</Id><Title>Ryan now says he requested stimulus funds</Title><Msg>Paul Ryan now says his office requested stimulus funds After initially denying he had requested stimulus funds, GOP vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan has acknowledged that his office had sought the money for his Wisconsin congressional district and took responsibility for it. “After having these letters called to my attention I checked into blah....blah....blah" http://www.latimes.com/news/politics/la-pn-paul-ryan-now-says-his-office-requested-stimulus-funds-20120817,0,1393813.story Right wing tea party misanthropes lie from both sides of their mouths and out their anus.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1345243456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 18:44:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345243713000-62</Id><Title>$607 Billion!</Title><Msg>Not MSFT!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345243713000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 18:48:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345243819000-63</Id><Title>Only 42% the value of Apple</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345243819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 18:50:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345243918000-64</Id><Title>iPhone unit has more revenue &amp; profit than MSFT!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345243918000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 18:51:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345245719000-65</Id><Title>The Hawfreak collective's favorite pollster...</Title><Msg>has Romney dropping like a rock. http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/obama_administration/daily_presidential_tracking_poll/ (Hopefully you have a media blocker turned on.) Bad session at the dart board. Perhaps the next batch of random numbers will work out better.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345245719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345246130000-66</Id><Topic><Title>The Hawfreak collective's favorite pollster...</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345245719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It must be the Bilderburger / Illuminati conspiracy Mitt "Glenn Beck" Romney was mapping out on his whiteboard.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345246130000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:28:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345246309000-67</Id><Topic><Title>Even More Stunning Obama Corruption....</Title><Username>general_squalor</Username><Timestamp>1345215055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:50:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba and a lot of his clowns going to jail.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345246309000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345246394000-68</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama uses racist phrase</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345245213000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:13:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>George Wilcken Romney July 8, 1907 Colonia Dublán, Galeana, Chihuahua, Mexico Perhaps Mitt is even worse, Louie Gomert should be contacted to investigate whether Mitt Romney is a "Terror Baby". I'm sure that Paul Ryan is just playing along to lull Mitt into a sense of false security before the SEAL team takes him out. Can't have Terror Babies trying to take over the U.S.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345246394000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:33:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345246493000-69</Id><Topic><Title>Even More Stunning Obama Corruption....</Title><Username>general_squalor</Username><Timestamp>1345215055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:50:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even if this was an OPIC loan a luxury car dealership hardly fits the description of industry that OPIC claims to encourage in foreign markets. They must have been thin on applications this year. OPIC allegedly promotes business that promote a positive developemental effect for other countries. Will the 99% please explain how the benefit to one american businessman (Biden's buddy) helps the american and Eukraine social and economic environment by providing high buck cars to a few (and likely corrupt) wealthy Eastern Europeans?</Msg><Username>truescoundrel</Username><Timestamp>1345246493000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345246615000-70</Id><Title>Hawfreak is a "typical nit-wit".</Title><Msg>It doesn't even matter that he's racially mixed between pond scum and sewer effluvia. Maybe he'll get out of the shack this weekend to party with the boys: http://i.telegraph.co.uk/multimedia/archive/00795/ku-klux-klan_795316c.jpg</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345246615000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345246629000-71</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan now says he requested stimulus funds</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1345243456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 18:44:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;Paul Ryan now says his office requested stimulus funds After initially denying he had requested stimulus funds, GOP vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan has acknowledged that his office had sought the money for his Wisconsin congressional district and took responsibility for it.&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt; In other words only AFTER Ryan got caught in another lie did he admit requesting stimulus.</Msg><Username>rush_limpballs_warning</Username><Timestamp>1345246629000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345247137000-72</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan: Mitt Romney's VP Pick Used Racist Term In 2011</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1345245006000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:10:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamanurist in action!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345247137000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345247295000-73</Id><Title>Mitt Romney: baldfaced liar.</Title><Msg>Boston Globe June 13, 2002: Romney had told a "baldfaced lie" when he originally told reporters he filed income tax returns as a resident of Massachusetts when living in Utah. Romney later acknowledged he had not filed as a resident, but Amended those Returns to claim resident status after he decided to run for governor. The New York Times: June 19, 2002 Until early June, Mr. Romney had said that he had paid his taxes as a Massachusetts resident while in Utah. He later acknowledged that in 1999 and 2000 he paid state taxes as a Utah resident and listed himself as either a part-time resident or a non-resident of Massachusetts. He said that in April, after deciding to run for governor, he had amended his 1999 and 2000 tax returns to say that he was a Massachusetts resident.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345247295000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:48:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345247333000-74</Id><Title>Lots of Obamanure shoveled on this board!</Title><Msg>I love it!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345247333000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345247378000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney: baldfaced liar.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345247295000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:48:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One more Obamanurist in action!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345247378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345247738000-76</Id><Topic><Title>The Hawfreak collective's favorite pollster...</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345245719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Inaccurate? His darts are loaded? With "Demoncrateic" support such as yours our post-racial President should be about eight or nine points ahead just like Fox news found he is? **** Fox News Poll conducted by Anderson Robbins Research (D) and Shaw &amp; Company Research (R). Aug. 5-7, 2012. N=930 registered voters nationwide. Margin of error 3%. 2010: Conducted by Opinion Dynamics Corp. Obama 49 Romney 40 **** And that was before the negative Ryan "bounce" that Rasmussen finds to have made another five percentage point deficit for Romney. Wow, team evil is suck'n some nasty tailpipe. Maybe they need a new bus.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345247738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345248092000-77</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan: Mitt Romney's VP Pick Used Racist Term In 2011</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1345245006000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:10:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't believe "anchor babies" cost money"?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345248092000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345248166000-78</Id><Title>Stonewalling Day 18: Where's my chicken foot?</Title><Msg>After laying aside doubts about his ability to lie about his income taxes (trust me, Mass residents have already been quite impressed by his prowess) Mitt Beck goes to his favorite whiteboard to draw out the conspiracy for us. Kenya, British colony &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; Anti-Colonialism == Socialism &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; Mao sleeping with Stalin fathering Obamneycare &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; Hawaii was sort of British Colony once &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; Hawaii == Kenya &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; Obama =+ Kenyan Hawaii Devil Stalin Baby Userper! Q. E. D. Charlie Sheen has nothing on this guy. Charlie's "sister wives" are older than Mitt's too.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345248166000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:02:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345248282000-79</Id><Title>Where are all the pictures of dead soldiers</Title><Msg>coming back from Afghanistan? I saw them in the Bush admin. but don't see them now. Hypocrites!!!</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1345248282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345248364000-80</Id><Title>Mitt "Chicken foot" Romney spells it all out.</Title><Msg>http://upload.democraticunderground.com/imgs/home/120817-romney-does-the-math.jpg</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345248364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345248448000-81</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan now says he requested stimulus funds</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1345243456000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 18:44:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt;Paul Ryan now says his office requested stimulus funds After initially denying he had requested stimulus funds, GOP vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan has acknowledged that his office had sought the money for his Wisconsin congressional district and took responsibility for it.&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt; &gt;In other words only AFTER Ryan got caught in another lie did he admit requesting stimulus. &lt;&lt; RYAN IS A LIAR AND HYPOCRITE!</Msg><Username>hi_speed_jebus_motors</Username><Timestamp>1345248448000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:07:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345248750000-82</Id><Topic><Title>Stonewalling day 1343, where are the transcripts?</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345248354000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:05:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps he's a secret Papist, sent to undermine our Jeffersonian Freedoms! Maybe he didn't write that "what I did over the Summer" assignment in fifth grade. Perhaps Hawfreak didn't ever run a "successful construction company" and only posts regurgitated right-wing spew on an obscure financial message board twelve to sixteen hours a day (except during campaign season when it's more like eighteen to twenty hours). On the other hand, there's no question that Mitt Romney paid ZERO Federal income and capital gains taxes from the year 1999 up to the year 2009. That's why Hawfreak and his wingnut klavern is soooooo desperate to try to make some kind of distraction as Mitt makes an idiot out of himself.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345248750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:12:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345248963000-83</Id><Topic><Title>Obama incompetent bald faced liar</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345248562000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The definition of a Hawfreak. Desperate wingnut Taffy A-Hole.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345248963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:16:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345249247000-84</Id><Topic><Title>Leftist welfare bums don't get it's Ryan's job</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345247253000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:47:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the law. They forced him to do it. Fortunately, Mitt Romney wasn't ripped off by Paul Ryan grabbing pork to advance his political career. It's only us "little people" who pay taxes anyway (and at a higher percentage rate than mulch-millionare Paul Ryan).</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345249247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:20:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345250637000-85</Id><Title>Ryan Lied About Taking Stimulus Money</Title><Msg>Paul Ryan now says his office requested stimulus funds After initially denying he had requested stimulus funds, GOP vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan has acknowledged that his office had sought the money for his Wisconsin congressional district and took responsibility for it. http://www.latimes.com/news/politics/la-pn-paul-ryan-now-says-his-office-requested-stimulus-funds-20120817,0,1393813.story WHY DID RYAN LIE ABOUT TAKING STIMULUS?</Msg><Username>hi_speed_jebus_motors</Username><Timestamp>1345250637000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345250846000-86</Id><Title>Is It OK To Game The System?</Title><Msg>Billionaires have the means to game the system due to Cayman Isl, Swiss, Bahama off shore accounts. Romney gamed the system and paid "no less than 13%" he claims. But he won't release his returns so he can lie without verification. I paid 23%. WTF??</Msg><Username>the_jebus_machine</Username><Timestamp>1345250846000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345251977000-87</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Lied About Taking Stimulus Money</Title><Username>hi_speed_jebus_motors</Username><Timestamp>1345250637000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much Obamanure do you take in every day?</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345251977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345252275000-88</Id><Topic><Title>American Heritage Dictionary added an entry</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1345248718000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They also added another definition for Obamanure addicts, they are Obamanurists.</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345252275000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:11:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345252649000-89</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt "Chicken foot" Romney spells it all out.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345248364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:06:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A great Obamanure site! They shovel it out with bulldozers!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345252649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345252866000-90</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan: Mitt Romney's VP Pick Used Racist Term In 2011</Title><Username>hawcraper</Username><Timestamp>1345245006000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:10:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about that an Obamanurist and ignoramus at the same time! The definition of a liberal!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345252866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345252989000-91</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney: baldfaced liar.</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345247295000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:48:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two Obamanurists on this post!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345252989000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345253115000-92</Id><Topic><Title>Lots of Obamanure shoveled on this board!</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345247333000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump it for the Obamanure so far!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345253115000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345253641000-93</Id><Topic><Title>Only 42% the value of Apple</Title><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345243819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 18:50:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump up the MSFT failure!</Msg><Username>obadidosss</Username><Timestamp>1345253641000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345254154000-94</Id><Topic><Title>Help for Trading</Title><Username>curciofki633</Username><Timestamp>1345214350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:39:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its Useful</Msg><Username>joseymks126</Username><Timestamp>1345254154000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345255330000-95</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Lied About Taking Stimulus Money</Title><Username>hi_speed_jebus_motors</Username><Timestamp>1345250637000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:43:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His signature is on he requests for stimulus money. So he allows papers signed by himself to be used without his approval? That's no good. It's all bs, the gop will spend and stimulate and spend some more, plus start a new war, just like they did last time. All bs they spew.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345255330000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345256010000-96</Id><Topic><Title>Hawfreak is a "typical nit-wit".</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1345246615000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:36:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is he still talkng about Obama saying his GRANDMOTHER is "a typical white woman"? He thinks that's racism, he attempts to say Obama is a racist on that. I probably have said that about my mother a number of times, in some setting, rest her soul dying in 1988. I don't think I am a racist toward my own mother. So you are kind in saying hawfreaky is a typical nit wit.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1345256010000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:13:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345257625000-97</Id><Topic><Title>Obama incompetent bald faced liar</Title><Username>hawcreek10</Username><Timestamp>1345248562000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's one thing everyone can agree on ... that Obama is an incompetent bald faced liar. Some LWNJs would argue about other matters but even they know in their hearts that Obama is an incompetent bald faced liar.</Msg><Username>reasonableme53</Username><Timestamp>1345257625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>