<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344605507000-1</Id><Topic><Title>What a great week for me!</Title><Username>tpeter299</Username><Timestamp>1344600943000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 08:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1344605507000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:31:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344606946000-2</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;Linux dominates&gt;&gt; linsux dominates my a.s s! Windows dominates and grosses more than 50 billion and nets more than 15 billion a year to prove it- what does sux do?? you got to be dumber than the dumbest jack a s.s clouseau- come to think of it thats why they call you inspector clouseau</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1344606946000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344607162000-3</Id><Title>Digia swoops as Nokia unloads open source Qt platform</Title><Msg>The agricultural equivalent of this would be to eat your seed corn. It means having something to eat this year by guaranteeing that you will starve next year. This is the last extremity of desperation. http://www.itproportal.com/2012/08/10/digia-swoops-as-nokia-unloads-open-source-qt-platform/ Digia swoops as Nokia unloads open source Qt platform by Angela Moscaritolo, 10 August, 2012 Nokia has unloaded its open-source development platform Qt. The company announced yesterday it had sold Qt to Finland-based software services firm Digia. Financial terms of the acquisition were not disclosed. In a statement, Digia said it plans to "quickly enable" Qt for Android, iOS, and Windows 8 devices. The company said it intends to strengthen Qt's research and development capabilities, and expand its reach on many platforms. "By adding this world class organisation to our existing team we plan to build the next generation leading cross-platform development environment," Tommi Laitinen, senior vice president of international products at Digia, said in a statement. "Now is a good time for everyone to revisit their perception of Qt. Digia's targeted R&amp;D investments will bring back focus on Qt's desktop and embedded platform support, while widening the support for mobile operating systems." Pronounced "cute," Qt allows developers to write code for Windows, Mac, and Linux environments. A number of popular programs have been written in Qt, such as Google Earth, Skype, and the KDE interface used in Linux. It currently offers mobile development support for Symbian, Nokia's N9, and Windows Phone. Nokia acquired Qt back in 2008 from its original developers, Trolltech. But since Nokia shifted its smartphone strategy away from Qt in favor of Microsoft's Windows Phone, the future of the platform has been in question. Nokia last year denied that Qt was dead, but later said there would be no Qt for Windows Phone 7.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1344607162000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:59:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344607195000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Hurry Time Is Ticking`</Title><Username>eamonawd375</Username><Timestamp>1344605440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMMER MALWARE VIRUS LINKS - BEWARE</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1344607195000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344607431000-5</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;thats why they call you inspector clouseau&gt; They? Only you call him that.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1344607431000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 10:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344607577000-6</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;what does sux do?&gt; What is sux? Never heard of it.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1344607577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 10:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344608308000-7</Id><Title>Nokia to reveal first Windows Phone 8</Title><Msg>http://www.xbitlabs.com/news/mobile/display/20120807230146_Nokia_to_Reveal_First_Windows_Phone_8_Smartphones_at_Nokia_World_Report.html Nokia Corp. is expected to reveal its first Windows Phone 8-based smartphones in early September at its Nokia World event. The move will enable the company to demonstrate its next-gen cell phones ahead of Apple's introduction of new iPhone rumoured to happen in mid-September, which is important as the Windows Phone 8 operating system is in many ways comparable to the iOS 6. "We understand from people familiar with the situation that Nokia will be introducing [its Windows Phone 8 phone] before the iPhone [5] comes out," said Tom Giles, a correspondent for Bloomberg TV news in a report. Back in July, chief exec of Nokia, Stephen Elop, implied that the WP 8 smartphones would become available in October, but did not elaborate. Since Nokia has a number of privileges in the Windows Phone ecosystem, it may have an opportunity to show off its WP8-based phone earlier than the others. Moreover, Nokia last month also hinted at "something amazing" that was going to happen on September 7, 2012. The "amazing" campaign was "enriched" with a QR code that led to Nokia Graffiti Me web-site. Nokia World will take place in Helsinki, Finland, on September 5-6, 2012. It is widely believed that Microsoft Windows Phone 8 platform will be comparable with Apple iOS 6 when it comes to feature-set. Although the WP8 will still not be able to march the iOS with the number of apps, it will have capabilities that will bridge smartphones with personal computers, game consoles and media tablets, something which Windows Phone 7 and 7.5 failed to do. Therefore, it is important to show off Windows Phone 8-powered handsets ahead of Apple iOS 6 and Apple iPhone 5 so that to impress the general public.</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1344608308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 10:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344610428000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Corporation is showing historic technical movement</Title><Username>averybackstrom</Username><Timestamp>1344608948000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 10:29:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More craopla spammer malware virus links - beware and ignore</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1344610428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 10:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344611144000-9</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;So is that a nes or a yo? Because it doesn't answer the question with either a yes or a no.&lt; Question? What question? ----------------------------------------------------- &gt;What it *implies* is that they never bothered because of the lack of a market.&lt; Implies? It's a fact. ""For us, it's not about some exotic supercomputers that are available to a small amount of users," he added. "We're really interested in the bottom 500,000 computing users." (TOMSHAREWARE) ---------------------------------------------------- &gt;And they sell that product, to the few folks interested in it, Few folks? "We're really interested in the bottom 500,000 computing users." is more than a few. (TOMSHAREWARE) ---------------------------------------------------- &gt;on the page that I have been showing you since you first started saying they don't make it&lt; LIAR I never said they did'nt make it! You did! Post a link to prove your below LIE! inspector: "he always says that there are only 500 supercomputers {(o8[&gt;-| } and that M$ doesn't offer the HPC packages that they advertise and sell on their website because supercomputers can't be made to any standard that would allow commercial software to be used on it." ---------------------------------------------------- &gt;By saying that they _want_ to cater to some market that isn't the supercomputer market&lt; Repetitive but I'll answer. ""We're really interested in the bottom 500,000 computing users." (TOMSHAREWARE) ------------------------------------------------------ &gt;but is a personal supercomputer niche market&lt; Niche? 500,000 to just 500 WORLD CLASS SUPERCOMPUTERS? IDIOT..!! ------------------------------------------------------ &gt;Here is the Tom's Hardware page: It says absolutely nothing about personal class supercomputers." So? "We're really interested in the bottom 500,000 computing users." (TOMSHAREWARE) Find out what a "personal class supercomputer" is, then report back here. Bing Search "personal class supercomputers",,,IDIOT! Bing gets 1,180,000 hits,,,IDIOT. Microsoft Site "personal class supercomputers",,,135 hits,,,IDIOT! And when you are finished with that, this would apply to you, search "World Class Stupid Idiot,,, ------------------------------------------------ &gt;ignorance by posting TA voodoo stuff again&lt; Showing your ignorance again! The TA post was directed to another poster, NOT YOU, and in no way effected your subject matter except in your empty little skull. And even it it did, so what? I'll post to who ever and when ever I choose and that's none of your business. The more you post the more protocols you break, confirming you're ignorant.</Msg><Username>krarners_ghost</Username><Timestamp>1344611144000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344611976000-10</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;If your chair tips over will it make a sound?&gt; Not if you believe that when a tree falls in a forest and there is no one to hear it, there is no sound :) There is nobody there to hear his chair hit the floor....</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1344611976000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:19:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344618230000-11</Id><Topic><Title>What a great week for me!</Title><Username>tpeter299</Username><Timestamp>1344600943000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 08:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAMER FOAD</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1344618230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344622631000-12</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey clouseau did you find a way to prove that zero is actually the same as 5X10**11 dollars if you did be sure and let us know how you did it- also the suxers want to know - they have virtualy no raison d'être these days</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1344622631000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344625011000-13</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;5X10**11 dollars&gt; 50 billion dollars is only 5 * 10**10 dollars. But don't worry about that, you only overstated it by a factor of 10, i.e. 1000%, which is normal for you...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1344625011000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344627001000-14</Id><Title>MSFT has been a pos today!</Title><Msg>Keeping the market down! Now market is turning green but MSFT still not cooperating! ick stock!</Msg><Username>spamwithlilsugar</Username><Timestamp>1344627001000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:30:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344627900000-15</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Im talking 500 billion dollars since MSFT went on their jihad against the infidels back in the 1970s dimbulb</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1344627900000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344628155000-16</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, right &lt;sarcasm/&gt;</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1344628155000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344628212000-17</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, right &lt;sarcasm/&gt;</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1344628212000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344628289000-18</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zero = 5X10**11 dollars is about a half trillion since the 1970's when Microsoft started - zero is about what free sux earned- now take your broken brain to the task of comparing the two and see which one has overpowered the other in the market place. You can also use these numbers to project the performance of the droid turds and Iturds in the near future. Oh dont forget to tell your mother that you escaped the playpen and are posting again</Msg><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1344628289000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344629060000-19</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT has been a pos today!</Title><Username>spamwithlilsugar</Username><Timestamp>1344627001000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:30:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will get even uglier when Windows 8 flops like Vista.</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1344629060000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344629234000-20</Id><Topic><Title>What a great week for me!</Title><Username>tpeter299</Username><Timestamp>1344600943000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 08:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was a better week for me. I had 3 oriental massages with happy ending.</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1344629234000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:07:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344634049000-21</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;zero is about what free sux earned&gt; What is sux? Never heard of it.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1344634049000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:27:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344634987000-22</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PU: Redesign! Common sense should tell you that one can't build a ""SUPER COMPUTER"" then download a copy of Windows or Linux and expect it to perform with max functionality. You could call BALLMER and ask what it would cost for MSFT to write, design, a O/S for your one of a kind computer or you could contact some top Linux programmers, either way you would need your very own O/S and wording it with "redesign" don't change the fact that when they got done working on the O/S, it would only FULLY perform on your one computer. Oh, you might install a copy of Ubuntu and run notepad but if you want the computer to be all it can be, you "WILL" need one specific O/S that will only max perform on your one supercomputer. scheeeeec, you're a IDIOT. Great post by PU! The key words being "then download a copy of Windows or Linux and expect it to perform with max functionality." ------------------------------ easily proved the PU statement is correct: "Although most modern supercomputers use the Linux operating system, each manufacturer has made its own specific changes to the Linux-derivative they use, and no industry standard exists, partly due to the fact that the differences in hardware architectures require changes to optimize the operating system to each hardware design. The key words being "no industry standard exists, partly due to the fact that the differences in hardware architectures require changes to optimize the operating system to each hardware design." http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supercomputer_operating_systems PU: Common sense should tell you that one can't build a ""SUPER COMPUTER"" then download a copy of Windows or Linux and expect it to perform with max functionality. Wikipedia: require changes to optimize the operating system to each hardware design." -------------------------------- And now,,,admit you're a idiot!</Msg><Username>krarners_ghost</Username><Timestamp>1344634987000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:43:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344638452000-23</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>-We *ALL*- Who is we? you &amp; the other skanks ? LOL!!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1344638452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:40:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344639399000-24</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL what is sux? Never heard of it.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1344639399000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344641806000-25</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>-LOL what is sux? Never heard of it- sure you have now run along &amp; go stink up a relevant board.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1344641806000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344643620000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Buyers Beware: 4 High-Flying Stocks with Increased Short Selling</Title><Username>mattiebaresi</Username><Timestamp>1344634261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:31:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RIGHT ON - BEWARE SPAMMER MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1344643620000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344643711000-27</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;then lied and tried to change what you said&lt; I vehemently deny that, SKANK. How could say such a thing against me? I'm as clean as fresh snow.</Msg><Username>krarners_ghost</Username><Timestamp>1344643711000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344644019000-28</Id><Topic><Title>FASTER GAMING WITH LINUX THAN WINDOZE !!</Title><Username>henkepek</Username><Timestamp>1343911836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>-sux is better?? better than what?- heneputz means better than smoke signals or two cans tied together.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1344644019000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344647401000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Hurry Time Is Ticking`</Title><Username>eamonawd375</Username><Timestamp>1344605440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great return</Msg><Username>mayerfqn927</Username><Timestamp>1344647401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 21:10:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>