<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368159893816-1</Id><Topic><Title>Bad news for pepeekook, Obama lied again to mother of victim 3 days after Benghazi, as did Hillary</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368144801100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:13:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>show the quote from Pres to Mother, not your opinion. I guarantee he wasn't lying as there is no reason to lie #1, and he is as honest as the day is long, #2. I guarantee you falsify the truth and distort it into your cause.And I will prove you wrong as always when you show the actual quote, all of what he said, not parts snipped out to mean something he did not say. the rose garden speech, for the hundredth time, says acts of terror, attackers, and in no way says demonstration. You can't make it not about benghazi because that was the reason for the speech, and what he talked about. You keep reaching for the 9/11 reference as something, but it was a side comment to the subject. You can't change the context, the subject, or the truth. He gave the rose garden speech specifically to address benghazi. There is no other side to it, none. This President does not lie, honest Abe II.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1368159893816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 00:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368160089225-2</Id><Topic><Title>Laptop sales are down sequentially quarter over quarter as Surface Pro and Convertible Laptops are....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368123388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:16:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surface Pro is killing customers with hits ultra-high price tag.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1368160089225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 00:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368160150731-3</Id><Topic><Title>hawfeces your back, what happened, did an_obama_nation get banned</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368151078246</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:57:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I support the new term for your posts, Feeces, all of them, "online fukery." It's very concise.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1368160150731</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 00:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368160321766-4</Id><Topic><Title>WHY Windows will win this round as well....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368147359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will definitely see a change in IT when customers switch from Windows XP to something else next April. The change might not be to Windows 8 or Windows Blue. I plan to buy a Google Chromebook for $249 instead of a $999 Surface Pro for example.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1368160321766</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 00:32:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368160504057-5</Id><Topic><Title>ballmer</Title><Username>beenhereforever</Username><Timestamp>1368128127851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 15:35:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't he gone yet? MSFT shares will soar at least 10% the day Ballmer leaves.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1368160504057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 00:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368160655811-6</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi is a stinky thread that RWNJ hold onto for source of online fukery</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368150970297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:56:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Benghazi won't help Hillary's chances for election in 2016.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1368160655811</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 00:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368160960919-7</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi is a stinky thread that RWNJ hold onto for source of online fukery</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368150970297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:56:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will commit online fukery for years on it. They are in panic mode with it, because they are losing.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368160960919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 00:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368162249836-8</Id><Topic><Title>The New Xbox Bigger Than You Think....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368056603409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 19:43:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it may be. maybe even in the way you imagine. :-D</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368162249836</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:04:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368162440929-9</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo confirms Windows Phone 8 handset plans (Source ZDNet - Jan 2013)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368149383337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:29:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hope they make more than they did of ver. 7 winpho. you hear anything since jan.? no? hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm ...</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368162440929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:07:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368163045265-10</Id><Topic><Title>WHY Windows will win this round as well....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368147359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This sort of blather is known as "whistling past the graveyard". The PC may not disappear altogether, but it is already giving way to tablets and smartphones as the type of device the great majority of people will use. That includes "enterprise" users. You can't change it by closing your eyes to it.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368163045265</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368164477201-11</Id><Title>Nokia Breaks Away From Microsoft With New $99 Asha Phone</Title><Msg>Google it. Now watch osso have a hissy fit.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368164477201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368169193025-12</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Breaks Away From Microsoft With New $99 Asha Phone</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368164477201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Osso == total #$%$</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368169193025</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 02:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368169361563-13</Id><Topic><Title>Osso-bumble is a dumb M$hill idiot</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368144972491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:16:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get dead, wally.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368169361563</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 03:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368174856754-14</Id><Topic><Title>Will code name "Durango" aka XBOX 720 push this stock higher</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368129924843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 16:05:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason that decline in PC sales does not matter is #1 there were more upgrades, the new Xbox is a Windows 8 PC. I am not a gamer at all. I will buy this for the music, cable pass through, internet tv and using my tv as speakers. Sales of Xbox will be a blowout this time.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368174856754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 04:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368181423959-15</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Breaks Away From Microsoft With New $99 Asha Phone</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368164477201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The lumias are nice but that Asha is a pos. It only works on 2g for India and Africa mainly. They could not go anywhere with that Asha. It was an attempt to rip off w8, just not a good one.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368181423959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368181839200-16</Id><Title>It frustrates the multi-aliased Obama supporter here that Benghazi isn't dropped</Title><Msg>Obama has told us there is nothing to the story. Nixon swore there was nothing to Watergate. If you ever tried to put out a fire in short dry grass on a hot day and in a slight breeze you know how it is. The flames remain low and you can stomp out a location with your foot but with the dry tender and the breeze as you move down the line putting out fire the embers and breeze re-ignite spots and the fire grows slowly. Obama boi focus on these points. (1) Rice was briefed with known lies and visited 5 Sunday talk shows spreading the official line lie. (2) The day after the incident Obama used carefully worded, scripted text in the Rose Garden to later fool dense. He said "terrorist attacks" while referring to the original 9/11, non native speakers were fooled (3) Three days after the incident, Obama, Hillary and Rice all told the other of a slain ex SEAL that it was a spontaneous demonstration protesting a video TO HER FACE. Now here is the point, there is a reason these lies were told. The reason may be less damaging than the lies but there is a reason, and Obama cannot tell us because to do so would admit the lying to the few dense dolts still defending the lies...so we must continue digging, until the reason for the lying is uncovered.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368181839200</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368182265349-17</Id><Title>At one point futures were up almost 70 points, does anyone actually still believe this pretend anxious</Title><Msg>buying is not manipulation? There were a number of runs down yesterday. This market is all about where it can be pushed and little to do with value. The difference this run is that the Fed is helping the push, it is clear. Ultimately the market will be much bigger than the Fed. The saying of "live by the sword, die by the sword" applies. Too many Bots are poorly programmed to consider only price direction. A pressure washer has a lot of push when the target is small, but don't try to put out a house fire with one.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368182265349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368183055846-18</Id><Topic><Title>It frustrates the multi-aliased Obama supporter here that Benghazi isn't dropped</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368181839200</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is frustrating that Iraq and WMDS or the lack of them are still in the news, but the RWNJ don't want to talk about that because a conservative president decided on war, instead of peace...</Msg><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1368183055846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368184070444-19</Id><Topic><Title>WHY Windows will win this round as well....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368147359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is perhaps the best reasoned write up on the history and the future of computing and a must read for long term investors and smart analysts. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368184070444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:07:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368184287468-20</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo confirms Windows Phone 8 handset plans (Source ZDNet - Jan 2013)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368149383337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:29:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe Lenovo will be under pressure to launch a Windows 8 Phone now that Huawei has introduced theirs.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368184287468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368184536888-21</Id><Topic><Title>It frustrates the multi-aliased Obama supporter here that Benghazi isn't dropped</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368181839200</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"(2) The day after the incident Obama used carefully worded, scripted text in the Rose Garden to later fool dense. He said "terrorist attacks" while referring to the original 9/11, non native speakers were fooled" The "non native speakers were fooled" weren't the only ones fooled. Romney (his debate coaches were also fooled) and when Romney said Obama never mentioned terrorist in the 3rd debate, Obama made sure the commentator, Candy, made the point that terrorist was mentioned in the rose garden speech, winning that point clearly for Obama and making Romney look stupid. Criminals are really good liars and it takes overwhelming proof to find them out. The bottom line is nobody has connected Obama to Benghazi when he is the only one who could order a troop movement. Instead, the republicans are after Hilary, thus wasting their time.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1368184536888</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368184547133-22</Id><Topic><Title>Laptop sales are down sequentially quarter over quarter as Surface Pro and Convertible Laptops are....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368123388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:16:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we will see the real impact of Surface Pro in the third quarter after reports from all the new markets carrying the Microsoft mobility devices come in. The 7 inch tablet will also change the equation in favor of Microsoft. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368184547133</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368184651933-23</Id><Topic><Title>100M Windows 8 licenses is NOTHING</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368059634840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:33:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to be mentally disturbed.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368184651933</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:17:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368184815379-24</Id><Topic><Title>May 21/2013: The Nail in the Death of PC Myth's Coffin....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368039617319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I totally agree since the earnings estimates are taken down so much based on the imminent death of pc that we will end up with shock earnings to the upside and analysts no where to be found to defend themselves. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368184815379</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368185106375-25</Id><Topic><Title>CIO Road Test: Microsoft Surface Pro Beats Apple iPad....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368132220908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 16:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have used both machines and there is no question that surface pro is the superior machine. I also read somewhere that new chips will allow the next generation of surface tablets to have more computing and battery power.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368185106375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368186532856-26</Id><Title>ms money and mistakes</Title><Msg>MSFT's large cash hoard allows it to make mistakes. The issue is when the cash and cash flow run dry, that's when mistakes will push a company to chap 11. In many ways MSFT is like a large Pharma company, many products in the pipeline, but only one or 2 become a blockbuster. I'm holding looking for dip to buy more.</Msg><Username>albacornus</Username><Timestamp>1368186532856</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:48:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368187729573-27</Id><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Msg>Folks as I wrote yesterday, the CIO's nightmare is multiple OSs and patchwork and extra training to keep MIS infrastructure productive, secure, reliable and cost efficient.... AS we can see, the Start Button removal in Windows 8 has become the lightening rod used by our detractors just to prove the point that change is impossible and PCs and Windows will rule the Enterprise space till the end of Time.... THE latest on the Enterprise front is that as CIOs want to cut cost and increase efficiency, DELL and HP Tablets and Convertible Laptops are replacing iPad at an "alarming rate" as they are the largest vendors of Hardware and Windows software to corporate clients.... THE next shoe to fall is switching to Windows-8 Phone which as Lenovo folks have pointed out, Android OS are infested with malware (Some even suggest that they come pre-installed with malware, kind of pre-hacked ready for sabotage and theft of personal/corporate data); the CIOs are pushing for a "consistent and seamless" OS across the corporate IT domain now that Cloud computing and security issues are becoming front and center.... SO folks the first victim on Phone wars will be Android OS followed by iPhone and the only reason that it may take a bit longer than Tablets/iPads is that DELL and HP do not have a Phone "to offer a more price competitive Hardware package", unless of course they develop one or team up with Nokia to stick it to AAPL. Stay tuned. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368188028400-28</Id><Title>Microsoft says Yammer sales up 259%, added 312 customers in quarter....</Title><Msg>Microsoft said yesterday in a blog post that Yammer, its enterprise social networking tool, grew its sales 259% year-over year and gained 312 new customers in the company's third quarter. March marked Yammer's best month to-date in terms of user engagement, the company added.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368188028400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368188118977-29</Id><Topic><Title>Osso-bumble is a dumb M$hill idiot</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368144972491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:16:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After busting 7 Dems for corruption, ex-State Sen. Shirley Huntley sentenced to prison for looting charity NYC PAPERS OUT. Social media use restricted to low res file max 184 x 128 pixels and 72 dpi A 74-year-old state senator who secretly recorded her elected colleagues for the FBI was sentenced Thursday to a year and a day in prison for looting a taxpayer-funded charity she controlled.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1368188118977</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368188457107-30</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The CIO will just have to deal with the problems if in fact there are any, because Windows as the only OS is just not acceptable any more.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368188457107</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368188548027-31</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have suggested that they come preinstalled with spyware and malware and it is not being addressed by goog because they make billions of dollars because their are redirects from peoples browsers that land on adwords accounts and goog get's a cut. It is complicated. Goog says Russian mobs take out AdSense accounts and than plant malware to make random users redirects to the site to hit the ad being displayed racking up profits for the adsense holder and goog at the same time. Not much incentive for them to stop that or are their engineers the ones doing it??????</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368188548027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368188906281-32</Id><Title>Buy a Windows phone no worries buy an Android keep it in a drawer girls.</Title><Msg>Android phones can be hacked and taken over within 1 minute when used on public wifi. They can also be accessed without you knowing it. Look at an app called hidden camera or something like that. That is sort of what is happening. That app can record video with the phone screen off and the camera light not on. So a hacker can turn on you video and watch you. They can also turn on your mic. Android phones are insanely unsafe. Anyone can alter the source code. That should be banned. Microsoft has namespaces and safeguard that make it a royal pain to get around. Most do not have that patience or skill. So put your android in a drawer if you do not want some creep sitting in China spying on you and your open source hippie phone. ENJOY!</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368188906281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368189134049-33</Id><Title>The Big Picture</Title><Msg>Like osso says, "MSFT is made up of 12 different profit centers and Windows is 20% of our revenues and Windows 8 a fraction of that" Meanwhile, shorts would have you believe Windows 8 is the entire company or something. Another great point by Osso, "the Start Button removal in Windows 8 has become the lightening rod used by our detractors just to prove the point that change is impossible....." Conclusion? "... PCs and Windows will rule the Enterprise space till the end of Time...."</Msg><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1368189134049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368189142660-34</Id><Topic><Title>Buy a Windows phone no worries buy an Android keep it in a drawer girls.</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368188906281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forgot to mention, that it is my prediction that Android will be spun off soon as goog has a target on their back. People will want to get paid. I mean billions of people when they find out that their privacy has been invaded and they are blatantly negligent. Teenagers are not safe and they know it! FB is knocking on the I want to be sued for negligence as well. Bing FBI says Androids phones are unsafe.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368189142660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368189312895-35</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as you wrote yesterday? "Start Button removal in Windows 8" As I wrote yesterday the "START BUTTON" is still there in W8, and it's in the same place it always was through w7, lower left corner in Desktop Mode. You actually posted "windows key x" to pop it up and see the list of programs, so the question is, why would you post "Start Button removal in Windows 8" when you know there is a start button?</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1368189312895</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368189589974-36</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under either scenario, the crash test dummy shorts have taken a non-issue to trash MSFT and the uninformed and paid analysts have been bashing Windows 8.... NO worries as all will be in order soon.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368189589974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368189887864-37</Id><Topic><Title>The Big Picture</Title><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1368189134049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:32:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU see folks by the time the dust of the Mobility/windows-8 Armageddon settles, there will be a monumental transfer of wealth and capital to MSFT shareholders; some $300-400 billion of Market Cap that is; all coming from AAPL and Google shareholders and of course from the crash test dummy shorts. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368189887864</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368190679898-38</Id><Topic><Title>Buy a Windows phone no worries buy an Android keep it in a drawer girls.</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368188906281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>youre full of #$%$. how about you show me a NEW article about android phones.</Msg><Username>fulison</Username><Timestamp>1368190679898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368191081219-39</Id><Title>Start your DD on PLPL ASAP</Title><Msg>I heard there is a massive promo coming into PLPL. Keep an eye on it</Msg><Username>bowenelijah701</Username><Timestamp>1368191081219</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:04:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368191574777-40</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have an Android phone and have no clue about the malware you are talking about.</Msg><Username>commodityhq</Username><Timestamp>1368191574777</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:12:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368192270367-41</Id><Topic><Title>May 21/2013: The Nail in the Death of PC Myth's Coffin....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368039617319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THAT is a great point you make as the analysts have taken down DELL and HPQ estimates by 18.6% and 17.35% for the current quarter YoY..... AND they have done that in a growing economy and full quarter of having several Tablets and Convertible Laptops with varying and affordable price points.... Too bad DELL does not have an upside because of the Buyout; but HPQ could be a real killer for the shorts both here and at HPQ. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368192270367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368192652199-42</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This ties in well with the current discussion on the message board for those who missed it. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368192652199</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368192939476-43</Id><Title>Once again markets up...</Title><Msg>..this pig is down again - day after day of beat downs for this oinker. When will it end? $27-$28 as always. OINK OINK</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1368192939476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368193300439-44</Id><Title>This is all short selling at the open....</Title><Msg>BUY on the dip.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368193300439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368193438435-45</Id><Topic><Title>This is all short selling at the open....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368193300439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really? do you realize how stupid you sound? WHO SHORT SELLS WHEN THE PRICE IS DOWN?</Msg><Username>fulison</Username><Timestamp>1368193438435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368193611751-46</Id><Topic><Title>This is all short selling at the open....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368193300439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another clueless short.... I just picked up 2,000 more shares @...... Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368193611751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368193791299-47</Id><Title>EASY MONEY TODAY BUY CAT 90 calls now</Title><Msg>will double again today</Msg><Username>lkphomes</Username><Timestamp>1368193791299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368193814920-48</Id><Title>EASY MONEY TODAY BUY CAT 90 calls now</Title><Msg>will double again today</Msg><Username>lkphomes</Username><Timestamp>1368193814920</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368194685757-49</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This will be another reason for the carriers to get behind Windows 8 phone and give the customers a choice and try to argue that they gave the consumers a choice and avoid corporate killer class action lawsuits.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368194685757</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:04:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368195233486-50</Id><Topic><Title>It frustrates the multi-aliased Obama supporter here that Benghazi isn't dropped</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368181839200</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rose Garden 10:43 A.M. EDT THE PRESIDENT: Good morning. Every day, all across the world, American diplomats and civilians work tirelessly to advance the interests and values of our nation. Often, they are away from their families. Sometimes, they brave great danger. Yesterday, four of these extraordinary Americans were killed in an attack on our diplomatic post in Benghazi. Among those killed was our Ambassador, Chris Stevens, as well as Foreign Service Officer Sean Smith. We are still notifying the families of the others who were killed. And today, the American people stand united in holding the families of the four Americans in our thoughts and in our prayers. The United States condemns in the strongest terms this outrageous and shocking attack. We're working with the government of Libya to secure our diplomats. I've also directed my administration to increase our security at diplomatic posts around the world. And make no mistake, we will work with the Libyan government to bring to justice the killers who attacked our people. Since our founding, the United States has been a nation that respects all faiths. We reject all efforts to denigrate the religious beliefs of others. But there is absolutely no justification to this type of senseless violence. None. The world must stand together to unequivocally reject these brutal acts. Already, many Libyans have joined us in doing so, and this attack will not break the bonds between the United States and Libya. Libyan security personnel fought back against the attackers alongside Americans. Libyans helped some of our diplomats find safety, and they carried Ambassador Stevensâ€™s body to the hospital, where we tragically learned that he had died. It's especially tragic that Chris Stevens died in Benghazi because it is a city that he helped to save. At the height of the Libyan revolution, Chris led our diplomatic post in Benghazi. With characteristic skill, courage, and resolve, he built partnerships with Libyan revolutionaries, and helped them as they planned to build a new Libya. When the Qaddafi regime came to an end, Chris was there to serve as our ambassador to the new Libya, and he worked tirelessly to support this young democracy, and I think both Secretary Clinton and I relied deeply on his knowledge of the situation on the ground there. He was a role model to all who worked with him and to the young diplomats who aspire to walk in his footsteps. Along with his colleagues, Chris died in a country that is still striving to emerge from the recent experience of war. Today, the loss of these four Americans is fresh, but our memories of them linger on. I have no doubt that their legacy will live on through the work that they did far from our shores and in the hearts of those who love them back home. Of course, yesterday was already a painful day for our nation as we marked the solemn memory of the 9/11 attacks. We mourned with the families who were lost on that day. I visited the graves of troops who made the ultimate sacrifice in Iraq and Afghanistan at the hallowed grounds of Arlington Cemetery, and had the opportunity to say thank you and visit some of our wounded warriors at Walter Reed. And then last night, we learned the news of this attack in Benghazi. As Americans, let us never, ever forget that our freedom is only sustained because there are people who are willing to fight for it, to stand up for it, and in some cases, lay down their lives for it. Our country is only as strong as the character of our people and the service of those both civilian and military who represent us around the globe. No acts of terror will ever shake the resolve of this great nation, alter that character, or eclipse the light of the values that we stand for. Today we mourn four more Americans who represent the very best of the United States of America. We will not waver in our commitment to see that justice is done for this terrible act. And make no mistake, justice will be done. But we also know that the lives these Americans led stand in stark contrast to those of their attackers. These four Americans stood up for freedom and human dignity. They should give every American great pride in the country that they served, and the hope that our flag represents to people around the globe who also yearn to live in freedom and with dignity. We grieve with their families, but let us carry on their memory, and let us continue their work of seeking a stronger America and a better world for all of our children. Thank you. May God bless the memory of those we lost and may God bless the United States of America. END 10:48 A.M. EDT</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368195233486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368195333009-51</Id><Title>LOAD UP ON MARGIN!!!</Title><Msg>TO INFINITY AND BEYOND!!!!</Msg><Username>marketeer1001</Username><Timestamp>1368195333009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:15:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368195366394-52</Id><Topic><Title>This is all short selling at the open....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368193300439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>youre such a bad liar it hurts. you spent 65000 on 2000 more shares when you could have bought them a few weeks ago for less? youre stupid.</Msg><Username>fulison</Username><Timestamp>1368195366394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:16:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368195419139-53</Id><Title>SKYPE</Title><Msg>MSFT--SHOULD DO ALOT MORE WITH SKYPE</Msg><Username>a.hudkins</Username><Timestamp>1368195419139</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368195444721-54</Id><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Msg>I think I have heard that !</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368195489650-55</Id><Topic><Title>This is all short selling at the open....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368193300439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you think he stupid that only mean you not osso bucco! :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368195489650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368195513002-56</Id><Topic><Title>This is all short selling at the open....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368193300439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no he doesn't realize - the man is an imbecile</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1368195513002</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368195589477-57</Id><Topic><Title>This is all short selling at the open....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368193300439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you predict short sale and accumulation hold vol. down today? or just on some other days? :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368195589477</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368195738280-58</Id><Topic><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No he said Microsoft is now worth more than it once was so it wasn't a bubble is what I heard.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368195738280</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:22:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368195746040-59</Id><Topic><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no no no. Ben said Microsoft is worth more now....he loves microsoft</Msg><Username>whartonmba99</Username><Timestamp>1368195746040</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:22:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368195929228-60</Id><Title>Msft is a bubble because windows is dwindling away market share!</Title><Msg>However Microsoft in the grand father of web and should transition better than most! But Google is more youthful and updated!</Msg><Username>stockanalysisinfo</Username><Timestamp>1368195929228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:25:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368195943408-61</Id><Topic><Title>SKYPE</Title><Username>a.hudkins</Username><Timestamp>1368195419139</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe there will be a Microsoft no carrier phone that just needs a wifi connection. Wouldn't it be a slap in the face if they release it in one of goog's free internet wifi areas. Than everyone can make phone calls for free except a small Skype monthly fee or advertising subsidized for free.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368195943408</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368195950885-62</Id><Topic><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HE is pointing out the economy is improving so the fortunes of the good folks at MSFT. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368195950885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368195981914-63</Id><Topic><Title>Once again markets up...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1368192939476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 09:35:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you not understand! new w8 bullet-proof lipstick will make price shoot up to $33! :-D</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368195981914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196028762-64</Id><Topic><Title>It frustrates the multi-aliased Obama supporter here that Benghazi isn't dropped</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368181839200</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"No acts of terror will ever shake the resolve of this great nation, alter that character, or eclipse the light of the values that we stand for. Today we mourn four more Americans who represent the very best of the United States of America. We will not waver in our commitment to see that justice is done for this terrible act. And make no mistake, justice will be done." For the lazy Feeces who can't read. Like romney and the right wing they rarely read or listen to Obama, they just know already wat he said. Anything else? I see no evidence from you on what you said.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368196028762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196354048-65</Id><Topic><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has Microsoft on his mind because they have huge gov. contract and a nice ritzy Bld. in Chevy Chase on the boarder of DC. They provide a securer option than goog. Goog sued the Gov. in Washington, DC claiming they were unfair to giv Microsoft all the contracts. LoL, it is still on his mind because Microsoft seems like the largest tech company in Washington, DC. The pc's are almost entirely Dell, HP &amp; IBM with contract by Microsoft the companies themselves and NetApp. Microsoft has service contracts. It amazes me that there are a lot of investors that think they only sell Windows.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368196354048</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196424670-66</Id><Topic><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Europe: "Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!" USA: "Did Bernanke just say on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble?"</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1368196424670</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:33:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196440499-67</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The message is that android is no longer acceptable and is being replaced by W-8 OR CANT YOU READ- mowrawn</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368196440499</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:34:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368196466503-68</Id><Title>What's the record for the most...</Title><Msg>...consecutive down days for a stock? Whatever it is we may see it broken by this pig.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1368196466503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196475541-69</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi is a stinky thread that RWNJ hold onto for source of online fukery</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368150970297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:56:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>{Look for em to keep stiring this dying fire for quite some time} Looks like ABC is "stiring" the fire now. What a super smart dumb-bass you are. And it's not dying. At all. The all-out media offensive to first ignore the administration's lethal incompetence since the event, and now to comically try to paint it as some kind of a GOP witch hunt (I thought they already found Hillary BTW), is falling apart. The media now is being forced to report the actual malfeasance, lying, and cover up as the information slowly oozes out of the administration due to their inability to stop mandated public disclosures and the fact that the congress, in this country, is Constitutionally charged with oversight of the Executive branch. It's all coming out whether you like it or not.</Msg><Username>plmartin02</Username><Timestamp>1368196475541</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196542768-70</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Breaks Away From Microsoft With New $99 Asha Phone</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368164477201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rip off w8? how nok asha phone rip off w8, or msft phone os, either one, by using s40/meego/smartephone function, look and feel? msft invent those things and give them to nok before partnership? this big news if true. so, probably not ...</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368196542768</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196594003-71</Id><Topic><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a moment Bernanke probably wishes he could take back, he specifically mentioned Microsoft (MSFT) stock in the context of bubble-watching, seemingly in an effort to take a benign example of something that has risen in value apparently based on fundamentals and underscoring how difficult it can be to tell the difference between that type of valuation growth and broader bubble-like growth.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368196594003</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196618765-72</Id><Topic><Title>Crash Mode About to be Activated....</Title><Username>jbspectrum</Username><Timestamp>1368109162950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 10:19:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>put your helmet on....and stand by...</Msg><Username>jbspectrum</Username><Timestamp>1368196618765</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:36:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196622520-73</Id><Topic><Title>WHY Windows will win this round as well....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368147359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how sad for you!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368196622520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196664219-74</Id><Topic><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Either that or the Gov. is scared as hell of the Linux based systems since they are almost paranoid now in regards to the Chinese Spying thought to originate from Android phones. It sounds like I am making it up. I am not, and I here this stuff every day. Every time I hear it, I am thinking it sounds like some stuff that would be said on this board. I turn around and it is a high level gov, military or law enforcement saying it. It actually is crazy and they are scrambling to redo their entire IT because everyone is clueless how to tell, what to do, who to call to prevent it, etc. Even the IT people are 100% clueless what to do. So they ask Microsoft.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368196664219</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:37:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196719793-75</Id><Topic><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks ossobucco2012 for the clarification.</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368196719793</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368196788800-76</Id><Topic><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the clarification.....</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368196788800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368196803143-77</Id><Title>"Doomed Operating System ($MSFT)"</Title><Msg>Google it ( it's on Credit Bubble Stocks) Quoting: "A Credit Bubble Stocks correspondent writes in with this gem from the Phoenix airport. "I assume they are going to be pushing their stupid tablet and/or doomed operating system. Maybe you'll get to hold something sticky that a bunch of bored proles played with after eating Pizza Hut? "Is a quick demo in a crowded, noisy environment going to be what sells people on the ease of use of Windows 8? "It's times like this I wish Apple stock was trading at book value ($125, which is my bid) so I could buy some. "Also, Microsoft, the downside of "leveraging" your monopoly through brutal customer service and gouging for two decades is that we're going to be glad to twist the knife."</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368196803143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:40:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368196913428-78</Id><Title>Nokia to sell high-end Lumia smartphone through Verizon Wireless....</Title><Msg>HELSINKI (Reuters) - Nokia said it was launching a new high-end smartphone, Lumia 928, through an exclusive agreement with U.S. carrier Verizon Wireless. The smartphone, which uses Microsoft's Windows Phone 8 software, will feature a 8.7 megapixel camera capable of recording high-quality video. It will cost $99 after a $50 mail-in rebate for those signing up to a new two-year agreement. Nokia is trying to boost its share in the high-margin smartphone market after years of falling behind Samsung and Apple Inc.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368196913428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197021009-79</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo confirms Windows Phone 8 handset plans (Source ZDNet - Jan 2013)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368149383337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:29:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>huawei phone is low end unit. based off of ascend android phone. lenovo not really compete in bargain segment. that not target mkt. for them. business sector is lenovo area. they plan on making ver. 7 winpho and then never do it. no news on ver. 8 phone since jan. hmmmmmmmmmmmm ...</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368197021009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197062131-80</Id><Topic><Title>"Doomed Operating System ($MSFT)"</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368196803143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:40:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES credit bubble stock, you dummy MSFT is one of the only 4 stocks with AAA rating, higher than the US Treasuries.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368197062131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:44:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197088415-81</Id><Topic><Title>Laptop sales are down sequentially quarter over quarter as Surface Pro and Convertible Laptops are....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368123388575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 14:16:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i thinks so too. diff. is you think impact will be positive.</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368197088415</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197089405-82</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi is a stinky thread that RWNJ hold onto for source of online fukery</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368150970297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:56:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>plmowrawn illegal alien kisses RWNJ sas but too dumb to notice that RWNJ's are racist to the core and don't have anything to do with illegal aliens from oxMice</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368197089405</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197149271-83</Id><Topic><Title>Lenovo confirms Windows Phone 8 handset plans (Source ZDNet - Jan 2013)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368149383337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:29:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THEY will go against iPhone. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368197149271</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197195590-84</Id><Topic><Title>Did Bernanke just said on CNBC that MSFT is a bubble!</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368195444721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:17:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On way to tell is to look at all the billions in increasing revenue last quarter. You can't fake billions of increasing revenue per quarter. When the new Xbox and increased Windows Phone sales kick in it will be a hurricane of billions blowing in.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368197195590</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197316840-85</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi is a stinky thread that RWNJ hold onto for source of online fukery</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368150970297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 21:56:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you talking loud to the inventor of the popular term, "online fukery?" Better not be. You may continue with the "online fukery" now. Don't make it too long, as no one will read it.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368197316840</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368197347881-86</Id><Title>All of the tech indicators are pointing to a bull run in PLPL</Title><Msg>Looks like PLPL is about to take off. With all of the recent developments I am going to start accumulating some PLPL</Msg><Username>danielharvey166</Username><Timestamp>1368197347881</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197375400-87</Id><Topic><Title>ms money and mistakes</Title><Username>albacornus</Username><Timestamp>1368186532856</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:48:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>osso buy more. you looking for him?</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368197375400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197527095-88</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Breaks Away From Microsoft With New $99 Asha Phone</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368164477201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The look of the Windows Phone was designed with Microsoft. Nokia made an Asha look like it from the outside case and duplicate colors. They changed to a touch screen and it incorporates routines that act more like W8 than the old point and click on a charm OS. If you are making Lumia's for a while, I guess your ideas change and you start looking like the thing you make for someone else. They are advertising it as more like Windows Phone. It is odd.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368197527095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197657860-89</Id><Topic><Title>ms money and mistakes</Title><Username>albacornus</Username><Timestamp>1368186532856</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:48:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This may be the most out of it post I have ever read and there have been some real winners. Microsoft Chapter 11? Man are you misinformed.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368197657860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368197743568-90</Id><Title>Has there ever been....</Title><Msg>...a stock that could drop 5% of its value as quickly as MSFT does any time it makes a rare (unsupported) run? You can count on it like a Swiss watch. Money in the bank.</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1368197743568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368197987094-91</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet the legal departments at the Carriers are watching this complaint closely as it will have tragic consequences for cash rich Telcos with deep pockets..... Expect "Disclaimers" in fine-print of all service contracts.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368197987094</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:59:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368198170810-92</Id><Title>Nokia Sells Phone Through Verizon to Accelerate U.S. Push (Source Bloomberg)</Title><Msg>Just Bing it!</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368198170810</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368198412577-93</Id><Topic><Title>It frustrates the multi-aliased Obama supporter here that Benghazi isn't dropped</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368181839200</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""No acts of terror will ever shake the resolve of this great nation..." He is correct in that, accident probably. It's unfortunate that two days after that "both sides of his mouth" speech to fool the dolts, he and Hillary and Rice told the mother of the slain SEAL it was a spontaneous demonstration due to a video. That confirms two things (1) the Rose Garden speech wrt terror was not referring to Benghazi, and Obama and crew are pathological in their insideous lies.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368198412577</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368198961714-94</Id><Title>MSFT a AAA Growth and Dividend Stock....</Title><Msg>Microsoft has an impressive record of stable and increasing dividends for many years. During the past six years, annualized dividend payments grew no less than 10% each year except for 2010, which has seen a growth of only 5.8%. But in the last couple of years, the annualized payout had increased by an average rate of a whooping 22.8%. How safe is the dividend? The company has a payout ratio based on cash flow of 20.2% and its free cash flow has been increasing since 2010. Both factors indicate its ability to pay the same if not increase dividends in the near future. Also, improvements in its core business can be observed as the net operating cash flow continues to grow at double-digit rates. The increase was 26% in 2010, 12% in 2011, and 17% in 2012. In fact, one analyst has calculated that the companyâ€™s core operating cash flow, where non-cash adjustments in its cash flow statement are eliminated, grew by 21% and was higher than what rivals Google, Apple, and BlackBerry have had in the past year. Also, Microsoft continues to show its profitability prowess; its profit margin is almost back in the 30% range based on its performance in the last quarter of 2012 and the first quarter of 2013. Together with the robust revenue performance, this had brought the company to surpass earnings estimates in the two most recent quarters.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368198961714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368198979078-95</Id><Topic><Title>"Doomed Operating System ($MSFT)"</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368196803143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:40:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW I know what he means by "brutal customer service" from Microsoft. I've had to deal with it myself, and I'm very glad I will never have to suffer it again.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368198979078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368198995155-96</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft says Yammer sales up 259%, added 312 customers in quarter....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368188028400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in non-news: osso yammer continue on about same as always. maybe slight improvement tho ... film growing thinner over eyes? find out later, maybe by 11. ;)</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368198995155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368199005289-97</Id><Title>Looks like I have found another winner. Check out MISM</Title><Msg>Looks like volume and momentum are really starting to pick up on MISM. I bet MISMwont stay this cheap for long</Msg><Username>danielharvey166</Username><Timestamp>1368199005289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:16:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199064448-98</Id><Topic><Title>"Doomed Operating System ($MSFT)"</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368196803143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:40:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why it's a bubble, bozo.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368199064448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199104437-99</Id><Topic><Title>It frustrates the multi-aliased Obama supporter here that Benghazi isn't dropped</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368181839200</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1.Prove what you say with evidence, like I did. Otherwise it is just empty yammering. 2. His speeches are historic and have the depth of a great man and intellect. Lincoln like in their value. You don't like Lincoln either, do you. 3. You can't read or comprehend English well. 4. Obviously he is totally talking about Benghazi and refers to the attacks as acts of terror 5. You're lazy to back up what you claim. 6. There is no cover up and no story, never was. 7. Yoiu even tried to blame him for the Boston bombings 8. Your credibility is zilch. etc</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368199104437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:18:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199174932-100</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Breaks Away From Microsoft With New $99 Asha Phone</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368164477201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Asha is for the third world countries, however Huawei can challenge Nokia on this mis-adventure as they are now selling WP-8 in the US phones that competes with Lumia 521 and can do so in India as well. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368199174932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:19:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199178963-101</Id><Topic><Title>It frustrates the multi-aliased Obama supporter here that Benghazi isn't dropped</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368181839200</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think you mean 'amuses'</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368199178963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199215422-102</Id><Topic><Title>It frustrates the multi-aliased Obama supporter here that Benghazi isn't dropped</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368181839200</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 06:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think you mean 'amuses'</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368199215422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199368687-103</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Breaks Away From Microsoft With New $99 Asha Phone</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368164477201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hissy fit as predicted.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368199368687</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199630861-104</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe. but if they not willing to allow update to other os, why you think they allow update to winpho sooner/faster/better. att just start to allow update to 7.8 yesterday. you know of any lawsuit like you describe?</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368199630861</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:27:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199640186-105</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Breaks Away From Microsoft With New $99 Asha Phone</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368164477201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 01:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Incidentally the only softie shill I can recall who always insisted on signing his posts was Zogdan. He went away, but for a time would come back when Microsoft was in especially dire straits. So you are probably Zogdan in drag, and you are here in the usual circumstance for Zogdan, i.e. dire straits for Microsoft.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368199640186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199719003-106</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any idea what that discussion is? :-D why you leave out relevant info so often? :haha: bum p :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368199719003</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199786287-107</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bum p</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368199786287</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:29:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199955549-108</Id><Topic><Title>"Doomed Operating System ($MSFT)"</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368196803143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:40:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how os by other aaa rated company doing? :haha: :haha: :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368199955549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368199993641-109</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSFT system automatically updates its Security settings compared to Android which seems no one is in charge and even when updates are available, the service providers fail to do so according to ACLU.... And that opens them up to considerable liability as all it takes is an aggressive Law firm to take on the case and the rest will be history. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368199993641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368200134897-110</Id><Topic><Title>WHY Windows will win this round as well....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368147359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU are obviously as clueless as they come.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368200134897</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:35:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368200193497-111</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for posting that. I have been saying that for 7 months on the Nokia board and no one believes me. Goof is in trouble in regards to their software engineers and hippie attitudes. FB too.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368200193497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368200387797-112</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IT seems the average consumer awareness with defects of Android is increasing exponentially while the Copybot fanboys are still in denial.... Just listen to Lenovo's CEO and you will see why. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368200387797</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368200414673-113</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Sells Phone Through Verizon to Accelerate U.S. Push (Source Bloomberg)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368198170810</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:02:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you on binge already! not remember you already post about this? http://finance.yahoo.com/mbview/threadview/;_ylt=AqgA4h2bUmfdLA2dlAt791beAohG;_ylu=X3oDMTFqNDg2ajdhBG1pdANNZXNzYWdlIEJvYXJkcyB3aWRnZXQEcG9zAzY4BHNlYwNNZWRpYU1zZ0JvYXJkcw--;_ylg=X3oDMTIyb3VhOHBoBGludGwDdXMEbGFuZwNlbi11cwRwc3RhaWQDBHBzdGNhdAMEcHQDc2VjdGlvbnMEdGVzdANidWNrZXRfcmVtb3ZlZA--;_ylv=3?&amp;bn=30ec85b4-d1ce-32fe-a71c-f56c94fe758b&amp;tid=1368196913428-d0908f97-8d58-44b3-beff-7c7a046b2458&amp;tls=la%2Cd%2C18%2C3 :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368200414673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368200599465-114</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia to sell high-end Lumia smartphone through Verizon Wireless....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368196913428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>introduction delayed from last march bcuz phone not work correctly on verizon network so nokia fall even further behind. but everything ok now!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! become crash test dummy with new 2 year contract today! oh, not avail. today. well, still poss. to become dummy ...</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368200599465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368200837982-115</Id><Title>Windows 8: Success Or Fail?</Title><Msg>Microsoft announced record revenue for the financial quarter ending December 31, 2012 attributing some of this success to its new Windows devices. But is Windows 8 actually the success story Steve Ballmer claims?</Msg><Username>cristian.bissattini</Username><Timestamp>1368200837982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368200960215-116</Id><Topic><Title>Should you steer clear of MSFT? Consider why.</Title><Username>thomasbrock58</Username><Timestamp>1368196071007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spam mean spam! all reader: run away from this fast!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368200960215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368200977333-117</Id><Title>Janet Napolitano for next President</Title><Msg>I like her style, intellect, and she has the quals. I have a feeling Hilary may not run anyway, she'll be like 69, so could be 77 before she finishes second term. That's getting up there to endure the stress of a modern day President. Either one would be great though.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368200977333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368201014719-118</Id><Topic><Title>Should you steer clear of MSFT? Consider why.</Title><Username>thomasbrock58</Username><Timestamp>1368196071007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 10:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you use initial ys for "you suck" to avoid yahoo bad word filter?</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368201014719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368201384060-119</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that not message! that desperate wish. you not see low usage figure? only 1/3 as many w8 user compared to w7 at 100 mio. license point. you not able to tell because you posting from pejing? something else block ability to see and understand? you not still use potato in moon shine!!!!!!!! it eat your brain. if any still left ... :-D now go back out to yard and finish mowing rawn, mr. bigot. :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368201384060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:56:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368201399418-120</Id><Topic><Title>Janet Napolitano for next President</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368200977333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"... could be 77 before she finishes second term. " Her first term should be life without possibility...</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368201399418</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368201421298-121</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>link? triple :haha: rating!!!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368201421298</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:57:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368201472100-122</Id><Title>Check out MISM right now! It is about to go on a massive run</Title><Msg>MISM has proven gold reserves and trades at just .08 cents. This one is going to be huge. Check it out</Msg><Username>jjordan986</Username><Timestamp>1368201472100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368201489501-123</Id><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Msg>ABC News - May 10, 2013 6:33 a.m. ABC News has obtained 12 different versions of the talking points that show they were extensively edited as they evolved from the drafts first written entirely by the CIA to the final version distributed by the administration. White House emails reviewed by ABC News suggest the edits were made with extensive input from the State Department. The edits included requests from the State Department that references to the Al Qaeda-affiliated group Ansar al-Sharia be deleted as well references to CIA warnings {to the administration} about terrorist threats in Benghazi {that were ignored} in the months preceding the attack. That directly contradicts what White House Press Secretary Jay Carney said about the talking points in November. â€œThe White House and the State Department have made clear that the single adjustment that was made to those talking points by either of those two institutions were changing the word â€˜consulateâ€™ to â€˜diplomatic facilityâ€™ because â€˜consulateâ€™ was inaccurate,â€ Carney told reporters at the White House press briefing on November 28, 2012.</Msg><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368201601572-124</Id><Topic><Title>WHY Windows will win this round as well....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368147359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this comment inappropriate! you not allowed to be contestant and judge contest too! :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368201601572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368201964409-125</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Within hours of the initial attack, the State Department sent out two alerts. The first, at 4:05 p.m., indicated that the compound was under attack; the second, at 6:08 p.m., indicated that Ansar al Sharia, an al Qaeda-linked terrorist group operating in Libya, had claimed credit for the attack. The story from Obama, Hillary and Rice that went on for months about it all being a protest about an offensive on-line film was an intentional lie. "What difference does it make" asks Hillary and maybe many low information kooks out there? The administration was warned by the CIA about the terrorists before the strike and did nothing. The embassy pleaded for additional security - they were denied. When the terrorists attacked, Obama went to bed, and the administration did nothing. They HAD to cover up their incompetence. Thanks to the good guys that are willing to trek into the darkness to find and testify to the truth. America deserves it.</Msg><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201964409</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368202302726-126</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The time line now shows lie after coverup lie, after lie. The 4 Americans were allowed to be murdered rather than bring in support because the Administration along with the State Dept's knowledge, and top Military officials were supplying the Muslim Brotherhood with Arms. They didn't want that covert operation known so they gave the "stand down" order to bring in NO support to save the 4 Americans. The attack lasted for 4 hrs. with plenty of time to bring in support.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368202302726</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368202405609-127</Id><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Msg>The slow update schedule for smartphones running Google's Android operating system, along with the resulting fragmentation in OS versions on the platform, creates a security risk for owners of those phones, according to the American Civil Liberties Union. The ACLU's complaint notes that only two percent of the hundreds of millions of Android handsets on the market today are running the most recent version of Android. The majority of handsets run a version released in the last two years, but nearly half of all Android users are running software older than that. This fragmentation of the Android market has led to many users being locked out from some software offerings, such as Facebook Home. It has also led to no small level of discontent within the developer community, with some predicting that independent developers will be squeezed out due to their inability to develop across so many version numbers.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368202657695-128</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft says Yammer sales up 259%, added 312 customers in quarter....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368188028400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IN fact this is the next Big offering by MSFT to large organizations and governments.... THE potential is enormous.... Stay tuned. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202657695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368202980031-129</Id><Topic><Title>Janet Napolitano for next President</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368200977333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>{...and she has the quals} Would you enlighten us with those quals, praytell? We'll give you 15 minutes to scramble over to wiki her. You low information twits would be hilarious, except that your emotion-based voting brings us the wickedness and weakness of the darkness that is upon us now.</Msg><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202980031</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368203482358-130</Id><Title>MSFT: Way OVERBOUGHT: Next 50 DMA=$29.69 or 200 DMA:$28.60</Title><Msg>Stampede for exit next???</Msg><Username>jpmhedgefund</Username><Timestamp>1368203482358</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368203533529-131</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft says Yammer sales up 259%, added 312 customers in quarter....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368188028400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so, you increase personal yammer in response now? :haha: potential across electric power substation terminal points enormous too. but no sane person will touch them. pr-speak not a real discussion, osso! it just more yammering ...</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368203533529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368203918009-132</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SO folks, just Bing this article as there are more critical comments.... SO with 2% Security, all the Android fanboys are either lying through their teeth or are clueless and dumb like a door #$%$.... Also the developer community seems to get ready to dump this junk as they may also be implicated in any class action lawsuit as they basically face mission impossible as now one is minding the shop while keep selling this bogus and flawed OS. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368203918009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368204090758-133</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again, another excellent and informed report from you, ossobucco. While I bought MSFT between $26/$28, I just bought 1,500 more shares on this current dip. This is a $40 stock by this summer and a $50 stock by the end of the year.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1368204090758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368204099139-134</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft says Yammer sales up 259%, added 312 customers in quarter....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368188028400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh oh - its the noodle guy ! noodle you need to spend some time trysting with phands- You two could make mad passionate ........-well at least he would side with you in your jihad against Microsoft</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368204099139</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368204301774-135</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>once again dopey bengahazi isn more than a little hill of sh.t --kind of like you in that respect isn't it - the only lie is the big lie that the RWNJ's and the GOP try to propagate every time they open their mouths</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368204301774</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368204562661-136</Id><Topic><Title>Janet Napolitano for next President</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368200977333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're lazy, enlighten yourself. Her quals are there to see. She would be a great Pres. How about some evidence on your other claims, too lazy? Or there is none, is the better answer.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368204562661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368204803014-137</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft says Yammer sales up 259%, added 312 customers in quarter....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368188028400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where you see noodle guy? this mean you posting from non-existent location of pejing? :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368204803014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368204825091-138</Id><Title>It's OK for the Abomination team to yammer</Title><Msg>away all day, with opinions, not evidence, but then claim every one else with court ready evidence is a liar. The term I heard for this recently is "online fukery", and it fits. Buy MSFT buy buy buy</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368204825091</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368204968587-139</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"once again dopey bengahazi isn more than a little hill of sh.t " You got that backwards, Wally. The official line from the Liar in Chief on Benghazi is a pile of #$%$ from the Hill or the Hill ary. Too bad it wasn't you in the consulate and your relatives telling us it doesn't matter, eh? But in fact in that case it wouldn't matter.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368204968587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368205113389-140</Id><Topic><Title>Janet Napolitano for next President</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368200977333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Hilary steps aside, Janet should go for it. I liked the way she handled the questions recently, besides her great resume. She has the right stuff to be Pres.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1368205113389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368205271930-141</Id><Topic><Title>Janet Napolitano for next President</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368200977333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah. I'd like to see a woman get the job next time around.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1368205271930</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368205339821-142</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's Bing? Is that the half-baked Google clone? I saw an ad for it the other night, I think.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1368205339821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368205512032-143</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"{to the administration}{that were ignored}" opinions about opinions, opinions within opinions, or as some call it "online fukery." I call it something else too, but "online fukery" is a good one.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368205512032</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:05:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368205749917-144</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The proof is there for anyone to see that they lied to the American public to save Obama's sorry incompetent a&amp;&amp;, it's good ABC finally got so embarrassed even they could no longer deny it.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368205749917</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368205951594-145</Id><Title>I have seen individual stock pumps for as long as there has been a market, before Obama</Title><Msg>I had never seen blatant, open pumping of the overall market to pretend failure is success. At $685 when AAPl began it's consolidation they did the exact same thing, they can do it with a single stock and even so with AAPL it failed. It requires coordination, and that is illegal, but what isn't with Obama in office?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368205951594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368205964192-146</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What- do you think your sweethearts have finally found the smoking gun?? If you weren't so stoooopid ;you would recognize that there is no smoking gun- there are only desperate ignorant Tdouchebaggers who are willing to commit crimes themselves to smear the Democrats- that ought to really make you proud- when they don't find anything you will be down to your last desperate hope which will have failed- will you be popping some cyanide capsules hawfaeces- let us know- also try and let Beelzibub know- he is preparing a place for you in the hottest circle of hades and may need to hurry a little</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368205964192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368206127059-147</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again no evidence supporting your claim, including the title. Zilch, zero, nada. It's getting to be be too much, to see how excited you get on false , or faux, news. One humiliation for you after another, and you change aliases and come back for more punishment. If you went to high school, somewhere in there someone must have told you what the words proof and evidence mean.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1368206127059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:15:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368206334152-148</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What- do you think your sweethearts have finally found the smoking gun??" I don't think that. They have found dozens of smoking guns since the criminal in chief took office and they swept them all under the rug. I think they found the smoking artillery piece and the noise is too loud to ignore and pretend it isn't there. ABC News caved because they had a choice to admit it or commit journalistic suicide.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368206334152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:18:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368206569746-149</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe msft should try this since it seems to have really boosted android sales! :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368206569746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368206639273-150</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that the drain hole where all the online services div. money go. :-D</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368206639273</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368206688324-151</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only smoking guns are the ones that Darrell Issa brought about on himself back in the days when he was a car thief- Issa being a thief and criminal himself thinks everybody else is a thief also- the typical reaction of the habitual criminal and psychopath- once again one of your sweethearts. But I guess you like other psychos feel no guilt for your own crimes and suspect everybody else and Issa is ok with you. This characteristic is prevalent and is a prerequisite to entering the Tbagger organization</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368206688324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:24:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368206699855-152</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sorry but you are wrong. It is the OS of Google and possibly criminal actions of its software developers.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368206699855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368206912142-153</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so 2% of newest version on phones = 2% security? you know only 3% of pc using w8 so far, right? (i already posted link. can you find it?) ;) new aclu suit coming soon? :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368206912142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368206948734-154</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is near zero security, hope the regulators are going to step in and shut this thing down.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368206948734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368207356145-155</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you notice they suing carriers, right? not google, not phone maker, not developer, etc. you notice they want more android delivered to consumer, not get rid of it, right? so if consumers get safe updated android os, then what? oh, right, end of world for android and google!!!!!!!!!! :haha: or maybe msft just get a little more patent money from increase in android market share bcuz consumer like it and since they can't sell own phone os. ;..-D</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368207356145</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:35:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368207403195-156</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we go to $35 and new record high today again too? :-D</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368207403195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:36:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368207603186-157</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft says Yammer sales up 259%, added 312 customers in quarter....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368188028400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the future of corporate communications from the HR, to the CIO, CTO and the CEO all the way to the Board. Everyone communicates freely without restriction and exchange news, ideas and is a great educational and developmental tool.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368207603186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:40:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368207788484-158</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it seem you are wrong about updates. as usual with most of your posts. :-D nexus. new ver. always avail. carrier cannot block it. you not liable for posting libel here? :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368207788484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368208192171-159</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the proof is there why can't you show it. You have nothing but your lies, is why. Just be honest already, show evidence, not opinions, when you claim "someone said". So far, on many multiple issues over long periods of time, you show nothing but your opinions on other opinions. Means nothing.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368208192171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368208415564-160</Id><Title>Bloomberg: Greenhouse Gases Hit Threshold Unseen in 3 Million Years</Title><Msg>The concentration of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere surpassed 400 parts per million for the first time since measurements began, breaching a threshold not seen for 3 million years. The main greenhouse gas blamed for global warming averaged 400.03 parts per million at a monitoring station on Hawaiiâ€™s Mauna Loa volcano yesterday, according to data published today on the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration website. The administrationâ€™s data stretches back to 1958. The reading is considered a landmark by scientists and environmentalists, who say carbon emissions caused by burning fossil fuels are warming the planet and must be reined in before they cause irreversible changes to weather, sea levels and Arctic ice cover. â€œWe are in the process of creating a prehistoric climate that humans have no evolutionary experience of,â€ Bob Ward, policy director at the Grantham Research Institute on Climate Change and the Environment at the London School of Economics said in a telephone interview. The last time CO2 levels were this high was at least 3 million years ago, he said. Then, â€œtemperatures were 2 to 3 degrees Celsius higher than pre-industrial times, the polar ice caps were much smaller, and sea levels were about 20 meters (66 feet) higher than today,â€ he said. ********************************************************************************************** BELIEVE THE SCIENCE OR BELIEVE THE KOCH BROS, THEIR SHILLS ON THIS BOARD AND THE HOUSE MEMBERS IN THEIR POCKETS. THE CHOICE IS YOURS.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368208415564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368208465428-161</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good to know as we should all be buying on the dips. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368208465428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368208503476-162</Id><Topic><Title>Janet Napolitano for next President</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368200977333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a good call, it's something to think about. After the questioning and how she handled herself, she will do well. I'm on board.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1368208503476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368208777783-163</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By design? There are a plethora of different things going on. From the US Gov &amp; Military concerned about spying &amp; hacking, id theft and other odd happenings like 100's of thousands of clicks redirected to google ad sense pages and generating 100's of millions of dollars in phony ad clicks. That means someone allows other peoples ads to be delivered to their own web site and they get paid and google get's paid by the advertisers whose ad words account ads are displayed. The likely hood of figuring out how to bypass googles security for click fraud and malware detection without internal previous or current knowledge from the inside of google is slim to none. Google says Russian &amp; Chinese organized crime controls it. I have ad words and ad sense. If you even click your own ads one time they shut it off. These people have figured out how to hit a page 100's of thousand times without being detected. You cannot do what they are doing without some internal experience in google its software, safeguards and policies on detecting fraud accounts. You don't just learn how to hack Linux and be able to know their extensive security policies to prevent even minor click fraud. That part of it is just too hard to do and to blame it on some organized crime outfits is iffy. We are not talking about just redirecting a hit. We are talking about bypassing numerous google safeguards and taking over peoples phones and browser undetected. Not likely that they cannot trace, stop or explain it. I have no knowledge that it is being done internally, I just do not know how it can happen being a programmer and a little familiar with their policies. I could not do it as I have no idea how googles internal safeguards are set-up to catch click fraud.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368208777783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368208945721-164</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg: Greenhouse Gases Hit Threshold Unseen in 3 Million Years</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368208415564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:53:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>66 feet should get rid of The Feeces and his whole clan of misfits. It's almost worth it.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1368208945721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368208962662-165</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libel vs. Slander?????? The FBI is the one who originally said all this. Should they sue them? They will not be intimidated by your post. You can't get them to just go away. Goog is at the heart of the entire US Information Technology week link. They are going to have to make changes or they are going to be tied up in court like Microsoft was with the DOJ.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368208962662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:02:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368209564578-166</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg: Greenhouse Gases Hit Threshold Unseen in 3 Million Years</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368208415564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:53:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And nothing happened as to warming, coldest spring in recorded history.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368209564578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368209963109-167</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg: Greenhouse Gases Hit Threshold Unseen in 3 Million Years</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368208415564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:53:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>das right hawcreek, don U wurry ur ole grey haired head about it, the problem will be borne out by Andrew and his peers.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368209963109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368210267228-168</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More utter garbage from ossokkkunto.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368210267228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368210400665-169</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bing has not had the ad click fraud problem that google does. The FBI is not putting out warnings on Microsoft only Android. I have said that all of this almost sounds like some message board BS. It is not, they are really investigating and making accusations. I think it is crazy every single time this comes up. The Microsoft Phones are hard as hell to hack. I was originally doing Silverlight programming which used XAP files. You cannot visit a website and have your Microsoft Phone infected, etc. Documentation I have read says can only install a xap app via the sdmicro card on the phone if you do not go through the Microsoft Store. That does not sound correct to me, but I have not had a chance to play around with it yet. Most of the phones do not even have an SD micro card. Luckily I have one to experiment with. You cannot get any malware through their system and you cannot alter source code. I am working on ways to get legitimate apps on the phones via xap files without going through the Windows Store for businesses. Windows Phone &amp; Android are just so far on different ends of the security measuring stick they cannot be compared.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368210400665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368210403877-170</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg: Greenhouse Gases Hit Threshold Unseen in 3 Million Years</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368208415564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:53:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess I missed something in the thread re Andrew and peers but nevertheless I suspect you missed somethingas well. He says the CO2 levels are where they were when sea levels were 20 metres higher, ergo CO2 was not the issue, moe. Actual sea levels are not rising, moe, they make excuses why they're not.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368210403877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368210731494-171</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg: Greenhouse Gases Hit Threshold Unseen in 3 Million Years</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368208415564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:53:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A implies B does not mean B implies A Ask your son Andrew about it....</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368210731494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368210732135-172</Id><Title>Why the new Xbox will beat the Apple iTV to the Smart TV punch (Source Techradar)</Title><Msg>Folks this is a great write up, just Bing it! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368210732135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:32:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368210909744-173</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If the proof is there why can't you show it." Ever see a picture from the third world perhaps of a mother hugging the body of a dead child and denying it is dead? That's you with Obama's agenda.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368210909744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368211141669-174</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU see the only way Google, Android Phone suppliers, service providers and ecosystem can escape potential class action lawsuits is to post Disclaimers on their phones that "Buyer Beware".... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368211141669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368211173801-175</Id><Topic><Title>Bloomberg: Greenhouse Gases Hit Threshold Unseen in 3 Million Years</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368208415564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 13:53:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A implies B does not mean B implies A" How many times must any real scientist fail to see what he/she expects to see before a real scientist would question that "A" implies "B"? "Ask your son Andrew about it..." Ah yes, my son Andrew, my bad, I didn't immediately make the connection, of course.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368211173801</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368211823685-176</Id><Topic><Title>Why the new Xbox will beat the Apple iTV to the Smart TV punch (Source Techradar)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368210732135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:32:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow this will be the game changer and not only batter apple's hopes but also go after Netflix. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368211823685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368212569931-177</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, but I've seen similar in the third world. Most parents in the first and second world would do the same. Where's your proof? Evidence? Can't find it? Lost it? Never had it? Someone stole it? Afraid to show the truth? Lazy? hahahahaha. woo this frustration is tough going hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368212569931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368212943515-178</Id><Title>Current sea level rise</Title><Msg>Current sea level rise Sea levels around the world are rising. Current sea-level rise potentially affects human populations (e.g., those living in coastal regions and on islands)[2] and the natural environment (e.g., marine ecosystems).[3] Between 1870 and 2004, global average sea levels rose 195 mm (7.7 in).[4] From 1950 to 2009, measurements show an average annual rise in sea level of 1.7 Â± 0.3 mm per year, with satellite data showing a rise of 3.3 Â± 0.4 mm per year from 1993 to 2009,[5] a faster rate of increase than previously estimated.[6] It is unclear whether the increased rate reflects an increase in the underlying long-term trend.[7] Two main factors contributed to observed sea level rise.[8] The first is thermal expansion: as ocean water warms, it expands.[9] The second is from the contribution of land-based ice due to increased melting. The major store of water on land is found in glaciers and ice sheets. Sea level rise is one of several lines of evidence that support the view that the climate has recently warmed.[10] It is very likely that human-induced (anthropogenic) warming contributed to the sea level rise observed in the latter half of the 20th century.[11] Sea level rise is expected to continue for centuries.[12] In 2007, the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) projected that during the 21st century, sea level will rise another 18 to 59 cm (7.1 to 23 in), but these numbers do not include "uncertainties in climate-carbon cycle feedbacks nor do they include the full effects of changes in ice sheet flow".[13] More recent projections assessed by the US National Research Council (2010)[14] suggest possible sea level rise over the 21st century of between 56 and 200 cm (22 and 79 in).</Msg><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368212943515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368213188148-179</Id><Title>Will MSFT ever go up?</Title><Msg>will this pig EVER have an up day? what happens when the markets start having down days? this pig will get CRUSHED , that's what</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1368213188148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368213259714-180</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The 4 Americans were allowed to be murdered rather than bring in support because the Administration along with the State Dept's knowledge, and top Military officials were supplying the Muslim Brotherhood with Arms" Is that the MBA group for short? yeah that's what hapened all right, mmm hmmm. Time for meds, then crafts, lunch, and nap nap time. hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>kinderyimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368213259714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368213273909-181</Id><Topic><Title>Why the new Xbox will beat the Apple iTV to the Smart TV punch (Source Techradar)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368210732135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:32:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i just saw picture. apple will sue for sure. it exact copy of mac mini! gray case, small form factor, rounded corner, etc., etc., etc. :-D best thing about article is it very long. lots of room for ads on page! but not a lot of ads there anyway. just lot of links to other pages on web site. article up for 5 hour and no comment. maybe kind of low traffic site. kinf of chatty but not just fanboi drivel. lots of background about smart tv and why they not take off (and so smart tv controllers still stalled and not already selling well), other player in tv game, and how it show msft going more into hardware and need to get into more market/product. great? meh. but i give it a 6. way better than most stuff you want us to look at tho! :-)</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368213273909</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368213529343-182</Id><Topic><Title>Janet Napolitano for next President</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368200977333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>figures you would judge her without evidence, called "online fukery" by others here But yeah that Janet Napolitano has promise, she should go for it..</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1368213529343</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:18:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368213551807-183</Id><Title>Down EVERY day this week!!</Title><Msg>That's: Monday DOWN ! Tuesday DOWN ! Wednesday DOWN ! Thursday DOWN ! Friday DOWN ! At least it's consistent! OINK OINK OINK</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1368213551807</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368213780071-184</Id><Title>Even Janet (from another planet) Napolitano would be better than Obama</Title><Msg>I think she told the truth once or twice.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368213780071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368213836629-185</Id><Title>Shorts have been aggressive this week....</Title><Msg>Going into the weekend short will be futile.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368213836629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368213953845-186</Id><Topic><Title>Current sea level rise</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368212943515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would feel sorry for you gullible moes if you were not trying to impose your pseudo science quakery on the rest of us. CO2 levels are where they were when the water was 66 feet higher (per you) why are we guessing in millimeters for the pretend rise? Why is the water not 30 feet higher now?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368213953845</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368214118902-187</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU Asks Government to Investigate Phone Carriers Over Android Security Threat....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367838976579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 07:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have link to fbi mouthing false claim by osso? you think fbi never been sued? ever? (you think they read my post, too? maybe have hole in foil hat!) you have info on link between google and technology week? not hear of that before ... ;) or that just a typo? google making changes to search all the time. some by choice/need/mistake some under pressure. not the same thing as os developer or owner being complicit with criminal gang in fraud, theft, id theft, or cattle dying in drought in youbetchastan. ;) if two layer of foil not enough consider custom aluminum casting.</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368214118902</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368214155111-188</Id><Title>Why Benghazi matters:</Title><Msg>About a month after the attacks, at the solemn ceremony where the bodies of the American victims from Benghazi were returned to Andrews Air Force base in flag-draped coffins, Secretary of State Hillary Clinton told Charles Woods â€” father of Tyrone, a slain Navy seal whose body lay nearby â€” that the administration would hunt down and arrest the anti-Muslim filmmaker whom she shamelessly tried to blame for the Woods family loss. That filmmaker remains jailed on a parole violation, continuing to serve as a scapegoat for the failings of the Obama administration. Meanwhile, the perpetrators of the Benghazi attack run free and presumably plan new attacks against America, either overseas or here at home. That's the point of this week's latest Benghazi hearings: Americans deserve the truth. If that reflects mistakes by the administration, so be it.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368214155111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368214216740-189</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts have been aggressive this week....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368213836629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meathead guarantees new highs next week !!!!!!! $40-$45-$50 - then $100 by 4th of July - GUARANTEED!!!!!! LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLLOLOLOL!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1368214216740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368214549257-190</Id><Topic><Title>Why Benghazi matters:</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368214155111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:29:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cauze it gives the RWNJ truckloads of fukery to post, dat is Y it matters.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368214549257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368214573264-191</Id><Topic><Title>Why Benghazi matters:</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368214155111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:29:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's hope the real perpetrators get jailed, and the Grand Shanker gets impeached.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368214573264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368214605054-192</Id><Topic><Title>Current sea level rise</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368212943515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because A implies B does not mean B implies A think about hawcrack.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368214605054</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368215022141-193</Id><Topic><Title>Why Benghazi matters:</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368214155111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:29:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already done with finals, Frito? Betchu got that game controller in your hand already, eh? Mommy making you work this summer, or you just gonna hang out in her basement yelling for more grilled cheese sandwiches and Flamin' Hot Funyuns?</Msg><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368215022141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368215096586-194</Id><Topic><Title>Janet Napolitano for next President</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368200977333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know Janet and one thing is for sure, she doesn't spend her time fantasizing about "kinky fukery" that obviously you do. (It's obvious you are obsessed as you use that word on almost every post.) Is that new word the only thing you got out of "Shades"? Just asking Yea, I think she should go for it too.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368215096586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368215305282-195</Id><Topic><Title>Current sea level rise</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368212943515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A implies B" Because you SAY A implies B but it never actually does, means you should question your premise, think about that Science Moe.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368215305282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368215399389-196</Id><Title>IT would be interesting to see what Phone the Google, Samsung and the Carriers' Top Management Use....</Title><Msg>That would shed more light on the Android fiasco....</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368215399389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368215402498-197</Id><Topic><Title>Janet Napolitano for next President</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368200977333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:49:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ANGELA MILLER FOR PRESIDENT..!!.. " LIVE ON AMERICAN IDOL"</Msg><Username>trendpicker</Username><Timestamp>1368215402498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368215565835-198</Id><Topic><Title>Why Benghazi matters:</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368214155111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:29:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ironically the Americans may have given their lives for an unintended but positive cause. Obama fell into the trap that only a man child would (don't blame me, mommy) and thus, now caught, his second term agenda (of destruction) is as dead as the Americans he failed to protect.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368215565835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368216326036-199</Id><Title>Today's futures low = 15,000.00 = pure coincidence, no manipulation going on here</Title><Msg>move along, nothing to see. Bernanke was not sitting there with the plunge team re-nymed the pump team to make sure there was no run if 15,000.0000000 was broken, no sire, all coicidence.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368216326036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368216560735-200</Id><Topic><Title>Why Benghazi matters:</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368214155111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:29:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you done makin burritos on the corner of loser and stew pid.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368216560735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368216742138-201</Id><Topic><Title>Current sea level rise</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368212943515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now hawstewpid, U said asked why B - A isn't true, I told you.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1368216742138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368218328999-202</Id><Topic><Title>Current sea level rise</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368212943515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because have just recently arrived at those CO2 levels, you dumb baldheaded pig. Now that we have reached those CO2 levels the temps and the sea levels will climb until they reach the same benchmark as 2 million years ago, you stupid baldheaded pig.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368218328999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368218371092-203</Id><Title>Boston Replacing M$ Exchange With Google Apps</Title><Msg>Excellent news..... ...................................................... "The city of Boston, which employs 20,000 people, has become the latest large organization to switch from Microsoft Exchange to Google Apps. The city estimates that the move will save it $280,000 a year. Microsoft's reaction? 'We believe the citizens of Boston deserve cloud productivity tools that protect their security and privacy. Google's investments in these areas are inadequate, and they lack the proper protections most organizations require.' More and more customers aren't buying that FUD." ........................................................</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368218371092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:39:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368218386236-204</Id><Title>Nokia Extends Asha Family</Title><Msg>Google it... Quoting: "Global handset manufacturer, Nokia Corporation (NOK), introduced Asha 501, the first from its new Asha smartphone platform. The company is targeting the entry level smartphone customers who want to upgrade their phones. "Asha 501 happens to be the first smartphone to be built on the new Asha platform, which is an open standard platform and allows any developer to create and upload mobile applications. The new smartphone possesses many high-end features like a 4GB memory card, Wi-Fi facility, a 3.2 megapixel camera and is preloaded with social networking sites. However, the 3 inch screen is smaller than most smartphones and it does not support 3G networks. "Significantly, Nokia has introduced two new features namely Home and Fastlane in the smartphone. Home is a standardised application grid used for launching individual apps while Fastlane keeps track of the recently accessed contacts, social networks and applications used by the user. "Asha 501 is designed to simplify smartphone usage and comes at a low price of $99. The phone is expected to be shipped from Jun 2013 and is likely to be available through 60 operators and distributors spread across 90 countries." ________________________________________ I like the part about allowing any developer to create and upload mobile applications...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368218386236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:39:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368218885336-205</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Extends Asha Family</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368218386236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:39:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah...windoze phone has failed Nokia.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368218885336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368218924161-206</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Replacing M$ Exchange With Google Apps</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368218371092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:39:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like Microsoft's moat is beginning to silt up...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368218924161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:48:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368219157827-207</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Extends Asha Family</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368218386236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:39:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That has nothing to do with Microsoft Windows 8 Phone. Nokia Asha is just Nokia no connection to Microsoft and that phone is a very low end 2g phone for developing markets. Windows 8 does not let any developer to upload mobile applications. Windows 7 used Silverlight which is xap. Windows 8 is different xaml but still uses xap files to deploy. I just happened to get into the Silverlight developing when it first came out so I am way ahead of the game on the xap files and deployment. It would take someone months to a year to be able to figure all of the stuff involved in Windows 8 phone development and deployment. It is hard stuff not like creating a web site. You can actually use html/java to build Windows 8 apps now. So it is easy. I am just saying the deploying and creating xap files and knowing how to get them onto the phone is a major project. Hacking W8 phone will never ever in a million years get to the point of Android. Those guys cannot figure it out and even if there are isolated problem it will never be like 60% infected with Malware which is what I heard about Android. That Asha probably is just as bad. That has nothing to do with Microsoft though. Maybe take the Asha phone being unsecure over to the nuts on the Nokia board. Microsoft Windows 8 phones are safe as you can get. Nothing is ever fool proof but it is not a freaking cluster F like Android.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368219157827</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368219211492-208</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Extends Asha Family</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368218386236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:39:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm trying to learn more about the Asha platform. I'd bet it's related to Android, but don't really know, very little solid info available.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368219211492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:53:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368219252269-209</Id><Topic><Title>SJVN: M$'s most profitable mobile Operating System is Android</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368146306279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:38:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumpo bump....</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368219252269</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:54:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368219548474-210</Id><Title>Windows Phone &amp; Blackbarry 10 OS can become leader few years out.</Title><Msg>Both OS is far superior than iOS &amp; Android (Security, Social function integration, Interface, business function). Application advantage for iOS and Android is short live as applications are standalone and not integrate like web. People will soon realize using Web is better option in most cases (As Mobile web become more mature). iOS and Android can't change their core OS easily and so They can trunout as loser if they can't upgrade OS to match.</Msg><Username>vs1234gs</Username><Timestamp>1368219548474</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368220094391-211</Id><Topic><Title>IT would be interesting to see what Phone the Google, Samsung and the Carriers' Top Management Use....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368215399389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:49:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have news for you, most people in this world do not care if there are privacy can be violated on a phone or they think it will never happen to them. Once I had an apple device and all of a sudden I hear this guy snoring on the phone. I was like what the F. I had not made any calls and the device was at the start screen. Someone listening in fell asleep while eavesdropping and started snoring. I than realized it was real. I also have been able to demo a phone taking video and recording with the screen off and camera off. Even if you had it in your hand you would not know it was recording. Unless it happens to you, most people will not believe it or care. Apple has had problems also and that is a closed system. Right now the only thing Microsoft has on it's side is hacking the phone is hard as hell and the guys that are used to effortless hacking on the Android are going to be like what the F is this. I cannot spend a year trying to figure out Windows 8 framework and how to get a xap file on there. It's like going to school for a few years. I am wondering the posts on here are on the up and up. Because yesterday I started talking about this and I was the only one talking about this. I think I will take a time out and check some news feeds to see if the posts on here are true. This is sounding like someone may be trying to razz me because I was talking about it.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368220094391</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368220278035-212</Id><Topic><Title>Down EVERY day this week!!</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1368213551807</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so that a new record hah! every day this week? i predict it will hit another new price on monday!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368220278035</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368220401110-213</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there's a hole in daddy's arm where all the money goes ... --j. prine</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368220401110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368220441900-214</Id><Topic><Title>SJVN: M$'s most profitable mobile Operating System is Android</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368146306279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:38:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quoting from the article: 'Today, only Motorola Mobility, a division of Google and Huawei, remains free of the Microsoft-Android intellectual-property (IP) tax. In a statement to Dow Jones Business News, Google spokesman Matt Kallman said: "This is the same tactic we've seen time and again from Microsoft. Instead of building great new products, Microsoft attacks the competition, and tries to drive up the prices of Android devices for consumers." 'No case has ever been successfully made for any of Microsoft's undisclosed patents that are being used to profit from Android, but that's not what is important for businesses. The bottom line is that it's usually cheaper to pay off patent trolls than it is to fight them in court. Whether Microsoft's publicly undisclosed patents are valid or have any relevance to Android is beside the point. 'That's why Motorola Mobility's patent lawsuit against Microsoft is anything but done. In today's legal climate, the biggest companies use patents to battle over market share and patent licensing. Nokia, Microsoft, and Oracle's attempt to knock Android out of the European Union market as "a below-cost Trojan horse", is simply another tactic in their legal attempts to win profits from a market where Microsoft is unable to compete with its products.'</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368220441900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368220515249-215</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Replacing M$ Exchange With Google Apps</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368218371092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:39:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When they start getting sued after someone steals info with address and pictures and commits some type of crime. They will not think it is cheaper if 1000's of people have their id's stolen and the city records are being spied on etc. Who the heck is going to want to use a system that everyone and his brother all over the world can get into. That is negligence if you keep public records on it. I say start the law suits. Who want's to be the first to get paid?</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368220515249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368221176008-216</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts have been aggressive this week....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368213836629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so, you not know that short interest go from 118 mio. share on 4/15 to 99 mio. as of 4/30 then? and time to cover now down to just over 1 day. you still saying 250 mio. share short? maybe all that aggressive covering last month is what make both price and vol. go down all this week? :-D that and accumulation. both hard on stock price and vol. right? :haha: you think they keep shorting just as much on sat. and sun. too?!?!?!? :haha: maybe by mon. there be no short interest at all! this may make disaster! price take sharp drop and vol. go to zero!!??!!?? lucky i do lot of aerobics! otherwise i die laughing!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368221176008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368221697974-217</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Replacing M$ Exchange With Google Apps</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368218371092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:39:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do talk some utter #$%$, #$%$.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368221697974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368221815195-218</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia Extends Asha Family</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368218386236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:39:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>application grid? get torch and pitchfork!! kill the monster! recently used apps? get priest to exorcise same old song touchwiz!!!!! ashadroid rising from graveyard of feature phone that have 30% die-off last qtr.!! i e e e e e ! :-D well if not able to beat android then join it, huh?</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368221815195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368221914944-219</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all already know you're stupid....you don't have to prove it again and again. You do realise that ACLU are suing the CARRIERS? For not updating to the available, newer version? And I note you say nothing about the fact that M$ left 7.x windoze phone victims with no future at all? Ossodi ldo: a waste of atoms.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368221914944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:38:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368222720381-220</Id><Topic><Title>SJVN: M$'s most profitable mobile Operating System is Android</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368146306279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:38:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uh oh. new z-land going to outlaw software patent! it not matter how tiny they are tho ... :-) and now "CLS Bank v. Alice Corp. has been decided"! and court "finds many software patents ineligible"! can google get refund and give moto back to prev. owner? will apple now start to sell license to some patent they not allow before so that they can get $ for them before they no longer valid? msft, well, they already got paided, so maybe they already know this coming and did blackmail on everyone before it fall into dustbin of bad idea in law &amp; tech.</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368222720381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368222817546-221</Id><Topic><Title>Why the new Xbox will beat the Apple iTV to the Smart TV punch (Source Techradar)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368210732135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 14:32:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mark May 21/2013 as the day gaming and streaming video will change forever.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368222817546</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368222886337-222</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft says Yammer sales up 259%, added 312 customers in quarter....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368188028400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368222886337</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368222944006-223</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Phone &amp; Blackbarry 10 OS can become leader few years out.</Title><Username>vs1234gs</Username><Timestamp>1368219548474</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roman empire come back too? farce up ear your to modern empire! i can wait, but can't go back in time.</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1368222944006</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368223020062-224</Id><Topic><Title>Current sea level rise</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368212943515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" U said asked why B - A isn't true, " I missed his post but you are responding to my post and you are a lair, I never asked that. Are you truly that stupid?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368223020062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368223238340-225</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IT is also important to bear in mind that CIOs and CTOs are an integral part of MSFT ecosystem and that is how Mr. Softy has stolen the hearts and minds of real decision makers in the Enterprise space. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368223238340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368223250284-226</Id><Title>To be fair to O'bummer, he does have the most transparent administration ever.</Title><Msg>I have never seen anything or anyone so obviously, openly corrupt and then lie at every turn. Benghazi is just the latest and the one he got so openly caught at.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368223250284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368223409314-227</Id><Topic><Title>May 21/2013: The Nail in the Death of PC Myth's Coffin....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368039617319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mark your calendars folks.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368223409314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:03:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368223538893-228</Id><Topic><Title>Why Benghazi matters:</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368214155111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:29:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Are you done makin burritos on the corner of loser and stew pid" Ewww! Making burritos on your head sounds like a disgusting concept.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368223538893</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368223556024-229</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shadup s-k,a-n,k</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368223556024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368223948275-230</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the service that offers better search results, cheaper advertising and privacy. You sound like a guy with no kids or females around you. If you had kids or a girlfriend or wife, you would take the google lack of privacy more seriously. It is really not a joke. Luckily the average criminal would not know how to do anything. I just hate to think how many guys are getting their jollies looking at a 13 year girl in her room secretly. Looking at her searches, looking at her messages. He can see her texts. If you think it is a joke, it is not. If a small company did what google is doing they would be in pull ups in the county joint. It is basically too big to prosecute. What do investigators do when they get to the campus. They will be awe struck and they will be met by professionals and then what do they do. They do not know where to go, how to look in the system. Google is going to just act professional and they will all smile and shake hands. It is like the banks "too big to fail". Google will be "too big to prosecute". The campus is just too impressive and it makes them look like they own the world. They probably will get a slap on the wrist and a pep talk. Then the investigators will eat in the cafeteria.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368223948275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:12:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368224458232-231</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft says Yammer sales up 259%, added 312 customers in quarter....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368188028400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YAWN....yammer sucks</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368224458232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:20:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368224641806-232</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolute #$%$. Bing sucks #$%$, and is losing money like crazy. As for privacy....who are you kidding? M$ is the least secure software on the planet.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368224641806</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368224672482-233</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GO die, wally.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368224672482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368224998160-234</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Phone &amp; Blackbarry 10 OS can become leader few years out.</Title><Username>vs1234gs</Username><Timestamp>1368219548474</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a load of #$%$.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368224998160</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:29:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368225301186-235</Id><Title>Oh Oh! now Andrea Michelle says what the White House claimed was "NOT TRUE"</Title><Msg>For Pepeekook and others in denial, that is a fancy way to say they lied because it is apparent what they said the KNEW was "NOT TRUE" when they said it.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368225301186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368225378500-236</Id><Title>IRS apologizes, thugs Chicago tactics and goons falling left and right</Title><Msg>We are getting our nation back. Thanks for being so corrupt it was transparent, Obama.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368225378500</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368225387334-237</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that relationship is beginning to wear thin here and there, as witness for example the City of Boston's adoption of Google Apps in preference to Microsoft. Microsoft's situation is looking increasingly desperate, which of course is why you are here, flooding the board with your propaganda.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368225387334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:36:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368225608812-238</Id><Title>Chuck Todd NBC uses the term "Nixonian"</Title><Msg>Nixon was a choir boy compared to Obama.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368225608812</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368226422538-239</Id><Title>Tornado activity hits 60-year low...more weather extremes indicate MMGW????</Title><Msg>What do lower weather extremes indicate? Another attempt to make what we were seeing (short term) match the preconceived notions bites the dust.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368226422538</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368226433384-240</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Okay genius MS employee, I use Google. Go read my search strings, texts, and emails and report back what you find. Just pretend I am the 13 yo girl you fantasize about, weirdo. Luckily for all of us MS was just the right size to prosecute, many many times the world over. Largest criminal monopoly ever. Proud to work for them?</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1368226433384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368227597315-241</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are suing the carriers to do the updates????? The current version is no better. LOL. Google has had the NSA "work" their phones and make them safe for the NSA to use. However, that is not the way it works for public phones. In 2010 google tried to make a deal with NSA to find the wholes in their own system or at least make it a good show that they were trying to deal with the problem. The current version is still being exploited. It would be good to have it updated if they can do it without crashing the phones completely. I am not sure why they think it is safer. No one including google has been able to find the ongoing holes. It needs to be scrapped. They will never ever be able to secure a Linux based phone. You can ask the NSA to look into it, but they cannot be there every minute. The Pentagon etc, are using 3rd party IT security firms to try and enlighten them what to do. In all fairness to Google they do not have an easy solution here. They did not create Linux or it's variants. They are under attack 24/7 from every country in the world. This is not going to be a solve able problem. It is just going to be kicking the can down the road. Let's see how long before Facebook Home has problems. It is scary that all these kids are using Facebook Home running Android. I hope nothing happens, but they should not be allowed to put kids lives in danger.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368227597315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368228344240-242</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read the #$%$ article dimwit. The new versions are MUCH better, and ALL versions of Android are better than anything that ever came out of M$.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368228344240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368228769234-243</Id><Title>Pete Rose, Rob Schneider mock Google for Microsoft Office (Source C/Net)</Title><Msg>Folks this is the latest Microsoft Video.... Just Bing it! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368228769234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368228770870-244</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The difference with the new version is it scans apps that users download on their own and the Google Play store. Users have an option to turn this feature on or off. I have the feeling lot's turn it off to speed installation. Google has admitted they do not know why their software cannot detect all the malware. That is because the code is not all the same. They can just write brand new stuff and keep fooling it. So the ACLU is suing the carriers to force an upgrade that is a little safer but NOT SAFE. #$%$? It only helps if someone downloads a porn app with spy ware or something on their own. It will not stop the ever changing code of the Chinese Army. It's not going to ever be safe. Get over it, this is not going to work.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368228770870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368229066342-245</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You haven't a clue what you're talking about....as usual. The least secure software on the planet remains anything from M$.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368229066342</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368229104214-246</Id><Topic><Title>Pete Rose, Rob Schneider mock Google for Microsoft Office (Source C/Net)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368228769234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's garbage, like you....and no-one uses bog-awful bing.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368229104214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368229130697-247</Id><Title>Boston dumps Microsoft Exchange for Google Apps</Title><Msg>It will cost Boston around $800,000 to move over to Gmail, Google Docs for word processing, and Google's cloud service for storing documents. But by dropping some Microsoft products, the city government will save at least $280,000 a year. "The number one reason that organizations are going to Google is price," said Matt Cain, an analyst at the tech research firm Gartner Inc. so yea, suck on that osso</Msg><Username>fulison</Username><Timestamp>1368229130697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368229194990-248</Id><Title>court ruling could be 'death' of software patents</Title><Msg>On network world now. That would stop the horrible patent-trolling M$ dead in its tracks.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368229194990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368229571734-249</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Replacing M$ Exchange With Google Apps</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368218371092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:39:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump it back up near the other one.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368229571734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368229631471-250</Id><Topic><Title>Boston dumps Microsoft Exchange for Google Apps</Title><Username>fulison</Username><Timestamp>1368229130697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post - I bumped mine on the same topic up just to annoy bone-head osso and the other M$hills.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368229631471</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:47:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368229688731-251</Id><Title>I am going to pass on a tip to some of the Washington Post writers in regards to the city of Boston switching to Google Apps.</Title><Msg>Boston has just gotten over a tragedy and there has been no shortage of talk of the lack of proper security there. So on the same day the ALCU threatens to sue carrier because Google software is not safe they announce they are switching to Google to save money. TO SAVE MONEY!!!! It is just that they did this on the day the ALCU broke the story that really irks me. It makes it worse that they are doing this after what just happened there. You think they would want to make the city safer rather than saving money. I am sending this info and all the info in these threads to Post Reporters. Maybe some of these guys on TV like Fox too. This is crazy. Microsoft comment was they were disappointed the city chose to use unsafe software.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368229688731</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368230329246-252</Id><Topic><Title>court ruling could be 'death' of software patents</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368229194990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quoting: 'The ruling in CLS Bank v. Alice gives "staggering breadth to what is meant to be a narrow judicial exception" on patent ineligibility, she wrote. "And let's be clear: if all of these claims, including the system claims, are not patent-eligible, this case is the death of hundreds of thousands of patents, including all business method, financial system, and software patents as well as many computer implemented and telecommunications patents." 'Several recent U.S. Supreme Court rulings against patent eligibility are "causing a free fall in the patent system," Moore added. "Today, several of my colleagues would take that precedent significantly further, lumping together the asserted method, media, and system claims, and holding that they are all patent-ineligible." '</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368230329246</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368230580072-253</Id><Topic><Title>court ruling could be 'death' of software patents</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368229194990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 1980, software was not patentable, not even copyrightable. The law didn't change, only judicial precedent. It's high time the whole house of cards came crashing down.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368230580072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368230974611-254</Id><Title>Harvard Liquidates Apple Stake After IPhone Sales Lose Steam....</Title><Msg>Harvard University, the worldâ€™s wealthiest university, has liquidated its stake in Apple Inc. as the iPhone makerâ€™s shares tumbled after reaching a record high of $702.10 in September.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368230974611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368231177628-255</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Liquidates Apple Stake After IPhone Sales Lose Steam....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368230974611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:09:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing for you to celebrate, bozo. iPhone sales lost steam because of Android, not because of WP.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368231177628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368231244157-256</Id><Topic><Title>Boston dumps Microsoft Exchange for Google Apps</Title><Username>fulison</Username><Timestamp>1368229130697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big mistake, GOOG is an info stealing monster,huge security risk that will cost them heavily in the long run IMO.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368231244157</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:14:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368231423078-257</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Oh! now Andrea Michelle says what the White House claimed was "NOT TRUE"</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368225301186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Go Watch More FAUX ...." The beauty of this is that ABC broke it. They were smart not to leak emails to Fox or you idiots would be able to dismiss it. ABC broke it, Andrea works for NBC, game over, moe, Obama won't likely resign nor get anything done for the rest of his lame duck presidency. He's a caught thug, denials don't work anymore.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368231423078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368231762337-258</Id><Topic><Title>Boston dumps Microsoft Exchange for Google Apps</Title><Username>fulison</Username><Timestamp>1368229130697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can a MSFT investor be a shill on his own board f**ktard? You SUX shills are a joke,no vested interest, Go post your trash on a SUX board &amp; stink them up.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368231762337</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368231991857-259</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Liquidates Apple Stake After IPhone Sales Lose Steam....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368230974611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:09:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WinDOZE phones are kicking the shet out of AAPL/GOOG I Love it! stay tuned.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368231991857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368232138408-260</Id><Topic><Title>Pete Rose, Rob Schneider mock Google for Microsoft Office (Source C/Net)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368228769234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I give you 2 THUMBS DOWN! Bing is GREAT!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368232138408</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368232389169-261</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU: Android fragmentation creates privacy risk (Source Apple Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368202405609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 12:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SUX is a hackers dream come true shethead it's a proven fact .</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368232389169</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368232390697-262</Id><Topic><Title>court ruling could be 'death' of software patents</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368229194990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK Girls hang on to your G-Strings as there is no ruling and that this is not a new debate.... When you write a book, no one can copy it and give it away for free it, place Ads on it and make a profit.... IF you want free software, the history shows it is a bad idea, just look at the mess Android has created.... ANYONE who thinks software is just a mathematical formula and can not be protected is dishonest to the core.... There are many ways to "design" a software from structural viewpoint that make one software faster, easier to use and more secure, otherwise no one will innovate and any ruling to alter the current status quo will have disastrous implications.... WE live in a capitalistic system and the people are rewarded for their innovation and hard work and anyone who thinks differently can move to North Korea. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368232390697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368232394599-263</Id><Topic><Title>Tornado activity hits 60-year low...more weather extremes indicate MMGW????</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368226422538</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Global warming is leading to it being colder than normal, which is limiting tornadoes this year. What don't you understand?</Msg><Username>don_cornwell</Username><Timestamp>1368232394599</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:33:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368232542378-264</Id><Topic><Title>Current sea level rise</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368212943515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 15:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is no global warming....we as people make stuff up ....then put the spin on it....all phony....in the 70's a new ice age was apon us they were saying....yes our coastlines will change and storms will be bad....some worse than others....BIG DEAL....SOME WILL BE EVEN OF BIBLICAL PROPORTIONS..... the world evolves.....hundreds,..thousands,..millions of years....who knows...."In the grand scheme of things"....if we've been around for thousands of years.....the polution and gases we as a people and the earth give off is nothing....people adjust and adapt and become imune to the environment ....we're kinda like mutants....(we create jobs out of thin air and keep people in the lab)....now that we think we're techniclogically advanced we say we're destroying the earth....ALL BOGUS....what is technology?....we're no more advanced now than the day's of trading rocks.....which we could easily go back to....the point is.....in this universe and the many other's out there that go on forever and ever we assume.....ALL HAVE GASSES....this whole mish mosh of a universe that goes on and on is all comprised of gasses and stuff we don't even have names for....so what ever we do on this planet is nothing.....little old earth and all the cars and smokestacks do not do a darn thing....it's only now that we feel we're so far advanced we make these claims....because we as people feel ....SO MUCH SMARTER....so it must be true.....this earth wioll be here long after we're all gone....WITH PEOPLE ON IT....even if we NUKE ourselves....just saying....</Msg><Username>trendpicker</Username><Timestamp>1368232542378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368232767240-265</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Liquidates Apple Stake After IPhone Sales Lose Steam....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368230974611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:09:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just wait till Windows 8 Phones and Tablets brutalize AAPL and Android based "Mobility" devices.... I say we will see a lot of blood on the Street and red ink on their income statements. Stay tuned. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368232767240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368233106745-266</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Liquidates Apple Stake After IPhone Sales Lose Steam....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368230974611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:09:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree,Trouble with these AAPL/GOOG freaks they started to believe their own BS ,WINTEL will rule mobile like they do the desk IMO.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368233106745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:45:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368233333794-267</Id><Topic><Title>Tornado activity hits 60-year low...more weather extremes indicate MMGW????</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368226422538</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Global warming is leading to it being colder than normal..." Thank you. You are the first to explain it so I could understand.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368233333794</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368233622550-268</Id><Title>Bernake is long Microsoft</Title><Msg>He gave me the nod to BUY THE F'IN DIP on Microsoft today on TV. He said it is worth more than it was before and while we don't know if it is a bubble yet , so far so good right. He then rolled up his sleeves and pushed BUY BUY BUY! FREE MARKET MYTH!</Msg><Username>karla_tango</Username><Timestamp>1368233622550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368233657620-269</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Oh! now Andrea Michelle says what the White House claimed was "NOT TRUE"</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368225301186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think President Obama is doing a fine job. He authorized the taking out of the Somalian Pirates, Osama Bin Laden, and other high profile terrorists. The stock market is at an all time high, unemployment is slowly dropping, why all the gloom, and doom ??</Msg><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1368233657620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368233855674-270</Id><Topic><Title>Boston dumps Microsoft Exchange for Google Apps</Title><Username>fulison</Username><Timestamp>1368229130697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The mayor who doesnâ€™t do e-mail is now on Gmail.... IT will cost them over $800,000.00 to change over so to save $200,000.00 a year and will take one year to migrate to Google.... Boston Mayor doesn't know how to use a computer and doesn't know his #$%$ from his elbow when it comes to IT.... A perfect Scroogle victim and by the time they wake up they have been hacked to death in Cyberspace. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368233855674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:57:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368234363642-271</Id><Topic><Title>Bernake is long Microsoft</Title><Username>karla_tango</Username><Timestamp>1368233622550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah....i heard that also when he was speaking....he specifically mentioned MSFT being higher now than before and blah,blah, blah snooze......but yeah....he did say that....these people aren't up on the market....</Msg><Username>trendpicker</Username><Timestamp>1368234363642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368234998776-272</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Oh! now Andrea Michelle says what the White House claimed was "NOT TRUE"</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368225301186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama acted on information gathered during the Bush administration by methods he opposed. Obama is losing Afghanistan, Obama is a pathological liar, Obama lied to the American people to save his own sorry butt. Obama has enough given up to reduce the numbers, employment is NOT keeping even with population growth. Obama continues to spend $3 to get $1, the stock market tripled during the Great Depression, it means nothing and Obama and Bernanke are openly manipulating the market. Why are you cheering overt failure, or are you so stupid that you think you can continue to spend $3 to get $1 and that will work, Lugi?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368234998776</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368235637539-273</Id><Title>Windows Phone 8 full-resolution media backup goes global....</Title><Msg>This week the developer teams working for Windows Phone camera and photos have announced that users will soon be able to instantly save full-resolution photos and video to the cloud no matter where they are on our planet. Previously this feature had only been available to select users in limited areas, and a full roll-out wasnâ€™t yet on the books. This week Windows Phone 8 will have its full connection to SkyDrive the whole globe wide. This feature will be available within the next few days to everyone using Windows Phone 8, and will be accessible in Photo settings.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368235637539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368235708075-274</Id><Topic><Title>ms money and mistakes</Title><Username>albacornus</Username><Timestamp>1368186532856</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 07:48:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>learn to read, its a good thing, "that's when mistakes will push a company to chap 11" not that Microsoft is that company.</Msg><Username>albacornus</Username><Timestamp>1368235708075</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368235752685-275</Id><Topic><Title>ABC News: Administration Lied About Not Contriving the Benghazi Fairy Tale</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1368201489501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>party before God and Country(men), huh chrissie, err spart</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368235752685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368236297461-276</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Oh! now Andrea Michelle says what the White House claimed was "NOT TRUE"</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368225301186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is nothing showing Pres Obama lied, because he didn't. The next morning, he went out and told the nation about the terrorist attack on BenGhazi, you think so or not. That pops your balloon on the so called cover up, because he already said it was acts of terror. Nothing to cover up. He did not say spontaneous demonstrations. 10,000 dollars to your paypal account if you can prove he said s.d. in the rose garden speech. Andrea is not evidence, again it is still opinion. Next the emerging emails. They need to be fuly verified and investigated before a conclusion about any mistake. Who has not changed wording in emails sent? There were a bunch of people involved, all trying to say the right thing, and that's all it was. It doesn't matter what it is called, Americans were killed. Call it boys out for a lark, the deed has been done already, the name is not what is important. What is important is what the President stated so eloquently in the Rose Garden speech, what we must do, and who we are. It's detrimental to the nation's security to not allow officials to do what they think best at the time, in real time. Name how they like, change the name how they like, it is not good to help terrorists know what is up. Sorry if your excited little pre parade is rained on. You latch onto things like a starving shark. If Obama ever lies I will be the first to say yes he did. So far, nothing.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368236297461</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368238024268-277</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Oh! now Andrea Michelle says what the White House claimed was "NOT TRUE"</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368225301186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He said it was a terrorist attack? HAHAHAHA Obama? That would have been true, and we know Obama never tells the truth.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368238024268</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368238071746-278</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Oh! now Andrea Michelle says what the White House claimed was "NOT TRUE"</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368225301186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 18:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just watching a piece on Jodi Arias. I didn't watch the trial but you and her have a lot in common. Both pathological, neither smart enough to know "game over". Obama's agenda is done, kaput. We may not find out why he lied, tonight Carney shoved Hillary towards the front wheels of the bus, game over, the wheels are coming off that bus, and everyone with a brain knows what I knew from the second month of his presidency, he is a poser and a liar, nothing more, no substance. hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368238071746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368238717791-279</Id><Title>Windows 8 Pro "Tablets" Picking Up Steam....</Title><Msg>D&amp;H cited recent data from research firm ABI Research, which forecast tablet growth shipments to jump 38 percent this year, with 78 percent of U.S. businesses deploying tablets in some capacity as opposed to just 22 percent in 2012. Meanwhile, D&amp;H said it's started to see stronger sales around Windows 8 Pro-based tablets such as the Lenovo ThinkPad Tablet 2 and HP (NYSE:HPQ) ElitePad 900. Davis said Windows 8 Pro tablets are being received much better than Windows RT devices. Additionally some solution providers haven't seen strong demand yet for Android in the commercial market. "We don't see Android happening in the commercial market," said Iris Sepulveda, sales and marketing manager for PR Computer Services. "I think most customers right now on the corporate side are choosing between Apple and Windows." SO FOLKS AS YOU CAN SEE THE ENTERPRISE MARKET IS A MORE SOPHISTICATED ONE AND IT IS DRWING THE BATTLE LINES BETWEEN WINDOWS 8 AND APPL MOBILITY DEVICES FOR OBVIOUS REASONS OF COURSE. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368238717791</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:18:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368240552968-280</Id><Topic><Title>Pete Rose, Rob Schneider mock Google for Microsoft Office (Source C/Net)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368228769234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today the head of MSFT Corporate Communication fired back at the Financial Times for taking MSFT Exec's comments out of context and instead of being an objective reporter resorted to journalistic malpractice.... SO as I wrote a couple of weeks ago, MSFT should get tough with folks who have a vested interest to portray Windows 8 as a bust and call them out by name in public.... Back in February when Samsung management back stabbed Mr. Softy, the corporate decided to let it go which in hindsight was a mistake.... SO the new aggressive posture will be a welcome move for the shareholders and MSFT loyalists alike. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368240552968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368240817140-281</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES Mayor of Boston doesn't know how to use a computer let alone to have an email address or any appreciation for high quality and secure IT infrastructure.... When the City of Boston gets sued by the employees or the residents, they will rush coming back to Mr. Softy in no time. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368240817140</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368241183947-282</Id><Topic><Title>May 21/2013: The Nail in the Death of PC Myth's Coffin....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368039617319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Folks I just posted a report on Windows 8 Tablets sale and it seems that the Corporate clients are NOT buying any Android Tablets and Windows 8 is gaining traction.... There is good demand for HP and Lenovo W-8 Tablets as DELL sells direct and the stats will be out on May 21 when they report along with HP's own direct sales to Corporate clients. THE word also is that Surface Pro is becoming a cult/status symbol with the CIOs and IT professionals as a "MUST HAVE DEVICE". More to come, stay tuned. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368241183947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 22:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368241455049-283</Id><Topic><Title>Pete Rose, Rob Schneider mock Google for Microsoft Office (Source C/Net)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368228769234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 19:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I 100% agree with that strategy.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368241455049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:04:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368241494455-284</Id><Topic><Title>WHY Windows will win this round as well....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368147359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks man as I state my case and let folks with intelligence and integrity make up their own mind and do what is right for them. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368241494455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368243243640-285</Id><Title>Obama likes to present himself as an Abe Lincoln but Abe warned Americans of thugs like Obama</Title><Msg>so he said this We the people are the rightful masters of both Congress and the Courts, not to overthrow the Constitution but to overthrow the men who would pervert the Constitution. ~ Abraham Lincoln Abe an honest righteous man, Obama a demon from HELL</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368243243640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>