<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370756335061-1</Id><Title>Xbox One will go Viral Next Week</Title><Msg>With E3 convention from June 11-13th, it is bound to get a lot of attention. In addition, the shorts, in their attempt to bash the amazing xbox, sited Xbox as a device that the government could potentially use to spy on civilians through camera and motion sensing. Controversy and innovative technology are primed for a media frenzy. My answer is the spy bashing is TAPE. Msft may suggest that you leave your xbox one on all the time to fully take advantage of smart phone synching, video surveillance into your living room while you are on vacation, and immediate voice command as you walk into the living room. But if you don't want any of it, put a scotch tape over the camera. With that being said, here are some of the projected games with this new innovative Kinect motion sensing technology. 1) Track and field- imagine your avatar running through different sceneries as you jump and dodge over obstacles, and fighting off thugs and animals. 2) Fighting games like "street fighters" and "takken" will be amazing as your avatar jumps, kicks, punches-- mirror imaging to your every motions. Special moves like fireballs and helicopter spins may be acquire by a combination of body motion and hand gestures. 3) Sport games like basketball, football, and soccer can not be any more virtual reality as your avatar moves, dribbles, and kicks to your every move. 4) War and combats? Aren't you tired of using those stoneage controllers that hurt your fingers and give you cramps and your joystick doesn't move the way you want to move. With this motion Kinect, your avatar mimicks your every motions; you can crawl, run, jump, and change direction like real life and blast away oponents with msft guns (you have to expect those are coming). Combating obesity is a multitrillion dollar industry, with consumers are having fun jumping, running, dodging in their living room, I wonder if there will be a need to subscribe to 24-hour Nautilus or use that XP90?</Msg><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370756335061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 01:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370756705663-2</Id><Topic><Title>Xbox One will go Viral Next Week</Title><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370756335061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 01:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With Skype, smart phone synch, internet access, movies, music, and voice command, the Xbox One alone will generate more cash than msft's bread and butter softwares.</Msg><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370756705663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 01:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370759102107-3</Id><Topic><Title>This New Rival Is Coming for Apple and Google</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370740962857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 21:22:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not at all. Android already dominates in mobile. The only real contender, iOS, is fading. WP has no chance. W8 is not a factor in mobile, and is not likely to become one. So what is the prospect? When another version of Linux turns up, under the stewardship of the current hardware leader Samsung, there could be a serious contest for dominance between the two versions of Linux.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370759102107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 02:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370773266785-4</Id><Topic><Title>A Lot Of People Are Freaking Out Because They Think Microsoft's New Xbox Is Going To Spy On Them</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370646007639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bing FBI says Android is unsafe. I think you are going to look like a complete fool in just a few short months in regards to Microsoft Phones. I guess all you clowns will just change id's you will be so embarrassed.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1370773266785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 06:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370773342352-5</Id><Title>penguinx64 SUCKS</Title><Msg>Almost as much as phands- and boy that is saying something</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370773342352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 06:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370775467422-6</Id><Topic><Title>you might live in a country founded by geniuses but run by idiots. part 2</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370732148286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:55:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why did Hawcreek waste time making 2 parts to some Right-Wing Opinions ?" to make little girls ask questions?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370775467422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 06:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370782352360-7</Id><Topic><Title>you might live in a country founded by geniuses but run by idiots. part 2</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370732148286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:55:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I couldn't have said it any better. It's good to know there are still people out there that think like me.</Msg><Username>awm0912</Username><Timestamp>1370782352360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 08:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370782586226-8</Id><Topic><Title>you might live in a country founded by geniuses but run by idiots. part 1</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370731828364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said my friend.</Msg><Username>awm0912</Username><Timestamp>1370782586226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 08:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370785312694-9</Id><Topic><Title>you might live in a country founded by geniuses but run by idiots. part 2</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370732148286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:55:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IF is an important word to understand. Five wrong ifs don't make five truths in your silly post.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1370785312694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 09:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370787014749-10</Id><Topic><Title>you might live in a country founded by geniuses but run by idiots. part 1</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370731828364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sign your name at the polls, and you register beforehand. Now who goes to a polling place and says they are someone else and signs the name and votes? What happens when the real voter comes in? First you have to read the names upside down to pick one to say you are that one. Do you really believe all that happens? They still catch it. It doesn't happen, there are many voting procedural laws. There were no requirements to get on a plane except to pay. Isn't it better now? What we had for Obama was OK during Bush's non election. All you say is unrelated garbage. Connecting unrelated dots and saying look , see how bad Obama is doing, see, see. All the world has chaNGED BECAUSE i DIDN'T GET MY WAY, WAAAAA BOOO HOOO.I laugh at you all the time if you hadn't noticed. As for gun rights, one living child saved by one background check is enough reason to have them. Even war guy McCain voted for background checks.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1370787014749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370787144271-11</Id><Title>GT RID OF INTERNET EXPLORER, FIREFOX..DITCHED UPDATER...STILL GET BING...EVERY HOUR. BINGED TO DEATH</Title><Msg>MSFT IS A VIRUS. TROJAN, AND CANCER. VICTIM.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370787144271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370787823791-12</Id><Title>GETTING BINGED. AS MSFT GOES BINGE ON KRAPPY BING. TRYING TO ADD CLICKS. BY AMBUSH !</Title><Msg>GPOP, developers of the mobile sensation "Draw Something" - for $180 million. After months of losing users that once peaked to 14.5 million players over a year ago, Zynga last week shut its New York-based studio, effectively laying off the OMGPOP team. Industry executives say mobile gamers today are spoiled for choice as the industry has exploded. In 2007, when Apple Inc launched the iPhone, there were but a handful of developers. Today, there are hundreds, whose apps sell across the globe on Apple and Google Inc's Android devices. "You see these rocket ships in the industry that explode on the scene with a casual game that's easy to develop with not much money and they gain users quickly. But users get bored or angry because they can't progress without paying more money," Nexon's Mahoney told Reuters in an interview. Nexon has had some success boosting its mobile portfolio, a likely factor behind revenue growth of 24 percent in 2012 to 108 million yen ($1.1 million). LOOKING FOR ANSWERS To stand out from the crowd, developers big and small are seeking ways to build a sustainable business. EA, as one of the best-funded competitors, is turning to data analytics to keep track of its players' gaming patterns and behavior. Japanese gaming giant DeNA is experimenting with on-the-spot tweaks to its games by employees, who adjust conditions depending on what players do, CEO of DeNA West Clive Downie said. Canadian indie studio Noodlecake, known for games like "Zombie Road Trip", is employing loyalty programs similar to airlines with daily virtual currency rewards for first-time and frequent players. Others resort to tricks like seasonal deals and holiday-themed content to boost their rankings on app-download charts during the crucial holiday period. Up-and-coming GungHo, which has seen its shares rise tenfold since October as investors bet on its ability to rise above the fray with its sole title "Puzzle &amp; Dragons," is turning to costly TV advertising to place i</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370787823791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370788070012-13</Id><Topic><Title>A Lot Of People Are Freaking Out Because They Think Microsoft's New Xbox Is Going To Spy On Them</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370646007639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm going to dance naked in front of my Kinnect and moon it. Hopefully, that will appear on Obama's Big Brother monitor at the White House.</Msg><Username>atlas_shrugged_2009</Username><Timestamp>1370788070012</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370788679053-14</Id><Title>Expect to see $42 - $44 this week...</Title><Msg>Run up to ex-div will start late this week with huge gains setting up $75 by July 4th. Cheers. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1370788679053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370789050942-15</Id><Topic><Title>Expect to see $42 - $44 this week...</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1370788679053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:37:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe bro, will buy 1 million shares tomorrow at market, thanks for your advice! Signed: the IDIOT</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1370789050942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370789210427-16</Id><Topic><Title>Expect to see $42 - $44 this week...</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1370788679053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:37:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not an idiot! Good move. You won't regret it. This will be at $250 by Labor Day. Cheers. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1370789210427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370789360203-17</Id><Topic><Title>Xbox One will go Viral Next Week</Title><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370756335061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 01:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That depends on how many Xbox's they sell, and that depends on how much it costs, and if consumers see the value in it, and that depends on how it is marketed, and marketing has never been Microsoft's strong point. If Microsoft can develop and execute a good marketing strategy, then things will be looking up. The marketing for the Surface has been mixed - some good elements, some weak elements, IMHO. Xbox will be marketed to the home market, a more price sensitive market than business. I expect the initial pricing will be in the high side to make profits from first-users who will pay $ to be "first". I would then expect to see big discounting going into the Christmas buying season.</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1370789360203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370789422750-18</Id><Topic><Title>Xbox One will go Viral Next Week</Title><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370756335061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 01:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The game experience will be awesome, better than anything we have experienced. But in regards to other businesses like skyping, music, movies, and TV msft has not really told us their plans. They still need internet access and partnership with major music or movies content providers.</Msg><Username>mediaikiller</Username><Timestamp>1370789422750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370789605364-19</Id><Title>Y not buy on the rumor sell on the news this time arund????</Title><Msg>seriously. a nice run but why would msft run continue? xbox is good. but what about cloud which is much bigger in the back ground</Msg><Username>fracisp</Username><Timestamp>1370789605364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370791525695-20</Id><Topic><Title>We have the biggest most bloated and wasteful government money can buy, it human nature</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370727322934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 17:35:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep "it human nature" on top for awhile for everyone to see</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1370791525695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:25:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370793997399-21</Id><Topic><Title>This New Rival Is Coming for Apple and Google</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370740962857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 21:22:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not at all. Android already dominates in mobile. The only real contender, iOS, is fading. WP has no chance. W8 is not a factor in mobile, and is not likely to become one. So what is the prospect? When another version of Linux turns up, under the stewardship of the current hardware leader Samsung, there could be a serious contest for dominance between the two versions of Linux.</Msg><Username>modelbroken</Username><Timestamp>1370793997399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370794156492-22</Id><Title>MSFT LAST IN PHONES.....LAST IN GAMING. BING IS A VIRUS... AND 8 STINKS....GO APPLE. GOOGLE</Title><Msg>And samsung, sony, and ninteno,....oooh and the big dog in phone...android. the msft killer !</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370794156492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370794248579-23</Id><Topic><Title>This New Rival Is Coming for Apple and Google</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370740962857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 21:22:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is the difference between Samsung trying to create an eco-system from scratch using Tizen, and Nokia trying to create an eco-system using Symbian? Symbian was a great system that went nowhere due to the lack of a larger "ecosystem". The battle of mobile is the battle of the eco-systems. Apple thinks they have the best eco-system because they have lots of apps. Apps were cool items for early adapters, but not so much for the average consumer. VALUE will be the driver - with value being the best ratio of performance/functionality, to price. Windows will offer an encompassing ecosystem, and here I don't define ecosystem as the number of apps - an ecosystem is ALL your platforms (PC, laptop, tablet phone, games), and all of your "stuff" (cloud storage, music, teleconferencing, video, work papers, photos, etc etc), having ONE easy to use and understand user interface, with you stuff available wherever you are. No one EXCEPT MICROSOFT is in a position to offer that to the average consumer in the near future. The clincher is Apple and Google have no games to speak of (unless you want to count Angry Birds) - neither have any presence in the living room except via laptop or tablet. It is taking some time for W8 to catch-on, but it will catch-on, and the W8 ecosystem will be everywhere. Samsung is going to try to create an ecosystem from scratch using Tizen. I think they have their work cut out for them.</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1370794248579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370794421041-24</Id><Title>on gaming, rumor is buying PWRD, a $16 stock with $90 price target</Title><Msg>An 8 PE and major announcements in the last 3 weeks including earnings.</Msg><Username>internetreatiler</Username><Timestamp>1370794421041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370795553282-25</Id><Title>WINDOZE 8 RAN AWAY WITH MY PC...AGAIN...FLYIN' TILES...CHARMS AINT CHARMING MORE LIK CHARMIN</Title><Msg>Worse tan vista.... Fact... I'm using this rubbish !!! oh and msft is #7 in games. fact. last in phones. all supercomputers run linux...i now see why ! fact.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370795553282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370795684385-26</Id><Title>NOTICE ALL THE POSTS CLAIMING WHAT MSFT AND XBOX ARE "GONNA BE AND GONNA DO". MSFT AT BACK OF PACK</Title><Msg>In every catagory.....but hopium and pumpers galore. proven loser is msft. !</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370795684385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:34:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370800271280-27</Id><Topic><Title>Xbox One will go Viral Next Week</Title><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370756335061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 01:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pricing strategy is only important when there is competition. Xbox ONE has no competition, it is the only available motion sensing technology in the market (Leap motion is experimental and too small to do anything). Sony and Ninento don't even come close with the old technology when it comes to games. Msft xbox one is beyond gamings. The only question is how amazing is this technology and how much are consumers willing to spend on it? Like i said, Kinect belongs to NASA, now it will be in our living room.</Msg><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370800271280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370804868839-28</Id><Topic><Title>We have the biggest most bloated and wasteful government money can buy, it human nature</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370727322934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 17:35:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nancy Pelosi said, "DRAIN THE SWAMP!" I agree!</Msg><Username>hardwarenincompoopfrompottsylvan</Username><Timestamp>1370804868839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370805088635-29</Id><Topic><Title>A Lot Of People Are Freaking Out Because They Think Microsoft's New Xbox Is Going To Spy On Them</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370646007639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I am an investor trying to figure out who will emerge the ecosystem wars in good shape, and I've concluded that Microsoft will emerge in very good shape. I'm not a "fanboy", or a MS employee - I'm just someone who's up a lot on my MSFT investment so far, and looking to be up some more in the next year. No talking points - just objective analysis and conclusions. You can/should similarly invest in accord with your own analysis and conclusions.</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1370805088635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370805685972-30</Id><Title>hawfarce Fondles His Man Boobs While Posting Around The Clock</Title><Msg>13 years on this message board is hawfarce. He knows everything and everyone but spends no time off this message board. How many "multi-millionaire business men" do you know that behave in this manner? The man is a fukingmess.</Msg><Username>urinate_on_the_confederacy</Username><Timestamp>1370805685972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370806575590-31</Id><Topic><Title>We have the biggest most bloated and wasteful government money can buy, it human nature</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370727322934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 17:35:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Governments are instituted among Men, deriving their just Powers from the consent of the Governed, that whenever any form of government becomes destructive of these ends, it is the right of the people to alter or to abolish it, and to institute new government....it is their right, it is their duty, to throw off such government, and to provide new guards for their future security. T. Jefferson, The Declaration of Independence</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1370806575590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370806720539-32</Id><Topic><Title>hawfarce Fondles His Man Boobs While Posting Around The Clock</Title><Username>urinate_on_the_confederacy</Username><Timestamp>1370805685972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:21:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what are you fondling as you urinate on the confederacy?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1370806720539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370807003292-33</Id><Topic><Title>A Lot Of People Are Freaking Out Because They Think Microsoft's New Xbox Is Going To Spy On Them</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370646007639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 19:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The media is being sensationalized, overemotional, and exaggerated. Oh, yeah, Xbox users are awake all night in a cold sweat worried about the camera. Puuuhhhhlease. That is so melodramatic. 99% of users in the end could care less.</Msg><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1370807003292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:43:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370807203696-34</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Now Making Almost As Much as Google When Every Android Phone Sells</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1370564249210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:17:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed. If MSFT hits $37 this week shorts will be in hysterics, posting article after article trying to scare away investors. But who do they think they are scaring? Big fund managers who are loading up on Microsoft stock, NOT!</Msg><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1370807203696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370807860723-35</Id><Topic><Title>KILL THE 'APPS' DEBATE</Title><Username>thermonuke</Username><Timestamp>1367945107449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:45:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOKIA announces Sonic the Hedgehog for Nokia Lumia devices! Excellent! About 100,000 90s classic titles yet to come!!</Msg><Username>thermonuke</Username><Timestamp>1370807860723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:57:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370808306839-36</Id><Title>Windows Azure: Announcing New Dev/Test Offering, BizTalk Services, SSL Support with Web Sites, AD Improvements, Per Minute Billing ....</Title><Msg>Folks following the Analyst meeting at the Merrill Lynch Investor Conference, Microsoft’s Satya Nadella spotlighted the Enterprise Cloud Era at TechEd 2013.... Just Bing the title above. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370808306839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370808406861-37</Id><Topic><Title>XBOX ONE - The Day The World Changed Forever....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369158573053</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AND tomorrow the real show gets underway in LA.... Stay tuned. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370808406861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370808519077-38</Id><Topic><Title>Xbox One will go Viral Next Week</Title><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370756335061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 01:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WE will own the Home Entertainment from Games, to TV, Movies, Music and anything in between.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370808519077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370808605973-39</Id><Topic><Title>Retail shorts are all out and now the game begins with the Pros....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370633434737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:30:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WE will close above $40.00 this week.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370808605973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370808688603-40</Id><Topic><Title>IF you think May was a good month, wait till June and July 2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370022862594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:54:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOW the bogus Fed correction is behind us, we will start moving to $50.00 starting tomorrow.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370808688603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370811724323-41</Id><Topic><Title>NOTICE ALL THE POSTS CLAIMING WHAT MSFT AND XBOX ARE "GONNA BE AND GONNA DO". MSFT AT BACK OF PACK</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370795684385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:34:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I've noticed that. These guys are all hat and no cattle...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370811724323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 17:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370811894168-42</Id><Topic><Title>KILL THE 'APPS' DEBATE</Title><Username>thermonuke</Username><Timestamp>1367945107449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:45:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Mobile Office for Android and iOS have been delayed another year." Whose fault is that? Microsoft's, of course.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370811894168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 17:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370812920284-43</Id><Topic><Title>you might live in a country founded by geniuses but run by idiots. part 1</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370731828364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So if one needs an I.D. to register to vote, what is the problem with presenting it to vote? 10's of thousands of votes are available to steal via canvassers going around to houses to "get out the vote". For example they visit Mrs. McGillicutty who says she is fed up with all of them and not voting, a quick text to a co-conspirator and Mrs. McGillicutty's vote is cast for the thug in Chief from Chicago. There are a thousand variations possible and no excuse except the desire to steal votes not to thwart the crooks. %</Msg><Username>false</Username><Timestamp>1370812920284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 17:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370812980832-44</Id><Topic><Title>Xbox One will go Viral Next Week</Title><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370756335061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 01:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forbe/John Gaudiosi (who looks like he has Down's) thinks that Xbox One will be the last of game consoles. Wow! I thought that Forbes hired insightful, intelligent writters. This guy claims to have 20 years of experience in gamings, yet he has no clue in the technology behind the xbox one? If the xbox One is just an upgrade to the original xbox, I would say the same too. But Mr. Gaudiosis is obviously a paid basher or he is illed informed (severely).</Msg><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370812980832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 17:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370813098502-45</Id><Topic><Title>Why the valuation of Local Corp with lower than 40 million is one of the biggest jokes the Nasdaq had ever seen</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1370098076284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SECURITY OWNERSHIP OF CERTAIN BENEFICIAL OWNERS AND MANAGEMENT The following table sets forth the beneficial ownership of shares of our Common Stock as of June 13, 2013: • each person (or group of affiliated persons) known by us to beneficially own more than 5% of our common stock; • each of our directors and nominees; • each named executive officer; and • all of our directors and executive officers as a group. Information with respect to beneficial ownership has been furnished by each director, officer or beneficial owner of more than 5% of our Common Stock. Beneficial ownership is determined in accordance with the rules of the SEC and generally requires that such person have voting or investment power with respect to securities. In computing the number of shares beneficially owned by a person listed below and the percentage ownership of such person, shares of Common Stock underlying options, restricted stock units, warrants or convertible securities held by each such person that are exercisable, vested or convertible within 60 days of June 13, 2013, are deemed outstanding, but are not deemed outstanding for computing the percentage ownership of any other person. The percentage of beneficial ownership is based on 22,877,526 shares of Common Stock outstanding as of June 13, 2013. Name and Address of Beneficial Owner Number of Shares of Common Stock Beneficially Held Percentage of Shares Beneficially Owned 5% Stockholders: Goldman Capital Management Inc.(1) 1,367,500 6.0% The Tail Wind Fund Ltd.(2) 1,616,915 6.6% Executive Officers and Directors: Heath B. Clarke(3) 531,306 2.3% Michael A. Sawtell(4) 183,826 *% Kenneth S. Cragun(5) 172,404 *% Peter S. Hutto(6) 179,362 *% Erick Herring(7) 42,499 *% Norman K. Farra Jr.(8) 162,718 *% Philip K. Fricke(9) 129,903 *% John E. Rehfeld(10) 219,544 *% Frederick G. Thiel(11) 22,499 *% All directors and executive officers as a group (8 persons)(12) 1,644,061 6.8%</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1370813098502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 17:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370813445905-46</Id><Topic><Title>Why the valuation of Local Corp with lower than 40 million is one of the biggest jokes the Nasdaq had ever seen</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1370098076284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About 25% in strong hands: Goldman Capital Management Inc.(1) 1,367,500 6.0% The Tail Wind Fund Ltd.(2) 1,616,915 6.6% All directors and executive officers as a group (8 persons) 1,644,061 6.8% Vanguard Group Inc 349,347 1.53% HUDSON BAY CAPITAL MANAGEMENT LP 320,494 1,40% CALIFORNIA PUBLIC EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM 89,800 0.39% GEODE CAPITAL MANAGEMENT LLC 78,770 0.34% Flankenking 77,800 shares 0.34% BANK OF NEW YORK MELLON CORP 59,731 shares 0.26% JACOBS LEVY EQUITY MANAGEMENT INC 57,300 shares 0.25% 6.0% + 6.6% + 6.8% + 1.53% + 1,40% + 0.39 + 0.34% + 0.26 = 23.91% of outstanding 22.9 million shares. (= bad times for legal shortsellers and not legal naked shortsellers, which exist because SEC and FINRA had never done any control)</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1370813445905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 17:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370814913834-47</Id><Topic><Title>This New Rival Is Coming for Apple and Google</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370740962857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 21:22:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Samsung is going to try to create an ecosystem from scratch using Tizen. I think they have their work cut out for them." You sound very defensive, as if you feel very threatened by Tizen. I'm making no predictions for the success of Tizen, but given that Tizen is basically Linux plus Webkit, and that Android is just another version of Linux, it would appear that Tizen is just moving into a ready-made Android "ecosystem" plus the enormous community of web developers using Javascript and HTML 5.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370814913834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 17:55:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370815141661-48</Id><Topic><Title>you might live in a country founded by geniuses but run by idiots. part 1</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370731828364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So if one needs an I.D. to register to vote, what is the problem with presenting it to vote? 10's of thousands of votes are available to steal via canvassers going around to houses to "get out the vote". For example they visit Mrs. McGillicutty who says she is fed up with all of them and not voting, a quick text to a co-conspirator and Mrs. McGillicutty's vote is cast for the thug in Chief from Chicago. There are a thousand variations possible and no excuse except the desire to steal votes not to thwart the crooks. You are aware the sting guy who outted the ACORN crooks claimed to be Eric Holder and was given his ballot to cast? He didn't but wanted to see if it's possible and it was. And what happens if the real voter shows up later well the fake vote is cast and cannot be uncast. You just hate the idea of the criminal left's action being thwarted by honest people because that's where your head is at.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370815141661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 17:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370815226206-49</Id><Topic><Title>you might live in a country founded by geniuses but run by idiots. part 2</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370732148286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:55:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""to make little girls ask questions?" That sounds bad ..." It worked, you asked a question.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370815226206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370815414311-50</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT will own the Cloud business and here is why....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1366931968933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:19:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another great article at the CIO Magazine: "Large Companies Making the Cloud Their Own".... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370815414311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370815556064-51</Id><Title>X-TUBE IS MSFT's NEXT INNOVATION....</Title><Msg>Folks with the infrastructure that XBOX has built, our next move is to put Youtube out of business with X-TUBE.... Stay tuned. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370815556064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370815789841-52</Id><Title>Not since the Civil War has this nation been more divided, thanks Obama</Title><Msg>and if you question that it is intentional refer to the case of Rice. Rice was sent out to tell lies, that was known at the time. So whether Rice knew she was distributing lies or not, others knew and told her to do it. Now we want to know who told her to tell the falsehoods so we discover if it was intentional own her part and Obama promotes her. That is "in your face" confrontation, and intentionally so. Obama is a thug, that's all he knows and he is dividing the country because some of us are not going to take his divisive arrogance silently.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370815789841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370819700291-53</Id><Title>Haswell Highlights: 6 New And Noteworthy Gaming Laptops....</Title><Msg>Folks with XBOX-ONE Cloud, this is going to be a great month for MSFT.... Just Bing the title above. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370819700291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:15:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370819932468-54</Id><Topic><Title>Not since the Civil War has this nation been more divided, thanks Obama</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370815789841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:09:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Naw, it is people llke you and the tea party that are dividing and talking secession and civil war. As soon as you lost the election, the response was secession from many. Why? Can't accept other ideas and the Constitution? Only when it goes your way? This is just like asking for birth certificates over and over, saying we want to know, even though the proof is in your face. There already was an investigation, there is nothing for you to wonder about. No matter how many testimonies you hear, none will be good enough because none will show what you want them to say. The fake scandals aren't working.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1370819932468</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:18:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370821271211-55</Id><Topic><Title>X-TUBE IS MSFT's NEXT INNOVATION....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370815556064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They should not use "X" tube - connotation of "X" rating, adult. Also "deadly" - x-rays. Something cheerful and engaging - "your vids", or "win vids" or One Tube (per Xbox One), or Sky Tube,.....</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1370821271211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:41:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370821437502-56</Id><Topic><Title>500% in profit just this MONTH</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368250132474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 01:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SWAZ</Msg><Username>millyherr</Username><Timestamp>1370821437502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370821708827-57</Id><Topic><Title>This New Rival Is Coming for Apple and Google</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370740962857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 21:22:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You say you make no predictions, then you proceed to make a de facto prediction that Tizen will do well. What "ready-made" Android ecosystem? There are a lot of uses of an OS, but no ecosystem to speak of beyond malware infused apps. Also, it Android is ready-made, why is Samsung going to Tizen when Andriod is free (malware included), and Google going with Chrome? Games, enterprise, cloud, desktop; an established base in PCs and tablets and phones - zeor for Tizen - Tizen starts with zero. Given the choice between being MSFT with Windows, and Samsung with Tizen, which would you want to be?</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1370821708827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370821749399-58</Id><Topic><Title>Not since the Civil War has this nation been more divided, thanks Obama</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370815789841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:09:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And just what is the Tea Party. People who want to cut the massive spending and waste. And you are against that? Just look at the people that have been targeted. People who are good law abiding citizens. And look at who is against them. People who think that having 22 kids and wanting more to be paid for by the government. You don't find fault with that? You are truly delusional and are apparently against good law abiding citizens.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1370821749399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370821750983-59</Id><Topic><Title>500% in profit just this MONTH</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368250132474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 01:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>see your problem is your not doubling down-losing big-cmon double your profits.eh</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1370821750983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370821903847-60</Id><Topic><Title>going LONG here, oh BILL GATES</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368549474411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MUCX</Msg><Username>millyherr</Username><Timestamp>1370821903847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370821958826-61</Id><Topic><Title>KILL THE 'APPS' DEBATE</Title><Username>thermonuke</Username><Timestamp>1367945107449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:45:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Android and iOS will see Mobile Office when they both get to the point where it is clear they are "has been" mobile operating systems, and Windows 8 is growing at escape velocity. Then MSFT will throw Android and iOS a bone, and make money doing it, further securing Office as the standard in enterprise and personal productivity software.</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1370821958826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370822488989-62</Id><Topic><Title>Xbox One will go Viral Next Week</Title><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1370756335061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 01:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't miss what you never had. How many average consumers (not gamers) will be willing to spend big $ on the services/capabilities offered by Xbox One? I truly don't know. I assume MSFT has tested pricing extensively, but an introduction of a new product (well, at least a significantly changed product to a new market segment) is always dicey - success depends on good marketing, and good marketing depends on a good assessment of consumer's wants and needs and pocketbooks. As I said, MSFT does not have a great record mass marketing to consumers - I hope they get it right this time - it's a good product - the trick is to convince people to spend their scarce, hard-earned dollars on a good product. On the other hand, there are lots of good products out there from which consumers can choose....</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1370822488989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370823535689-63</Id><Topic><Title>Not since the Civil War has this nation been more divided, thanks Obama</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370815789841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:09:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pepeekook, I made that point because the appointment of Rice is the perfect undeniable example of Obama's divisiveness. They sent her out to tell lies and as a reward for doing their bidding he promotes her. A promotion for telling their lies.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370823535689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370824453638-64</Id><Topic><Title>Not since the Civil War has this nation been more divided, thanks Obama</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370815789841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:09:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Actually it is Thanks to the Conservative Talking Heads that spread Fake Scandals, Opinion and Speculation that Divides America." He promoted Rice for telling his lies, that's no one's fault but Obama.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370824453638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:34:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370826047049-65</Id><Topic><Title>Will Conservative News Stations Cover This ?</Title><Username>cyber_critiqer</Username><Timestamp>1370824870882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:41:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...who described himself ..." LOL! hahahahahahahahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1370826047049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370827559963-66</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Now Making Almost As Much as Google When Every Android Phone Sells</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1370564249210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 20:17:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice PR fluff, but there is no hard data to back up your claims, only reports from hand picked analysts based on spoon fed numbers. The actual settlement agreements are, of course, secret. There has been no noticeable increase in price for Android devices that would lend credence to those claims. Microsoft has announced plans to restructure itself as a "devices and services company". If Microsoft is going to produce devices, naturally they are going to have to license the necessary patents to do so. Companies such as HTC, Foxconn, LG and Samsung all have extensive patent portfolios of their own related fields, and cross-licensing agreements with each other. They could not function otherwise. Read between the lines: “Hon Hai is the world’s largest contract electronics manufacturer that holds more than 54,000 patents worldwide,” said Samuel #$%$, director of the Intellectual Property Department at Hon Hai. “We recognize and respect the importance of international efforts that seek to protect intellectual property. The licensing agreement with Microsoft represents those efforts and our continued support of international trade agreements that facilitate implementation of effective patent protection.” No big deal.</Msg><Username>crunchie812</Username><Timestamp>1370827559963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370827615593-67</Id><Title>For ill coming out and saying increase my taxes. he will be #1 in wealth again soon.</Title><Msg>MSFT could double this year that would do it.</Msg><Username>fracisp</Username><Timestamp>1370827615593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:26:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370828107455-68</Id><Topic><Title>Will Conservative News Stations Cover This ?</Title><Username>cyber_critiqer</Username><Timestamp>1370824870882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:41:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By JOSH GERSTEIN | 6/9/13 7:10 AM EDT Updated: 6/9/13 3:30 PM EDT The investigations that seized Associated Press phone records and dug into the email account of a Fox News reporter labeled a co-conspirator are just a warm-up act for what’s coming next. New probes might be uncomfortable politically after the recoil from recent revelations of how far the Justice Department went in hunting leaks — and President Barack Obama says he welcomes the debate that the flurry of new and potentially more significant leaks in recent days have sparked. But revealing the government’s telephone call tracking, surveillance conducted on foreign users of America’s top web companies and a highly-classified order Obama signed authorizing the development of offensive cyber-operations have, according to Director of National Intelligence James Clapper, caused “potentially long-lasting and irreversible harm” to intelligence operations. And they may be far more broad and far reaching in their impact than what was behind the AP’s stories about a terrorism plot busted in Yemen or the information about North Korea’s nuclear program that James Rosen reported for Fox. “I’ve been saying for two weeks that this would be the best time in the world to leak, because no one is going to want to launch a leak investigation, but I was wrong,” said Peter Zeidenberg, a former federal prosecutor who worked on the investigation into the leak of CIA officer Valerie Plame’s identity. “When you look at this pattern of leaks, they don’t have any choice.” “They’ve really got immediate huge, major leaks that sort of put the AP story and the Fox and Rosen things in a comple</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1370828107455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:35:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370830174006-69</Id><Title>Xbox: Prism - Say Hi to Obama from the Privacy of Your Living Room</Title><Msg>Wow, that's pretty cool. It's too bad only conservatives will have the SPY feature activated by default on their new Xboxes. I'm sure even some dems would love to wave at Michele and Barack from the privacy of their own living rooms. It's possible that the Dear Leader may access their devices by mistake.</Msg><Username>sillymuppets</Username><Timestamp>1370830174006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 22:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370830219174-70</Id><Topic><Title>This New Rival Is Coming for Apple and Google</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370740962857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 21:22:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I said, bozo, I am making no predictions as to the success of Tizen. But the obstacles you speak of are imaginary. Dream on....</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1370830219174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 22:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370831914700-71</Id><Topic><Title>MY NEW WIN. 8 WITH IE 10. I WAS SITTING, EATING A SALAD WATCHING MY DESKTOP, BING JUST APPEARED. AGAIN.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370488987378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This has been a constant problem since buying my new hp. well i use chrome now.... hey and bing is a trojan by msft. and loaded on ie 10. so now i must get rid of ie. the trojan front. kill it. Bing is a trojan. Invasive and predatory , an unappreciated by me. the owner of this machine, that msft has complete control over. constant interruptions. during my working... Side margins pop out all the time. And constant misinterpreted commands...and down the rabbit hole. very time consuming.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370831914700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 22:38:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370831981294-72</Id><Topic><Title>MY NEW WIN. 8 WITH IE 10. I WAS SITTING, EATING A SALAD WATCHING MY DESKTOP, BING JUST APPEARED. AGAIN.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370488987378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try a $249 Samsung Google Chromebook instead. No Windows 8 Metro, No Internet Explorer, No Bing and NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370831981294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 22:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370832371440-73</Id><Topic><Title>Osso is a bag of excrement</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370287761738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YEP YEP</Msg><Username>modelbroken</Username><Timestamp>1370832371440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 22:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370832490975-74</Id><Title>TRENDING NOW....HP SICK OF WINTEL</Title><Msg>For decades, PC makers had little choice but to succumb to the Microsoft (NASDAQ: MSFT ) and Intel (NASDAQ: INTC ) hegemony known as Wintel. The software giant and chip maker both rose to ubiquity together, enjoying the most valuable roles in the segmented PC value chain. The vast majority of computers ran Windows and were powered by Intel processors during the rise of the PC. However, one PC maker has had enough: Hewlett-Packard (NYSE: HPQ ) . HP has been in turmoil for years. Mark Hurd's controversial ouster in 2011 also came at a time when the broader computing industry was at an inflection point. Apple had launched the iPad just a year prior, jump-starting the tablet renaissance. Leo Apotheker's reign didn't last long, and current CEO Meg Whitman's turnaround is starting to take shape. That turnaround is very much hinged on a broader approach than HP has historically implemented, one that acknowledges the shift away from Microsoft and Intel in favor of iOS, Google (NASDAQ: GOOG ) Android, and ARM-based chips. On the last earnings conference call, Whitman made it clear that HP is intent on "using multiple operating systems, multiple architectures, and multiple form factors" going forward. Whereas once HP's PC portfolio were all Windows PCs with Intel inside, HP has now broadened its horizons and is embracing Google's vision of the future. HP released its first Chromebook earlier this year, followed almost immediately by a Slate 7 Android tablet reminiscent of Google's Nexus 7. The Android-powered SlateBook x2 convertible was just announced, which sports an NVIDIA Tegra 4 processor. Google is uprooting many of Microsoft's core businesses, and HP wants in.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370832490975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 22:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370833316138-75</Id><Title>SOME KNOW WHY MSFT IS IN LAST PLACE IN PHONE IOS. SOME KNOW 8 IS RIDDLED WITH FLAWS.</Title><Msg>Some know msft loaded bing the way they did, attached to everything, tiles and ie-10, just to get all those fake clicks everytime thisdamnthing bings. Everytime you try 2 use this pos, there's bing. in the middle of e-mail, or reading an article, or putting it to sleep, or signing in. over and over all day. and then add charms in the flying margings... The touchscreen or pad has this non-stop. this is getting much notic. google it. or ask jeeves... Or ask leo. or omni-tech. soon this will be more trouble fro msft than vista. i have both. Vistasucks. 8 is worse. Touch is dumb. And not finished. period.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370833316138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 23:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370834774416-76</Id><Title>Chromebook boots faster than a Windows PC</Title><Msg>My $249 Samsung Google Chromebook cold boots in only 7 seconds. That's 7 seconds from pressing the power button to the login screen. Chrome OS is very fast without all of Microsoft's bloatware to slow it down. That's with a 1.7 GHZ dual core Samsung Exynos ARM processor, 2 GB of RAM, a 16gb SSD and NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1370834774416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 23:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370835074791-77</Id><Topic><Title>Chromebook boots faster than a Windows PC</Title><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1370834774416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 23:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the MSFT financial board go shill your insecure POS on the GOOG board.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1370835074791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 23:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370835996822-78</Id><Topic><Title>KILL THE 'APPS' DEBATE</Title><Username>thermonuke</Username><Timestamp>1367945107449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:45:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This 'money making' plan to only provide software for other platforms and then only when they have being wiped out. It sounds way better than selling lots of software to all the users of the dominant platforms in their heyday. Couldn't be any money in that. Have you suggested it to the Board of Directors yet? [end sarcasm]</Msg><Username>fan_tazer</Username><Timestamp>1370835996822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 23:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370836487442-79</Id><Topic><Title>Chromebook boots faster than a Windows PC</Title><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1370834774416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 23:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too bad you don't have enough bloatware to get something done with your sh.tty toy</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370836487442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 23:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>