<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367036444133-1</Id><Topic><Title>Within 12 months, Widows 8 Tablets and Phones will be standard for Business customers...</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367017540786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 19:05:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*sigh* even more schoolgirl hysteria. What CIOs want doesn't matter as much as it once did. CFOs want more productivity at less cost with greater security, and Windows just delivers too little with far too much maintenance cost and no security. The result is what is being called the "consumerization" of the enterprise. BYOD is the order of the day.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1367036444133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 00:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367037608013-2</Id><Topic><Title>Within 12 months, Widows 8 Tablets and Phones will be standard for Business customers...</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367017540786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 19:05:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 = Game Over !</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1367037608013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 00:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367039244329-3</Id><Topic><Title>iPad Slows As Surface Grows: Microsoft Proves Its Worth to Apple</Title><Username>dell_stk</Username><Timestamp>1366997717258</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>may be he have it on a floppy disk?</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1367039244329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 01:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367039633525-4</Id><Topic><Title>M$'s EXTRAORDINARILY successfull surface pro sales....</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1367009901508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:58:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow, you still think you doing/saying something? :haha: little-willie pull his gun out. then realize he not armed ...</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1367039633525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 01:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367039730090-5</Id><Topic><Title>Windoze Phone is a total success.</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1367010002527</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 17:00:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jealous? no worry, he not competition for you.</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1367039730090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 01:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367039951747-6</Id><Topic><Title>Windoze Phone is a total success.</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1367010002527</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 17:00:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe some day be as big as it was 5 year ago? :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1367039951747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 01:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367039975479-7</Id><Topic><Title>Windoze Phone is a total success.</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1367010002527</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 17:00:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>have another drink!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1367039975479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 01:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367040548672-8</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT got 7% marketshare on tablets in 6 months, from nothing</Title><Username>seriouslynot</Username><Timestamp>1366990687438</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:38:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why it nowhere when msft invent tablet? 10 year short time? :haha: you nowhere now. in 10 year you dominate nowhere?</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1367040548672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 01:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367063528560-9</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 50 DMAVG is gaining ground on 200 DMAVG....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1366976855208</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 07:47:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AND here is the latest.... $28.6357 (50-day) vs $28.7101 (200-day) WE will cross in a couple of day.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367063528560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 07:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367064967914-10</Id><Title>Why does MSFT do so little to help "partner"" Nokia??? MSFT should just buy out NOK while....</Title><Msg>...it is so cheap but then they should have bought out YHOO when tit was at below $15 for so long and they could have gotten it very cheap and own 43% of Alibaba. That train has left.</Msg><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1367064967914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 08:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367072099989-11</Id><Topic><Title>M$'s EXTRAORDINARILY successfull surface pro sales....</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1367009901508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:58:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love my Surface Pro,great all in one mobile PC/Tablet !</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1367072099989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:14:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367072438049-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why does MSFT do so little to help "partner"" Nokia??? MSFT should just buy out NOK while....</Title><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1367064967914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 08:16:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think MSFT would gain anything by buying NOK/YHOO that it doesn't already have through their partnerships, IMO a MSFT buyout of NFLX would make more sense.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1367072438049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367072672986-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why does MSFT do so little to help "partner"" Nokia??? MSFT should just buy out NOK while....</Title><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1367064967914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 08:16:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better idea: you buy nok and donate it to msft. that way you get wish and msft can show how useful it is to them. maybe they give you stock grant,,,,,,,,,,,</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1367072672986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367073846062-14</Id><Title>Chairman Ballmer … I Have a Question…</Title><Msg>First of all, congratulations for a quite good financial results achieved by Microsoft in Q1 2013, surprisingly contradicting predictions of many doomsayers. Kudos to you for quietly making progress and maintaining steady course in spite of unending hostile attacks by mostly negatively biased media and unfriendly financial expert/analysts community. Having expressed my appreciation for your accomplishments now I want to ask you a question to you. We all realize, how critically important W 8 and WP 8 success is for Microsoft future including a new generation of devices based on these OS. I’m absolutely convinced that success of WP8 devices is impossible without success of W8 OS. They are so closely interconnected and interdependent. Now time for my question: How could you possibly approve this TV ad… you know, the one with young crowd, each holding Surface tablet, shaking/jumping/dancing around this big table with young boy dancing/rotating on his head on the top, everything in wild party atmosphere. Maybe I’m old fashion traditionalist… call me as you wish… but, is this how we want to sell this product (Tablet Surface) to business community and mature adult customers ? C’mon, what is this? Somebody has a serious problem here. Trying to be respectful, I’d say, it’s got to be me who has a problem. Where is the old, good, common sense , critical thinking, healthy judgment. What happened to those values. Who at his right mind can advertise Surface Pro or even RT in commercial like that which btw, completely misses intended target audience . This simply is ridiculous ad, a total turnoff. It is like having some hard rock or rap group performing on (let’s say) MS shareholders meeting with all the institutional big shots present. I don’t want to completely discredit this TV ad, but the appropriate places for them might be, MTV, Disney Ch. Nickelodeon Ch or even Saturday morning children programs. After all Surface is light, handy, relatively small and easily fit into a backpack. Every time this ad is on TV, I begin to question the sanity of people who entrusted their money and often their future by owning the stock (MS, NOK) of companies whose marketing departments are being run by unbelievably incompetent people. This commercial is simply a disgrace. Shame on you Microsoft! In spite of last quarter good results I worry about your and your partners (Nok) future. Mr. Ballmer this situation requires immediate correction. There’s plenty of highly talented and competent people out there …Mr. Ballmer, Mr. Ballmer, one more thing, in case if you need a good, creative consultant… you know how to find me, contact Yahoo Message Board .</Msg><Username>zutko118</Username><Timestamp>1367073846062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367074896502-15</Id><Topic><Title>M$'s EXTRAORDINARILY successfull surface pro sales....</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1367009901508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:58:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just saw a TV ad for Pro,MSFT is doing a wonderful job promoting this great product.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1367074896502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367076206044-16</Id><Title>xbox720</Title><Msg>will be the biggest flop ever, none of my friends are buying, u cant use old games. Why buy another system, when you already got a system that works perfectly? why Buy it new when u can wait a long time, and it will drop in prices? Ask your friend if their getting the new system and come out?</Msg><Username>tinle123</Username><Timestamp>1367076206044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:23:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367076882838-17</Id><Topic><Title>Chairman Ballmer … I Have a Question…</Title><Username>zutko118</Username><Timestamp>1367073846062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:44:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU raise some good points and I agree that commercial was ill advised and was intended to portray Surface Pro as a cool product going directly after AAPL's marketing scam.... However MSFT does not make "toys", we make "tools" for business and consumers alike.... ON S. Ballmer, he is the most underestimated CEO (Please note our Chairman is Bill Gates) and most attacked by the paid bashers on Wall Street to defend AAPL and Google.... MSFT runs over 80% of the Enterprise PCs and that the decision to develop Windows 8 was a strategic one to not only to catch up with Mobility (Phones/Tablets) but also to integrate Desktop and Mobility.... This was in direct response to S. Jobs' assertions that PC is dead, long live Tablets.... Now Microsoft has turned the table around with Windows 8 thus advocating the death AAPL and Google.... In essence as Windows 8 gains a foothold in the Tablet market (The Windows 8 Phones are on their way to become a force in that Market already) and the Desktop/Mobility integration becomes "more evident", as I said in my earlier post, the CIOs would want to have a single OS platform for Data/Audio/Video and as MSFT Office 365 and Bing get more traction with corporate clients, we will see astronomical demand for Windows based tablets and a move away from AAPL and Google sponsored OS. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367076882838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367078374784-18</Id><Topic><Title>Why does MSFT do so little to help "partner"" Nokia??? MSFT should just buy out NOK while....</Title><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1367064967914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 08:16:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too late to buy YHOO, (that train left) but if they had last year and still had 43% of of Alibaba, along w/ recent gains for Yahoo Japan, and the synergies of combining Bing and MS net w/ YHOO, etc. they would have really scored big. They can still buy NOK cheap and really get into good tablets and phones before NOK decides it better start going Android as MSFT "partnership" not working out.</Msg><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1367078374784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367078621125-19</Id><Topic><Title>Chairman Ballmer … I Have a Question…</Title><Username>zutko118</Username><Timestamp>1367073846062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:44:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I appreciate your remarks and fully agree with you. However we should address business community, and mature segment of society at least in my opinion, in more serious and more dignified way. It's all about image and this one clearly projects immaturity and therefore doubtful quality. Thanks for your input</Msg><Username>zutko118</Username><Timestamp>1367078621125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 12:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367081296490-20</Id><Topic><Title>Why does MSFT do so little to help "partner"" Nokia??? MSFT should just buy out NOK while....</Title><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1367064967914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 08:16:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No doubt NOK is dirt cheap,but there's a reason,they really droped the ball &amp; severely underestimated the significance of the smartphone &amp; let AAPL get away with the lead due to management arrogance I think that old rumor about a buy out is being pushed so people can make money off a price increase MSFT already has a Killer tablet called the Surface Pro.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1367081296490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 12:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367093974932-21</Id><Topic><Title>Chairman Ballmer … I Have a Question…</Title><Username>zutko118</Username><Timestamp>1367073846062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:44:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think that is what is happening now.... ONE thing is for certain as Wall Street is very worried about the success of Windows 8 and even the folks at the IDC were blaming Windows 8 for "poor" PC sales.... THE fact is the PC sales are not based on the success of Windows 8 as the corporations each have their own refresh cycle(s) and if they have up-to-date PCs that can run Windows 7 or 8 they do not need to rush and buy a new machine and the same goes for consumers as I just bought a new PC after 6 years and migrated from Windows XP to Windows 8 and man what a awesome upgrade.... THERE is no doubt that Windows 8 will be a Grand Slam with all bases loaded as Tablets powered by it would be gaining ground in the corporate world and with its unmatched security features, there would be no need for anti-Virus software any longer.... SO the stakes are huge and the rewards for MSFT shareholders are immense.... IT is also very funny that paid bashers by APPL and Google are asking S. Ballmer to be fired as he is enemy number one for the Wall Street's phony technical analysts. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367093974932</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 16:19:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367094399355-22</Id><Topic><Title>Within 12 months, Widows 8 Tablets and Phones will be standard for Business customers...</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367017540786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 19:05:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU couldn't be more wrong as Windows 8 has unmatched security features as the US Government and Law Enforcement authorities have already selected Windows 8 for exactly the same reason.... AS for productivity, you are out of your league on this one.... My suggestion to you is, if you are shorting MSFT for the reasons you have been advocating on this Message Board, you are in for a very rude surprise. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367094399355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 16:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367101587719-23</Id><Topic><Title>Why does MSFT do so little to help "partner"" Nokia??? MSFT should just buy out NOK while....</Title><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1367064967914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 08:16:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No question NOK dropped the ball but that is why MSFT can pick them up so cheap and bring good direction that would benefit MSFT and NOK shareholders. MSFT could sell NSN but keep patents and Navi. And w/OK they would put out a better tablet/phablet/</Msg><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1367101587719</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 18:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367103377470-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why does MSFT do so little to help "partner"" Nokia??? MSFT should just buy out NOK while....</Title><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1367064967914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 08:16:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You morons (especially wally) miss one point: if M$ buys Noka, all the OEMs currently putting windoze malware on PCs and tablets (not many!), will automatically be competitors, not allies. Windoze license costs add too much already, so Android will win anyway. M$ is #$%$.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1367103377470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 18:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367103420063-25</Id><Topic><Title>Windoze Phone is a total dud.</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1366334198327</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 21:16:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump it again.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1367103420063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 18:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367104337936-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why does MSFT do so little to help "partner"" Nokia??? MSFT should just buy out NOK while....</Title><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1367064967914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 08:16:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WINDOZE 8 is the safest &amp; best OS out there, FOAD! you horrible old Troll.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1367104337936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 19:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367106231465-27</Id><Topic><Title>Chairman Ballmer … I Have a Question…</Title><Username>zutko118</Username><Timestamp>1367073846062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:44:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, please. Yes, the ad is ridiculous; and yes, it is exactly the kind of ad one would expect Ballmer the Monkey Boy to approve.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1367106231465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 19:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367119985145-28</Id><Topic><Title>Ghoul Obama Broadens His Support Of Infanticide</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1366997034418</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's nothing wrong with my reading skills. It's your intellectual skills and moral outlook that's the problem. The subject is infanticide, aka murder of an innocent human being. It happens that the babies in question are very young, but murder statutes and civilized moral standards don't make exceptions for the age of a human being. It is murder to kill a 40 year old or a 4 minute old human being. Abortion has lead to ever increasing levels of depravity and a major breakdown in civilization. It leads to further levels of debauchery such as support of partial birth abortion and infanticide by Obama and many of his followers. The argument they present is that the baby is only a few hours old so its ok to kill her .... but that's just another push of the boundary further toward murdering inconvenient children up to age 4 or 5 years and old folks who have outlived their usefulness. Be careful, you may someday fall victim to Obamacare's death squads.</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1367119985145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 23:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367120695245-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ghoul Obama Broadens His Support Of Infanticide</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1366997034418</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are ill informed about the "legal" limits of abortion. There are none. Abortion is legal throughout the entire pregnancy for any reason or for no reason at all. There is no bottom to the hell hole in which abortion dwells . Pro-lifers don't kill babies and they don't kill abortionists either. They are pro-life; they respect all human life, even that of abortionists and infanticide supporters such as Obama. We simply believe that all human beings have a right to life, and that includes babies still in the womb ... since they are beings of the human kind, perhaps smaller and younger than you and I but just as human.</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1367120695245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 23:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367121292638-30</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Off Democrat Felons One at a Time</Title><Username>plmartin02</Username><Timestamp>1366998620289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:50:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So many Democrat felons .... so little time to hunt them down. It's not surprising that at every stage of Obama's rise, he was pushed along by fraud, forgery, and boatloads of lies. Birds of a feather flock together ... likewise con-men and fraudsters.</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1367121292638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 23:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>