<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372480527603-1</Id><Topic><Title>DOMA Will Stand</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1372254008493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:40:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because he's not a real investor.</Msg><Username>scooponcoop</Username><Timestamp>1372480527603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372480829143-2</Id><Topic><Title>DOMA Will Stand</Title><Username>plmartin_2012</Username><Timestamp>1372254008493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 09:40:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It wasn't "sarcasm" at all and anyone reading this knows better: it was your wish and your prediction. Not only were you wrong, but you have to deal with your bigotries being exposed and that your viewpoint is marginalized. Buy a singlewide, watch Fox and masturbate to Greta and you'll make it through your great disappointment.</Msg><Username>scooponcoop</Username><Timestamp>1372480829143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372480945742-3</Id><Topic><Title>Windows has won this round also with Windows 8.1....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372375031073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 19:17:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry, the trolls all have lost their #$%$ on gold and missed the biggest rally ever. They don't have any money. I do and I laugh at them and their "rage".</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1372480945742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372481121691-4</Id><Topic><Title>Witness: Trayvon Martin was straddling George Zimmerman</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372449650502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"for which there is no evidence" (1) The evidence shows that Zimmerman was following Trayvon ... was told by dipatchers not to do it ... Zimmerman did not follow the dispatcher and continued to follow Trayvon ... that is on the phone recordings. (2) Even though Zimmerman was legally permitted to carry a firearm under Florida law ... Zimmerman was carrying a weapon against neighborhood watch rules. (3) Since Trayvon is dead ... Zimmerman can say anything he wants ... like Trayvon jumping him as he walked back ... if someone is leaving you ... why would you jump them? Also, Zimmerman in his transcripts says that he reached in his pocket to get a cell phone ... If I was being followed and someone came up to me and reached in their pocket ... I'd fear for my life and his them first ... doesn't Trayvon have the "Stand Your Ground Rule" applied to him ? (4) the best witness admits he only saw 8 - 10 seconds ... not the whole thing. So, it looks like Zimmerman was the Provoker and if in fact he was doing a Neighbor hood watch ... should not have had his gun on him.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372481121691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372481235368-5</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. MSFT owns that market.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1372481235368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:47:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372495726558-6</Id><Topic><Title>Witness: Trayvon Martin was straddling George Zimmerman</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372449650502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"(1) The evidence shows that Zimmerman was following Trayvon ... was told by dipatchers not to do it ... " When you learn English and American law, (1) we do not know that Zimmerman was following Trayvon after being requested not to, he said he was returning to his car when jumped, there is no evidence to dispute that so far. (2) If Zimmerman followed after being told, that is not illegal. (3) Violating Watch rules is not illegal. That rule is stupid. Why would you have the right to carry and NOT carry when looking for possible bad guys? (4) In America you are presumed innocent until PROVEN guilty under the law only, what the best witness saw exonerates Zimmerman. Not one shred of evidence now public even suggests mmore than (non illegal) bad judgement. So since each of your whines was "debunked" do you have any idea why we are proceeding with this political witch hunt? While we can agree it turned out badly due to decisions which were not illegal, there is no reason shown to have a trial. If Trayvon had returned directly to his father's apartment he'd be alive today, no way Zimmerman would have ever caught up to him after he disappeared.. And the revealing part about you is that all you listed may be a problem in places like where you live there in East Marxistan, but are fundamentally insufficient to even bring charges in America. The original police declination to bring charges was correct, then the racist political witch hunt began.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372495726558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 04:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372498083085-7</Id><Title>Why are open threats to kill white people if Zimmerman is acquitted not terrorist threats?</Title><Msg>If Muslims were openly tweeting to convert or we are going to kill Americans the FBI would be all over them. Local news people are already questioning if there will be riots WHEN Zimmermna is acquitted. The mere question can taint a jury should it leak to them. I personally think that blacks as a race have assimilated into American society to a degree that rioting will be local and opportunistic, but why are threats and hate speech by blacks ignored by Holder?...oh yeah, never mind, Holder is another racist.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372498083085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 05:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372498574376-8</Id><Title>Is Microsoft in Trouble?</Title><Msg>Google it. Basically, the message is, "Yes, but..." The numbers look bad, but here and there one can find a silver lining behind the dark cloud.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372498574376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 05:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372515227580-9</Id><Topic><Title>Why are open threats to kill white people if Zimmerman is acquitted not terrorist threats?</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372498083085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 05:28:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you really are a bona fide r word, aren't you. you don't get it, you distort news meanings and cant be educated to any extent like you claim. Your kkkk has been actually doing what you imagine and are you calling them terrorists, no. All law is followed for all such activities and saying Holder is not permitting law to be followed is totally the r word on your part. That's is a in your mind.You don't even understand what the r word means. it was only a matter of time before you got back to the zimmer case. don't get too excited yet.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1372515227580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372515313167-10</Id><Topic><Title>Why are open threats to kill white people if Zimmerman is acquitted not terrorist threats?</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372498083085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 05:28:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's all in your mind, correction of mistyping..</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1372515313167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372515428829-11</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just so you know, a friend of mine works at a Fortune 500 software company and he told me it has negotiated an extended support contract for Windows XP with Microsoft. Enterprises don't like change. Unless there are features they absolutely need, they won't jump in to Windows 8 with both feet.</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1372515428829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372517936776-12</Id><Topic><Title>Witness: Trayvon Martin was straddling George Zimmerman</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372449650502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That rule is stupid." So are all your other Opinions .... all they have to do is convince the Jury ... and I see Trayvon protecting himself against someone that is there to possibly harm him ... his own self defense.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372517936776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 10:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372518167568-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why are open threats to kill white people if Zimmerman is acquitted not terrorist threats?</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372498083085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 05:28:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If" Is that all you have to make up stuff ... "If". "Local news people are already questioning if there will be riots WHEN Zimmermna is acquitted." Only in your "Local" racist areas ... And Other Blah, Blah, Blah ... Racist Hawcreek Remarks .... "I personally think that blacks as a race " "Holder is another racist"</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372518167568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372519588777-14</Id><Topic><Title>Why are open threats to kill white people if Zimmerman is acquitted not terrorist threats?</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372498083085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 05:28:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" "If". "Local news people are already questioning if there will be riots WHEN Zimmermna is acquitted." So you're guessing they may riot either way, functionally illiterate moron? I only saw the danger when he is acquitted. "Racist Hawcreek Remarks .... "I personally think that blacks as a race " Not racist in the least in the context that I used it. Maybe if you learn English? "Holder is another racist" Yes we agree, that has been established by Holder's actions.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372519588777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372519760394-15</Id><Topic><Title>Witness: Trayvon Martin was straddling George Zimmerman</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372449650502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...and I see Trayvon protecting himself against someone that is there to possibly harm him ..." Naturally with your racist perspective you would be the one to "see" something for which there is no evidence presented to date, is your first name "Clair" Mr. Voyant?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372519760394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 11:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372522319815-16</Id><Topic><Title>Another lousy day for MSFT</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372446534558</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 15:08:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW dennishrz - I seem to leave many folks speechless - even my boyfriend ! Don't sweat it ! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372522319815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372522411512-17</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True - I still use Vista myself just for that reason. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372522411512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372523122004-18</Id><Title>Microsoft has failed</Title><Msg>Google it. A bit dated, but still pertinent. Quoting: "Microsoft is in deep trouble, their two main product lines are failing, and the blame game is intensifying. Steve Sinofsky gets the blame this time for the failure of Windows 8, but the real problem is the patterns that are so clearly illustrated by these actions. "Microsoft is largely irrelevant to computing of late, the only markets they still play in are evaporating with stunning rapidity. Their long history of circling the wagons tighter and tighter works decently as long as there is not a credible alternative, and that strategy has been the entirety of the Microsoft playbook for so long that there is nothing else now. It works, and as the walls grow higher, customer enmity builds while the value of an alternative grows. This cycle repeats as long as there is no alternative. If there is, everything unravels with frightening rapidity. "A company that plays this game for too long becomes set in their ways, and any chance of real change simply becomes impossible. Microsoft is there, and has been for a long long time. Their product lines have stagnated, creating customer lock in is prioritized over creating customer value, and the supply chain is controlled by an iron fisted monopoly. Any attempt at innovation with a Windows PC has been shut out for over a decade, woe betide anyone who tried to buck that trend. The history books are littered with the corpses of companies that tried to make change the ‘Windows experience’. Microsoft’s displeasure is swift and fatal to those that try. Or at least it was. "In the end, Windows advanced only to the point of undercutting any competition, and even then to the minimum extent possible. The rules in Redmond were, “Do not change anything unless it is to crush someone doing something innovative”. _________________________________________</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372523122004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:25:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372523740855-19</Id><Title>The Top 10 Reasons Why Steve Ballmer has Failed as Microsoft’s CEO</Title><Msg>Google it.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372523740855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:35:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372524211202-20</Id><Topic><Title>Witness: Trayvon Martin was straddling George Zimmerman</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372449650502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because a man profiled, followed, and killed a juvenile who was going home, unarmed and minding his own business in his own neighborhood. it is pointless to argue with you. Since your false scandals against Obama have failed and are gone, now you turn to this. Your idea Zimmer should have never been arrestd will also fail. Oddly, you convict black people without trial or evidence, yet release white, or closer to white as long as not black, people on their word. Sort of like that poor girl on the stand, she is black, so is a liar if her testimony was misunderstood before, yet when Good's testimonies don't match, it was because of "clarifying." Black people are lying, white people merely clarifying. I was happy to see the prosecution point that fact out when examining Good.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1372524211202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372525299094-21</Id><Title>by the end of next week, msft price will go down below 33.5</Title><Msg>you will see it</Msg><Username>dennishrz</Username><Timestamp>1372525299094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372525751345-22</Id><Title>Microsoft Surface Rt Last 2 days on sale</Title><Msg>Surface RT = Free Microsoft Office -$249.00 Free Cover/real keyboard -$149 Store price is $499.00 However you are getting about $400.00 worth of free savings This sale ends tomorrow. It is a hard decision. Get a Surface RT just for using while watching tv, on the go, machine to browse freely and keep your pc with sensitive email off the sketchy sites. It is certainly a hard deal to pass up. You have to pay $499.00 but office is not free with the pro and the cover keyboard is not free with pro. If you use office it is a hard deal to pass up. Do you wait for the next model of Surface. Who is making the 7 " is it Microsoft or Nokia? The Surface RT is great to have for general browsing and keeping a pc with all your data off the web and secure. If you visit porn, you definitely want a separate machine and not a general pc or your info may be sniffed out why you are looking at the girls.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1372525751345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372526121988-23</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Rt Last 2 days on sale</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1372525751345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol,msft thinks they do you a favor for the #$%$ they want u to buy, any other reason besides that?</Msg><Username>dennishrz</Username><Timestamp>1372526121988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372527194313-24</Id><Topic><Title>Let’s get the Windows 8.1 party started....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372463120526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:45:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dell is offering both the 660 desktop and the XPS 8700 desktop with either Win 8 or Win 7 but Win 7 is a $30 option. Then one month of Office 365 is included while Office Home &amp; Student is a $190 option. If the buyer wants a video card then get the XPS model. HP Direct has a note that they have a few Win 7 computers in stock. Wow, thanks ! But then under their Everyday listing they have two Win 7 desktops out of ten. And under their High Performance listing they have one Win 7 desktop out of twelve. There's also a Win 7 desktop under their Gaming listing. The Samsung U.S. website is showing three models of 13" Series 9 laptops and they all have Win 8. But a 13" Series 9 laptop can be found on Amazon with Win 7. But look for the second generation mobile processor model.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1372527194313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:33:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372527333543-25</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Rt Last 2 days on sale</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1372525751345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You get the sleekest looking drop dead gorgeous device on the market. It works really great. It runs better than the others. I tested them all. It is not practical for putting on your lap as it flops. You have to put it on a tablet or stand. It just works great as a tablet for surfing the web and taking with you on trips, etc. If you have no use do not buy one. All tablet sales are down because of the power of the new Windows Phones. When you run the browser in desktop mode you can access any website just like from home. I did my bank transfer while waiting in line at the store. People love their smart phones and that drops the need for a tablet. If you do not need one have a nice day.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1372527333543</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372527556682-26</Id><Topic><Title>Witness: Trayvon Martin was straddling George Zimmerman</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372449650502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Because a man profiled, followed, and killed a juvenile who was going home, unarmed and minding his own business in his own neighborhood" If he was "going home" Zimmerman would have never gotten to him. "Creep a&amp;&amp; cracker" now THAT is profiling so we know there was one racist in the mix with an attitude. " it is pointless to argue with you." Only when you are wrong, so yes it is in this case. There are two things to note about you, ironically you refuse to see guilt when it is presented to you in broad daylight and you find guilt where non is evidenced, and your split comes along racial lines, so that certainly strongly suggests that YOU, not I , are the racist.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372527556682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:39:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372527637983-27</Id><Topic><Title>Witness: Trayvon Martin was straddling George Zimmerman</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372449650502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"in his own neighborhood" NO, he was in a Gated Community and had no business being there. If you want a conviction, email the prosecution and tell them they definitely need witnesses with a better gene pool than that girl monkey. Case dismissed!</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1372527637983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372528506112-28</Id><Topic><Title>Let’s get the Windows 8.1 party started....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372463120526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:45:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 13.3" Samsung Series 9, with first generation processor, is on Amazon at $899.99 . The model number is NP900X3B-A01US and that's with Win 7 . Then the 13.3" Samsung Series 9, with second generation processor, is on Amazon at $1369 . The model number is NP900X3C-A02US and that's with Win 7 .</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1372528506112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372529289446-29</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Rt Last 2 days on sale</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1372525751345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't you think it is a bit late for msft to get shares in the tablet market? or in other markets?</Msg><Username>dennishrz</Username><Timestamp>1372529289446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 14:08:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372535254598-30</Id><Title>time to make new run at buying YAHOO?</Title><Msg>been 5 years sure yahoo would jump on the 31.00 price this time??</Msg><Username>celk40</Username><Timestamp>1372535254598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 15:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372536244332-31</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Rt Last 2 days on sale</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1372525751345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I went over to Best Buy trying to pick one up. Not for personal use, I have a business. There was actually a crowd around the Surfaces. The black salesman was saying yea it is a little hard to use but you get used to it. The hispanic salesman said I have been selling a ton of these. People like them a lot. They were totally and completely confused on which keyboard if any comes with it and which would be free. They were confused on which had office. Every single time I go into a store I become the salesman for the people asking questions. I left there but was happy to hear they were selling like crazy. I went to Staple where it was a cute girl an I was unshure if I hit on her before. Anyway she was confused about the keyboard and which was free. I told her to get a box an ring it up an see what happens. She came back and said they were sold out. I used my standard line of can I get a date for the inconveience? It did not work but that line often works. So the bottom line is Surface is selling better than people think and no one is sure wich keyboard you get for free. I am. The one that has the flat keys is included. It is like a flat sheet of paper and you just touch the flat key. The free keyboar is like a normal keyboard with raised keys. You cannot expecte the salespeople at those two store to know all the answers. It is unfair. The dedicated softy store at Best Buy will be huge.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1372536244332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 16:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372554599157-32</Id><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Msg>Trayvon was unarmed walking through the neighborhood when Zimmerman approached. The popo told Zimmerman, we don't need you to do that", when he said he would follow Trayvon. Zimmerman ignored the orders from the popo. Did Zimmerman make the first move? Was Trayvon too much for Zimmerman to handle after Travon was assauted by Zimmerman? Was Trayvon defending just himself?</Msg><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372558875094-33</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Zimmerman ignored the orders from the popo." Actually if you learned to read, we don't know that, in fact the only testimony is opposite of that, moron.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372558875094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 22:21:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372558987429-34</Id><Topic><Title>The Top 10 Reasons Why Steve Ballmer has Failed as Microsoft’s CEO</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372523740855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listing just the headings: 1) Ballmer Has an Exceptionally Low Approval Rating. As of July 18, 2012, Microsoft’s CEO Steve Ballmer has a paltry 46% internal approval rating with *his own employees*. 2) Ballmer Has Led No Real Innovation. Microsoft isn’t innovating fast enough or aggressively enough. 3) Ballmer Squandered Major Market Opportunities. 4) Ballmer has Overseen Dismal Product Releases. 5) Ballmer has made horrible investments. a. aQuantive. b. Skype. c. Yammer. 6) Ballmer has accomplished nothing 7) Ballmer has eroded shareholder value. 8) Ballmer Can’t Leverage His Cash. 9) Ballmer is a Maniac. 10) Ballmer can’t get Microsoft to compete (and win) with consumers.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372558987429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 22:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>