<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364986572167-1</Id><Topic><Title>Prices of Windows RT tablets drop, point to failure of OS</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364948580741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows RT tablets are a joke. Nobody in their right mind would pay $500 for one. They'd even be a tough sell half price at $249. Windows RT tablets are destined for the big consumer electronics discount rack in the sky. LOL!!!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1364986572167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 06:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364987649640-2</Id><Topic><Title>Windows XP decline stalls as users hold onto aged OS, flaunt 2014 deadline</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364911519352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look what happened in 2008 when Microsoft tried to kill XP and force Vista on the world. By 2009, XP still had major market share and Vista was the most hated OS since Windows ME. Now Microsoft is trying the same thing with Windows 8. Windows 8 is already off to a rough start. Only this time, there are plenty of alternatives like iPad, iPhone, Mac, Android tablets, Android phones, Chromebooks and other Linux devices. In fact, lots of Linux distros will run just fine on older XP hardware.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1364987649640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 07:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364987985674-3</Id><Topic><Title>3 Ways to Get Microsoft Office on Your iPad, Android Tablet</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364927579513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 14:32:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft Office is pointless without a keyboard and mouse. Sure, it would be nice to open Office email attachments with some kind of 'viewer' or 'player' software, but that's about it. Even if Microsoft did offer Office for iPad, I wouldn't pay $100 for it.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1364987985674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 07:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364988403721-4</Id><Topic><Title>New 52 week high after this Q earnings report.</Title><Username>dell_stk</Username><Timestamp>1364947669666</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be high! Windows 8 is the most hated OS since Vista!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1364988403721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 07:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364988530375-5</Id><Topic><Title>Uptake gap between Windows 8 and Vista is unclear but virtually 100% of new PC's, laptops and tablets come equipped with W-8</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364911483721</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:04:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Steve Ballmer keeps saying Windows 8 is not a Flop. It's Not! It's Not! It's Not! I don't think anyone believes him anymore.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1364988530375</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 07:28:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364988773615-6</Id><Topic><Title>windows 9 rumored to have classic view</Title><Username>ddeboy</Username><Timestamp>1364906418559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 08:40:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now THAT would boost MSFT's share price!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1364988773615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 07:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364988849970-7</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft's Windows 8 turning off PC buyers</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364843050294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 15:04:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1364988849970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 07:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364988942249-8</Id><Topic><Title>nokia and softie are both on the way to the dumps</Title><Username>alex_sptrader</Username><Timestamp>1364911756704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:09:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know anybody with a Lumina phone, but lots of my friends have iPhone and Android phones.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1364988942249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 07:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364993258720-9</Id><Topic><Title>Prices of Windows RT tablets drop, point to failure of OS</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364948580741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah....they're doomed #$%$. The fact that wally shows up to defend it is total confirmation that it is a FAIL. That stupid turd is still trying to defend vista, zune and kin....all of which are FAILS.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364993258720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 08:47:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364994770735-10</Id><Topic><Title>show me a poster named plmowrawn and I will show you an illegal alien</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364931484290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 15:38:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sybil, just because tax bills are nonexistent for you doesn't mean the rest of us aren't paying your way. BTW, didn't you get the memo, your party says the term "illegal alien" is not to be used anymore. Why don't you try getting up to speed and find out what is going on. Oh, you must be one of those low information voters.l</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1364994770735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364994806170-11</Id><Title>The Plot to Dethrone Android</Title><Msg>Google it. Cut to the chase: The author thinks "wireless operators", by which he means AT&amp;T etc, want to take down Android. What he thinks they will push as challenger is Firefox OS. Why not Windows Phone? The question answers itself.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364994806170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364994927932-12</Id><Topic><Title>Windows XP decline stalls as users hold onto aged OS, flaunt 2014 deadline</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364911519352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"your forte eh phands- " No. Your career and life's calling, wally- HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1364994927932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:15:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364995944794-13</Id><Topic><Title>Giving assistance to a part that can kill the whole body is pure emotion and senseless</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364925241591</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By charities I guess you mean PAC's, wonderful. Remember when on the 1040 a check off was first instituted to finance campaigns so that large corporations unions etc. would not have too much power. Those days are gone.</Msg><Username>dudsix</Username><Timestamp>1364995944794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:32:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364997089426-14</Id><Topic><Title>nokia and softie are both on the way to the dumps</Title><Username>alex_sptrader</Username><Timestamp>1364911756704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:09:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's because like most linix fanatics you're shut in Trolls,MSFT doesn't need any stinking penguins!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1364997089426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364997400548-15</Id><Topic><Title>windows 9 rumored to have classic view</Title><Username>ddeboy</Username><Timestamp>1364906418559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 08:40:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wonton will spend the rest of his life licking Steve Ballmer's boots like the lackey stooge wonton is.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1364997400548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:56:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364997781613-16</Id><Topic><Title>Giving assistance to a part that can kill the whole body is pure emotion and senseless</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364925241591</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The world didn't start in 2009 genius. We are effectively living in the aftermath of a GOP giant asteroid that almost wiped out the USA. Obama did the right things and we are much much better. Obama is right on, great man and President.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364997781613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364998201192-17</Id><Topic><Title>windows 9 rumored to have classic view</Title><Username>ddeboy</Username><Timestamp>1364906418559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 08:40:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"wonton will spend the rest of his life licking Steve Ballmer's boots" Why? Is Steve replacing you and wally as co Boot Lickers in Chief? What did you do, Billy Boy, drool on the floor? Did you gag and make him pull out of your throat before he was finished? Bad shill, Billy, bad bad bad...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1364998201192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:10:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364998873051-18</Id><Topic><Title>windows 9 rumored to have classic view</Title><Username>ddeboy</Username><Timestamp>1364906418559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 08:40:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wonton hiding under your skirt Queen? maybe you two can have a same sex marriage performed LOL!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1364998873051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:21:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364998923816-19</Id><Title>The cost to vets to life and limb is a great sacifice and we applaud them</Title><Msg>GWB failed to recognixze the material costs of his wars however. Having it all his whole life, none of that really effects him. Besides, he had a checking account balanced and chock full of money to spend. Seems to be a common thought process amongst the right wing fanatics. Until one has a gay child, until one has a loved one shot, they just don't care, they just don't comprehend. They spend all the money wildly, then when it runs out, they blame the next guy. Now we get to pick up the pieces, thanks Pres Obama for doing a great job towards that goal, we the people support you 100%. Thanks for your strength and level headed leadership on all matters.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364998923816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:22:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364999441972-20</Id><Topic><Title>windows 9 rumored to have classic view</Title><Username>ddeboy</Username><Timestamp>1364906418559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 08:40:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"maybe you two can have a same sex marriage performed LOL!" Nah... That's not original enough for me. There's just no way I would copy or imitate you and wally...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1364999441972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364999524361-21</Id><Topic><Title>In Depth MSFT Research Report .</Title><Username>barry.white95</Username><Timestamp>1362317833519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:37:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome report!</Msg><Username>brownk858</Username><Timestamp>1364999524361</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365001393173-22</Id><Topic><Title>The cost to vets to life and limb is a great sacifice and we applaud them</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364998923816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:22:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hawk, haven't you discovered that you can't argue with stupid people. They will drag you down to their level then beat you with experience. LOL M.T.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1365001393173</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365001773364-23</Id><Title>If I like and pick Chinese food,</Title><Msg>does that mean I am a racist against Europeans, aka "white" people's food? Even though Europeans are not by any mans all "white." If I am very rich, and I vote for someone "white" who will give me large tax perks, loopholes, and look the other way when I spill toxics on the ground and in the waters, am I a racist too? If I am very sick, am I allowed to vote for someone "non-white" who favors my condition? Or am I a racist too for not voting "white"? To some on the right, the answer is no, if you vote for who you like, and they happen to be "non-white" you are a racist against "white" people. First these need to learn what racist means, second they need to stop imposing on others freedom. Are "white people" the only ones allowed to vote for who and what they like, and the vote counts?</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1365001773364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365002413082-24</Id><Topic><Title>The cost to vets to life and limb is a great sacifice and we applaud them</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364998923816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:22:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just keep ignoring the fact that the whole world is in a similar economic situation and had property bubbles at the same time. It will make you feel better to reinforce your emotionally driven agenda.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1365002413082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:20:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365002557032-25</Id><Title>Microsoft Loses the Computing Plot</Title><Msg>Google it... Quoting: "NEW YORK (TheStreet) -- Microsoft has lost the plot and needs an entirely new story. "Microsoft's old story was that it controlled the operating system, the base of the computing pyramid, and because it controlled this base, it would lead computing where it wanted it to go. "That's no longer true. Apple's iOS and Google's Android are both more powerful on clients. Linux is more powerful in the data center. The cloud makes Windows irrelevant. "Figures from NetMarketshare tell the story. Six months after its launch, Windows 8 has a desktop market share of 3%. Its progress is slower than Windows 7, and remember -- this is Windows' "touch" interface. Windows 7 is still all about the mouse. " .... "Microsoft has a play here, called Kinect. Invented in 2005, launched for its game machine in 2010, and for Windows last year, Kinect uses cameras, sensors and software to interpret your movements as computer commands. Microsoft handed it off to developers, who were initially excited by its possibilities. It gives a robot eyes. "But Microsoft didn't develop Kinect further, nor did it push Kinect as a computer product. A start-up called Leap Motion, launched the same year the Kinect first shipped, has done that, and come up with a device no bigger than a USB drive that you can see in this YouTube video. " .... "Leap, in short, is what Kinect should have been, and it will take Microsoft's competitors beyond where Kinect can go, even before Kinect gets there. "If that's not losing the plot, I don't know what is. Microsoft needs a quarterback, not a blocking back. Like IBM 30 years ago, it has become vulnerable to the first "kids with a clue" who came along: the guys at Leap Motion. " ______________________________________________ There's a reason for the Kinect debacle. The reason is that Microsoft didn't invent it, doesn't own it, and couldn't talk PrimeSense into rolling over and playing dead.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1365002557032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365002592426-26</Id><Title>The right extreme says</Title><Msg>"black" people shouldn't vote, they vote for the wrong person, not their person, and they are racists for not voting for a "white", no matter other reasons. Additionally, they say "black" people's votes don't count, even when they do make it up to the ballot through the obstacles. If who they vote for wins, it is said by rwnjs the election is bogus and their person still won. Unbelievable, but true</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1365002592426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365003036170-27</Id><Title>Amazing simple mindedness of the board RWNJ trolls about the economy.</Title><Msg>They basically have two emotional states about the economy. One is the bad ole Democrats pushed housing onto those who could not afford it. Two is the bad ole Bernanke that is pushing money into the economy and destroying our future. There is a miniscule basis of truth in these two memes as is required in any delusion. But where do these facts fit in. 1 Property values entered bubbles worldwide at the same time, no fan or fred involved. 2 Fan or Fred didn't originate most of the loans in question. 3 No banking institution could credibly believe that Fan or Fred would be there to buy troubled loans. 4 300+ Million low wage workers have entered the workforce of the US in the last 30 years depressing wages. 5 The new low wage workers allowed middlemen to buy labor low and sell it high to the US consumer despite this being a temporary system. 6 New technology requires fewer and higher trained workers leaving most of the population out of the expansion. 7 Unnecessary wars have cost our economy trillions and are still draining our money. Integrate some facts into your type one thinking hyper emotional ideas nut jobs.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1365003036170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365003109829-28</Id><Topic><Title>The cost to vets to life and limb is a great sacifice and we applaud them</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364998923816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:22:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you determine how many buyers are available for a stock??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1365003109829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365003701600-29</Id><Topic><Title>If I like and pick Chinese food,</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1365001773364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Put your ears on. People vote for who they like. All people are free to vote, and all votes count. If Obama, who was definitely not unknown, being a senator, same as Hilary, understands their condition, why can't they vote for him? Who are you to say Chinese people can't vote for Chinese people because they think the candidate understands their ways better? On the other hand how many "whites" did vote romney against all their principles of religion and being in the lower and middle economic classes, and because they don't like black people? Don't see you disallowing all those "white" votes for Hilary or romney. You give them a pass, same as you gave romney through all his blunders and dishonesty. Now how do you explain the racism behind the women's vote for President Obama. Don't wana count women's votes either, do you, as long as they don't go your way. Obama won fair and square and I don't even know why it is being discussed months later. GWB didn't even win an election by the people, but was still given President, and all was well.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1365003701600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:41:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365004569014-30</Id><Topic><Title>If I like and pick Chinese food,</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1365001773364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's more of a class thing rather than a racist thing. If you are middle class do you really want you or your kids forced to be around lower class #$%$? That principle applies to any race living on the "other side of the tracks" and it's not racism as you have defined, it's a common sense thing.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1365004569014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365005286877-31</Id><Topic><Title>If I like and pick Chinese food,</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1365001773364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Risky Business Military buildup in China near North Korean border continues as tanks, armored vehicles spotted Chinese Internet photo of a truck carrying a tank en route to an area near North Korea Chinese Internet photo of a truck carrying a tank en route to an area near North Korea April 3, 2013 4:59 am China continued moving tanks and armored vehicles and flying flights near North Korea this week as part of a military buildup in the northeastern part of the country that U.S. officials say is related to the crisis with North Korea. The Obama administration, meanwhile, sought to play down the Chinese military buildup along the border with Beijing’s fraternal communist ally despite the growing danger of conflict following unprecedented threats by Pyongyang to attack the United States and South Korea with nuclear weapons. The Obama Administration foreign policy failures weigh heavily in the situation that has developed. According to U.S. officials with access to intelligence reports, both intelligence and Internet reports from the region over the past week revealed the modest military movements in the border region that began in mid-March and are continuing.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1365005286877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365005795064-32</Id><Title>msft</Title><Msg>I do not understand it. Why does the public hate this stock so? As you know, it takes public selling to make prices go up and buying to make them go down. Not that I am complaining - it makes me money but still....</Msg><Username>x2073</Username><Timestamp>1365005795064</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365006980297-33</Id><Title>MIMV: Mobile apps play &amp; MSFT partner....Getting hot on news....InPlay soon.</Title><Msg>see news</Msg><Username>cashflow599</Username><Timestamp>1365006980297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:36:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365007143894-34</Id><Topic><Title>Amazing simple mindedness of the board RWNJ trolls about the economy.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1365003036170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:30:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You needn't reply we know you are simple minded and emotionally driven.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1365007143894</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365007190861-35</Id><Title>Finally breaking out!!!</Title><Msg>Fundementals are stong. Win 8 is almost 4% market share. Windows phoen reached market share of 7% in UK and Germany, and almost 5% in the US. Surface Tabkets are sellig in more and more countries, and new modles will be announced soon. INtc Haswall chips ar eon the way, which will make Surface Tablest much lighter and much cheaper. New XBox also on the way. New Offcie are selling well. Servers abd Tools are groing more than 10% a year. $70 billkions of cash , yet selling at p/e justy 6-7, ex cash. The shares should have never reached lower than 30 to start with. Expect the shares to move to 35 within 6 months!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1365007190861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365009152242-36</Id><Topic><Title>Finally breaking out!!!</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1365007190861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes MSFT is well positioned for huge future growth,funny how all the critics bashed the XBOX when it came out,now it's become #1 in the gaming,entertainment industry. MSFT will do the same thing with mobile IMO.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1365009152242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365011119654-37</Id><Title>You need to start your research on DDCC right away!</Title><Msg>DDCC looks pretty good at these levels. I bet after DDCC breaks resistance it will start to soar</Msg><Username>cmatthews665</Username><Timestamp>1365011119654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365013193908-38</Id><Topic><Title>If I like and pick Chinese food,</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1365001773364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I answered your question, put your ears on, people vote who they like. If Obama was white, all else the same, yes he would obviously still have won. No question. What about all those white voters who would now have voted for him, unlike blak voters, yes virginia it is racism uber alles for many of the anti Obama white voters. Your hypotheticals are a waste of time. Your racism views are shallow.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1365013193908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:19:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014054678-39</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Loses the Computing Plot</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1365002557032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:22:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>M$ lost the plot years ago. They cannot innovate and when they buy innovative companies, they kill them. When they try to innovate, we get Metro...a half-baked, amateurish mess that the market is avoiding.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1365014054678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014346177-40</Id><Topic><Title>If I like and pick Chinese food,</Title><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1365001773364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hispanics, Arabs and Jews are considered "White", so you are not Racist if you hate them.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1365014346177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:39:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014446487-41</Id><Topic><Title>Prices of Windows RT tablets drop, point to failure of OS</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364948580741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one think RT is any use at all. Because it isn't.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1365014446487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014729250-42</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, this board looks as screwed up, gay and liberal as the HAL board.</Title><Username>lib_scare_tactics</Username><Timestamp>1365014523164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:42:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>skrewed up?? then why dont you get your sas off this board and go stink up the apple board or the 'sux board</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365014729250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:45:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014919749-43</Id><Topic><Title>Prices of Windows RT tablets drop, point to failure of OS</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364948580741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>phands in the next post I mention the fact that you swallow for you boi friends- I know you want the world to know--BTW vista was a better OS than any 'sux even today and was the best on the market in its day. Oh and Zune technology survives and is available in Windows 7 phone and Windows 8 phone-- put that all in your nose</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365014919749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014997889-44</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, this board looks as screwed up, gay and liberal as the HAL board.</Title><Username>lib_scare_tactics</Username><Timestamp>1365014523164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:42:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Hey, this board looks as screwed up, gay and liberal as the HAL board." Hey, this poster sounds as screwed up, homophobic and rabid as the rest of the lame RWNJ trolls. "Why don't you invite those pervs over?" Why don't you invite yourself to a long free fall down an open elevator shaft?</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1365014997889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365015070985-45</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Loses the Computing Plot</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1365002557032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:22:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah the sucker has spoken or sucked whatever</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365015070985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:51:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365015207912-46</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester Blues</Title><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1365004463626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:54:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>plmowrawn bleats out his hate yet again. pl why dont you take your hate down there to your homeland- the drug cartels will be glad to have someone of your caliber-- for target practice</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365015207912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365015554754-47</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Loses the Computing Plot</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1365002557032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:22:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"yeah the sucker has spoken or sucked whatever" Billy Boy? Is he pitcher or catcher in your little twosome...? Or are you both switch hitters...?</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1365015554754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365016116761-48</Id><Title>MSFT and HP are strong buys today</Title><Msg>rich$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>adamwangwang47</Username><Timestamp>1365016116761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365016443542-49</Id><Topic><Title>Amazing simple mindedness of the board RWNJ trolls about the economy.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1365003036170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:30:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well i could find credible sources to demonstrate my claims but you wouldn't listen to them, cause only hear what you want to hear. Faux nuze any1</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1365016443542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:14:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365016548063-50</Id><Topic><Title>Five reasons why Windows 8 has failed</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1363976193416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump...it's really trailing vista ow.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1365016548063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365017611569-51</Id><Topic><Title>Five reasons why Windows 8 has failed</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1363976193416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's understandable a company could misjudge the market and make a mistake, OK several. Problem is the feedback has been continuous and clear about Windows 8 faults since launch which Microsoft continues to ignore. At some point an error in judgment turns into plain arrogance.</Msg><Username>merlot_1</Username><Timestamp>1365017611569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365019235530-52</Id><Topic><Title>In Depth MSFT Research Report .</Title><Username>barry.white95</Username><Timestamp>1362317833519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:37:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you !</Msg><Username>bradleybrown720</Username><Timestamp>1365019235530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365020588015-53</Id><Title>Felony charges dismissed in Va. voter fraud case</Title><Msg>The Associated Press © April 3, 2013 HARRISONBURG A Pennsylvania man charged in Virginia with throwing away completed voter registration forms no longer faces felony counts. Media outlets report that a Rockingham County General District Court judge dismissed eight felony charges against Colin Small on Tuesday. Small, 23, of Phoenixville, Pa., still faces misdemeanor charges of destruction of voter applications and obstruction of justice. Authorities have said Small was working for Pinpoint, an independent contractor hired by the Republican Party of Virginia to conduct voter registration drives, when eight completed registration forms were found in a trash bin behind a Harrisonburg store on Oct. 15, 2012. Small was arrested three days later. The felony charges alleged that Social Security numbers were disclosed when the forms were thrown away. Judge Marvin Hillsman ruled that the forms' disposal didn't equate with disclosing the numbers.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1365020588015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365027183118-54</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Is Returning 5% Of His Salary</Title><Username>captain_zee</Username><Timestamp>1365022905084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:01:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remind me again why he deserves any pay?</Msg><Username>oropan</Username><Timestamp>1365027183118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365031374468-55</Id><Topic><Title>Five reasons why Windows 8 has failed</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1363976193416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>M$ has been arrogant for decades....and not justifiably.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1365031374468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 19:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365033385249-56</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Is Returning 5% Of His Salary</Title><Username>captain_zee</Username><Timestamp>1365022905084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:01:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama is going to start a civil war... 70,291,049 Background Checks for Gun Purchases Under Obama April 3, 2013 By Gregory Gwyn-Williams, Jr. Subscribe to Gregory Gwyn-Williams, Jr. RSS 454 comments There have been 70,291,049 background checks for gun purchases since President Obama took office, according to data released by the FBI. In 2009, the FBI conducted 14,033,824 background checks. If we subtract the month of January (Obama did not assume office until the end of the month) we get 12,819,939. The FBI conducted 14,409,616 background checks in 2010, 16,454,951 in 2011, and 19,592,303 in 2012. Add to that the first three months of 2013 (2,495,440, 2,309,393 and 2,209,407, respectively) and the total number of background checks under President Obama comes to 70,291,049. Over the same time period, the number of background checks completed under President George W. Bush was 36,090,415, or about half the number conducted under Obama.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1365033385249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 19:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365034325066-57</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Is Returning 5% Of His Salary</Title><Username>captain_zee</Username><Timestamp>1365022905084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:01:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saved our economy? That was a joke I hope. He didn't even kill Bin ladin until almost a year after he knew where he was living. Not until he was assured it wouldn't be his fault if the attack on Bin Ladin's compound was unsuccessful. But you keep on bowing to your Messiah.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365034325066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:12:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365034664050-58</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT and HP are strong buys today</Title><Username>adamwangwang47</Username><Timestamp>1365016116761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably on the news of their upcoming joint product offerings: Windows 8 for Main Frames to be followed by Windows 8, Guttenberg Bible Edition.</Msg><Username>doindadorkus</Username><Timestamp>1365034664050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365035170809-59</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Is Returning 5% Of His Salary</Title><Username>captain_zee</Username><Timestamp>1365022905084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:01:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawfaeces when you post like you did with that last piece of hate its easy to make the diagnosis of paranoid schizophrenic for you- oh and also mildly #$%$(has no understanding of chemistry or economics or math etc etc)</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365035170809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365035478564-60</Id><Topic><Title>Five reasons why Windows 8 has failed</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1363976193416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not necessarily, at least for the purpose of saving his own skin...he'll just announce that it's the economy and that MS needs to throw thousands of loyal employees onto the street to correct what ails the company, and then send his toady-in-chief, Lisa Brummell, to do the wet work; then, he'll claim that he is a victim, too, because he only got a $550k bonus rather than a $600k bonus. The BOD falls for this one every time. How else do you think this t-urd has survived?</Msg><Username>doindadorkus</Username><Timestamp>1365035478564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365035489969-61</Id><Topic><Title>Five reasons why Windows 8 has failed</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1363976193416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 14:16:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>five reasons why Windows 8 is a great success 1. Metro, aka Modern: A beautiful useful interface. 2. Windows 8 brought many things innovative to the desktop. 3. Developers love it. 4. Legacy Windows 7 users aren't moving but only because they have just converted to 7 and need to catch their breath. 5. Tablet, smartphone, and desktop colaboration with the OS. so you see phands- once again you are proved dumber than the village idiot and you need to stick to the things you excel at like swallowing</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365035489969</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:31:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365035586480-62</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Is Returning 5% Of His Salary</Title><Username>captain_zee</Username><Timestamp>1365022905084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:01:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Horse #$%$.</Msg><Username>doindadorkus</Username><Timestamp>1365035586480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:33:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365035745031-63</Id><Topic><Title>The Sequestor Is Killing The Economy</Title><Username>captain_zee</Username><Timestamp>1365005252675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:07:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Argo #$%$ yourself.</Msg><Username>doindadorkus</Username><Timestamp>1365035745031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:35:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365040353014-64</Id><Title>It's All BS!!! Market will shoot up in next few days as usual. But It's All Fluff. What A CROCK!</Title><Msg>CROCK is similar to the word #$%$ for a reason. Don't invest in this garbage - it's a hoax designed to make the rich richer and sucker the other investors to feed them (otherwise, no food). A joke, really. J-O-K-E.</Msg><Username>ohnowhatsnext</Username><Timestamp>1365040353014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365041676393-65</Id><Title>I REMEMBER WHEN MSFT WANTED TO BUY YAHOO FOR $50BILLION. BUY NFLX FOR $15BILLION NOW.</Title><Msg>GET HER DONE MSFT!</Msg><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1365041676393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 22:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365042871026-66</Id><Topic><Title>The Sequestor Is Killing The Economy</Title><Username>captain_zee</Username><Timestamp>1365005252675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:07:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>captain you are smarter than what you write??? This is MSFT board with plenty of people who aren't dumb.</Msg><Username>doely_1</Username><Timestamp>1365042871026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 22:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>