<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357450077645-1</Id><Topic><Title>Logic question on Saturday night, who would win a fight, Superman or Batman</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1357430996332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 19:09:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither as they don't exist.</Msg><Username>isolated_eye</Username><Timestamp>1357450077645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 00:27:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357452052464-2</Id><Title>Window8 and Window7 market share jumped in December: MSFT now has 91.74% of global OS market share</Title><Msg>Windows 8 market share jumped in December Summary: December was a good month for Windows 8, with Microsoft's new platform gaining ground at the expense of Apple's OS X platform. By Adrian Kingsley-Hughes for Hardware 2.0 | January 2, 2013 -- 16:32 GMT (08:32 PST) 121 Comments 2 Votes inShare more + December was a good month for Microsoft's new operating system, with Windows 8's market share leapfrogging Linux to claim the number seven spot. Data released by Web metric firm Net Applications shows that over the course of December the Windows 8 market share grew to 1.72 percent, up from 1.09 percent in November. The leap in market share puts Windows 8 ahead of Linux, but behind Mac OS X 10.8, OS X 10.7, and OS X 10.6, and far behind Windows 7, Windows XP, and even Windows Vista. December wasn't just good for Windows 8, with Windows 7 also seeing a small bump in market share, up from 44.71 percent to 45.11 percent. This was to be expected as December is usually a good month for PC sales thanks to the holiday season. See also: Two must-have downloads that make Windows 8 more bearable Microsoft's Windows RT platform, which can be found on tablets such as the Surface, also makes an appearance in the listing, with a market share of 0.01 percent. According to a separate report released by AdDuplex, an ad network specializing in advertisements for Windows Phone and Windows 8/RT applications, Microsoft's Surface tablet is the single most popular device running the new platform. December was also the first month since February 2012 where the overall Windows market share grew, to 91.74 percent, from 91.45 percent in November. Coincidentally, it is also the first time since February 2012 that Apple's OS X has seen a decline in market share, which now stands at 7.07 percent, down from 7.3 percent in November. Back in November of 2012, a report by Web metrics firm StatCounter suggested that Windows 8 license sales were not yet translating into usage since its Web market share was trailing significantly behind what Windows 7 had achieved one month after launch. Net Applications data is based on 160 million unique visitors each month to some 40,000 Web sites which the company monitors for its clients.</Msg><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357452052464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 01:00:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357452290914-3</Id><Title>Dell Says Interest for Microsoft’s Windows 8 Is High: Bloomberg</Title><Msg>Dell Says Interest for Microsoft’s Windows 8 Is High By Aaron Ricadela - Dec 12, 2012 10:14 AM PT Facebook Share LinkedIn Google +1 6 COMMENTS Print QUEUE Q Dell Inc. Chief Executive Officer Michael Dell says that he’s seeing strong demand for computers and tablets running Windows 8, the newest version of Microsoft Corp. (MSFT)’s flagship operating system. “The interest in Windows 8 is quite high, even among commercial customers” who tend to be slower to install new software, he said at the Dell World customer conference in Austin, Texas. “PCs are still how business gets done,” he said. Dell is also a few quarters away from being the world’s biggest server supplier, the company’s founder said. “We’re only 64,000 servers away from being No. 1 in the world,” Dell said.</Msg><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357452290914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 01:04:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357452628285-4</Id><Title>MSFT's likely sold 8Million HALO4 as of Dec31st generating: 1/2billion in revenue</Title><Msg>7.03m units sold globally as of 12/22/2012. That's a little over a month (6 weeks). So obviously people are still buying the game, so the assumption that only 100k of the same exact people play War Games throughout the day is absurd and blatantly ignorant.</Msg><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357452628285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 01:10:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357452901412-5</Id><Topic><Title>My prediction of a MSFT double....</Title><Username>richeydouglas</Username><Timestamp>1357155106643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:31:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahem, I bought Weyerhaeuser some time ago at $15.54. It didn't shoot straight up, but nice steady gain (currently around $29). Once in a while I get lucky....</Msg><Username>clcellve</Username><Timestamp>1357452901412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 01:15:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357478449042-6</Id><Topic><Title>sat night math problem...</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357427104857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 18:05:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you don't get it that you ARE the idiot.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1357478449042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 08:20:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357480862770-7</Id><Topic><Title>Good news everyone ! NEW</Title><Username>joseallen138</Username><Timestamp>1355332997474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:23:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you !</Msg><Username>flowersroyce</Username><Timestamp>1357480862770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 09:01:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357481127120-8</Id><Topic><Title>stock chart patterns,</Title><Username>pearlieseabrookstsrvg5631</Username><Timestamp>1307458515000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-06-07 10:55:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job guys</Msg><Username>doylelauren88</Username><Timestamp>1357481127120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 09:05:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357481733555-9</Id><Topic><Title>sat night math problem...</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357427104857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 18:05:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The question corresponds to real world problems. The stock market uses XX day moving averages without knowing the statistical characteristics of the errors. Ya just are too stewpid to consider the question, you don't understand it apparently despite its simplicity.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357481733555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 09:15:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357482008325-10</Id><Topic><Title>sat night math problem...</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357427104857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 18:05:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't bother waiting for Hawfreak to chime in, he's busy studying up for his GED and trying to find a way to divide his precious 0.9999... dollars into three piles and make them all equal. He's certainly not busy getting laid or anything, what with his diaper funding shortfalls..</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1357482008325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 09:20:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357484348548-11</Id><Title>Innovation at Microsoft? Show Us, Don't Tell Us!</Title><Msg>Google it.... "Microsoft has all of this awesome stuff percolating in labs staffed by small teams and pumped-up interns, but what does it have to show for it? What does it bring to market? "The Surface tablet. Where's the innovation? "Is it the keyboard that snaps on and off? Is it the use of what looks and feels like cheap plastic when held next to an iPad or even a Kindle Fire? "It's certainly not in Microsoft's approach to retail, which is a blatant and embarrassing knock off of Apple's concept. "There's zero innovation in Microsoft's marketing. It's confusing at best. Watch a Surface tablet commercial. Who is Microsoft going after? Can the company capture whoever these people are with dancing schoolgirls and jelly bean-jumping you really can't tell if it's a laptop or tablet devices? "That's the core of Microsoft's problem. "</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1357484348548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 09:59:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357485228599-12</Id><Topic><Title>Logic question on Saturday night, who would win a fight, Superman or Batman</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1357430996332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 19:09:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously Superman. He's invulnerable, except to kryptonite, while Batman is just a clever ordinary guy with some neat toys. If he thinks Batman might be carrying some kryptonite, and if there is a way to conceal it -- in a lead box, say -- Superman need only wear lead armor, which wouldn't hinder him, as he's strong enough to carry an entire railroad train on his back. If lead doesn't block the radiation from kryptonite, then Batman's possible kryptonite can't be concealed, and Superman can fight from a distance -- say, by dropping a small mountain on Batman from an altitude of a few miles.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1357485228599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 10:13:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357488033492-13</Id><Title>last quarter</Title><Msg>the final quarter of '12 showed an 8% drop in revenue, an 11% drop in revenue from third quarter as well, a 13% drop in margin, a 26% drop in operating margin,and a 15% drop in total earnings per share for 2012. Will microsoft test new lows?? When does the ship turn around? The yield is now over 3% and seems to be stable. Debt to equity is 18% which is normal for the industry. Will the P/E which is now at 15 begin to sag?? The hell with Superman and all other superfluous comments....</Msg><Username>scovey2</Username><Timestamp>1357488033492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 11:00:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357488146998-14</Id><Topic><Title>sat night math problem...</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357427104857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 18:05:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs are exempt from answering....they are math deficit. Pelosi...."the benefit to the economy regarding unemployment insurance is ...for every $ dollar of unemployment benefits they receive, a $1.60 goes into growing the economy"</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357488146998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 11:02:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357489492956-15</Id><Topic><Title>sat night math problem...</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357427104857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 18:05:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Libs", whoever they might be, aren't exempt from paying the bills idiots like you racked up pretending that your Lord God Bush was "expanding the economy" instead of breaking it, Hawfreak.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1357489492956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 11:24:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357489900307-16</Id><Title>MSFT yearly cash flow: 24B - 27B - 31.6B : Growing 17% per year</Title><Msg>People who want to INVEST must focus on cash flow and its growth. Instead people end up focusing on too many wrong things. Most people either don't understand or don't study deep enough. For example there is where little talk about how is office (largest business), or server/tools or the games (Halo, xbox) is doing. Additionally people are too much focused on windows8 instead of looking at combination of Windows7+windows8+Surface. What if Windows7 continued to sell at the previous quarters rate of 60Million/quarter and we have additional 80-100Million of Windows8 this quarter? Imagine..WIndows division more than doubling sequentially from 3.2B in rev last Q to 7b+ this Q. On a year over year basis that could be well over 50% growth on the windows/live division. Microsoft is a 40 dollar stock. "Price is what you pay and value is what you get eventually" so said Ben Graham</Msg><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357489900307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 11:31:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357490115023-17</Id><Title>Why Are We Swimming In Debt? 2 Unfunded Bush Wars, Bush Tax Cuts On Wealthy, Bush Financial Collapse</Title><Msg>All brought on by the Bush security failure on 9/11/2001. Did the Bush Tax cuts and 2 unfunded wars create any jobs? Bush Failure = Supply Side On Steroids "Total employment was 132,466,000 at the beginning of George W. Bush’s term and 133,561,000 at the end, an increase of 0.83 percent over eight years, or an average of 136,875 per year. In contrast, jobs increased by 2,584,750 per year under Carter, 2,012,750 per year under Reagan, and 2,842,500 per year under Clinton."</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1357490115023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 11:35:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357490352644-18</Id><Topic><Title>Logic question on Saturday night, who would win a fight, Superman or Batman</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1357430996332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 19:09:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW wotopimp can you tell us what the half life of kryptonite is and what is the character of the radiation- Higgs bosons? ?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1357490352644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 11:39:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357492531767-19</Id><Topic><Title>For four years, Obama added more to debt in EVERY SIX MONTH INCREMENT than both Bush wars in totality.</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1357491752556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 12:02:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hawfreak math doesn't add up as usual. Bush sicko-panties like the bankrupt, innumerate, swamp-dwelling nincompoop Hawfreak don't want to pay the bills they racked up under the Bush-Cheney reign of terror. Unfortunately their message board trolling efforts didn't seem to succeed in getting the white collar criminal they favored into the office of the presidency, so they have to double down on their efforts and prepare to blame Senator Frank for all of the misfortunes they brought on themselves through their ignorance.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1357492531767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 12:15:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357492733293-20</Id><Topic><Title>Dell Says Interest for Microsoft’s Windows 8 Is High: Bloomberg</Title><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357452290914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 01:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No business is only going to buy computers from only one source (like Apple). MSFT business model is lower cost.</Msg><Username>don_cornwell</Username><Timestamp>1357492733293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 12:18:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357495044756-21</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Ratings: Fox News Number One For 11 Straight Years</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1357494726881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 12:52:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conservatives lost the last two presidential elections because their candidates were weak. McCain, for all his past glories, was not a good campaigner or communicator, and picked then unknown Palin as running mate. Romney never came across as real or empathetic to anyone, rich or poor. And Ryan was polarizing, broadly cast as a radical by the unfailingly pro-Obama press. So, two marginal candidates, two questionable VP picks, a press that runs pro-Obama 24/7, and a populace of increasingly dumbed-down and gullible voters. Recipe for disaster for conservatives. Conservative ideas are still valid and popular. Witness the 2010 races and outcomes. 32 state governors. The problem is the presidential candidates, not the ideology.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1357495044756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 12:57:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357497692139-22</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Ratings: Fox News Number One For 11 Straight Years</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1357494726881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 12:52:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With most people. But they have to be articulated well. If all people know is what bad candidates say, and what the hysterical left-wing press reports, they won't get it. But sit down with almost any reasonable person, and conservative ideas resonate well. Would most people say they believe in: - Individual accountability? - Reduced government waste? - A free market that allows competition to flourish? - Smaller government, performing the duties is was chartered for, and not overreaching? - Freedom and independence for our citizens? - More to charity, communities organizations, and churches, and less to bureaucracies to help those who can't help themselves? I argue most people would agree with at least most of this. Do you?</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1357497692139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 13:41:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357500059983-23</Id><Topic><Title>Innovation at Microsoft? Show Us, Don't Tell Us!</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1357484348548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 09:59:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over at Scientific American they see M$ innovation this way: ::: For decades the cynical observer could be forgiven for viewing Microsoft as a giant copying machine. The inspiration for just about every major Microsoft initiative can be traced back to a successful predecessor: Windows (Macintosh), Internet Explorer (Netscape), Bing (Google), Zune (iPod). But in late 2012 Microsoft broke from the pack. It made a billion-dollar gamble that personal computing is taking a new direction. The gamble was Windows 8, and the direction is touch. Using a series of fluid, light finger taps and swipes across the screen on a PC running Windows 8, you can open programs, flip between them, navigate, adjust settings and split the screen between apps, among other functions. It's fresh, efficient and joyous to use—all on a touch-screen tablet. But this, of course, is not some special touch-screen edition of Windows. This is the Windows. It's the operating system that Microsoft expects us to run on our tens of millions of everyday PCs. For screens that do not respond to touch, Microsoft has built in mouse and keyboard equivalents for each tap and swipe. Yet these methods are second-class citizens, meant to be a crutch during these transitional times—the phase after which, Microsoft bets, touch will finally have come to all computers. At first, you might think, “Touch has been incredibly successful on our phones, tablets, airport kiosks and cash machines. Why not on our computers?” I'll tell you why not: because of “gorilla arm.” There are three big differences between these handy touch screens and a PC's screen: angle, distance and time interval. The screen of a phone or tablet is generally more or less horizontal. The screen of a desktop (or a laptop on a desk), however, is more or less vertical. Phone, tablet and kiosk screens, furthermore, are usually close to your body. But desktop and laptop screens are usually a couple of feet away from you. You have to reach out to touch them. And then there's the interval issue: you don't sit there all day using a phone, tablet or airport kiosk, as you do with a PC. Finally, you're not just tapping big, finger-friendly icons. You're trying to make tiny, precise movements on the glass, on a vertical surface, at arm's length. When Windows 7 came out, offering a touch mode for the first time, I spent a few weeks living with a couple of touch-screen PCs. It was a miserable experience. Part of the problem was that the targets—buttons, scroll bars and menus that were originally designed for a tiny arrow cursor—were too small for fat human fingers. The other problem was the tingling ache that came from extending my right arm to manipulate that screen for hours, an affliction that has earned the nickname of gorilla arm. Some experts say gorilla arm is what killed touch computing during its first wave in the early 1980s. (Another problem is finger grease. You can clean a phone's screen by wiping it on your jeans, but that's not as convenient with a 32-inch monitor.) Now, half of Windows 8 addresses half of the touch-screen PC problems: Windows 8 is actually two operating systems in one. The beautiful, fluid front end is ideal for touch; only the underlying Windows desktop has the too-small-targets problem. The angle and distance of PC screens are tougher nuts to crack. Microsoft is betting that Windows 8 will be so attractive that we won't mind touching our PC screens, at least until the PC concept fades away entirely. Yet although PC sales have slowed, they won't be zero any time soon. My belief is that touch screens make sense on mobile computers but not on stationary ones. Microsoft is making a gigantic bet that I'm wrong.::: John Dvorak agrees with that. But his perspective is historical, not predictive: ::: Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer is floating around extolling the virtues of Windows 8. Reviewers are giving more positive reviews than negative reviews. Smart people I know have actually changed their minds, agreeing that Windows 8 is great. Life is good at Microsoft. That said, I personally do not like it. I specifically dislike the idea of full-screen apps running on 27-inch screens. Will I like it more if the desktop PC becomes a touch-screen PC where the advantages of touch come to the fore? No. First off, I need to remind people that both touch-screen laptops and touch-screen PCs have come and gone in this marketplace. Sure, they were somewhat different, but the reasons for the disappearance are the same. HP had a touch-screen machine pro-Windows during the DOS era. It failed miserably in the market. One of the first laptop inventions in 1982 was the Gavilan computer with a touch panel called the "solid state mouse," which required users to hold their arm in the air and move things around much like with a touch pad. This motion was annoying and helped scuttle the machine. (To see my old write-up of the demise of this machine, click here.) The HP machine was also a 1980s era machine with the same problem. Using any touch system that is not on the lap or flat on the desk invites "mouse shoulder," a form of tendonitis. This can also develop from using the mouse improperly, which I unfortunately experienced some years back. It's an incredibly miserable ailment that can take six months to a year to resolve itself, during which you can barely move the shoulder. This is going to happen with these touch screens—not the touch screen on the phone, and not the touch screen on the tablet, but with desktop touch screens and some notebook touch screens. I predict there will be a huge increase in the number of tendonitis claims and the companies, possibly including Microsoft, will find themselves in a legal tangle because of it. Carpal tunnel syndrome almost destroyed the business once already and finally people learned new habits to stave it off. This resulted from pounding on improperly designed keyboards. There were a lot of lawsuits and people were in agony. ::: M$, reinventing the rack and looking to patent it.</Msg><Username>fan_tazer</Username><Timestamp>1357500059983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 14:20:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357500359115-24</Id><Topic><Title>Innovation at Microsoft? Show Us, Don't Tell Us!</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1357484348548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 09:59:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft is the most boring company in the world. They are the Sears, and IBM of the world. DINOSAUR.</Msg><Username>petemeatt</Username><Timestamp>1357500359115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 14:25:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357500922138-25</Id><Topic><Title>People are starting to buy windows 8, Looks like its starting to catch on thats a good thing for MSFT</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357407629029</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 is catching on, You better hold you nose, cover your short and BUY, BUY,BUY</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357500922138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 14:35:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357501975832-26</Id><Topic><Title>sat night math problem...</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357427104857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 18:05:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least i can understand the question.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357501975832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 14:52:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357504738816-27</Id><Title>my suggestion to Microsoft CEO for Windows 8 stop people bashing</Title><Msg>make Windows 8 with two modes in which user could switch between easily from setup or keyboard shortcut 1- Current Mode name it the Tablet mode where the main screen is the Tiles screen which work perfect with tablets 2- New Mode call it the PC mode where the user boot-up to the Desktop screen with Start Menu (still access the tiles menu as a window) that will give the user to chose the mode based on the device he acquired, if it is a tablet he may chose the tablet mode , if a notebook/desktop he chose the PC mode, if a convertible he could switch between modes based how he is using the Convertible</Msg><Username>swisslakes</Username><Timestamp>1357504738816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 15:38:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357505651110-28</Id><Topic><Title>sat night math problem...</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357427104857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 18:05:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good ole creeky posted this rambling nonsense. "The question is: Do you understand which variable you kept in that makes answering with certainty impossible? Hint: The nature of the variable is not typical in multiple measurements but was displayed clearly in the example of mine where you found the link and responded. The nature of the variable is also not contrived but very real in many cases." Ya must have taken the wrong pills this morning. Until you understand the question you cannot understand averaging. Didn't they teach you at least a little math in your enginerun course</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357505651110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 15:54:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357509934930-29</Id><Title>Windows8 floodgates open (Samsung, LG, Visio</Title><Msg>Samsung (Chronos) and LG launched Windows8 computers and tablets last week Today Engadget reports that Vizio is releasing the first AMD-powered Windows 8 tablet. The Vizio Tablet PC is an 11.6-inch slate running AMD’s dual-core, 1GHz AMD Z60 chip, 2GB of RAM, 64GB Let us watch all the wonderful Windows8 products rolling out the gate this week as we start with CES2013</Msg><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357509934930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 17:05:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357510021845-30</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT yearly cash flow: 24B - 27B - 31.6B : Growing 17% per year</Title><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357489900307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 11:31:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good thing about investing is mostly people don't care about what is important like Cash flow and growth in cash flow. This is why there is opportunity created with gap between high value and low stock price offered by Mr Market.</Msg><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357510021845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 17:07:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357526610673-31</Id><Title>I think we can be thankful to President Obama for the growing economy</Title><Msg>SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Asian shares outside Japan edged up on Monday, supported by data showing the U.S. economy continuing on a path of slow but steady recovery that had pushed Wall Street stocks to a five-year high.</Msg><Username>lugibrious</Username><Timestamp>1357526610673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 21:43:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357530619603-32</Id><Title>Windows 8 starting to catch on</Title><Msg>I think this is a good opportunity. Windows 8 is starting out slowly but is catching on. From this level MSFT can make a good move. I am in on friday at 26.80. Great divident with good chance of increase. Good risk reward at this level.</Msg><Username>byhisellhigher</Username><Timestamp>1357530619603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 22:50:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357530645678-33</Id><Topic><Title>People are starting to buy windows 8, Looks like its starting to catch on thats a good thing for MSFT</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357407629029</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time to BUY,BUY,BUY MSFT, Windows 8 is starting to catch on everywere, Just starting in the USA and very big over seas</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357530645678</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 22:50:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357530683028-34</Id><Topic><Title>Windows8 floodgates open (Samsung, LG, Visio</Title><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357509934930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 17:05:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i agree and I am in on Friday.</Msg><Username>byhisellhigher</Username><Timestamp>1357530683028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 22:51:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357530826238-35</Id><Title>30 % growth in Living Room &amp; XBOX live</Title><Msg>Microsoft has been feeding its living-room secret weapon a nonstop diet of software updates and hardware upgrades. This spring, for the first time, subscribers to Xbox’s Live online service in the U.S. spent more time consuming video and music than multiplayer games. Globally, the hours spent on Xbox Live have grown 30% year over year, including gaming and entertainment, while video consumption has risen 140%.</Msg><Username>whoaminot</Username><Timestamp>1357530826238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 22:53:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357531041170-36</Id><Topic><Title>30 % growth in Living Room &amp; XBOX live</Title><Username>whoaminot</Username><Timestamp>1357530826238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 22:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>High-tech giants have been battling for years over control of the living room. That war is far from over, but one company has grabbed a surprisingly strong position: Microsoft Corp. The software maker has progressively transformed its Xbox from just a videogame machine into a multipurpose hub for entertainment delivered over the Internet. Now, the 11-year-old hardware line is facing its stiffest competition yet.</Msg><Username>whoaminot</Username><Timestamp>1357531041170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 22:57:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357531090450-37</Id><Topic><Title>30 % growth in Living Room &amp; XBOX live</Title><Username>whoaminot</Username><Timestamp>1357530826238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 22:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Xbox also seems to finally be earning its keep. Wedbush Securities analyst Michael Pachter estimates Microsoft earns roughly $115 in gross profit on each Xbox console. The Microsoft division anchored by the Xbox business posted revenue of $1.95 billion for the fiscal first quarter ended Sept. 30, off from $1.96 billion a year earlier, and operating income of $19 million, down from $340 million. As the Xbox 360 ages, sales have been bumpy. The company says it shipped 25% fewer Xbox consoles, or 1.7 million units, in the quarter ended Sept. 30 compared with the year-earlier period.</Msg><Username>whoaminot</Username><Timestamp>1357531090450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 22:58:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357531770550-38</Id><Topic><Title>30 % growth in Living Room &amp; XBOX live</Title><Username>whoaminot</Username><Timestamp>1357530826238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 22:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>expect CES to showcase a number of new entrants into the Windows 8 Tablet segment with more licensees, shapes, sizes and price points than can be tracked.” In TV sets, “the TV OS will be the headline story” as the chips in the sets “take a giant leap” and the user interface gets closer to what you know in a tablet or smartphone.</Msg><Username>whoaminot</Username><Timestamp>1357531770550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 23:09:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357533372280-39</Id><Title>Microsoft Windows Chief to speak on Jan 8th at JPMorgan CES TechConference</Title><Msg>JP Morgan Tech Forum at the 2013 International CES Tuesday, January 8, 2013 12:45 p.m. PT Tami Reller, chief financial officer and chief marketing officer, Windows Division</Msg><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357533372280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 23:36:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357533421427-40</Id><Title>Lenovo storms CES with a deluge of Windows 8 hardware</Title><Msg>Lenovo storms CES with a deluge of Windows 8 hardware Jon Phillips@jonphillipssf Jan 6, 2013 3:00 PM print LAS VEGAS--Lenovo, stop. Please—just stop. The sheer volume of your CES offerings is out of control, and we’re not sure the world can absorb so many new Windows 8 hardware announcements in a single day. Microsoft, HP and Dell don’t even have booths at CES 2013, but Lenovo has come to Las Vegas with bullish bravado and a seemingly bottomless trunk of new Ultrabooks, laptops, desktops and even a mobile display. The theme that threads almost everything together: Windows 8, in all its touchy, feely, fingerprinty glory. The new Lenovo line-up spans from relatively pedestrian business machines to a hardcore gaming box, and the company made sure to include 10-point multitouch control on almost every device that warrants that feature. Let’s have a look at the seemingly never-ending line-up. (An intermission has not been scheduled, so please take your bathroom break now.) Six new Ultrabooks and laptops Lenovo’s U series Ultrabooks top the list with the addition of 10-point multitouch LCDs (previous U models lacked touch-sensitive displays). The U310 Touch is 18mm thick, 3.85 pounds, and has a 13.3-inch screen. The U410 Touch is 21mm thick, 4.4 pounds, and has a 14-inch screen. Both models include Lenovo’s “Intelligent Touchpad,” which supports Windows 8 gesture controls. image: lenovoThe new Lenovo U410 Ultrabook. Each U series machine boasts a 1366x768 widescreen display, and can be outfitted with various Intel processors up to Core i7. The U310 comes with integrated Intel graphics, while its big brother features Nvidia silicon. Wake-from-sleep is rated at 1 second, and battery life is spec’d at 8 hours. The U310 will be available in March with prices starting at about $780. The U410 hits in April with prices starting at about $850. If these entry fees are cost-prohibitive, you can explore two new Z Series machines. Aimed at, well, less discerning computer users, neither meets the lightweight Ultrabook spec, but they’re less expensive than the U models, and still include Windows 8-ready, multitouch displays. The Z400 Touch is 29.15mm thick, 5.3 pounds and comes with a 14-inch screen. The Z500 Touch is actually a smidgen thinner at 28.75mm, but weighs in at 5.7 pounds and comes with a 15.6-inch screen. Both models feature 1600x900 widescreen resolutions, Intel processors up to Core i7, Nvidia GeForce graphics, and the same Windows 8-ready “Intelligent Touchpad” founds on Lenovo’s new Ultrabooks. Both Z series machines start at around $699, with the Z400 landing in March, and the Z500 in April.</Msg><Username>bengraham650</Username><Timestamp>1357533421427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 23:37:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>