<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364184020528-1</Id><Topic><Title>Here is the frustrating thing our clueless 'leader' can't seem to grasp</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364076149596</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 18:02:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ballmer is a Billionaire that runs one of the biggest most profitable companies in the world, you're truly a clueless IDIOT!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1364184020528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 00:00:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364184161859-2</Id><Topic><Title>Wearable Computers</Title><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1364180112423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's time for your enema &amp; medication.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1364184161859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 00:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364190585965-3</Id><Topic><Title>I would give that all that stashed cash away before I would let Obama spend it...</Title><Username>richeydouglas</Username><Timestamp>1364094914832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 23:15:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone probably including you were crying for action after 9/11. How conveniently you forget. There hasn't been another attack in this country for over 10 yrs. You think bin Laden would have simply stopped after that if not put on the back foot? Your life in freedom is paid for by the blood of others and all you do is play Monday morning quarterback? Never putting anything at risk? Sitting in the comfort of your basement?</Msg><Username>xtromania</Username><Timestamp>1364190585965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 01:49:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364191365026-4</Id><Topic><Title>I would give that all that stashed cash away before I would let Obama spend it...</Title><Username>richeydouglas</Username><Timestamp>1364094914832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 23:15:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey you should join me in the basement. Don't knock it.</Msg><Username>logge_0dd</Username><Timestamp>1364191365026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 02:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364191628244-5</Id><Topic><Title>Wearable Computers</Title><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1364180112423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Depending on how broadly one defines both "wearable" and "computer", the first wearable computer could be as early as the first abacus on a string, worn around the neck, or, later, a 16th century abacus ring.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1364191628244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 02:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364204673491-6</Id><Title>Building HUGE Momentum About to Explode Big!</Title><Msg>Concurrent (CCUR) last week began breaking out and could explode today. Low float stock that is completely undiscovered, but CCUR is the world's leading video on demand company with reach of 50 million homes of cable TV subscribers worldwide. CCUR is now rapidly expanding into multi-screen video delivery and yesterday the UK's largest cable TV company Virgin Media (VMED) announced that they will be using CCUR's MediaHawk to power their new Virgin TV Anywhere platform! VMED is a $23 billion company with 3.8 million subscribers and for them to be using CCUR's technology is insane considering CCUR's only got 9.2mm o/s and a market cap at $7.79 of $71.47mm with $24.6mm in cash, no debt, and an enterprise value of $47mm or just 0.75x its revenues of $62.59 million. CCUR has huge gross margins of 58% and its EPS last quarter grew by 100% from quarter before and 300% from two quarters ago. Its main rival Seachange (SEAC) lost money this past year on lower margins of 50% yet is currently trading with an enterprise value of 1.85x revenues, which would make CCUR a $15+ stock.</Msg><Username>goodwe212</Username><Timestamp>1364204673491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 05:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364214905758-7</Id><Title>Windows Blue Build 9364</Title><Msg>Available for download. Bing it. But don't google it unless you want your personal data jeopardized and endangered by suspicious goolge behavior.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1364214905758</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 08:35:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364216970255-8</Id><Topic><Title>Wearable Computers</Title><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1364180112423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get real. First, the iWatch won't be aimed only at baby-boomers. Digital watches have been popular for decades, so an iWatch would be a natural evolution for all ages. And it's just one more trend that Microsoft will miss out on, if it goes true to form.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364216970255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 09:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364222480305-9</Id><Title>Ballmer Must Go: Windows Blue Won't Save Microsoft</Title><Msg>Google it. Quoting: "NEW YORK (TheStreet) -- It seems absurd to call Steve Ballmer, the billionaire CEO of Microsoft (MSFT), a failure. However, as billionaire CEOs go, it's not all that crazy. "Here's a guy who gets a free pass from the media as well as shareholders. He never gets asked the tough questions. He rarely puts himself in a position to get asked the tough questions. The Microsoft board gives Ballmer a free pass as well. Is it because of the company's massive cash hoard, seemingly endless free cash flow and Ballmer's presumably close relationship with Bill Gates? "Ballmer should be synonymous with MSFT's 12% dump over the last year, yet the collective known as "we" lets Ballmer slide, giving him chance after chance to bring something resembling excitement to Microsoft's product line. "Over the weekend, CNET told us about Windows Blue, which apparently fixes much of what's wrong with the current iterations of the Windows 8 desktop and mobile platforms. It's set to come out later in the year or something like that. We don't need details. Looking forward to another wholly uninspiring Microsoft offering should not be the focus. "While I understand that companies regularly put out OS updates, this one, at least as presented in early media reports, sounds like little more than a do-over. Another Ballmer-led attempt to fit a round peg into a square hole. To salvage the dying PC industry via an arranged marriage between the desktop and mobile. This is 2013, Balms, arranged marriages tend not to fly. "So Ballmer continues to oppress MSFT shareholders and the rest of us just dying to see a company other than Apple (AAPL) bring something innovative to market. The need does not exist for an OS that melds the desktop and mobile. That loud flop we heard late last year -- the Microsoft Surface tablet -- ..... " And so on....</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364222480305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:41:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364223463047-10</Id><Title>MSFT hater &amp; pimp woto says Windows Blue wont save Microsoft</Title><Msg>well he passes on a story which is a lie - and all because he cant work for Microsoft as a urinal technician I suppose HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364223463047</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364224545914-11</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT hater &amp; pimp woto says Windows Blue wont save Microsoft</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364223463047</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:57:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wonton the ugly SUX shill hate troll is always posting on the WB.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1364224545914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 11:15:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364225808900-12</Id><Title>do you remember when we went after mimv not so along go</Title><Msg>if we ever are going to by anything now is the time to do it now MIMV stock price is only 17 cents a share and we need something good now .... i'm with the most we do need a change at the top or out stock price will fall to $10.00</Msg><Username>northernman003</Username><Timestamp>1364225808900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 11:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364228064789-13</Id><Title>Microsoft Outlook Lowered Because Of Slow PC Sales</Title><Msg>Google it.....</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364228064789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364228684478-14</Id><Topic><Title>I Give My Cash To Greenpeace Before I Buy Koch Industries Products.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_nation</Username><Timestamp>1364142577633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>70,000 Koch employees, most of them in unions, want to thank you for living out your loony fantasies. A boycott will surely be useful.</Msg><Username>thuddite</Username><Timestamp>1364228684478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364229172209-15</Id><Topic><Title>I Give My Cash To Greenpeace Before I Buy Koch Industries Products.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_nation</Username><Timestamp>1364142577633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*yawn* Microsoft's anti-Koch vendetta continues.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364229172209</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:32:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364229226041-16</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Outlook Lowered Because Of Slow PC Sales</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364228064789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump....</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364229226041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:33:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364229844125-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer Must Go: Windows Blue Won't Save Microsoft</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364222480305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:41:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ballmer must stay! As long as he's in charge, M$ will continue to fail.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364229844125</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364231419611-18</Id><Topic><Title>I Give My Cash To Greenpeace Before I Buy Koch Industries Products.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_nation</Username><Timestamp>1364142577633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty good list of daily consumables, how about using cash to wipe instead of Koch? No wonder they make so much money, selling products flushed and thrown in the trash, made from trees. They don't have to be the way they are politically, they have large excess for themselves already. Why can't they just stop being rich a hoes and live a peaceful life?</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1364231419611</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364231931416-19</Id><Topic><Title>I Give My Cash To Greenpeace Before I Buy Koch Industries Products.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_nation</Username><Timestamp>1364142577633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Administration moves $500M in Palestinian aid, as agencies scramble to delay furloughs Published March 25, 2013 As federal agencies scramble to avert or delay sequester-tied furloughs, the Obama administration continues to spend millions of dollars on foreign aid to the Palestinians – and seek millions more, despite past efforts by Congress to freeze the money. The State Department confirmed this month the administration has moved forward with $500 million in aid, and is trying to secure another $200 million from Congress. Department spokeswoman Victoria Nuland says the aid is important, because an “economically viable Palestinian Authority” would help regional peace and security. The administration confirmed the transfers as President Obama, along with Secretary of State John Kerry, toured the Middle East last week. Obama met with Palestinian Authority President Mahmoud Abbas, as well as top Israeli officials. But lawmakers have heavily scrutinized a number of foreign aid transactions, given the fiscal crunch facing Washington. The capital was awash last week with memos and updates from federal agencies scrambling to manage sequester cuts and cushion their staff from the impact of furloughs. After initial warnings that furlough notices would start to go out for thousands of civilian employees at the Pentagon last Thursday, the Defense Department announced it would delay those notices for about two weeks while it continues to analyze the situation.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1364231931416</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:18:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364232244044-20</Id><Title>Serious ?</Title><Msg>Back below $28 - hard to fully grasp just how horrific this stock truly is because there's nothing to compare it to in the history of all stock markets. Dead stock price for 12 years and counting with no hope in sight while $70 BILLION $$$$ sits in the bank NOT being used to benefit shareholders. They could use that $$ to force the stock up into the 40's overnight but they couldn't care less about their shareholders suffering for nearly an entire generation! So the ? : When is the last time you heard ANYTHING that could reasonably be considered good news about this company?</Msg><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1364232244044</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364232364137-21</Id><Topic><Title>I Give My Cash To Greenpeace Before I Buy Koch Industries Products.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_nation</Username><Timestamp>1364142577633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd guess their paper products are byproducts of their lumber company. The trees would be cut anyway. Last I checked, the forested acreage in North America held constant through the twentieth century, and increased in Europe.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364232364137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364232710966-22</Id><Topic><Title>I Give My Cash To Greenpeace Before I Buy Koch Industries Products.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_nation</Username><Timestamp>1364142577633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you are saying is..."I sold my sole to the state a long time ago. No turnin back now."</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1364232710966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364234375471-23</Id><Title>BIG NEWS OUT ON--BCCI-- READ YAHOO NEWS HEADLINES$$$</Title><Msg>facts</Msg><Username>upper_ss</Username><Timestamp>1364234375471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364236191925-24</Id><Topic><Title>When will the press and American people demand reality accountability from the Liar in Chief?</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364232879307</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GWB is history that's why. As for Pres Obama, he doesn't use the whites only fountain. He and his family get to use the same things as the white first families did. When you understand what that means in regards to your postings, then hell will be frozen over.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364236191925</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364236894400-25</Id><Topic><Title>I Give My Cash To Greenpeace Before I Buy Koch Industries Products.</Title><Username>lordbalzy_nation</Username><Timestamp>1364142577633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:29:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one said trees aren't managed. They must be as modern society uses a huge amount of trees and wastes them. I remember a teacher I had who was from Germany, who lived in poorer times. She made us write on both sides, and said they would have to erase and reuse paper when she was in school. Koch knows that consumables and growing the material from sunlight and earth is a good ongoing business. The question is why do they want more, for what? Feel good about themselves? Why can't they pay more tax rate? They can is the answer. What would change for them to pay 5% more tax rate? Nothing is the answer.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1364236894400</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364237459960-26</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Outlook Lowered Because Of Slow PC Sales</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364228064789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee, do you think that the obtuse Windows 8 operating system has anything to do with slow sales? Nah.</Msg><Username>thuddite</Username><Timestamp>1364237459960</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364237625843-27</Id><Topic><Title>Late 'Global warming' to hit midwest, forecasters predicting</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364234440270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:00:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawfaecies if you had studied engineering you would have had to study chemistry and then you would understand why it is that MMGW is a real and growing danger to the human race. As it is you are content in you awesome ignorance of the physics and chemistry and climatology of this world</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364237625843</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364237703502-28</Id><Topic><Title>Late 'Global warming' to hit midwest, forecasters predicting</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364234440270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:00:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we know ur stew pid, ya don't need to keep reminding us.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364237703502</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364237882705-29</Id><Topic><Title>Equal rights for gays? Absolutely yes, but they can't be married any more than they can</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364233286589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:41:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The definition of 'marriage' is being changed by society BTW which God is it that you speak of ??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364237882705</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364238202855-30</Id><Topic><Title>Late 'Global warming' to hit midwest, forecasters predicting</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364234440270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:00:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, that explains where the 6,500 feet of ice went that covered my home site 11,000 years ago.</Msg><Username>thuddite</Username><Timestamp>1364238202855</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364238280502-31</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Outlook Lowered Because Of Slow PC Sales</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364228064789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 Metro looks like it was designed by Fisher Price! That's why nobody is buying it.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364238280502</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364238514262-32</Id><Title>Read This Very Carefully How Marissa Mayer will become MSFT CEO Within 2 Years!</Title><Msg>Yahoo will buy small companies here and there like it did once Again today! Microsoft business is dying. I just ordered my 2nd Chrome computer. Cheap and reliable like hell is for perverts! Story short - MSFT will buy Yahoo in Short Order - Was expected by EOM April but seems Mid May will see the smoke! Yahoo will be run separately to begin with then in 2 years Ballmer will retire to spend more time with family or become co-Chairman and Marissa will be CEO! This is written of MSFT is to survive! Gs</Msg><Username>gs_markets</Username><Timestamp>1364238514262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:08:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364238893151-33</Id><Topic><Title>Equal rights for gays? Absolutely yes, but they can't be married any more than they can</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364233286589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:41:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Words have meanings ????? That can never change ???</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364238893151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364238924417-34</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Outlook Lowered Because Of Slow PC Sales</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364228064789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holy #$%$ #$%$!! You old farts still on here crying and whining? It's going on 20 years now isn't? Amazing that you two still have no lives.</Msg><Username>trevor.williamson</Username><Timestamp>1364238924417</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364239062485-35</Id><Topic><Title>Why the opening pump rally this A.M. Cyprus' reason for being, fiscally speaking is done</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364238946998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:15:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah every day market rises is a 'pump' unless an old white guy is the president.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364239062485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364239255807-36</Id><Title>Word definitions are what society says they are. You can argue with this but</Title><Msg>when the new definition is in common usage your opinion is a moot point. Fur instance 'cookie' now means more than it use to.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364239255807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364239292026-37</Id><Title>Microsoft Outlok Raised Because of accelerating W-8, tablet, and phone sales</Title><Msg>Morning star rates MSFT as a 4 star buy with target of 35 and S&amp;P rates MSFT as a 5 star with a target of 34</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364239292026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:21:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364239496835-38</Id><Topic><Title>Word definitions are what society says they are. You can argue with this but</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364239255807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And a good economy now goes by a different definition. Bush recovered us from a recession with tax rebates, and lowered unemployment to 4.5% for months on end. Libs snuffed that one off, but now think lowering the unemployment numbers to 7.8% makes for a good economy, even though there are some 26,000,000 folks without a full time job, and over 45,000,000 folks below the poverty line.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1364239496835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364239569424-39</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer Must Go: Windows Blue Won't Save Microsoft</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364222480305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:41:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ballmer is the best thing that ever happened to AAPL and GOOG.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364239569424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:26:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364239689445-40</Id><Topic><Title>Serious ?</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1364232244044</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:24:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Below 25 in 6 months</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364239689445</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364240322439-41</Id><Title>Are most democrats sex deviots, stupid or both?</Title><Msg>Just last week we learned that Massachusetts Democrat John Fresolo pulled a Weiner. Now one of his fellow Democrats in New Jersey is getting in on the act. NY Post: A powerful New Jersey Democrat who’s being touted as the party’s next state chairman has an insatiable lust for bondage, oral sex and spanking, secret e-mails obtained by The Post reveal. Assemblyman Joe Cryan, of Union, graphically spelled out his kinky proclivities in more than 150 e-mails that he sent to a lobbyist — and then fought to keep them hidden after he stunned the state political world by having her busted</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1364240322439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:38:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364241973006-42</Id><Topic><Title>Word definitions are what society says they are. You can argue with this but</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364239255807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364241973006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:06:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364242051345-43</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Outlok Raised Because of accelerating W-8, tablet, and phone sales</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364239292026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:21:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And all in brand new markets and brand new revenue streams. It's only good news for MSFT.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1364242051345</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:07:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364242135198-44</Id><Title>MSFT WAS DEAD A LONG TIME AGO</Title><Msg>Why not consider medical MJ companies such as FITX AND SKTO</Msg><Username>htstocks</Username><Timestamp>1364242135198</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364247100966-45</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer Must Go: Windows Blue Won't Save Microsoft</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364222480305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:41:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can only agree. The article doesn't express my own sentiment, except in identifying the consequences of Ballmer's presence.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364247100966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364247430000-46</Id><Topic><Title>Trevor Williamson, when he last posted he was being outed as a former Microsoft executive</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364240568869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gone but not forgotten. I found his account on Facebook, as I recall. I'm sure it was him, he was wearing the same funny hat. A dyed-in-the-wool marketroid, who lied about the one thing everyone knows about marketing, i.e. the best advertising, bar none, is word of mouth.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364247430000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364247470830-47</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer Must Go: Windows Blue Won't Save Microsoft</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364222480305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:41:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You IDIOTS can feel free to address Mr BALLMER as the 'BIG BOSS MAN". har har har</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1364247470830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364248648757-48</Id><Title>IE11 to appear as Firefox to avoid legacy IE CSS</Title><Msg>On Neowin now: The only way M$ can make anything work with the #$%$ IE is to pretend it's Firefox..... ================================================== We already know that Internet Explorer 11, the next iteration of the world's most popular browser, will include tab syncing as part of the Windows Blue update, which has leaked onto the Internet. Neowin has also discovered that IE11 will include new code which tells the host website that IE is, in fact, Firefox. Some websites serve certain versions of Internet Explorer (we're looking at you, 6) with custom CSS code in order to make sure the website displays in a readable way. These practices are known as "CSS hacks" and target IE6, 7, 8 with a different type of CSS code than other browsers, such as Chrome and Firefox. Microsoft have replaced the "MSIE" string, which identifies the browser to the website as Internet Explorer, with just "IE," meaning host websites won't be able to use their current CSS hacks on IE11. To further ensure IE11 users don't receive an odd version of the site, Microsoft also included the command "Like Gecko" which instructs the website to send back the same version of the website as they would to Firefox. The results of this update are unknown, especially on websites which are poorly coded. The move is strange, but shows that Microsoft is desperate to clean up Internet Explorer and get away from the awful experience in IE6, 7 and 8. ==================================================</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364248648757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364250208701-49</Id><Topic><Title>Word definitions are what society says they are. You can argue with this but</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364239255807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>creeky as usual you miss the point on so many levels. But then again it doesn't really matter if you miss the point now does it. It's all about communication dum my.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364250208701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 18:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364250286691-50</Id><Topic><Title>Late 'Global warming' to hit midwest, forecasters predicting</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364234440270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:00:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excessive rainfall is an expected result of MMGW. Did you have a point.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364250286691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 18:24:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364250964963-51</Id><Title>Microsoft will make a huge comeback!!!</Title><Msg>They will adjust to the changing world. They are still brilliant over there.</Msg><Username>sbutler218</Username><Timestamp>1364250964963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 18:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364251880745-52</Id><Topic><Title>Read This Very Carefully How Marissa Mayer will become MSFT CEO Within 2 Years!</Title><Username>gs_markets</Username><Timestamp>1364238514262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just bought yourself the biggest malware magnet out there Congrats!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1364251880745</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 18:51:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364252159143-53</Id><Title>Why Can't Microsoft Catch a Break?</Title><Msg>Google it. Why do I get the impression Microsoft's PR department is going into overdrive? There's another very strange article out there, written by a Microsoft executive, which lists Microsoft among "the world's most ethical software companies" [article title is "The World's Most Ethical Software Companies: What They All Have in Common"]. I don't see how anyone could ever characterize Microsoft as even passably ethical, but it's not too surprising given who wrote the article. It's all so characteristic of Microsoft. Instead of trying to fix the actual problems, Microsoft seems to be trying to fumigate its public image through a media blitz.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364252159143</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 18:55:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364252623978-54</Id><Topic><Title>Read This Very Carefully How Marissa Mayer will become MSFT CEO Within 2 Years!</Title><Username>gs_markets</Username><Timestamp>1364238514262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get real. I'll believe it when I see it.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364252623978</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 19:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364254467154-55</Id><Topic><Title>Equal rights for gays? Absolutely yes, but they can't be married any more than they can</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364233286589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:41:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't need to be religious to get married with a marriage license. After getting that, you are married, and can be "gay" or "not gay." Otherwise, prohibiting "gays" to marry, the lawyers will lose business later, and you know you want more business, for the "producers." Look at it that way , it's good for business. Now go back in time and explain how ronmey's mormon ancestors could marry one man, and a bunch of women. Or is that why they fled America? ho ho ho</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364254467154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 19:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364254653503-56</Id><Title>Surface</Title><Msg>Anyone know when new version will be available. What will POS do?</Msg><Username>rickysmith1001</Username><Timestamp>1364254653503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 19:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364255113047-57</Id><Topic><Title>Word definitions are what society says they are. You can argue with this but</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1364239255807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like the old definition of gay better, what is gay about being gay? Two atheists can get married, no religion needed to be legally married. So if you like your religion, and it says man and woman, good, stick to that for yourself. Leave other people alone, it isn't your business to impose religious values on others. Try to talk them into it instead, ho ho ho.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364255113047</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 19:45:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364256177010-58</Id><Topic><Title>Read This Very Carefully How Marissa Mayer will become MSFT CEO Within 2 Years!</Title><Username>gs_markets</Username><Timestamp>1364238514262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am long Yahoo and MSFT. Bought Yhoo last year in the 14's when everyone was dissing it like they are now with MSFT. Short MSFT at your own peril. If you have, hedge. MSFT is going up, up and then up.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1364256177010</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 20:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364256800286-59</Id><Title>How many Republican Presidents had sex with young interns at the White House?</Title><Msg>In the Oval Office or in the White House pool?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1364256800286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 20:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364256988889-60</Id><Topic><Title>Equal rights for gays? Absolutely yes, but they can't be married any more than they can</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364233286589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:41:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are sterile and so is your partner you can't procreate, but you can marry. Marriage is defined legally by whoever is allowed to get a license. Religion is a personal issue. Imposing your religion on others is not allowed, last I checked.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364256988889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 20:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364257007744-61</Id><Topic><Title>Equal rights for gays? Absolutely yes, but they can't be married any more than they can</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364233286589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:41:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, though God/religion is irrelevant. "Marriage" is the merging of DNA that leads to offspring. Obviously that doesn't happen with gays. No reason they shouldn't be able to form legally binding partnerships, but the law doesn't change biology.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364257007744</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 20:16:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364257780095-62</Id><Topic><Title>Equal rights for gays? Absolutely yes, but they can't be married any more than they can</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364233286589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:41:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Marriage is the merging of DNA? That's a new one. The DNA is never merged unless there are children, which many times doesn't happen. Children are legal for 18 years then become legal entities. Marriage is a personal decision any two idiots crazy enough to sign away half their estate to a unrelated person, can enter into. You don't have to be in "love", you don't have to be anything, except alive enough to say I do, and sign your name on the license.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364257780095</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 20:29:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364258046569-63</Id><Topic><Title>Equal rights for gays? Absolutely yes, but they can't be married any more than they can</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364233286589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:41:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Children are yours for 18 years then become legal entities.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1364258046569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 20:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364258751835-64</Id><Title>Doom for MSFT</Title><Msg>Samsung Series 3 XE300M22-B01US No Screen Chromebox Celeron B840(1.90GHz) 4GB DDR3 16GB SSD HDD Capacity Intel HD Graphics Google Chrome OS....$300..will run Google Drive Apps/Mail..will even run skydrive, and outlook mail...LOL!</Msg><Username>watersfall9999</Username><Timestamp>1364258751835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 20:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364262475254-65</Id><Title>MSFT will go down to 19.00</Title><Msg>Get out of MSFT while you can. Get into the chance of a life time, Medical MJ , the best ones now are SKTO, and FITX</Msg><Username>htstocks</Username><Timestamp>1364262475254</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 21:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364264186613-66</Id><Topic><Title>IE11 to appear as Firefox to avoid legacy IE CSS</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364248648757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back to the top.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364264186613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364264536059-67</Id><Topic><Title>How Many Republican Congressmen &amp; Senators Have Had Sex With Interns?</Title><Username>captain_zee</Username><Timestamp>1364264201609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:16:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Define "ton".</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364264536059</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:22:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364264626807-68</Id><Topic><Title>IE11 to appear as Firefox to avoid legacy IE CSS</Title><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1364248648757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poetic justice...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364264626807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364265488322-69</Id><Title>Will the PC ever be great again?</Title><Msg>Not with Windows 8 Metro!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364265488322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364265693470-70</Id><Topic><Title>Doom for MSFT</Title><Username>watersfall9999</Username><Timestamp>1364258751835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 20:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google Chromebooks cost 70% less than an Ultrabook and 50% less than a Surface RT tablet.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364265693470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364265883963-71</Id><Topic><Title>Equal rights for gays? Absolutely yes, but they can't be married any more than they can</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1364233286589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:41:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gay marriage is a good thing. Then gays can be just as miserable as everybody else!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364265883963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364265979747-72</Id><Topic><Title>Surface</Title><Username>rickysmith1001</Username><Timestamp>1364254653503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 19:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody cares about Surface outside of Redmond.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364265979747</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364266100255-73</Id><Topic><Title>How Many Republican Congressmen &amp; Senators Have Had Sex With Interns?</Title><Username>captain_zee</Username><Timestamp>1364264201609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:16:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Clinton wants Hillary to run again in 2016. That way he can score with more interns!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364266100255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364266256449-74</Id><Topic><Title>Why Can't Microsoft Catch a Break?</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1364252159143</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 18:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSFT has more Lawyers than Developers</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364266256449</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364266415082-75</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft will make a huge comeback!!!</Title><Username>sbutler218</Username><Timestamp>1364250964963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 18:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They can't keep buying back shares to inflate MSFT's share price forever</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364266415082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364266524917-76</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Outlok Raised Because of accelerating W-8, tablet, and phone sales</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364239292026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:21:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This might be more believable if there were sales numbers to back it up.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364266524917</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 22:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364266803377-77</Id><Topic><Title>Read This Very Carefully How Marissa Mayer will become MSFT CEO Within 2 Years!</Title><Username>gs_markets</Username><Timestamp>1364238514262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:08:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A team of wild horses couldn't drag Ballmer away. It won't be so easy to get rid of him.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1364266803377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 23:00:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>