<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371537551281-1</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT HASN'T DISTINGUISHED ITSELF IN OVER A DECADE. AND IT'S SP. SHOWS IT. STILL 26-36. BIG DEAL.</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371422379028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fowl koan, birdy! how do you ever remember all that? but what about the rest of the story? what did the buddha/the young monk/the investor say when the master told him to be ready for a very early morning? how surprised was he? etc, etc, etc.</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1371537551281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 02:39:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371545461487-2</Id><Topic><Title>If #$%$ Cheney approves of what Obama is doing does that make Obama good</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371519857813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 21:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've read that Warren Buffett is bailing out of American corporations as fast as ever he can. Do you suppose he knows something we don't?</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371545461487</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 04:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371546083127-3</Id><Title>Microsoft Is Fast Turning Into A Sideshow</Title><Msg>Google it. Article now six months old, but events since then have only confirmed the points it makes. Quoting: "So, now it’s clear: Windows 8 did not blow the doors off during the holiday. In context, this tepid launch is just one of a litany of failures fast relegating Microsoft to the status of incidental spectacle in the information technology business. "If Windows 8 is Exhibit A, Exhibit B is Windows Phone 8. Nokia has started discounting recently launched Lumia phones, indicating that they’re not exactly moving like hotcakes. Microsoft makes excuses and says these things take time, but even a fool can tell a torrid introduction from a lukewarm launch. "Thus, in the important high-mobility category (phones and tablets), where Apple and Google are cleaning up, Microsoft is 0 for 2. "More on how bad it is: An in-depth review of Windows 8 by Brian Boyko pans Windows 8 for nearly 24 minutes. "How bad is it? Microsoft is not even mentioned among the four companies a Wall Street Journal team highlighted in an assessment of the great battles ahead in tech in 2013. According to the Journal, the firms to watch are Google, Apple, Facebook, and Amazon. "Microsoft has reached an Orwellian impasse, in which it cannot tell the truth — even to itself. It is blinded by its own hallucinations about how the market is operating. The result is that its public pronouncements entirely lack credibility. "When the Metro name had to be dropped, likely for legal reasons, the company said, “”We have used Metro style as a codename during the product development cycle across many of our product lines....</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371546083127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371549619995-4</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT</Title><Username>stockwoodie</Username><Timestamp>1371503790591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:16:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea, but businesses can send the employees all over the world with them and they can use their office doc, show their spread sheets, check their email, use gps, etc. It is a sweet device. It kills me when a company that has that much of a drop dead gorgeous device is known for software. If I was a phone maker, I would be sweating right now. Microsoft is putting out some killer shet. XBOX One, Surface, man those are epic. It is going to crush it in a good economy.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371549619995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 06:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371550400402-5</Id><Title>Will Microsoft really wait on Nokia?</Title><Msg>The Best Buy opportunity is here now. Ballmer is under the gun and anyone who knows Balmer knows that they can be fired or their contract terminated at any given time in a New York Minute. He is not Mr. Feel Good. Nokia is involving themselves in their own venture NSN which would prevent Microsoft from acquiring them. Elop who used to run the Office division at Microsoft is CEO of Nokia. So he probably do what he know he has to and get rid of NSN. If he does not, I would expect to see a Microsoft Surface phone produced by Foxconn by the holiday season. Microsoft needs a complete suite of products with their logo and brand on them to cross sell their entire eco system. They are getting huge Dept. of Defense &amp; s city contracts for 1000's of devices and they want everything from notebooks, phones. Surfaces, Xbox ONE conference calling via Skype, etc. They can send their employees on one training seminar Windows 8 and then they can run and use all the devices easily. People do not realize that if a DOD customer starts using Office or Windows they have every employee trained. If they use a different phone more training. It cut's down on the seminars and creates a seamless experience with Sky Drive. In addition, the system Administrator can erase all data remotely on a Windows Phone. The big kicker for small companies is this. The boss can see exactly where the phones are in real time on a map with no extra cost. Be careful if your boss gives you a Windows Phone. The gps is extremely accurate and if you are not where you are supposed to be your busted. This feature sells the phone instantly to small to large businesses. BE CAREFUL!</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371550400402</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 06:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371551569213-6</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Says Fortune 500 Firms Are Loving Its Amazon Cloud Killer (Source Business Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371492135165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 14:02:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You better buy your Champagne now as all this will happen in July 2013 after our earnings release. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371551569213</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 06:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371554970910-7</Id><Topic><Title>Siri Takes Another Beating From Microsoft In Latest Anti-iPad Commercial (Source Buinsess Insider)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371483317480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 11:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next beating will be directed at iPhone. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371554970910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:29:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371555013765-8</Id><Topic><Title>Skype Brings Free Video Messaging Out Of Preview, Redefines ‘Visual Voicemail’....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371488785392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a big one that no one can match. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371555013765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371555139186-9</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft BUY Recommendation update 2013.06.11.</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370954308316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 08:38:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earnings of $1.05-1.10 for Q2/2013, beating the 75 cents consensus estimate by 50% and that will give us the growth company P/E of 25 plus. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371555139186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371555149864-10</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT</Title><Username>stockwoodie</Username><Timestamp>1371503790591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:16:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My Samsung Google Chromebook comes with a keyboard and only costs $249. I'm using it right now. It works great with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371555149864</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371555241904-11</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT</Title><Username>stockwoodie</Username><Timestamp>1371503790591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:16:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eewww! I bet your keyboard is all sticky now.</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371555241904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371555454934-12</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MANY DECADES HAS IT BEEN SINCE MSFT WON ANYTHING. XP. THE LAST GOOD PRODUCT. 15 YRS. OLD</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371516432601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 20:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft won first place in the 2009 Fiasco Awards with Vista. Windows 8 has a good chance of winning in 2013. Sent from a Samsung Google Chromebook with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371555454934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371555617130-13</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Fast Turning Into A Sideshow</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371546083127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Steve Ballmer is the Sideshow Freak!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371555617130</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371556026677-14</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Fast Turning Into A Sideshow</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371546083127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey bozo are you sure its only 6 mos old and not 16 mos? Its as far off track as something that might come out of you- the only people really bashing W-8 are a handful of AAPL/GOOG investors who either already lost their sas or are about to in the case of GOOG--the WSJ get serious they are among the biggest losers in this game- sort of like you</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371556026677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371556146722-15</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT</Title><Username>stockwoodie</Username><Timestamp>1371503790591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:16:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The surface RT?? beats hell out of the droid turds and I turds doesnt it?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371556146722</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:49:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371556204336-16</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT</Title><Username>stockwoodie</Username><Timestamp>1371503790591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:16:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>phands keyboard would be all sticky too but he needs another infusion of juice to get going</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371556204336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371559198867-17</Id><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Msg>video, Guillory says it is the Republican Party that actually has the best interests of the black community in mind. He argues Democrats relentlessly push an agenda intended to exert control over blacks, not lift them out of poverty. “You see, in recent history, the Democrat party has created the illusion that their agenda and their policies are what’s best for black people,” Guillory said. “Somehow it has been forgotten that the Republican party was founded in 1854 as an abolitionist movement, with one simple creed: that slavery is a violation of the rights of man.” The former Democrat explained that Frederick Douglass called Republicans the “party of freedom and progress.” He also pointed out that former Republican President Abraham Lincoln signed the Emancipation Proclamation and Republicans in Congress wrote the Thirteenth, Fourteenth and Fifteenth Amendments. “The Democrats, on the other hand, were the party of Jim Crow,” Guillory added. “It was the Democrats who defended the rights of slave owners.” He went on: “You see, at the heart of liberalism, is the idea that only a great and powerful big Government can be the benefactor of social justice for all Americans. But the left is only concerned with one thing: control. And they disguise this control as charity.”</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371559643338-18</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MANY DECADES HAS IT BEEN SINCE MSFT WON ANYTHING. XP. THE LAST GOOD PRODUCT. 15 YRS. OLD</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371516432601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 20:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I own a new Suface Pro you dumb ignorant F.........." Backwards as usual, Billy Boy. Let me correct that for you. "I own a new Suface Pro therefore I am a dumb ignorant F.........." There ya' go! All better now...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371559643338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371559991588-19</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Control ?? Every black person has all the freedom possible, what is this 'control' you dreamt up.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1371559991588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371560439946-20</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How difficult is it to understand that fact? DUH! Conservatism is about cutting back on big wasteful gov. , and creates jobs that pays the bills for those in need. Unemployment amongst some Black segments has been in the 40% range. And we know what that leads to. Liberalism will always go broke at some point.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1371560439946</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371560601614-21</Id><Topic><Title>Tremendous Improvement for MSFT. Read Now!</Title><Username>byronmungia</Username><Timestamp>1371560371842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tight top.</Msg><Username>woodfordclifton</Username><Timestamp>1371560601614</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371560795729-22</Id><Topic><Title>Tremendous Improvement for MSFT. Read Now!</Title><Username>byronmungia</Username><Timestamp>1371560371842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>numbers are mildly good.</Msg><Username>watsonchristopher960</Username><Timestamp>1371560795729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371561485312-23</Id><Title>Microsoft wins $400 mil defense contract</Title><Msg>Blue badge, software developers and access to code according to govconwire</Msg><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1371561485312</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:18:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371561855464-24</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Fast Turning Into A Sideshow</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371546083127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for the incoherent and incorrect snot bubble, wally. Not your best effort but pretty much what we've come to expect from the bottom of the MS shilling and pimping cesspool.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371561855464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371562038824-25</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft wins $400 mil defense contract</Title><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1371561485312</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:18:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure there will be plenty more of that in the coming years.</Msg><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371562038824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:27:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371562100000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Fast Turning Into A Sideshow</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371546083127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor predip, Stupid self loathing Sybil drunk again and trolling despicable S-K,A-N-K.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371562100000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:28:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371562124428-27</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT</Title><Username>stockwoodie</Username><Timestamp>1371503790591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 17:16:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My Surface Pro gives me a woodie..." Everybody gives you their woodie [sic], Billy Boy. Does your SP blow enough pecker snot on your tonsils to keep you happy?</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371562124428</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371562350203-28</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Fast Turning Into A Sideshow</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371546083127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Off topic as usual and just the kind of snot bubble a juvenile delinquent sissy such as yourself is know for, pigeon#$%$.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371562350203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371562364471-29</Id><Topic><Title>Tremendous Improvement for MSFT. Read Now!</Title><Username>byronmungia</Username><Timestamp>1371560371842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>best out there .</Msg><Username>jnichols870</Username><Timestamp>1371562364471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371562806019-30</Id><Topic><Title>Tremendous Improvement for MSFT. Read Now!</Title><Username>byronmungia</Username><Timestamp>1371560371842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is so flat Im feeling gidddy</Msg><Username>justinsims550</Username><Timestamp>1371562806019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371563223608-31</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Fast Turning Into A Sideshow</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371546083127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's really interesting to me is the repsonses to this article on Reddit and elsewhere. They might have been written by osso. Indeed, if we compared the text closely, I'd bet we'd find them nearly identical, or so close that they could have been written following the same outline. The shills aren't only on this board, the are everywhere.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371563223608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371563308199-32</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft wins $400 mil defense contract</Title><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1371561485312</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:18:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's only the beginning............................</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371563308199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371563403174-33</Id><Title>Cartoon: Obama: "I wish we could find a video to blame all these other scandals on"</Title><Msg>"Consultant: "Here's one of your inauguration" So true. That works!</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371563403174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371563488866-34</Id><Topic><Title>Skype Brings Free Video Messaging Out Of Preview, Redefines ‘Visual Voicemail’....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371488785392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>M$FT is on the right track............................Bing!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371563488866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371563554963-35</Id><Title>Microsoft has changed their name in Ctr Alt Del soft</Title><Msg>The most important keys for all windows systems.</Msg><Username>dollar_printer</Username><Timestamp>1371563554963</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371563628201-36</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MANY DECADES HAS IT BEEN SINCE MSFT WON ANYTHING. XP. THE LAST GOOD PRODUCT. 15 YRS. OLD</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371516432601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 20:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With INTC's new chip Pro will be the best all around device hands down.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371563628201</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371563965807-37</Id><Topic><Title>Skype Brings Free Video Messaging Out Of Preview, Redefines ‘Visual Voicemail’....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371488785392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would have said there is nothing more annoying than voicemail, but probably visual voicemail is vastly more annoying.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371563965807</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:59:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371564362590-38</Id><Topic><Title>Skype Brings Free Video Messaging Out Of Preview, Redefines ‘Visual Voicemail’....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371488785392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know about that, I find your MSFT jealous trash posts infinitely more annoying.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371564362590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:06:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371564367984-39</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Fast Turning Into A Sideshow</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371546083127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I reckon MS subscribes to the idea that desperate times call for desperate measures. The palpable desperation coming out of their shilling and pimping stables reeks to the rafters. MS would be better served by putting as much effort into improving their product offerings.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371564367984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371564669427-40</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Stupid" Self descriptive and dead on balls accurate, Billy Boy.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371564669427</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371564684104-41</Id><Topic><Title>ACTUALLY. MSFT PE IS 18. QUITE HIGH. OVER THE CURRENT S&amp;P AVG. AND LOW YIELD. SO DOWN GOES SP.</Title><Username>joeeddy69</Username><Timestamp>1371349664077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The performance these paid msft employees are predicting... Hasn't happened in 13 years. greatest market ever msft under-performs. see apple or google chart. see dow chart. this is dead money.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371564684104</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371564722509-42</Id><Topic><Title>ERGONOMICALLY INCORRECT. TOUCHSCREEN WILL BE SHOULDER MISERY. AND QUICK. OLDER USERS WILL</Title><Username>joeeddy69</Username><Timestamp>1371517285952</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 21:01:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know folks wll hate yelling at the tv. As i hate yelling at my acer windows 8. or hp that's not touch like my acer.. But still 8 is sooooo flawed. You tv will be as confused as any pc with 8. Too many misreads. As 8 is still being ironed out. not finished and many misreads and flaws. period.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371564722509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371564763776-43</Id><Topic><Title>ERGONOMICALLY INCORRECT. TOUCHSCREEN WILL BE SHOULDER MISERY. AND QUICK. OLDER USERS WILL</Title><Username>joeeddy69</Username><Timestamp>1371517285952</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 21:01:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>singing4theirsuppers • 1 minute 33 seconds ago 0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply ERGONOMICALLY INCORRECT. TOUCHSCREEN WILL BE SHOULDER MISERY. AND QUICK. OLDER USERS WILL Figure this out quick. shoulders can't support long use. As all your arms weight will be suspended while your arm is extended to touch.....thousands of times a day. you may realize that the hands and wrists are bad enough. Carpel tunnel and all. But this soulder wear....will be a real problem. In a couple years. many work comp claims coming. normally a person rests his hands on pc. Well try that with touch. you can't. you must lift your arm for every command. arms are heavy. especially oler worker arms. this will be bad for america. And msft for sure. Many rotator cuff injuries coming. the bursa will swell and you will get what barbers and mechanics get....bursitis.......oh yeah. all true. I have one. 8 weeks now. And i can tell. Not good ergo..design. a silly gimmick that doesn't work well. Many many do overs. Poor design. Period</Msg><Username>wishin_aint_investin</Username><Timestamp>1371564763776</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371564802257-44</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MANY DECADES HAS IT BEEN SINCE MSFT WON ANYTHING. XP. THE LAST GOOD PRODUCT. 15 YRS. OLD</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371516432601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 20:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And this new 8. ha ha ha ha... What a friggin' joke. flying metro tiles. charms shoot out of all the margins... This pos is all over the place. well except where you want it to go. too many false reads. hand gestures fail....over and over...it gets old really really quick. msft. Support suggests downgrade to 7. Call tham. Omni-tech. Call em. I did.</Msg><Username>wishin_aint_investin</Username><Timestamp>1371564802257</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371564852212-45</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively On top500 now... Only 3 out 500 garbage POS M$ machines left... Quote:- In the latest TOP-500 supercomputer list Linux OS family has 476 out of 500 world fastest computers. This is 95.2%. There are 3 Windows running machines (0.6%), two Azure and one HPC. The rest are various Unices (16), BSD (1) and mixed (4). The number of Linux boxes increased within the latest 6 months by seven (4 less for Unix and 3 less mixed ones). It is even better if one looks at performance share. Linux has 97.44% of the total raw GFlop power, Unix 1.77%, mixed 0.53%, Windows 0.21% and BSD 0.05%. The Linux share increased by 1.33% while all the other decreased (in the case of Windows from 0.29% to 0.21%) showing the Windows machines have on average half the power of a typical TOP-500 supercomputer. In raw power Linux boxes increased from 155 to 217 TFlop within 6 months. No other OS family increased its raw power showing that most probably the only new supercomputers build within the last 6 months were Linux ones</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371564852212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:14:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371565103037-46</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MANY DECADES HAS IT BEEN SINCE MSFT WON ANYTHING. XP. THE LAST GOOD PRODUCT. 15 YRS. OLD</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371516432601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 20:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure it did &amp; that's why you perch on the M$FT financial board &amp; shill cheap shoddy Sux products LOL! I love my WinDoze8 OS........................</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371565103037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371565148492-47</Id><Topic><Title>If #$%$ Cheney approves of what Obama is doing does that make Obama good</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371519857813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 21:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The President, who is spot on in his thinking and makes sense to rational people, already explained the ongoing "spying" and how he has handled it . Which is very well. Unlike Bush of course who was unable to handle complex things. Fake scandal after fake scandal, nothing works, because they are made up tall tales. It's so sad for you.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1371565148492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371565252311-48</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tells me that M$FT is racing to hit$40++ LOL!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371565252311</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:20:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371565459417-49</Id><Topic><Title>If #$%$ Cheney approves of what Obama is doing does that make Obama good</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371519857813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 21:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" (1) "flush with a record number of jet orders, the industry is gearing its factories to produce at high volume and low cost. " (2) "Confidence among U.S. homebuilders surged in June, staging its biggest gain since 2002 in one of the strongest signs yet that the housing recovery is gaining traction." (3) "The economy added 165,000 jobs in April, according to the Labor Department. That was more than the 140,000 jobs economists expected, and it marked an improvement over March. " (4) "In May, the economy added 175,000 new jobs, a moderate pace" (1) buy hard assets as fast as you can, the dollar is being printed to oblivion. (2) Obama bailing out banks and redistributing trillions to support a new home value pump his kind destroyed (3)165,000 created, 200,000+ needed to stay even AFTER FOUR FKUCING YEARS (4)President spends $3 to get $1, morons think job creation short of keeping up is good...maybe good for the dolt in chief, but not good.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371565459417</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:24:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371565613118-50</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MANY DECADES HAS IT BEEN SINCE MSFT WON ANYTHING. XP. THE LAST GOOD PRODUCT. 15 YRS. OLD</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371516432601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 20:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aaah the liar william.....you are exactly why i'm here. Youchump.....get a trophy. you are the dumbest pumper going. any board. You.fool.</Msg><Username>gottaloveobama</Username><Timestamp>1371565613118</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371565709964-51</Id><Topic><Title>If #$%$ Cheney approves of what Obama is doing does that make Obama good</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371519857813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 21:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does "every body" include cats, dogs, insects, and the ocean, which is a body of water, too? hohohoho Everyone knows Obama is a thinker, doer, and great man, except those who are stuck in the old George Wallace skin of 1960. Hey old George W grew a new skin, more tolerant of others, so can you.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1371565709964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:28:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371565712390-52</Id><Title>OBAMA SETS THE RECORED STRAIGHT. AND TAKES ALL THE MYSTERY OUT OF THE FED.</Title><Msg>And leads a world recovery....and you prez. Basher idiots are commies. should be locked up for being stupid. In public.</Msg><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371565712390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371565860409-53</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks to me like it "raced" to the mid 30s by essentially tracking the market as it has risen and blowing a lot smoke and hype (much ado about nothing) over their mediocre product offerings. It has hovered and dithered at this low to mid 30 level for a couple of months and doesn't seem inclined to "race" anywhere at the moment. Typical shill pumping bilge from Billy Boy as expected.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371565860409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371565937416-54</Id><Topic><Title>If #$%$ Cheney approves of what Obama is doing does that make Obama good</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371519857813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 21:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You would be getting new jets under republicans... We'd be too broke. no fuel. we would have to get marines to hand push off aircraft carriers. Bush bush and reagan were schooled by nixon...how to totally destroy the economy.....and lie while doing it. gooooo ...obama. go usa.!!!</Msg><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371565937416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:32:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371566139127-55</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>{Up &amp; Away!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371566139127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371566142491-56</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly....predis....you right on !! this pos, has under-performed for ever ! see any chart. Goes nowhere. and actually has waaay under-performed the market and certainly the sector. As always. $26-$36 big deal....dead money.. Why? msft has been fully diluted for 2 decades. Period.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371566142491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371566275710-57</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL!!! TFAD or MORON. Which is it?</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371566275710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:37:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371566310732-58</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>{Every black person has all the freedom possible, what is this 'control' you dreamt up.} Once again, you have absolutely no idea what you're talking about, you young, inexperienced, know-it-all know-nothing, mindless, emotion-based liberal dumb-bass. Listen to the man! Try to understand the facts he is relating to you! Invest 4 minutes of your day to listen to a man of clarity and character. Type Elbert Guillory: "Why I Am a Republican" into the utuub search bar and enjoy simple, straightforward enlightenment.</Msg><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1371566310732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371566408499-59</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just keep telling yourself that partner &amp; live in the past LOL!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371566408499</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371566523250-60</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SETS THE RECORED STRAIGHT. AND TAKES ALL THE MYSTERY OUT OF THE FED.</Title><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371565712390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:28:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree on one point, they no longer even try to conceal the manipulation of the nation's currency in their attempts to defend the poser in chief.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371566523250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371566523774-61</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love how WinDoze8 syncs so beautifully with my Surface Pro.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371566523774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371566759309-62</Id><Title>Memo To Wall Street: WHO CARES?</Title><Msg>Intelligent people know that the crock market is a sham. We're in a second depression, but don't worry, Wall Street is doing just fine. Really? I think not. Big machines trading back and forth creating the ILLUSION. C'mon, do you really think we're that dumb. Judge Judy said it best, "Do you really think we have the word 'stupid' written across our foreheads?" This whole thing is s joke. And who cares? People I know just laugh. Go ask China for more handout money - see what their response is, LOL.</Msg><Username>ifpigscouldfly269</Username><Timestamp>1371566759309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371566813180-63</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I ain't googling s..., If youwant all your info to be sent to every sleazy marketer in the land, go ahead. Bing it, no pimple.</Msg><Username>lithiumniobate</Username><Timestamp>1371566813180</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371567365355-64</Id><Title>if the other team wins the championship game</Title><Msg>Don't be mad, don't be sore, don't be nasty and make up lies about the winner. Pretending that's another way to win. It will come back and bite you in the buttocks.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1371567365355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371567553432-65</Id><Topic><Title>Memo To Wall Street: WHO CARES?</Title><Username>ifpigscouldfly269</Username><Timestamp>1371566759309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:45:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.."Do you really think we have the word 'stupid' written across our foreheads?" .. Only if your a democrat.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371567553432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371567618818-66</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see you don't know of any control means either. But don't let that stop you from posing a truckload of online fukery.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1371567618818</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:00:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371567692189-67</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're being very factious, are you riding the rag?</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371567692189</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371568308519-68</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"factious" Learn to spell, pigeon_rumpranger. Can't ride anything while you're munching on it... How come you're not telling us some lies about your imaginary "falcon" today?</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371568308519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371568464677-69</Id><Title>Wow! Not good.</Title><Msg>MSFT up 2 cents on a huge up day for the markets. May have to cancel that call for $45 by this Friday. I was unaware that MSFT was reduced to giving the Surface away for free. Was this always the plan? Doesn't make sense but this is MSFT! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371568464677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371568644645-70</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MANY DECADES HAS IT BEEN SINCE MSFT WON ANYTHING. XP. THE LAST GOOD PRODUCT. 15 YRS. OLD</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371516432601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 20:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fool?I'm not the one pumping politics on a financial board LOL</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371568644645</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371568670185-71</Id><Topic><Title>Skype Brings Free Video Messaging Out Of Preview, Redefines ‘Visual Voicemail’....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371488785392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course I said the same thing about Zune, Vista, Kin, etc. So we'll have to wait and see if this is yet another bust or not. Only time will tell. Keep your fingers crossed longs! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371568670185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371568671531-72</Id><Title>Yet Another Foot Gun Blast From MS</Title><Msg>"E3 audience offended by "rape joke" at Microsoft Xbox One event" Google it.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371568671531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371569043319-73</Id><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Msg>Ya, those white kristchun values of the rightwing should appeal to people of color. Youse guys wouldn't lie. Would you?</Msg><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371569052855-74</Id><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Msg>Tianhe-2 or TH-2 (En: Milky Way-2) is a 33.86 PetaFLOP supercomputer in China. It was placed in service ahead of schedule in 2013 after it had been expected to be completed in 2015. It is currently the world's fastest supercomputer according to the TOP500 list for June 2013. It is housed at the National Supercomputing Center in Guangzhou (NSCC-GZ) and was designed and developed by the National University of Defense Technology (NUDT) and by Inspur. Inspur contributed to the manufacturing of the printed circuit boards and is also contributing to the system installation and testing. There are 16,000 compute nodes, each comprising two Intel Ivy Bridge Xeon processors and three Xeon Phi chips for a total of 3,120,000 cores. Resource management is based on Simple Linux Utility for Resource Management (SLURM). NO WIN INSIDE</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371569114724-75</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Super Computer at Wikipedia "Although most modern supercomputers use the Linux operating system, each manufacturer has made its own specific changes to the Linux-derivative they use, and no industry standard exists, partly due to the fact that the differences in hardware architectures require changes to optimize the operating system to each hardware design." I shall explain the above to you, SKIPPY. Each Super Computer needs it's very own proprietary O/S suitable to it's particular hardware, if there are 500 Super Computers there are 500 different O/S's. They don't just slap Linux Ubuntu or Windows on a Super Computer, each one needs it's own code written for that one machine. MSFT certainly ain't gonna write 500 different versions of Windows for the fun it, the money is made writing software for the over 1 BILLION PC's running Windows. You got that?</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371569114724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371569738513-76</Id><Topic><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CFury's M.O. is to set a premise that is demonstrably untrue so his ea brain has something he can grasp to attack. As to what appeals to whom, who would have guessed the largest membership ever (by far) in the KKK would have been realized by a state that fought to free the slaves?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371569738513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371570130803-77</Id><Topic><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The values of the world's 2+ billion Christians know no color or ethnicity. For my brothers and sisters in the Americas, to Africa, to Europe, to Asia, Christian values are the same as they were 1,000 years ago, and will be 1,000 years from now. The fleck of darkness that you and your ilk try to thread into the mainstream will not change that. One word for you LardBaldy/vonBelcher, if you are going to continue to fight the mainstream world, The Man: Abilify.</Msg><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1371570130803</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:42:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371570261081-78</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and it's got it's very own operating system, written specially for that one machine.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371570261081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371570364743-79</Id><Topic><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"During the Depression, the Klan continued to wither away -- except in Florida, which had an estimated 30,000 members. Jacksonville, Miami, Orlando, and Tampa were the most powerful klaverns." "One of the most notorious Klan incidents in Florida history occurred in Tampa in 1937, when labor organizer Joseph Shoemaker was flogged, castrated, and tarred and feathered."</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371570364743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371570630896-80</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Stop It: GOP Wants To Try Talking To Blacks Again" "It’s that time of the year again! We’re officially entering the brief period in which Republicans put on the facade that they don’t want to just be the party of heartless ultra-rich corporatists and White comically conservative minions."</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371570630896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371571176590-81</Id><Topic><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>classic hawcraper, take something out of context of the event and the whole story the "ESTIMATED" 30,000 members didn't come to Indiana which "had 250,000 members, an estimated 30% of native-born white men. By 1925 over half the elected members of the Indiana General Assembly, the Governor of Indiana, and many other high-ranking officials in local and state government were members of the Klan. Politicians had also learned they needed Klan endorsement to win office."</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371571176590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371571740993-82</Id><Title>OMG FIRE BALLMER ALREADY!!!!!</Title><Msg>The Surface was a FLOP. Windows 8 was a FLOP. The new X-Box was a FLOP.</Msg><Username>mrgreatcatchforyou</Username><Timestamp>1371571740993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371572047919-83</Id><Topic><Title>OMG FIRE BALLMER ALREADY!!!!!</Title><Username>mrgreatcatchforyou</Username><Timestamp>1371571740993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:09:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I die, I want to be reincarnated as Bill Gates' college roommate. That way, I could be a total incompetent, never accomplish anything of real value and still ride Bill G's coat tails all the way to a billion dollar net worth.</Msg><Username>doindadorkus</Username><Timestamp>1371572047919</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:14:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371572333474-84</Id><Title>Real markets don't dither, this one dithers every day, ERGO</Title><Msg>it's a pumped market and the only one with deep enough printing presses is guess who.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371572333474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371572700726-85</Id><Title>I Bought More MSFT &amp; BYOC, Both Could Really Rally Big Now.</Title><Msg>But BYOC is more speculative and I feel that MSFT is much more stable than BYOC. None the less BYOC could soon recover again to $1.00 or higher.</Msg><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1371572700726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371572854833-86</Id><Title>DOW UP 107...MSFT...NOPE....UNDER-PERFORMER. STILL. AND AGAIN... DEAD MONEY. SEE CHART.</Title><Msg>Pumpers... Get pumpin... Microscrotum shills.... Post 24/7. shows great weakness.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371572854833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371572905220-87</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly....predis....you right on !! this pos, has under-performed for ever ! see any chart. Goes nowhere. and actually has waaay under-performed the market and certainly the sector. As always. $26-$36 big deal....dead money.. Why? msft has been fully diluted for 2 decades. Period.</Msg><Username>wishin_aint_investin</Username><Timestamp>1371572905220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:28:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371573141954-88</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tianhe-2 or TH-2 (En: Milky Way-2) is a 33.86 PetaFLOP supercomputer in China. It was placed in service ahead of schedule in 2013 after it had been expected to be completed in 2015. It is currently the world's fastest supercomputer according to the TOP500 list for June 2013. It is housed at the National Supercomputing Center in Guangzhou (NSCC-GZ) and was designed and developed by the National University of Defense Technology (NUDT) and by Inspur. Inspur contributed to the manufacturing of the printed circuit boards and is also contributing to the system installation and testing. There are 16,000 compute nodes, each comprising two Intel Ivy Bridge Xeon processors and three Xeon Phi chips for a total of 3,120,000 cores. Resource management is based on Simple Linux Utility for Resource Management (SLURM). NO WIN INSIDE</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371573141954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371573440075-89</Id><Topic><Title>BUSH LEFT MILLIONS IN FORECLOSURE. AND UNEMPLOYED...OBAMA HAS LED US TO HERE. I SALUTE</Title><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371410407960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:20:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oooh but willie.. U love the constant barrage of right wing whackjob posts here 24/7. you never complaina about that.. Do ya.. Tea-bagger. Or is that just bagholder. Either way...as was posted.. Keep it up.. And recieve the same in return.... Cost of pumping waaaay up since willie and the crew attacked the msft-victim. who posted win. 8 poor unfinished...and broken. 1 post. And you all attacked. not smart. costs have incresed for msft. To pay lame pumpers. Lol... Right back atcha..</Msg><Username>gottaloveobama</Username><Timestamp>1371573440075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371574137350-90</Id><Title>Clinton signed the lending bill Barney Frank permitted abuse, Bush had nothing to do with it</Title><Msg>but the liars on the left know with Obama's approval rating falling, their lies are being seen through by more and more and they are losing the battle in the long term, so they double their lies.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371574137350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371574223006-91</Id><Topic><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"take something out of context" Naw, just analyzing traits.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371574223006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371574465068-92</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton signed the lending bill Barney Frank permitted abuse, Bush had nothing to do with it</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371574137350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:48:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Bush had nothing to do with it" Well, what do you know ??? "Bush Administration Ignored Warnings of Pending Financial Meltdown" "The Bush administration backed off proposed crackdowns on no-money-down, interest-only mortgages years before the economy collapsed, buckling to pressure from some of the same banks that have now failed. It ignored remarkably prescient warnings that foretold the financial meltdown, according to an Associated Press review of regulatory documents." ------- "The Credit Crisis: The Bush Administration's Record of Denial and Regulatory Neglect" "Not only did the Bush Administration ignore the warning signs about risky mortgages, they encouraged the very practices that are at the heart of the current economic crisis and stood in the way of efforts that would have prevented the crisis."</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371574465068</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371574849970-93</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton signed the lending bill Barney Frank permitted abuse, Bush had nothing to do with it</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371574137350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:48:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forgot to mention, the chief liar for Obama also likes to take an AP OPINION, since proven wrong by real time articles and C-Span video to promote and support his lie that Bush ignored warnings, when the facts show Bush tried to reign in the abuse 17 times, which is hardly ignoring anything.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371574849970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371574947845-94</Id><Topic><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"... just analyzing traits..." Just bald-faced lying with selective, intentionally misleading out of context quotes.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371574947845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371574967623-95</Id><Title>DOW UP 140....THISTURD....NOPE. AGAIN MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS...ALL.</Title><Msg>8 STINKS....ALL KNOW.</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371574967623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371575327550-96</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and it's got it's very own operating system, written specially for that one machine." Yes. Kylin Linux. Moron.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371575327550</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371575365497-97</Id><Topic><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Just bald-faced lying with selective, intentionally misleading out of context quotes." What a Loon ...</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371575365497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371575487660-98</Id><Topic><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What a Loon ..." You're that too, personally I don't know how you sleep at night, you must hate America so to promote it's destruction daily.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371575487660</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371575533761-99</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton signed the lending bill Barney Frank permitted abuse, Bush had nothing to do with it</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371574137350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:48:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"AP OPINION" It was on Fox News ... are you saying they are liars and the news they post are false ? "C-Span video" Please Play that ... it was made in 2004 and shows PROOF that the Financial Disaster and Great Recession happened during the Bush Administration.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371575533761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371575955969-100</Id><Topic><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't know how you sleep at night" Easily now that Bush is gone and Obama is reviving America. " you must hate America so to promote it's destruction daily." By siding with our president and promoting the recovery from the Bush Financial Disaster and Great Recession, I take pride in being an American. Now, you talk about hating America and promote it's destruction daily. That is the Hawcrek Team to a "T" ... consistantly downgrading an American President, Trying to Divide America daily with Fabricated Right-Wing talking points that have all been debunked ... like the Obama Scandals. I could Never Post Anti-America stuff all day ... at any salary you get. Now, Go Watch FAUX Opinions.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371575955969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371576063022-101</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton signed the lending bill Barney Frank permitted abuse, Bush had nothing to do with it</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371574137350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:48:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""AP OPINION" It was on Fox News ... are you saying they are liars and the news they post are false ? It's an AP story, idiot, learn how the news works in America, moron. If anyone with an I.Q. above 65 it is CLEARLY an OPINION anyway. Some research proves that OPINION WRONG.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371576063022</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371576464016-102</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They don't just slap Linux Ubuntu or Windows on a Super Computer, each one needs it's own code written for that one machine." So, penguin_brainvoid, let's get to the meat of the matter, shall we? Why are they tweaking Linux for the job and not Windows? The majority of the tweaking is about kernel mods required to deal with scaling across custom hardware and I/O. This is quite easy to do with an OS kernel that allows for inspecting and editing its source code, one that scales essentially infinitely over a vast array of processor core and memory resources. With few other exceptions aside from hardware and I/O driver tweaks, the basic Linux source requires scant editing prior to compiling relative to the total volume of code being deployed. Say, didn't you try to convince us that you were some kind of computer genius and that you had a "falcon" that would blow away all these HPC machines? HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR!!! It is to laugh...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371576464016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371576818545-103</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140....THISTURD....NOPE. AGAIN MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS...ALL.</Title><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371574967623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes all can see this bloated pig is fully diluted.</Msg><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371576818545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371577020630-104</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Foot Gun Blast From MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371568671531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where are the apologists? Where are the pimps and the shills? Where are the wallys, the pigeons and the Billy Boys to tell us how this was all staged by open source freaks and aliens from another dimension just to bash MS? C'mon MS boot lickers! Tell us how much this is going to push MS over the $40 mark by Friday on Xbox sales alone!!!</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371577020630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371577644746-105</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Elementary Skippy, Linux is open source and while they must hire professionals to "Tweak" as you say, they wouldn't have to pay for the actual software. Windows, on the other hand, is not open source and anybody wanting to "Tweak" it would have to get MSFT's permission and PAY for that right. If "They" want to call BALLMER and get a price for a O/S to run their Hardware they have my blessing, but MSFT is not going to open a new division to write 1 O/S for each of the 500 Super Computers when their market is the over 100 BILLION PC's running Windows. They're different classes of Super Computers and my qualifies for a desktop Super Computer where as your Linux netbook would need a lot of work to qualify. I know this is over your tiny head but try to grow a brain.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371577644746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371577829631-106</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I vehemently deny being a moron and demand a immediate apology. HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371577829631</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371578083964-107</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Elementary Skippy" Your "skippy" is dangling between my thighs ready to swamp your tonsils with hot sticky pecker snot, moron. You are a liar, pigeon_breath and have NO "falcon". With or without Baldy's permission, Redmond's krap OS would never be good enough. Why would anyone as disconnected from reality as you change nyms from pigeon_undertaker to misterreality? You're as disconnected from reality as any inert object or set thereof. You know, like a box of rocks...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371578083964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371578164275-108</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. Hold your breath now and wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371578164275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371578179318-109</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Foot Gun Blast From MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371568671531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ IF YOU CAN'T TAKE A JOKE.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371578179318</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371578510530-110</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.."Redmond's krap OS would never be good enough".. Are you dumb enough to say that if Bill Gates wanted to build the fastest SUPERCOMPUTER on the planet running Windows, tweaked of course, that he wouldn't have enough resources to get it done? You empty Skull is showing great wear and tear.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371578510530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:01:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371578589072-111</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your resulting to name calling is only showing your ignorance.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371578589072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371578638349-112</Id><Title>DOW UP 140. MSFT...AGAIN THE LAGGARD. PREDIS. NYM...SEEMS THE COMPUTER EXPERT. I JUST KNOW PS'S AND 8 SUCKS.</Title><Msg>I own many. never tried linux. but intend to. right after amzn del. My new chromebook, so i can trash this touchscreen 8 pos.</Msg><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371578638349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371578772094-113</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are far more heartless ultra-rich corporatists on the liberal side than conservative. They help create, and then live to suckle on the biggest government possible, in much the same way the poor do, shackled to the Democrat plantation. Elbert Guillory's 4 minute video talking clear and plain truth to his brothers and sisters is all the talking that needs to be done.</Msg><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1371578772094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:06:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371578857947-114</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOUR INSULTING RANTS SPEAK FOR THEMSELVES. ANYONE CAN READ YOU ILL INFORMED KRAP. BUT WHO WOULD.... BUT WHO WOULD... WHO.....WAIT FOR IT.... WAIT 4 IT........ WAIT SOME MORE... TOO MANY SHILLS.....NO CLUE. JUST TALKING POINTS.... A BOILER ROOM SALES JOB. CUBICLE...H E L - AHHHHHH ANSWER..... WAIT NOBODY.............</Msg><Username>shurlock_homes</Username><Timestamp>1371578857947</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371578888896-115</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Foot Gun Blast From MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371568671531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IT was not a rape joke. It's kinda sensationalism that it would be taken that way. I saw the whole E3 show, and it was while 2 people were playing a side scrolling fighter game. It was trash talk at best, and it felt forced anyhow.</Msg><Username>xtwinstarx</Username><Timestamp>1371578888896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371579016744-116</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There u r. when the kitchen gets to hot, and you can't defend loser....msft. turn to politics....or religeon.. Lol. sp. Error #$%$.</Msg><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371579016744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371579555426-117</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't confuse my contempt for you with the ignorance you manifest, moron.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371579555426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371579620884-118</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"BUT WHO WOULD" Apparently *YOU* did, moron.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371579620884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:20:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371579828941-119</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't mean to butt in must I must say predisposable is a Neanderthal and I hate him. burp</Msg><Username>the_original_al_coholic_2005</Username><Timestamp>1371579828941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371579901864-120</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Foot Gun Blast From MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371568671531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't write the article and I wasn't there. The comments of some that *were* there conflict with your view point but that is to be expected anytime more than one person is involved. I am merely posting what I read. Ya'll can be the judges of the quoted content based on your own perspectives.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371579901864</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580021194-121</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Foot Gun Blast From MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371568671531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wrote: "Where are the apologists? Where are the pimps and the shills?" pigeon_beak wrote: "#$%$ IF YOU CAN'T TAKE A JOKE." LOL! Looks like my question has been answered. HAR HAR HAR!!!</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580021194</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580038125-122</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140....THISTURD....NOPE. AGAIN MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS...ALL.</Title><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371574967623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry your little pointed head M$FT is merely consolidating for the next push to $40+.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371580038125</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:27:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580110595-123</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140. MSFT...AGAIN THE LAGGARD. PREDIS. NYM...SEEMS THE COMPUTER EXPERT. I JUST KNOW PS'S AND 8 SUCKS.</Title><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371578638349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:03:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree chrome really BLOWS.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371580110595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580169409-124</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cfur, if it isn't the liberal talking point of the day, you just can't figure it out can you. Also, being a lazy sob, I'll post it for you. The idea that blacks, or anyone for that matter, need the the government to get ahead in life is despicable. And even more important, this idea is a failure. Our communities are just as poor as they’ve always been. Our schools continue to fail children. Our prisons are filled with young black men who should be at home being fathers. Our self-initiative and our self-reliance have been sacrificed in exchange for allegiance to our overseers who control us by making us dependent on them. Sometimes I wonder if the word freedom is tossed around so frequently in our society that it has become a cliché. The idea of freedom is complex and it is all-encompassing. It’s the idea that the economy must remain free of government persuasion. It’s the idea that the press must operate without government intrusion. And it’s the idea that the emails and phone records of Americans should remain free from government search and seizure. It’s the idea that parents must be the decision makers in regards to their children's education — not some government bureaucrat. But most importantly, it is the idea that the individual must be free to pursue his or her own happiness free from government dependence and free from government control. Because to be truly free is to be reliant on no one other than the author of our destiny. These are the ideas at the core of the Republican Party, and it is why I am a Republican. So my brothers and sisters of the American community, please join with me today in abandoning the government plantation and the Party of disappointment. So that we may all echo the words of one Republican leader who famously said, ‘free at last, free at last, thank God Almighty, we are free at last.’</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371580169409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580171696-125</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG! I'll surely lose sleep over *THAT* tonight. Some anonymous troll doesn't like me!!! BOO #$%$ HOO...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580171696</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580280676-126</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140. MSFT...AGAIN THE LAGGARD. PREDIS. NYM...SEEMS THE COMPUTER EXPERT. I JUST KNOW PS'S AND 8 SUCKS.</Title><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371578638349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:03:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very frustrating. Add Apple to the list. MSFT needs raised guidance perhaps driven by the Cloud to blow the new shorts out.</Msg><Username>castandretrieve</Username><Timestamp>1371580280676</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371580363568-127</Id><Title>Way to Track the Market, MS</Title><Msg>Dow +0.94% MSFT +.05% HAR HAR HAR!!!</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580363568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371580506530-128</Id><Title>DOW UP 140....THISTURD....NOPE. AGAIN MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS...ALL. NOW RED AGAIN..=DEAD MONEY</Title><Msg>AND ALL KNOW IT.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371580506530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580725811-129</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140....THISTURD....NOPE. AGAIN MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS...ALL.</Title><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371574967623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For 13 years....learn to read a chart. msft. Is money for ballmer and insiders only....investors sit and spin....</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371580725811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580884800-130</Id><Topic><Title>Wow! Not good.</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371568464677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still up just 2 cents on huge up day!!!! Not sure why one more product failure - Surface - would tank the stock. Just because they are now giving Surface away for free? Aren't the markets used to this? Zune, Kin, Vista, Bing,etc.,etc.,etc.,etc., - now Xbox One and Surface. Every new product release can't be a home run people! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371580884800</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580885010-131</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the wear and tear in on your big mouth, moron, especially the suck muscles, tell traces of boot black and the well worn lip surfaces where Steve likes to park his member. I have made no mention nor rendered any opinion regarding what Bill may or not be able to accomplish with his resources. I thought you dealt with that ESL thing already, pigeon_coop.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580885010</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:41:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580901397-132</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excuse predis... But that post was agreeing with your premise....</Msg><Username>ucant_trade</Username><Timestamp>1371580901397</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:41:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580996018-133</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Missed the plot completely on that one. A thousand pardons for my fatigue and thanks for the correction.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580996018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371581044736-134</Id><Title>FYI GOOGLE UP $12 TODAY AND $11 YESTERDAY...SO IN 2 DAYS GOOG. HAS GAINED THE TOTAL SP. OF THIS DOG. !</Title><Msg>THOSE ARE FACTS....AND 8SUCKS THE BIG ONE.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371581044736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581083943-135</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My apologies for that last reply, shurlock. I'm trying to juggle too many trolls, pimps and shills at one time.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371581083943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581096885-136</Id><Topic><Title>Wow! Not good.</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371568464677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry the trend is UP UP UP !</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371581096885</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581200878-137</Id><Topic><Title>FYI GOOGLE UP $12 TODAY AND $11 YESTERDAY...SO IN 2 DAYS GOOG. HAS GAINED THE TOTAL SP. OF THIS DOG. !</Title><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371581044736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:44:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&amp; you know all about sucking don't you ? BARK BARK BARK !!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371581200878</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581283513-138</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140....THISTURD....NOPE. AGAIN MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS...ALL.</Title><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371574967623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's the past FOOL ! BARK BARK BARK!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371581283513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581356931-139</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140....THISTURD....NOPE. AGAIN MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS...ALL. NOW RED AGAIN..=DEAD MONEY</Title><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371580506530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:35:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get STUFFED ! BARK BARK BARK!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371581356931</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581462832-140</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're one of the only real posters who understand the complex structure of computers. most here are shills. you are doing a great service to america ferreting out these bold lies...i'm sure you must be tired of the constant sales barrage here. i know p/c's but not the inner hardware. But as to the average pc user. Many have come for my help with vista. i bought 8 and was sooo disappointed. this thing is soooo flakey. flying tiles and misreads. false reads on gesture....so many do overs. unreal. msft. Will be lambasted once word is spread. keep the faith. the truth is coming out. In spite of msft attempts to obfuscate the facts...like the phony ad showing apple touch not responding, but msft's just perfect. i assure you the opposite is true. I own 2 of these pos. and never will buy another msft. Product. Period. never. the msft. Vius machine=bing. horrible</Msg><Username>ucant_trade</Username><Timestamp>1371581462832</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581490087-141</Id><Topic><Title>Way to Track the Market, MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580363568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSFT +.05% I see you didn't learn anything in Linux stock trading school! One thing you need to learn to keep from looking stupid is: NEVER KNOCK A WINNER!</Msg><Username>blademan6o8o4</Username><Timestamp>1371581490087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371581514497-142</Id><Title>We're Going much Higher !</Title><Msg>Hurrah !</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371581514497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371581531746-143</Id><Title>Microsoft Likely to Release Surface Phone by November</Title><Msg>Nokia may decide to keep a boat anchor called NSN that restricts Microsoft from buying it. Huawei which can use NSN &amp; the handsets will possibly buy Nokia. It is also possible that no one will buy Nokia and they will go bankrupt. Huawei does make a Microsoft Windows Phone currently. They will probably continue selling the current phones. It is very unlikely that Microsoft will want an all Huawei Phone line. In other words it will not happen, so Huawei is wasting their money. There is probably a 100% chance you will not see a full line of Huwaei Windows Phones in the US. Maybe a few, but they are not going to ruin their brand name. US Gov. will not buy that brand. Military will not buy that brand. There was a warning to all US Businesses that Chinese computer equipment may be used for spying. Microsoft previously designed a Surface phone and is a drop dead gorgeous design. It is likely that Microsoft will open up the Windows Phone platform to all vendors just like PC's but focus on their own phone made by Foxconn. The Surface phone will be bundled at Best Buy and also to all the Gov. contracts that are prohibited from buying Chinese manufacturer equip. for infrastructure use. It really depends on what happens to Nokia. Believe me, people from Microsoft are on the phone to Foxconn right now to have an alternative to Huwaei Lumias. That is definitely a loser and will never happen.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371581531746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581687165-144</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I NOTICE PREDISPOS MISSES ALL THE SENSIBLE PLOTS!</Msg><Username>blademan6o8o4</Username><Timestamp>1371581687165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581818987-145</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140. MSFT...AGAIN THE LAGGARD. PREDIS. NYM...SEEMS THE COMPUTER EXPERT. I JUST KNOW PS'S AND 8 SUCKS.</Title><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371578638349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:03:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do not get a chromebook if you want to trade stocks! You must have ms windows.</Msg><Username>blademan6o8o4</Username><Timestamp>1371581818987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581820833-146</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. Hold your breath now and wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it...</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371581820833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581887397-147</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Foot Gun Blast From MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371568671531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where are the apologists? Where are the pimps and the shills? Where are the wallys, the pigeons and the Billy Boys to tell us how this was all staged by open source freaks and aliens from another dimension just to bash MS? C'mon MS boot lickers! Tell us how much this is going to push MS over the $40 mark by Friday on Xbox sales alone!!!</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371581887397</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581930335-148</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They don't just slap Linux Ubuntu or Windows on a Super Computer, each one needs it's own code written for that one machine." So, penguin_brainvoid, let's get to the meat of the matter, shall we? Why are they tweaking Linux for the job and not Windows? The majority of the tweaking is about kernel mods required to deal with scaling across custom hardware and I/O. This is quite easy to do with an OS kernel that allows for inspecting and editing its source code, one that scales essentially infinitely over a vast array of processor core and memory resources. With few other exceptions aside from hardware and I/O driver tweaks, the basic Linux source requires scant editing prior to compiling relative to the total volume of code being deployed. Say, didn't you try to convince us that you were some kind of computer genius and that you had a "falcon" that would blow away all these HPC machines? HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR!!! It is to laugh...</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371581930335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581992248-149</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly....predis....you right on !! this pos, has under-performed for ever ! see any chart. Goes nowhere. and actually has waaay under-performed the market and certainly the sector. As always. $26-$36 big deal....dead money.. Why? msft has been fully diluted for 2 decades. Period. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>ucant_trade</Username><Timestamp>1371581992248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:59:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582018257-150</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140. MSFT...AGAIN THE LAGGARD. PREDIS. NYM...SEEMS THE COMPUTER EXPERT. I JUST KNOW PS'S AND 8 SUCKS.</Title><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371578638349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:03:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True story,ok for a few laughs, for serious work chrome is a insecure joke.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371582018257</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:00:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582052834-151</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140. MSFT...AGAIN THE LAGGARD. PREDIS. NYM...SEEMS THE COMPUTER EXPERT. I JUST KNOW PS'S AND 8 SUCKS.</Title><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371578638349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:03:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THAT'S A LIE</Msg><Username>provendog</Username><Timestamp>1371582052834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:00:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582068835-152</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"These are the ideas at the core of the Republican Party, and it is why I am a Republican." So, you prefer to be a member of the Losing Side ? If your Core Values were so good ... why lose the Presidential Election 2 times in a row ?</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371582068835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582086091-153</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ANOTHER PUMPER LIE !!!!</Msg><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371582086091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:01:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582153233-154</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the wear and tear in on your big mouth, moron, especially the suck muscles, tell traces of boot black and the well worn lip surfaces where Steve likes to park his member. I have made no mention nor rendered any opinion regarding what Bill may or not be able to accomplish with his resources. I thought you dealt with that ESL thing already, pigeon_coop.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371582153233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582226729-155</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Foot Gun Blast From MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371568671531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't write the article and I wasn't there. The comments of some that *were* there conflict with your view point but that is to be expected anytime more than one person is involved. I am merely posting what I read. Ya'll can be the judges of the quoted content based on your own perspective</Msg><Username>provendog</Username><Timestamp>1371582226729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582319029-156</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Elementary Skippy" Your "skippy" is dangling between my thighs ready to swamp your tonsils with hot sticky pecker snot, moron. You are a liar, pigeon_breath and have NO "falcon". With or without Baldy's permission, Redmond's krap OS would never be good enough. Why would anyone as disconnected from reality as you change nyms from pigeon_undertaker to misterreality? You're as disconnected from reality as any inert object or set thereof. You know, like a box of rocks..</Msg><Username>ucant_trade</Username><Timestamp>1371582319029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582409747-157</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 140. MSFT...AGAIN THE LAGGARD. PREDIS. NYM...SEEMS THE COMPUTER EXPERT. I JUST KNOW PS'S AND 8 SUCKS.</Title><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371578638349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:03:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to change your new Troll name to provenliar.............</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371582409747</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582421269-158</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Likely to Release Surface Phone by November</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371581531746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huawie does have a Windows Phone at Walmart. Sales are horrible for that brand. Nokia sells well. If Huawie takes out Nokia, they will switch most of the phones to Android. They are after NSN and the maps HERE division. Microsoft's Balmer probably will have a tizzy if Elop even talks to him. In addition, Microsoft has several years left on a partnership with Nokia. It would not be the first time Balmer did a 180 though on a complete change. That happens often. So if you here an announcement that Huawie buys Nokia, expect a Surface Phone announcement shortly after that. Will Microsoft buy Nokia to keep them? Unlikely, due to the NSN division they have. It is very very likely that a Surface Phone has already started production on today's news. It me be a case of be careful what you wish for in Nokia's case. Huwaie will gut Nokia and it's employees and probably due some bogus stock deal rather than cash.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371582421269</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582460496-159</Id><Topic><Title>OMG FIRE BALLMER ALREADY!!!!!</Title><Username>mrgreatcatchforyou</Username><Timestamp>1371571740993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:09:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Surface was a FLOP. Windows 8 was a FLOP. The new X-Box was a FLOP.</Msg><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371582460496</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:07:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582559196-160</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"factious" Learn to spell, pigeon_rumpranger. Can't ride anything while you're munching on it... How come you're not telling us some lies about your imaginary "falcon" today?</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371582559196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582695585-161</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because the Master Manipulator data mined the easily manipulated. I'll bet you showed up on multiple lists. What we got out of all this is a Master manipulator and not a leader. No core values there. Right?</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371582695585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582870275-162</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Likely to Release Surface Phone by November</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371581531746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now they are reporting that Huawei says they are not buying Nokia and it was based on a bogus email sent to Bloomberg. Huawei is actually one of the only ones that may still buy it with their NSN business. It does not fit any other company out there. Surface Phone is probably on hold now but you never know. I say make it due to the uncertainty of Nokia. Nokia are the only phones selling and Nokia seems confused in their business model. Microsoft needs their own phone as a security measure. Today is a perfect example of why the Surface Phone needs to be made ASAP.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371582870275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582872638-163</Id><Topic><Title>OMG FIRE BALLMER ALREADY!!!!!</Title><Username>mrgreatcatchforyou</Username><Timestamp>1371571740993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:09:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me try to put this into perspective for you, Steve Ballmer is one of the richest most successful,smartest people on the planet you're chat room Trolls LOL.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371582872638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582884434-164</Id><Topic><Title>Way to Track the Market, MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580363568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey predip, I mean msft_a_dog, how many yahoo id's do you have you pathetic slug.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371582884434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:14:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583049446-165</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts: Cover Or...</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371428711234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:25:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tomorrow will be way too late.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371583049446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583159795-166</Id><Topic><Title>Way to Track the Market, MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580363568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong as usual. pigeon. Must be all that pecker snot washing down the back of your throat. I have had two (2) nyms here since I began lurking during the FiaSCO that was TSG, "preadaptive" and the current one that I am posting from now. Redirection is a common ploy resorted to by the weak minded and unskilled. I notice that you do it a lot.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371583159795</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583375556-167</Id><Topic><Title>Way to Track the Market, MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580363568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not predis....you douchebag...it's me yafool....and i gotz hundreds....just watch....as the cost of pumping has gone waaaaay up around here.....ask the victim...8sucks...</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371583375556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583436387-168</Id><Topic><Title>Way to Track the Market, MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580363568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"NEVER KNOCK A WINNER!" I never have. MS is a copy cat IP thief and I don't consider the criminal bullies to be a "WINNER". All their pimps and shills are losers as well. Are you one of those?.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371583436387</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371583524566-169</Id><Title>MARKET SPEAKS...GOOGLE UP BIG..ALMOST TO $900 A SHARE. SOON WILL TAKE OVER BERSHIRE</Title><Msg>This pos....goes nowhere ever. 13 years of wallowing in the investment sewer with willie.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371583524566</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583614218-170</Id><Topic><Title>OMG FIRE BALLMER ALREADY!!!!!</Title><Username>mrgreatcatchforyou</Username><Timestamp>1371571740993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:09:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Surface was a FLOP. Windows 8 was a FLOP. The new X-Box was a FLOP.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371583614218</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583624692-171</Id><Topic><Title>MARKET SPEAKS...GOOGLE UP BIG..ALMOST TO $900 A SHARE. SOON WILL TAKE OVER BERSHIRE</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371583524566</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cover now or die poor, you stupid S0B. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371583624692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583711805-172</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I notice you use all caps You must be blinded by the pecker snot in your eyes.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371583711805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371583757786-173</Id><Title>GOOGLE UP $14. MSFT...NOPE...JUST AN OLD FLOATING BLOATED TURD. FULLY DILUTED.</Title><Msg>That's why it never goes anywhere. Steve took all the money.</Msg><Username>xbox_stinks</Username><Timestamp>1371583757786</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583837484-174</Id><Topic><Title>Skype Brings Free Video Messaging Out Of Preview, Redefines ‘Visual Voicemail’....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371488785392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Skype! Global user base. Money to Microsoft.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371583837484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583840395-175</Id><Topic><Title>MARKET SPEAKS...GOOGLE UP BIG..ALMOST TO $900 A SHARE. SOON WILL TAKE OVER BERSHIRE</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371583524566</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So go Stink up the GOOG board then,they need you LOL.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371583840395</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584097996-176</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy o boy boooooooooooger you are dumber than dog doo. The republican party of Lincolns day has long been deader than King Tut. Cant you ever read any history or anything. The last of the civilized Republicans were run out of the party after Nixon's "Southern Strategy" was introduced. At the same time the Dixiecrat Democrats converted to the Republican party to a man to get aboard the GOP with ole RMN. At the same time thes turncoats took their slave master mentality with them. The Democrat party was left to the Intellectuals, labor, and minorities as the only place they could go. Do the Democrats beat up on the blacks ?? are you kiddin. Its the Southern Democrat turned Republican that does that. In other words you are full of it or dumber than dog doo---which is it</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371584097996</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584117976-177</Id><Topic><Title>SONY POS4 IS ONLY AVAILABLE ON DEC 31/2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371348729734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How on earth did Sony screw up the delivery date of their consoles? December 31st? Wow! That is totally lame. Dude, that's handing Microsoft the entire holiday game console business. The Number One Immutable Law of Marketing: It's Always Better to Be First. The Xbox One Just Won.</Msg><Username>scooponcoop</Username><Timestamp>1371584117976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371584133932-178</Id><Title>Shorts are wasting their time trying to scare the Longs on this Message Board:</Title><Msg>AS we all know even $50.00 would be cheap to sell.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371584133932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584157389-179</Id><Topic><Title>Skype Brings Free Video Messaging Out Of Preview, Redefines ‘Visual Voicemail’....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371488785392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually user base hase been in decline for some time now. google and apple are the market darlings. 8sucks. as did vista.</Msg><Username>wii_ps4_best</Username><Timestamp>1371584157389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584236236-180</Id><Topic><Title>Aapl drops Goog search!</Title><Username>k24chat</Username><Timestamp>1370893097753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The news of Apple dropping Google and moving their search on iPhones to Bing is quantum. It's a major game changer. Still more new revenue pouring into Microsoft.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371584236236</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584264552-181</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No istarted this due to arthritis. But the pumpers were sooo annoyed...it caught on. sorry predis. but this is my way to fight the shills.</Msg><Username>pumpas_nemesis</Username><Timestamp>1371584264552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:37:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584390799-182</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for a compliment that I'm not sure I deserve. I'm a work_a_day shirtsleeves type that was trained in telecom electronics and networking in the late '60s, moving on to more advanced electronics technologies in the test and calibration fields as well as CS classes at UCSD in the mid to late '70s. I worked and taught in those fields concurrently and am still at it some 45 or so years later though looking to retire and just ride my Harley soon. I am neither scholar nor genius but I am competent at what I do and don't take fools and shills lightly. Fortunately it is easy to spot the pretenders and even easier to pick them off and rub their noses in their own ignorance. Thanks again and regards, Gary Gibson Virginia Beach, VA</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371584390799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584696573-183</Id><Topic><Title>Aapl drops Goog search!</Title><Username>k24chat</Username><Timestamp>1370893097753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roid, you are another drip that doesn't understand the plain English difference between "default" and "removed entirely as an option". We'll see how many keep the default Bing garbage as opposed to how many will choose Google as their permanent option. Google has not been removed as an option, to do so would be against the law. Finish your ESL training and come back when you can follow a thread.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371584696573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371584833651-184</Id><Title>Ballmer is Going to Butcher Shorts. Butcher.</Title><Msg>Ballmer will absolutely butcher shorts with buybacks, new revenue streams and with still higher earnings again. Why will he butcher the shorts? Because he's so much smarter than they are because he actually KNOWS what's the real deal unlike the gamblers he's about to take out. Why will he butcher the shorts? Because he can. And he will. Bookmark this post. The butcher is taking out his cleaver.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371584833651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584887319-185</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are wasting their time trying to scare the Longs on this Message Board:</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371584133932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course it could very well be 15 MORE years until we actually see $50 but collect the dividend while waiting! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371584887319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371584972881-186</Id><Title>Why the rotten day for this stock?</Title><Msg>Is it only because they are giving away new products for free? Or is it something even worse? Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371584972881</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:49:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371585085827-187</Id><Title>Oh my!!!! Now negative!</Title><Msg>Huge market rally yet MSFT negative again! Be careful! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371585085827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585106214-188</Id><Topic><Title>Aapl drops Goog search!</Title><Username>k24chat</Username><Timestamp>1370893097753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bing is Great! so much more superior &amp; relevant to info stealing GOOG.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371585106214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585220512-189</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer is Going to Butcher Shorts. Butcher.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371584833651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cheers! Just one question - why has he waited 13 years to sharpen his cleaver? Maybe he's too smart and I'm too dumb to grasp this. TIA Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371585220512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:53:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585327542-190</Id><Topic><Title>Aapl drops Goog search!</Title><Username>k24chat</Username><Timestamp>1370893097753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roid, you are another drip that doesn't understand the plain English difference between "default" and "removed entirely as an option". We'll see how many keep the default Bing garbage as opposed to how many will choose Google as their permanent option. Google has not been removed as an option, to do so would be against the law. Finish your ESL training and come back when you can follow a thread.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371585327542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:55:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585381605-191</Id><Topic><Title>Oh my!!!! Now negative!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371585085827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:51:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry be happy.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371585381605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585440115-192</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer is Going to Butcher Shorts. Butcher.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371584833651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Butcher = Bluff Bluster BS Baloney and Bilge = Ballmer</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371585440115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585618742-193</Id><Topic><Title>Aapl drops Goog search!</Title><Username>k24chat</Username><Timestamp>1370893097753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You had to clone an alias to say that? LOL Go BING!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371585618742</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:00:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585748846-194</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer is Going to Butcher Shorts. Butcher.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371584833651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Steve will butcher them like the PIGS they are.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371585748846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:02:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585776342-195</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a far greater thing that you do. innocent or the uninitiateds here might accidently believe the whole shill rant. i do not. i am not any expert on computers or electronics. my field is business (mba from ucsb) minor in finance (pepperdine). these shills do much harm to young and innocent. i'm a retired trader. was hft. For a few years. I dabbled in music for 25 years...hence the arthritis. anyway, it's good to see a competant soul who cares. these bogus claims about how good msft and 8. crack me up. sooooooooo false. hey in closing. i drove the eastern coast from n. Carolina, all the way to maine. vt. is beautiful. i loved it. i'm west coast. on the beach.. good luck sir... Hoorah!!!! go usa</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371585776342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371585893787-196</Id><Title>My God! Very hard</Title><Msg>to find a stock negative today - unless you own MSFT. Maybe their next new product will be intended to actually sell - not give away again. I know Ballmer and Gates are very charitable but maybe sell something for shareholders sake? Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371585893787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585989544-197</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer is Going to Butcher Shorts. Butcher.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371584833651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why wait 13 years? That's a long time. Is the pork supposed to be aged? Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371585989544</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586026634-198</Id><Topic><Title>My God! Very hard</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371585893787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Settle down it will be fine.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586026634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:07:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586078263-199</Id><Topic><Title>Oh my!!!! Now negative!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371585085827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:51:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Happy? Are you short? They are the happy ones lately. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371586078263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:07:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586172802-200</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Sybil,; I'm not going to argue with a black Louisiana State Senator regarding the best interest of the black community. But you being an expert on dog doo probably would. The Republicans want to give blacks jobs so they can take care of themselves, not dole out bits and pieces that only kills their incentive to work and keep them down.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371586172802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371586345850-201</Id><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Msg>Beautiful Pictures, intuitive site.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586421819-202</Id><Topic><Title>Skype Brings Free Video Messaging Out Of Preview, Redefines ‘Visual Voicemail’....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371488785392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually user base hase been in decline for some time now. google and apple are the market darlings. 8sucks. as did vista.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371586421819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586474344-203</Id><Topic><Title>GOOGLE UP $14. MSFT...NOPE...JUST AN OLD FLOATING BLOATED TURD. FULLY DILUTED.</Title><Username>xbox_stinks</Username><Timestamp>1371583757786</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:29:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why it never goes anywhere. Steve took all the money</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371586474344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586522986-204</Id><Topic><Title>MARKET SPEAKS...GOOGLE UP BIG..ALMOST TO $900 A SHARE. SOON WILL TAKE OVER BERSHIRE</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371583524566</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOGLE IT.....ALL TRUE.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371586522986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586562286-205</Id><Topic><Title>OMG FIRE BALLMER ALREADY!!!!!</Title><Username>mrgreatcatchforyou</Username><Timestamp>1371571740993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:09:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Surface was a FLOP. Windows 8 was a FLOP. The new X-Box was a FLOP.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371586562286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586588199-206</Id><Topic><Title>Oh my!!!! Now negative!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371585085827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:51:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be facetious I'm no stinking trader I own M$FT through a DRIP account , only way to go IMO if you're long term minded.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586588199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586605406-207</Id><Topic><Title>Way to Track the Market, MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580363568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"NEVER KNOCK A WINNER!" I never have. MS is a copy cat IP thief and I don't consider the criminal bullies to be a "WINNER". All their pimps and shills are losers as well. Are you one of those?.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371586605406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:16:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586649749-208</Id><Topic><Title>Way to Track the Market, MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580363568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not predis....you douchebag...it's me yafool....and i gotz hundreds....just watch....as the cost of pumping has gone waaaaay up around here.....ask the victim...8sucks...</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371586649749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586703375-209</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They don't just slap Linux Ubuntu or Windows on a Super Computer, each one needs it's own code written for that one machine." So, penguin_brainvoid, let's get to the meat of the matter, shall we? Why are they tweaking Linux for the job and not Windows? The majority of the tweaking is about kernel mods required to deal with scaling across custom hardware and I/O. This is quite easy to do with an OS kernel that allows for inspecting and editing its source code, one that scales essentially infinitely over a vast array of processor core and memory resources. With few other exceptions aside from hardware and I/O driver tweaks, the basic Linux source requires scant editing prior to compiling relative to the total volume of code being deployed. Say, didn't you try to convince us that you were some kind of computer genius and that you had a "falcon" that would blow away all these HPC machines? HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR!!!</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371586703375</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586742667-210</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Foot Gun Blast From MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371568671531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where are the apologists? Where are the pimps and the shills? Where are the wallys, the pigeons and the Billy Boys to tell us how this was all staged by open source freaks and aliens from another dimension just to bash MS? C'mon MS boot lickers! Tell us how much this is going to push MS over the $40 mark by Friday on Xbox sales alone!!!</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371586742667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:19:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586789323-211</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. Hold your breath now and wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it... wait for it...</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371586789323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586882049-212</Id><Topic><Title>FYI GOOGLE UP $12 TODAY AND $11 YESTERDAY...SO IN 2 DAYS GOOG. HAS GAINED THE TOTAL SP. OF THIS DOG. !</Title><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371581044736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:44:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oooh the same msft lament for 13 years... Oh you just wait.. Lol.. Ha ha ha.. See a chart. !</Msg><Username>want_refund</Username><Timestamp>1371586882049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371587024934-213</Id><Topic><Title>FYI GOOGLE UP $12 TODAY AND $11 YESTERDAY...SO IN 2 DAYS GOOG. HAS GAINED THE TOTAL SP. OF THIS DOG. !</Title><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371581044736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:44:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"all about sucking" No doubt taught by you at the Redmond Campus.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371587024934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:23:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371587064797-214</Id><Title>YOU THOUGHT KARMA WAS A BEO---T-HC-AH...WAIT TIL YOU MEET PAYBACK !!!</Title><Msg>He he he...msft is red. market up huge. This...isa...turd.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371587064797</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371587114197-215</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer is Going to Butcher Shorts. Butcher.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371584833651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like last quarter, the upcoming revenues and earnings will be rolled out with without fanfare. Just numbers that kill all MSFT detractors. Here comes the squeeze and the butcher.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371587114197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371587198694-216</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. Superior in all regards. And it's the search "engine" for Yahoo and for iPhone now. Money!</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371587198694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:26:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371587226726-217</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Beautiful Pictures, intuitive site" But, if you need to do actual, productive work instead of looking at "Beautiful Pictures", then use FireFox.</Msg><Username>quasar_king</Username><Timestamp>1371587226726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:27:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371587303504-218</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Likely to Release Surface Phone by November</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371581531746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now it is up after hours on a report it is bogus. Not so bogus as Huawie has been considering Nokia for some time. Microsoft needs to turn the production of the Surface on 10 to cover themselves. The stock would take a hit if Huawei buys Nokia as Nokia is the main Windows Phone maker. Announcing the Surface now would reassure investors.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371587303504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371587435183-219</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Because the Master Manipulator data mined the easily manipulated." Sooooooooooooo funny ... especially when you cheered Palin ... were you manipulated or already Brain dead ?</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371587435183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:30:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371587542917-220</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>{The Democrat party was left to the Intellectuals, labor, and minorities} Right you are. Three of the laziest, emotional fantasy world-driven, low information segments in the country. Intellectuals are about .08% of the population, union labor (not to be confused with mainstream middle-class working Americans) is 11%, and minorities a little over 30%. In other words, the folks that don't have the self-trust to participate as a member of the majority, so they carve their niches and make them their life's activism. {Do the Democrats beat up on the blacks?} You didn't watch the video. Take a look at the state of the black family, unwed mothers and abortion rates in the black community, the rate of incarceration, drug and alcohol abuse, unemployment. ALL of the destruction, 100% of it, is the direct result of 50 years of emotion-based, unevaluated, undermining, spirit-robbing, self-worth destroying liberalism.</Msg><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1371587542917</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371588151095-221</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tried fireflop a couple times &amp; IMO found it to be a bloated buggy browser so I deleted it,IE is what I prefer &amp; like.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371588151095</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371588260326-222</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the Middle Class is gone and what Black middle class there was, have not moved on to be rich. There has been a 30% surge in people especially blacks living under the poverty level.. Obama's agenda has not helped blacks at all but only to destroy their freedom. It is true that liberalism preys on minority ignorance. Obama's policies have not supported a recovery, as Bernanke said. This 8% payroll tax is Killing job growth. agolferbogie post is the best post of the day</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371588260326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371588806597-223</Id><Topic><Title>The KKK Is White And Kristchun</Title><Username>baron_von_melcher</Username><Timestamp>1371569043319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slave traders held church services right over the dungeons. The castles are still there to show the hypocrisy of such people. The KKKK talks about Jesus. That doesn't change it for brown Christians. They know one of the main messages is not listening to the message. Jesus wasn't white, it's odd hw they hate Obama for being about the same color. Any yes it is all about the color, because the policies are excellent, and never before have I seen a President that knows what he is doing more than Obama. Quite the opposite to what you will hear daily on Faux News. The whole idea of being a Christian is not to hate, and they are at it every day. Just look at the example we have here posting away at Obama day and night, none of it being true.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1371588806597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589263727-224</Id><Topic><Title>MARKET SPEAKS...GOOGLE UP BIG..ALMOST TO $900 A SHARE. SOON WILL TAKE OVER BERSHIRE</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371583524566</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOGLE IT.....ALL TRUE. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371589263727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589328404-225</Id><Topic><Title>Way to Track the Market, MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580363568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"NEVER KNOCK A WINNER!" I never have. MS is a copy cat IP thief and I don't consider the criminal bullies to be a "WINNER". All their pimps and shills are losers as well. Are you one of those?. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>worst_system</Username><Timestamp>1371589328404</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589497938-226</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BING is the way to go IMO.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371589497938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:04:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371589671194-227</Id><Title>JUST CAME FROM PUBLIC FORUM....POSTERS COMPLAINING TO MSFT. ABOUT 8 AND BING</Title><Msg>Takes over without command...while typing. I swear.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371589671194</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589791713-228</Id><Topic><Title>MY NEW WIN. 8 WITH IE 10. I WAS SITTING, EATING A SALAD WATCHING MY DESKTOP, BING JUST APPEARED. AGAIN.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370488987378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This has been a constant problem since buying my new hp. well i use chrome now.... hey and bing is a trojan by msft. and loaded on ie 10. so now i must get rid of ie. the trojan front. kill it. Bing is a trojan. Invasive and predatory , an unappreciated by me. the owner of this machine, that msft has complete control over. constant interruptions. during my working... Side margins pop out all the time. And constant misinterpreted commands...and down the rabbit hole. very time consuming.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371589791713</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:09:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589834328-229</Id><Topic><Title>NOTICE ALL THE POSTS CLAIMING WHAT MSFT AND XBOX ARE "GONNA BE AND GONNA DO". MSFT AT BACK OF PACK</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370795684385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:34:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In every catagory.....but hopium and pumpers galore. proven loser is msft. !</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371589834328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:10:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589871531-230</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOZE 8 RAN AWAY WITH MY PC...AGAIN...FLYIN' TILES...CHARMS AINT CHARMING MORE LIK CHARMIN</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370795553282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worse tan vista.... Fact... I'm using this rubbish !!! oh and msft is #7 in games. fact. last in phones. all supercomputers run linux...i now see why ! fact.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371589871531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589928957-231</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT LAST IN PHONES.....LAST IN GAMING. BING IS A VIRUS... AND 8 STINKS....GO APPLE. GOOGLE</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370794156492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:09:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES IT'S A SCAM</Msg><Username>provendog</Username><Timestamp>1371589928957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:12:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589994239-232</Id><Topic><Title>GETTING BINGED. AS MSFT GOES BINGE ON KRAPPY BING. TRYING TO ADD CLICKS. BY AMBUSH !</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370787823791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:23:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GPOP, developers of the mobile sensation "Draw Something" - for $180 million. After months of losing users that once peaked to 14.5 million players over a year ago, Zynga last week shut its New York-based studio, effectively laying off the OMGPOP team. Industry executives say mobile gamers today are spoiled for choice as the industry has exploded. In 2007, when Apple Inc launched the iPhone, there were but a handful of developers. Today, there are hundreds, whose apps sell across the globe on Apple and Google Inc's Android devices. "You see these rocket ships in the industry that explode on the scene with a casual game that's easy to develop with not much money and they gain users quickly. But users get bored or angry because they can't progress without paying more money," Nexon's Mahoney told Reuters in an interview. Nexon has had some success boosting its mobile portfolio, a likely factor behind revenue growth of 24 percent in 2012 to 108 million yen ($1.1 million). LOOKING FOR ANSWERS To stand out from the crowd, developers big and small are seeking ways to build a sustainable business. EA, as one of the best-funded competitors, is turning to data analytics to keep track of its players' gaming patterns and behavior. Japanese gaming giant DeNA is experimenting with on-the-spot tweaks to its games by employees, who adjust conditions depending on what players do, CEO of DeNA West Clive Downie said. Canadian indie studio Noodlecake, known for games like "Zombie Road Trip", is employing loyalty programs similar to airlines with daily virtual currency rewards for first-time and frequent players. Others resort to tricks like seasonal deals and holiday-themed content to boost their rankings on app-download charts during the crucial holiday period. Up-and-coming GungHo, which has seen its shares rise tenfold since October as investors bet on its ability to rise above the fray with its sole title "Puzzle &amp; Dragons," is turning to costly TV advertising to place i Less Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371589994239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590021983-233</Id><Topic><Title>MY NEW WIN. 8 WITH IE 10. I WAS SITTING, EATING A SALAD WATCHING MY DESKTOP, BING JUST APPEARED. AGAIN.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370488987378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You meant to add the adjective "imaginary" Windows 8 because you do not have a Windows 8 PC, but you are entertaining to watch. I especially enjoy your ALL CAP postings. Obviously, you have no life or friends, but I'm glad you have your imaginary PC because it matches your imaginary girlfriend and your imaginary bank account.</Msg><Username>scooponcoop</Username><Timestamp>1371590021983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590027091-234</Id><Topic><Title>GT RID OF INTERNET EXPLORER, FIREFOX..DITCHED UPDATER...STILL GET BING...EVERY HOUR. BINGED TO DEATH</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370787144271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSFT IS A VIRUS. TROJAN, AND CANCER. VICTIM.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371590027091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590092175-235</Id><Topic><Title>I NOW HAVE TO USE MY OLD HP WIDESCREEN WITH VISTA DUT TO COFIG. WIN. 8 UPDATES. 1 HR.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370399582226</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:33:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This windoze 8 os. is sooooo flawed it's just junk. and takes over the pc, so the owner has to wait 2 hours to config. Downloads. on a 3 week old computer. this is soooo flawed. i had to turn to vista on an old 6year old pc. pathetic. total dysfunctional os. period.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371590092175</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590368241-236</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are wasting their time trying to scare the Longs on this Message Board:</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371584133932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371590368241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371590578004-237</Id><Title>hot off the press.</Title><Msg>Microsoft's main troubles in its traditional businesses have become clear. PC sales could drop by as much as 10% this year and a lackluster response to its Windows 8 operating system has prodded the company to begin work on a new version of the product (to be released later this year). Where the company has shown consistent strength is in its entertainment division. Its latest release, Xbox 360, managed to overcome major technical issues and offer big processing power with superior online functionality. The unit sold over 75 million units and brought more than 40 million customers to its Xbox Live online gaming service, making it one of the most acclaimed gaming consoles ever. But Microsoft's top positioning in these sectors is starting to look vulnerable, as the recently announced XBox One has been met with general disappointment in two areas: Xbox One users must maintain broadband internet connectivity and login at least once every 24 hours in order to play the games they have bought, and game publishers can block users from lending games or giving them away. In addition, rentals will not be supported when the new unit is launched. There are also privacy concerns, since large amounts of private data (videos, photos, and even things like recorded facial expressions and heart rate) are uploaded and saved on outside servers.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371590578004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590607844-238</Id><Topic><Title>I NOW HAVE TO USE MY OLD HP WIDESCREEN WITH VISTA DUT TO COFIG. WIN. 8 UPDATES. 1 HR.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370399582226</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:33:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure it is &amp; sure you did, if it really was you wouldn't be camped out wasting time on the MSFT board inventing new lame Troll aliases just to trash MSFT, that makes you a WHACKO. LOL. EXTREMELY STRONG BUY !!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371590607844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590637722-239</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly....predis....you right on !! this pos, has under-performed for ever ! see any chart. Goes nowhere. and actually has waaay under-performed the market and certainly the sector. As always. $26-$36 big deal....dead money.. Why? msft has been fully diluted for 2 decades. Period.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371590637722</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590692703-240</Id><Topic><Title>DOW UP 107...MSFT...NOPE....UNDER-PERFORMER. STILL. AND AGAIN... DEAD MONEY. SEE CHART.</Title><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371572854833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:27:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pumpers... Get pumpin... Microscrotum shills.... Post 24/7. shows great weakness.</Msg><Username>trollers_nightmare</Username><Timestamp>1371590692703</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:24:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371590719458-241</Id><Title>What a day! All DOW stocks up huge!!!</Title><Msg>Well....not all. Is the problem that MSFT doesn't make products people want to buy (thus they have to give them away) or is it those damn shorts, crooked reporters and the guvmint? Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371590719458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590735886-242</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAAAGGGHHHH DOWN AGAIN...GEEZ.. WHAT A POS.</Msg><Username>wishin_aint_investin</Username><Timestamp>1371590735886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590768906-243</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MANY DECADES HAS IT BEEN SINCE MSFT WON ANYTHING. XP. THE LAST GOOD PRODUCT. 15 YRS. OLD</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371516432601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 20:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8 IS RUBBISH !!!</Msg><Username>isee_clearly</Username><Timestamp>1371590768906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590814187-244</Id><Topic><Title>Oh my!!!! Now negative!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371585085827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:51:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you come here then? Just asking. Cheers. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371590814187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590859012-245</Id><Topic><Title>Oh my!!!! Now negative!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371585085827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:51:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ off, wally.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371590859012</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590883433-246</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"IE is what I prefer &amp; like." IE is SLOW to start, I tried Chrome for a couple days but it lacked many features I used in FireFox. Currently using FireFox 21.</Msg><Username>quasar_king</Username><Timestamp>1371590883433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590914076-247</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are just another M$hill #$%$.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371590914076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590931790-248</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, wally...you're a #$%$</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371590931790</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371590942627-249</Id><Title>ADBE up Big AH on Cloud Growth... Can't Wait to See MSFT Cloud Growth Soon!</Title><Msg>Azure is becoming a MONSTER.</Msg><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371590942627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:29:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591003465-250</Id><Topic><Title>I NOW HAVE TO USE MY OLD HP WIDESCREEN WITH VISTA DUT TO COFIG. WIN. 8 UPDATES. 1 HR.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370399582226</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:33:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Willie are u lookin in the mirror and ranting again... Wipe that peckersnot off your chin swallow and try again. get it right this time... 8 sucks and so do you....beeeotch</Msg><Username>msft_last_always</Username><Timestamp>1371591003465</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591022461-251</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FOAD, pigeon-poop</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371591022461</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591105753-252</Id><Topic><Title>Way to Track the Market, MS</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371580363568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"NEVER KNOCK A WINNER!" I never have. MS is a copy cat IP thief and I don't consider the criminal bullies to be a "WINNER". All their pimps and shills are losers as well. Are you one of those?.</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371591105753</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591136940-253</Id><Topic><Title>JUST CAME FROM PUBLIC FORUM....POSTERS COMPLAINING TO MSFT. ABOUT 8 AND BING</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371589671194</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:07:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Takes over without command...while typing. I swear.</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371591136940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:32:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591165402-254</Id><Topic><Title>MY NEW WIN. 8 WITH IE 10. I WAS SITTING, EATING A SALAD WATCHING MY DESKTOP, BING JUST APPEARED. AGAIN.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370488987378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This has been a constant problem since buying my new hp. well i use chrome now.... hey and bing is a trojan by msft. and loaded on ie 10. so now i must get rid of ie. the trojan front. kill it. Bing is a trojan. Invasive and predatory , an unappreciated by me. the owner of this machine, that msft has complete control over. constant interruptions. during my working... Side margins pop out all the time. And constant misinterpreted commands...and down the rabbit hole. very time consuming. Less Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371591165402</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:32:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591178398-255</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's because you are an a $$ wipe. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371591178398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591196358-256</Id><Topic><Title>NOTICE ALL THE POSTS CLAIMING WHAT MSFT AND XBOX ARE "GONNA BE AND GONNA DO". MSFT AT BACK OF PACK</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370795684385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:34:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In every catagory.....but hopium and pumpers galore. proven loser is msft. !</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371591196358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591223974-257</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOZE 8 RAN AWAY WITH MY PC...AGAIN...FLYIN' TILES...CHARMS AINT CHARMING MORE LIK CHARMIN</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370795553282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worse tan vista.... Fact... I'm using this rubbish !!! oh and msft is #7 in games. fact. last in phones. all supercomputers run linux...i now see why ! fact.</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371591223974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591417636-258</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You would look good spiting teeth.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371591417636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:36:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371591889078-259</Id><Title>SONY PLAYSTATION WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE FOR CHRISTMAS MARKET. UH, OH.</Title><Msg>It is more than official now. Sony cannot deliver a single PlayStation until December 31st. Meanwhile, Microsoft's Xbox One will be in all of the new Microsoft stores inside Best Buy, at Wal-Mart and stores all across North America starting in NOVEMBER when holiday shopping begins. Sony's missing the Christmas market is probably the biggest marketing/manufacturing screw-ups ever. The Xbox One Just Won.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371591889078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371592246295-260</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aaaaahhhh how sweet....willie plays tough guy... Tries to cyber-bully...lol...ha ha ha ha.. i've been on mb's for 10 years......manypunks like you... Oooooh scaaaawwwwyyyyyy. verwy scawwwy...not.. Big suckslikeu...and is msft's latest trojan virus... So swallow todays peckersnot and try again.... fierce this time... Try all caps....lol..he he he</Msg><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371592246295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371592410174-261</Id><Title>ALL THE FOCUS ON BOX CUZ 8SUCKS AND ALL KNOW IT. PROBLEM IS BOX IS A SPECK. 77MIL. WII 150 MIL</Title><Msg>And games ohhhhh msft is 7th. and zero have kinect. Period. Msft. Sp. goes lower. On fundies....msft is fully diluted...see specs.</Msg><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371592410174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371592434296-262</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you spite teeth? TIA Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371592434296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371592534240-263</Id><Title>GT RID OF INTERNET EXPLORER, FIREFOX..DITCHED UPDATER...STILL GET BING...EVERY HOUR. BINGED TO DEATH</Title><Msg>TRUTH</Msg><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371592534240</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371592631959-264</Id><Title>MSFT LAST IN PHONES.....LAST IN GAMING. BING IS A VIRUS... AND 8 STINKS....GO APPLE. GOOGLE</Title><Msg>FACTS.....JUST SAYIN'</Msg><Username>shurlock_homes</Username><Timestamp>1371592631959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:57:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371593444017-265</Id><Title>EVERY FRIGGIN TIME MY PC HAS A RE-START, THERE IS BING. I'VE BEEN DINGED TO DEATH BY BING. NOW I CALL</Title><Msg>The attorney general in my state, and the bbb. this will go badly for msft. i promise this board...you will regret this invasion.</Msg><Username>thee_flame</Username><Timestamp>1371593444017</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371593892952-266</Id><Topic><Title>EVERY FRIGGIN TIME MY PC HAS A RE-START, THERE IS BING. I'VE BEEN DINGED TO DEATH BY BING. NOW I CALL</Title><Username>thee_flame</Username><Timestamp>1371593444017</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:10:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"EVERY FRIGGIN TIME" what are you the soprano's ? LOL</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371593892952</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371594112770-267</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You heard me right the first time you gutless little SOB.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371594112770</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371594171425-268</Id><Title>At Work With Microsoft Office on an iPhone....</Title><Msg>"If you asked someone on the street to name a Microsoft product they can’t live without, they would likely mention Microsoft Office, the suite that includes Outlook, Word, Excel and PowerPoint. Even Apple fans find themselves installing Office the second they buy a new Mac. IPhone owners have yearned for a way to access and edit Office documents on the go, yet Microsoft has kept this valuable asset restricted to its Windows Phones and Surface tablets. Until now". Just Bing the title above. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371594171425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371594277087-269</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right through your ugly Troll Csucker.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371594277087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371594291212-270</Id><Title>Bernanke has remained at Fed longer than *HE* wanted? G-zus Cree Rised</Title><Msg>The sad part is we are so deep into his shell game now it's likely whoever takes over will be forced to ddo more until the collapse. Remember Bernanke, the wizard of printing dollars whos says it won't hurt also said there was no recession and little chance of one 4 months into the collapse.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371594291212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:24:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371595440684-271</Id><Topic><Title>At Work With Microsoft Office on an iPhone....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371594171425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes and this small move "at no cost" to Microsoft would yield $2.4 billion a year or about 30 cents a share. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371595440684</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371595790805-272</Id><Topic><Title>Some blacks are finally getting it....LA S. Senator Elbert Guillory</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371559198867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cfur abandons searching for the truth and settles for a good fairy tail.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371595790805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371596552314-273</Id><Topic><Title>EVERY FRIGGIN TIME MY PC HAS A RE-START, THERE IS BING. I'VE BEEN DINGED TO DEATH BY BING. NOW I CALL</Title><Username>thee_flame</Username><Timestamp>1371593444017</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:10:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh willie, you got sucha mouth on you. well, yahoo won't let it come out full force so yaz gotta lay it between the lines....so fahgetaboutit. the points are understood by others...you you gotta nuthin' sukka.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371596552314</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:02:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371596650852-274</Id><Topic><Title>At Work With Microsoft Office on an iPhone....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371594171425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just wait till the 100 million Enterprise customers who use iPad start buying Surface pro for $1000.00 a shot or $100 billion and counting.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371596650852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:04:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371596701861-275</Id><Topic><Title>100 million iPad owners are "frustrated" as they can NOT use MSFT Office....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368455117441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 10:25:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time for a re-read.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371596701861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371596759890-276</Id><Title>WELL BOARD. I'VE JUST FILED MY COMPLAINT AGAINST MSFT. W/ THE BBB. IN MY STATE ALONE 1400 COMPLAINTS.</Title><Msg>Mine will get me out of this bing trap and into a new os. never again will msft. Interrupt with stupid bing. i will be calling the ag, in the morning. this is commie garbage pc marketing krap, and it will cost msft mucho. the victim.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371596759890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:05:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371596898840-277</Id><Title>WINDOZE 8 RAN AWAY WITH MY PC...AGAIN...FLYIN' TILES...CHARMS AINT CHARMING MORE LIK CHARMIN</Title><Msg>And now i fight back... Ya' all come now ya hear...my name and address on the complaint...andi'mpacakin'</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371596898840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371596926328-278</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Says Fortune 500 Firms Are Loving Its Amazon Cloud Killer (Source Business Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371492135165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 14:02:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SO folks we had 50,000 New Enterprise customers in May adding 25% in a months from April 2013.... This one is going to get us the 25 plus P/E by itself. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371596926328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371597063954-279</Id><Topic><Title>I love the Bing site</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371586345850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aaaaahhhh how sweet....willie plays tough guy... Tries to cyber-bully...lol...ha ha ha ha.. i've been on mb's for 10 years......manypunks like you... Oooooh scaaaawwwwyyyyyy. verwy scawwwy...not.. Big suckslikeu...and is msft's latest trojan virus... So swallow todays peckersnot and try again.... fierce this time... Try all caps....lol..he he he</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371597063954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:11:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371597403185-280</Id><Topic><Title>ADBE up Big AH on Cloud Growth... Can't Wait to See MSFT Cloud Growth Soon!</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371590942627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Azure alone has the ability to double or triple MSFT stock in the next 12 months with very little downside risk. All hail the cloud!</Msg><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1371597403185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371597817538-281</Id><Topic><Title>ADBE up Big AH on Cloud Growth... Can't Wait to See MSFT Cloud Growth Soon!</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371590942627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OHHHBULL.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371597817538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:23:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371597830480-282</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Says Fortune 500 Firms Are Loving Its Amazon Cloud Killer (Source Business Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371492135165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 14:02:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely and you can add to that 10,000 new small customers "per day" as we had 1000,000 new customers in 100 days alone and as you may know we have close to 2 billion Windows customers. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371597830480</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:23:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371597948720-283</Id><Title>I CAN'T DECIDE... DO I WANT ICLOUD..MMMM OR DRIVE...MMM BIG DATA.......FREE CLOUD. NO MSFT INVOLVED</Title><Msg>Just free sweet cloud....and no xbox spying on my daughter...mmmm</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371597948720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598046898-284</Id><Topic><Title>ADBE up Big AH on Cloud Growth... Can't Wait to See MSFT Cloud Growth Soon!</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371590942627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We grew the Azure customer base by 25% in May so we had 250000 enterprise customers on June 1 and also we added 1000000 small Cloud customers or 10000 per day during the last 100 days. This will go ballistic.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371598046898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371598128517-285</Id><Title>I JUST CAME FROM A SEARCH FOR TOP TEN CLOUD PROVIDERS. NO MSFT. ANYWHERE. WOW, SO MANY FREE CLOUDS.</Title><Msg>I think cloud is outta msft's league... Should have golden showers for longs.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371598128517</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598133317-286</Id><Topic><Title>100 million iPad owners are "frustrated" as they can NOT use MSFT Office....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368455117441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 10:25:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371598133317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598196918-287</Id><Topic><Title>At Work With Microsoft Office on an iPhone....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371594171425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371598196918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371598253564-288</Id><Title>YOU BETTER SPIN SOMFIN OTHER THAN CLOUD AS MSFT...IN LAST PLACE AND LOSING TO ASAP.. FOR 1.</Title><Msg>Google amzn. csco...on and on...msft...always last. and no money in cloud try again.</Msg><Username>provendog</Username><Timestamp>1371598253564</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:30:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598286104-289</Id><Topic><Title>SONY PLAYSTATION WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE FOR CHRISTMAS MARKET. UH, OH.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371591889078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:44:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sony is going to be sold off piece by piece by Hedge Funds. Game over for Phony. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371598286104</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598428630-290</Id><Topic><Title>SONY PLAYSTATION WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE FOR CHRISTMAS MARKET. UH, OH.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371591889078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:44:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And I sold my 15 shares of Sony only last week! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371598428630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371598700711-291</Id><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Msg>Is it easy to learn how to use a Mac? Every Mac is created with the guiding principle that computers should be easy to use, so you can spend more time doing what you love and less time figuring out how your computer works. If you’ve never owned a Mac, you may need a little time to get used to it. But within a week or two, chances are you’ll get along like old friends. And because all Mac applications are designed to work in the same, intuitive way, once you learn one application — iTunes, for example — you’ll quickly pick up iPhoto, Mail, or any of the other software that comes with your Mac.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598929413-292</Id><Topic><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can a Mac run Windows and Microsoft Office? DOC, XLS and PPT icons Yes. Microsoft Office is available for the Mac, and Word, PowerPoint, and Excel files created on a Mac are fully compatible with Windows. Most other popular applications are available for the Mac, too. But if you need to use a particular Windows-only application, you have a few options: Boot Camp comes with every new Mac, and it lets you run Windows natively — as if your Mac were a PC. If you want to run OS X and Windows side by side, you can purchase Parallels Desktop for Mac or VMware Fusion. Install one of these applications, along with the Windows Installation CDs, and you can run the occasional Windows program right next to your Mac applications, without having to restart.1</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371598929413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:42:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371599022704-293</Id><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Msg>Is a Mac safe from PC viruses? Yes. The OS X operating system isn’t susceptible to the thousands of viruses plaguing Windows-based computers. And although no computer connected to the Internet is completely immune to all viruses and spyware, OS X has built-in defenses designed with your safety in mind. The Mac web browser, Safari, alerts you whenever you’re downloading an application — even if it’s disguised as a picture or movie file. And Apple continually makes free security updates available for Mac owners. You can even have them download automatically.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371599022704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371599167360-294</Id><Title>FACT IS MSFT HAS FAILED TO COPY APPLE. VOICE RECOG. ON 8 DOESN'T LISTEN.. MUST REPEAT NON-STOP</Title><Msg>Is a Mac reliable? When you buy a PC, you’re buying hardware from one company and an operating system and software from other companies. Not so with a Mac. Because Apple builds both the computer and the software that comes with it, they’re literally made for each other. This means that a Mac rarely freezes or crashes. Occasionally an application might quit, but it won’t affect the rest of your system. And OS X resists most viruses, so you can do anything — without worrying about losing everything.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371599167360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:46:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371599288649-295</Id><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Msg>Which web browsers will work on a Mac? Every Mac includes Safari, the fastest web browser in the world. You can also use Mac versions of Firefox, Chrome, Opera, and others.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599288649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371599438965-296</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599288649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:48:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beware phony Osso! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371599438965</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:50:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371599481834-297</Id><Title>WINDOZE HAS ONLY.. A .53% OF ENTERPRIZE MARKET...SO PUNY.... VERY PUNY.....BUT GOOGLE WOW</Title><Msg>By far.....don't forget big blue ya all. Waaaaaay more ent. customers... Paying customers. msft. Has lagged so long they have to give their faulty junk...away.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371599481834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371599565453-298</Id><Topic><Title>At Work With Microsoft Office on an iPhone....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371594171425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will trade over $50.00 in 4 weeks. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599565453</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371599640718-299</Id><Topic><Title>100 million iPad owners are "frustrated" as they can NOT use MSFT Office....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368455117441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 10:25:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to mention 500 million Windows XP migrating to W-8 or 7 as we speak. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599640718</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371599750442-300</Id><Topic><Title>SONY PLAYSTATION WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE FOR CHRISTMAS MARKET. UH, OH.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371591889078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:44:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. Mr. Loeb is already there with his fork and knife doing exactly what you wrote: splitting Sony into bits and pieces. This, of course, will have the Sony Corporate Staff focused on their stock options, their parachutes, their severances, their buy-outs and not on delivering high quality products. But this news (which you first broke here on the Board, by the way) of Sony not having their new PlayStation until after the entire shopping holiday is a dream come true for Microsoft and their better Xbox One which will be in stock, on shelves and in consumers hands in November. No pun intended, as you wrote "game over".</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371599750442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371599825349-301</Id><Topic><Title>ADBE up Big AH on Cloud Growth... Can't Wait to See MSFT Cloud Growth Soon!</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371590942627</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And this is just the start as we have 75% installed base for MSFT on Enterprise. AND each year $2 Trillion of money will be spent by corporate as 90% of data in the future will be only two years old at any given time and will need major data/systems management day in day out. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599825349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371599873828-302</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Says Fortune 500 Firms Are Loving Its Amazon Cloud Killer (Source Business Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371492135165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 14:02:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We own this business called IT. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599873828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:57:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371599930062-303</Id><Topic><Title>At Work With Microsoft Office on an iPhone....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371594171425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This one is really upsetting the shorts. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599930062</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371599959817-304</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are wasting their time trying to scare the Longs on this Message Board:</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371584133932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no question. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599959817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:59:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371599994632-305</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts: Cover Or...</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371428711234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:25:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that is an understatement. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599994632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371600221547-306</Id><Title>MSFT CO-FOUDER PAUL ALLEN HATES 8 TOO. HERE'S A QUOTE......</Title><Msg>With multi-monitor setups, Allen finds it challenging to raise the "charms" bar inside of the Metro interface due to the fact that your cursor, when pointed near the corner of the screen, can easily navigate to the next display. Further, he also mentions that it's impossible to keep the Metro interface on one display permanently, which would be ideal for those who like a dashboard. Another complaint is pretty mind-boggling to me. Because Windows 8 can associate a protocol to either an app in the Metro interface or on the desktop, you could find yourself looking at the opposite interface depending on how things are configured. As Allen's example lays out, clicking on a URL while using Outlook on the desktop can open it up in Internet Explorer inside of the Metro interface - and I assume the vice versa can also be true. This is a major beef with me because I'm drawn to OSes that improve efficiency and workflow - not those that destroy it. Want to open a bookmark you saved in the desktop version of IE in the Metro version? It's not going to happen, as both apps do not work with the same profiles. I'm also not sure it's even possible for an add-on to be developed for this, as Microsoft has strict rules about what can and can't be done when it comes to Metro apps. Microsoft could however remedy this issue itself, and competitors are likely to fill the void at some point.</Msg><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371600221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371600283743-307</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT CO-FOUDER PAUL ALLEN HATES 8 TOO. HERE'S A QUOTE......</Title><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371600221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As victim mentioned... 8 is all over the place. flying tiles.. And jumping charms.</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371600283743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:04:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371600403930-308</Id><Title>THE MARGINS JUMP OUT AND YOUR WORK IS GONE...CALLED DO OVER. ALLEN ADMITS THE SAME.</Title><Msg>Very dysfunctional 8 will be vista again...but much much worse. won't be a happy ending.</Msg><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371600403930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371600528301-309</Id><Topic><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it easy to learn how to use a Mac? Every Mac is created with the guiding principle that computers should be easy to use, so you can spend more time doing what you love and less time figuring out how your computer works. If you’ve never owned a Mac, you may need a little time to get used to it. But within a week or two, chances are you’ll get along like old friends. And because all Mac applications are designed to work in the same, intuitive way, once you learn one application — iTunes, for example — you’ll quickly pick up iPhoto, Mail, or any of the other software that comes with your Mac.</Msg><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371600528301</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371600989945-310</Id><Title>FAUX NEWS TOBIN SMITH GETS 50K TO TOUT AN ENERGY CO. HA HA HA HA...NO CRED.</Title><Msg>And the funnies just keep on commin' on the backs of paid pumpers here.</Msg><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371600989945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371601761161-311</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOZE HAS ONLY.. A .53% OF ENTERPRIZE MARKET...SO PUNY.... VERY PUNY.....BUT GOOGLE WOW</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371599481834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:51:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bing you "ya all" ! I love WinDoze8 &amp; I'm not alone.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371601761161</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371602015110-312</Id><Title>Bill Ayers: Try Obama for War Crimes</Title><Msg>Each president enters an office dripping with blood, then adds to it. He doesn't like killing terrorists no doubt thinking how he could have been a target at one point.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371602015110</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:33:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602100394-313</Id><Topic><Title>Cartoon: Obama: "I wish we could find a video to blame all these other scandals on"</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371563403174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Here's one of your inauguration" Just a fact...</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371602100394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602358428-314</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599288649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:48:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which web browsers will work on a Mac? Every Mac includes Safari, the fastest web browser in the world. You can also use Mac versions of Firefox, Chrome, Opera, and others.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371602358428</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602394432-315</Id><Topic><Title>FACT IS MSFT HAS FAILED TO COPY APPLE. VOICE RECOG. ON 8 DOESN'T LISTEN.. MUST REPEAT NON-STOP</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371599167360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:46:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is a Mac reliable? When you buy a PC, you’re buying hardware from one company and an operating system and software from other companies. Not so with a Mac. Because Apple builds both the computer and the software that comes with it, they’re literally made for each other. This means that a Mac rarely freezes or crashes. Occasionally an application might quit, but it won’t affect the rest of your system. And OS X resists most viruses, so you can do anything — without worrying about losing everything.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371602394432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371602423455-316</Id><Title>NSA justification, for those of us with mixed feelings, the test is would you want Nixon</Title><Msg>in charge of that power? Obama could well be much worse than Nixon, we have yet to discover the truth, something is causing the wagons to circle around him.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371602423455</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602445062-317</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371599022704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is a Mac safe from PC viruses? Yes. The OS X operating system isn’t susceptible to the thousands of viruses plaguing Windows-based computers. And although no computer connected to the Internet is completely immune to all viruses and spyware, OS X has built-in defenses designed with your safety in mind. The Mac web browser, Safari, alerts you whenever you’re downloading an application — even if it’s disguised as a picture or movie file. And Apple continually makes free security updates available for Mac owners. You can even have them download automatically.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371602445062</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602478261-318</Id><Topic><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can a Mac run Windows and Microsoft Office? DOC, XLS and PPT icons Yes. Microsoft Office is available for the Mac, and Word, PowerPoint, and Excel files created on a Mac are fully compatible with Windows. Most other popular applications are available for the Mac, too. But if you need to use a particular Windows-only application, you have a few options: Boot Camp comes with every new Mac, and it lets you run Windows natively — as if your Mac were a PC. If you want to run OS X and Windows side by side, you can purchase Parallels Desktop for Mac or VMware Fusion. Install one of these applications, along with the Windows Installation CDs, and you can run the occasional Windows program right next to your Mac applications, without having to restart.1</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371602478261</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:41:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602513441-319</Id><Topic><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it easy to learn how to use a Mac? Every Mac is created with the guiding principle that computers should be easy to use, so you can spend more time doing what you love and less time figuring out how your computer works. If you’ve never owned a Mac, you may need a little time to get used to it. But within a week or two, chances are you’ll get along like old friends. And because all Mac applications are designed to work in the same, intuitive way, once you learn one application — iTunes, for example — you’ll quickly pick up iPhoto, Mail, or any of the other software that comes with your Mac.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371602513441</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602563044-320</Id><Topic><Title>YOU BETTER SPIN SOMFIN OTHER THAN CLOUD AS MSFT...IN LAST PLACE AND LOSING TO ASAP.. FOR 1.</Title><Username>provendog</Username><Timestamp>1371598253564</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:30:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google amzn. csco...on and on...msft...always last. and no money in cloud try again.</Msg><Username>trollers_nightmare</Username><Timestamp>1371602563044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:42:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602609898-321</Id><Topic><Title>I JUST CAME FROM A SEARCH FOR TOP TEN CLOUD PROVIDERS. NO MSFT. ANYWHERE. WOW, SO MANY FREE CLOUDS.</Title><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371598128517</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:28:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think cloud is outta msft's league... Should have golden showers for longs.</Msg><Username>wishin_aint_investin</Username><Timestamp>1371602609898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602657175-322</Id><Topic><Title>I CAN'T DECIDE... DO I WANT ICLOUD..MMMM OR DRIVE...MMM BIG DATA.......FREE CLOUD. NO MSFT INVOLVED</Title><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371597948720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just free sweet cloud....and no xbox spying on my daughter...mmmm</Msg><Username>trollers_nightmare</Username><Timestamp>1371602657175</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:44:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602732031-323</Id><Topic><Title>WELL BOARD. I'VE JUST FILED MY COMPLAINT AGAINST MSFT. W/ THE BBB. IN MY STATE ALONE 1400 COMPLAINTS.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371596759890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:05:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mine will get me out of this bing trap and into a new os. never again will msft. Interrupt with stupid bing. i will be calling the ag, in the morning. this is commie garbage pc marketing krap, and it will cost msft mucho. the victim.</Msg><Username>trollers_nightmare</Username><Timestamp>1371602732031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371602885929-324</Id><Topic><Title>hot off the press.</Title><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371590578004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft's main troubles in its traditional businesses have become clear. PC sales could drop by as much as 10% this year and a lackluster response to its Windows 8 operating system has prodded the company to begin work on a new version of the product (to be released later this year). Where the company has shown consistent strength is in its entertainment division. Its latest release, Xbox 360, managed to overcome major technical issues and offer big processing power with superior online functionality. The unit sold over 75 million units and brought more than 40 million customers to its Xbox Live online gaming service, making it one of the most acclaimed gaming consoles ever. But Microsoft's top positioning in these sectors is starting to look vulnerable, as the recently announced XBox One has been met with general disappointment in two areas: Xbox One users must maintain broadband internet connectivity and login at least once every 24 hours in order to play the games they have bought, and game publishers can block users from lending games or giving them away. In addition, rentals will not be supported when the new unit is launched. There are also privacy concerns, since large amounts of private data (videos, photos, and even things like recorded facial expressions and heart rate) are uploaded and saved on outside servers.</Msg><Username>isee_clearly</Username><Timestamp>1371602885929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371603363681-325</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are wasting their time trying to scare the Longs on this Message Board:</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371584133932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is all about fear and stupidity.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371603363681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371603422687-326</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are wasting their time trying to scare the Longs on this Message Board:</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371584133932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You two sucking each other off again?</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371603422687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371603643315-327</Id><Title>osso-dil do is a giant bag of pus</Title><Msg>And smells like manure.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371603643315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:00:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371603674284-328</Id><Topic><Title>Osso is a bag of excrement</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370287761738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reminder time.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371603674284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:01:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371603795998-329</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The revolting osso is the worst.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371603795998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371603813154-330</Id><Topic><Title>osso-dil do is a giant bag of pus</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371603643315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a MORON would call themselves hereturd7............</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371603813154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371603902358-331</Id><Topic><Title>Newest and By Far the Fastest New Super Computer</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1371569052855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong, as always, #$%$.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371603902358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371603970277-332</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are wasting their time trying to scare the Longs on this Message Board:</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371584133932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Projecting again Pervert Eh Boi ?</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371603970277</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:06:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604026857-333</Id><Topic><Title>osso-dil do is a giant bag of pus</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371603643315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how wally (that's you, williamdavis-the-turd) you always show up at the mention of pus or excrement.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371604026857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:07:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604074364-334</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are wasting their time trying to scare the Longs on this Message Board:</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371584133932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get dead, wally, you closet gay.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371604074364</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:07:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604090422-335</Id><Topic><Title>FAUX NEWS TOBIN SMITH GETS 50K TO TOUT AN ENERGY CO. HA HA HA HA...NO CRED.</Title><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371600989945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:16:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worse, Faux News convinced its racist audience that Obama would cause runaway inflation so everyone should buy gold which Cavuto and Hannity and Beck (before he went into the asylum) all pitched. "Inflation is coming! Get out of the stock market! Buy gold!" That was what they screamed for the last two years and their Fox "audience" are all stuck with gold dropping like a boat anchor...and worse, they missed out on the biggest stock rally in history. Fox doesn't just make you stupid, it makes you poor.</Msg><Username>scooponcoop</Username><Timestamp>1371604090422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604110823-336</Id><Topic><Title>At a tiny 0.53%, Windoze 8 adoption levels in the enterprise are shockingly low</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370388335249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back up there....</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371604110823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604131799-337</Id><Topic><Title>At Work With Microsoft Office on an iPhone....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371594171425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371604131799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604134041-338</Id><Topic><Title>osso-dil do is a giant bag of pus</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371603643315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how you like to get verbally abused 24/7 you ghastly old Troll.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371604134041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604225782-339</Id><Topic><Title>SONY PLAYSTATION WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE FOR CHRISTMAS MARKET. UH, OH.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371591889078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:44:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The marketing advantage that Microsoft has with the Xbox One on shelves in November is a marketing dream. Millions will sell. Billions will be made.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371604225782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604338074-340</Id><Topic><Title>SONY PLAYSTATION WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE FOR CHRISTMAS MARKET. UH, OH.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371591889078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:44:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Post! Go softy!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371604338074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604389586-341</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Says Fortune 500 Firms Are Loving Its Amazon Cloud Killer (Source Business Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371492135165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 14:02:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ballmer played the shorts like a violin with the last quarter numbers. And then he pulled the rug out from under their feet. This coming quarter will showcase how big the Enterprise Cloud business is and how Microsoft is all out there alone sealing the deals.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371604389586</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604471273-342</Id><Topic><Title>Ballmer is Going to Butcher Shorts. Butcher.</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371584833651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just bookmark this thread. Wait until this quarter's numbers are released.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371604471273</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604567086-343</Id><Topic><Title>At Work With Microsoft Office on an iPhone....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371594171425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More billions into Microsoft's fat wallet and more dividends to its shareholders.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371604567086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371604740386-344</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are wasting their time trying to scare the Longs on this Message Board:</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371584133932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's OK. There are around nine of them with fifty aliases and none of them have any real money. They are the ones who are scared. Ha. Microsoft is into all new revenue streams now: tablets, windows phones, subscriptions to MS Office for iPhones, Azure, Enterprise, Xbox One all by itself on the shelves throughout the entire holiday season. MONEY.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1371604740386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:19:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371604958018-345</Id><Title>Windows 8 enterprise take-up terrible</Title><Msg>Google it. Quoting: “Statistics from Net Applications also showed in April 2013 that Windows 8 had a usage share of 3.84%, however, our IT Benchmark data demonstrates that the majority of Windows 8 implementations are by consumers and not by enterprises,” said Israel Lifshitz, Founder and Chairman of SysAid. “While it is clear that Windows 7 was a highly anticipated release, businesses are not at all eager to adopt Windows 8. It will be interesting to see if the upcoming Windows 8.1 launch will be attractive enough to increase adoption among enterprises.”</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371604958018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605014710-346</Id><Topic><Title>hot off the press.</Title><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371590578004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft's main troubles in its traditional businesses have become clear. PC sales could drop by as much as 10% this year and a lackluster response to its Windows 8 operating system has prodded the company to begin work on a new version of the product (to be released later this year). Where the company has shown consistent strength is in its entertainment division. Its latest release, Xbox 360, managed to overcome major technical issues and offer big processing power with superior online functionality. The unit sold over 75 million units and brought more than 40 million customers to its Xbox Live online gaming service, making it one of the most acclaimed gaming consoles ever. But Microsoft's top positioning in these sectors is starting to look vulnerable, as the recently announced XBox One has been met with general disappointment in two areas: Xbox One users must maintain broadband internet connectivity and login at least once every 24 hours in order to play the games they have bought, and game publishers can block users from lending games or giving them away. In addition, rentals will not be supported when the new unit is launched. There are also privacy concerns, since large amounts of private data (videos, photos, and even things like recorded facial expressions and heart rate) are uploaded and saved on outside servers.</Msg><Username>wishin_aint_investin</Username><Timestamp>1371605014710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605109403-347</Id><Topic><Title>I CAN'T DECIDE... DO I WANT ICLOUD..MMMM OR DRIVE...MMM BIG DATA.......FREE CLOUD. NO MSFT INVOLVED</Title><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371597948720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:25:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just free sweet cloud....and no xbox spying on my daughter...mmmm Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>wishin_aint_investin</Username><Timestamp>1371605109403</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605141614-348</Id><Topic><Title>I JUST CAME FROM A SEARCH FOR TOP TEN CLOUD PROVIDERS. NO MSFT. ANYWHERE. WOW, SO MANY FREE CLOUDS.</Title><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371598128517</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:28:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think cloud is outta msft's league... Should have golden showers for longs. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371605141614</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605535457-349</Id><Topic><Title>hot off the press.</Title><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371590578004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft's main troubles in its traditional businesses have become clear. PC sales could drop by as much as 10% this year and a lackluster response to its Windows 8 operating system has prodded the company to begin work on a new version of the product (to be released later this year). Where the company has shown consistent strength is in its entertainment division. Its latest release, Xbox 360, managed to overcome major technical issues and offer big processing power with superior online functionality. The unit sold over 75 million units and brought more than 40 million customers to its Xbox Live online gaming service, making it one of the most acclaimed gaming consoles ever. But Microsoft's top positioning in these sectors is starting to look vulnerable, as the recently announced XBox One has been met with general disappointment in two areas: Xbox One users must maintain broadband internet connectivity and login at least once every 24 hours in order to play the games they have bought, and game publishers can block users from lending games or giving them away. In addition, rentals will not be supported when the new unit is launched. There are also privacy concerns, since large amounts of private data (videos, photos, and even things like recorded facial expressions and heart rate) are uploaded and saved on outside servers.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371605535457</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605563162-350</Id><Topic><Title>WELL BOARD. I'VE JUST FILED MY COMPLAINT AGAINST MSFT. W/ THE BBB. IN MY STATE ALONE 1400 COMPLAINTS.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371596759890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:05:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mine will get me out of this bing trap and into a new os. never again will msft. Interrupt with stupid bing. i will be calling the ag, in the morning. this is commie garbage pc marketing krap, and it will cost msft mucho. the victim.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371605563162</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605601220-351</Id><Topic><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it easy to learn how to use a Mac? Every Mac is created with the guiding principle that computers should be easy to use, so you can spend more time doing what you love and less time figuring out how your computer works. If you’ve never owned a Mac, you may need a little time to get used to it. But within a week or two, chances are you’ll get along like old friends. And because all Mac applications are designed to work in the same, intuitive way, once you learn one application — iTunes, for example — you’ll quickly pick up iPhoto, Mail, or any of the other software that comes with your Mac.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371605601220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605632949-352</Id><Topic><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can a Mac run Windows and Microsoft Office? DOC, XLS and PPT icons Yes. Microsoft Office is available for the Mac, and Word, PowerPoint, and Excel files created on a Mac are fully compatible with Windows. Most other popular applications are available for the Mac, too. But if you need to use a particular Windows-only application, you have a few options: Boot Camp comes with every new Mac, and it lets you run Windows natively — as if your Mac were a PC. If you want to run OS X and Windows side by side, you can purchase Parallels Desktop for Mac or VMware Fusion. Install one of these applications, along with the Windows Installation CDs, and you can run the occasional Windows program right next to your Mac applications, without having to restart.1</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371605632949</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605663714-353</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371599022704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is a Mac safe from PC viruses? Yes. The OS X operating system isn’t susceptible to the thousands of viruses plaguing Windows-based computers. And although no computer connected to the Internet is completely immune to all viruses and spyware, OS X has built-in defenses designed with your safety in mind. The Mac web browser, Safari, alerts you whenever you’re downloading an application — even if it’s disguised as a picture or movie file. And Apple continually makes free security updates available for Mac owners. You can even have them download automatically.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371605663714</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605717331-354</Id><Topic><Title>FACT IS MSFT HAS FAILED TO COPY APPLE. VOICE RECOG. ON 8 DOESN'T LISTEN.. MUST REPEAT NON-STOP</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371599167360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:46:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is a Mac reliable? When you buy a PC, you’re buying hardware from one company and an operating system and software from other companies. Not so with a Mac. Because Apple builds both the computer and the software that comes with it, they’re literally made for each other. This means that a Mac rarely freezes or crashes. Occasionally an application might quit, but it won’t affect the rest of your system. And OS X resists most viruses, so you can do anything — without worrying about losing everything.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371605717331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605749064-355</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599288649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:48:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which web browsers will work on a Mac? Every Mac includes Safari, the fastest web browser in the world. You can also use Mac versions of Firefox, Chrome, Opera, and others</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371605749064</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605791941-356</Id><Topic><Title>FAUX NEWS TOBIN SMITH GETS 50K TO TOUT AN ENERGY CO. HA HA HA HA...NO CRED.</Title><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371600989945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:16:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the funnies just keep on commin' on the backs of paid pumpers here.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371605791941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371605998130-357</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT CO-FOUDER PAUL ALLEN HATES 8 TOO. HERE'S A QUOTE......</Title><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371600221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With multi-monitor setups, Allen finds it challenging to raise the "charms" bar inside of the Metro interface due to the fact that your cursor, when pointed near the corner of the screen, can easily navigate to the next display. Further, he also mentions that it's impossible to keep the Metro interface on one display permanently, which would be ideal for those who like a dashboard. Another complaint is pretty mind-boggling to me. Because Windows 8 can associate a protocol to either an app in the Metro interface or on the desktop, you could find yourself looking at the opposite interface depending on how things are configured. As Allen's example lays out, clicking on a URL while using Outlook on the desktop can open it up in Internet Explorer inside of the Metro interface - and I assume the vice versa can also be true. This is a major beef with me because I'm drawn to OSes that improve efficiency and workflow - not those that destroy it.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371605998130</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371606060729-358</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOZE HAS ONLY.. A .53% OF ENTERPRIZE MARKET...SO PUNY.... VERY PUNY.....BUT GOOGLE WOW</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371599481834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:51:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By far.....don't forget big blue ya all. Waaaaaay more ent. customers... Paying customers. msft. Has lagged so long they have to give their faulty junk...away.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371606060729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:41:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371606236023-359</Id><Topic><Title>mjna DUMP dont lose your money, i made 400% month</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368989019609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i signed up</Msg><Username>stocktrader733</Username><Timestamp>1371606236023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371607608711-360</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT CO-FOUDER PAUL ALLEN HATES 8 TOO. HERE'S A QUOTE......</Title><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371600221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 sucks! Switch to Linux!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1371607608711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:06:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371607725449-361</Id><Topic><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lots of people will buy new Macs when Microsoft ends XP support next April. My next computer will be a MacBook Air.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1371607725449</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371607736222-362</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts are wasting their time trying to scare the Longs on this Message Board:</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371584133932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are a bunch of losers as I am sure they all went out and shorted around $34.50 again after having their head handed to them several times and tomorrow they will be getting killed like a bunch roaches. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371607736222</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371607802678-363</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 enterprise take-up terrible</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371604958018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:22:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time to switch to Linux instead!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1371607802678</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371608073970-364</Id><Title>LATEST SUIT AGAINST MSFT. IS HILARIOUS. AND 42% OF SOFTWARE GLOBALLY IS PIRATED. ZERO $$$ TO THE EVIL MSFT. LOL</Title><Msg>Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer wants to stop software pirates. An insurance company in Guatemala is suing Microsoft for allegedly raiding its offices with armed police officers to search for pirated software. Paul Brinkmann of the South Florida Business Journal, first reported on the lawsuit on Monday. Here's what the company, Seguros Universales SA of Guatemala City, claims happened during the April 2012 raid: "Microsoft appeared with armed Guatemalan law enforcement officers and halted plaintiffs’ business operations. Microsoft then proceeded to extort Plaintiffs by demanding an on-the-spot agreement to pay $70,000 or Microsoft would remove all… servers containing ALL data and operational software." Seguros Universales also alleges that Microsoft tried to strong-arm other Guatemalan insurance firms into paying on-the-spot fines for using pirated software, Brinkmann reported. But Microsoft has a different version of how things went down. "Seguras Universales confessed to a Guatemalan judge and prosecutor that it used illegal software and freely entered into an agreement to compensate Microsoft for its wrongdoing," a Microsoft spokesperson told us in an email. "This suit is a meritless attempt to distract from its own software piracy, and we look forward to addressing the claims," the spokesperson said. Microsoft is a member of the Business Software Alliance, an industry group that tracks usage of illegal software. In a 2011 survey, the BSA found that 79% of software in use in Guatemala is pirated, compared to 61% for Latin America as a whole, and 42% globally.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371608073970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371608636223-365</Id><Topic><Title>osso-dil do is a giant bag of pus</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371603643315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny what a #$%$ you are.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371608636223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371608687542-366</Id><Topic><Title>At a tiny 0.53%, Windoze 8 adoption levels in the enterprise are shockingly low</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370388335249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Needs bumping</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371608687542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371608713882-367</Id><Topic><Title>osso-dil do is a giant bag of pus</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371603643315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ you stupid malignant Csucker.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371608713882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371608958493-368</Id><Topic><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why ? XP was a good OS but it's 15 YR old &amp; obsolete, only a cheap dumpster diving shill like you would use it.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371608958493</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:29:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371609052038-369</Id><Title>Huawei to buy the corpse of Nokia, and kill windoze phone</Title><Msg>Google it! Huawei will buy the remains of nokia and jettison the awful windoze phone OS.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371609052038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371609112417-370</Id><Topic><Title>osso-dil do is a giant bag of pus</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371603643315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fellatio is YOUR fixation, wally, you closet shirt-lifter.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371609112417</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371609179915-371</Id><Topic><Title>Huawei to buy the corpse of Nokia, and kill windoze phone</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371609052038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go post your malignant hate trash there then stupid.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371609179915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371609685752-372</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT CO-FOUDER PAUL ALLEN HATES 8 TOO. HERE'S A QUOTE......</Title><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371600221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only an IDIOT like you would want to use linix &amp; all it's 600+ shety aborted POS versions. This message brought to you by wonderful WIN8 with no Stinking penguins inside.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371609685752</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:41:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371610588942-373</Id><Topic><Title>At Work With Microsoft Office on an iPhone....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371594171425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>last week!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1371610588942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371610766620-374</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371599022704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is a Mac safe from PC viruses? Yes. The OS X operating system isn’t susceptible to the thousands of viruses plaguing Windows-based computers. And although no computer connected to the Internet is completely immune to all viruses and spyware, OS X has built-in defenses designed with your safety in mind. The Mac web browser, Safari, alerts you whenever you’re downloading an application — even if it’s disguised as a picture or movie file. And Apple continually makes free security updates available for Mac owners. You can even have them download automatically.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371610766620</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371610799197-375</Id><Topic><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can a Mac run Windows and Microsoft Office? DOC, XLS and PPT icons Yes. Microsoft Office is available for the Mac, and Word, PowerPoint, and Excel files created on a Mac are fully compatible with Windows. Most other popular applications are available for the Mac, too. But if you need to use a particular Windows-only application, you have a few options: Boot Camp comes with every new Mac, and it lets you run Windows natively — as if your Mac were a PC. If you want to run OS X and Windows side by side, you can purchase Parallels Desktop for Mac or VMware Fusion. Install one of these applications, along with the Windows Installation CDs, and you can run the occasional Windows program right next to your Mac applications, without having to restart.1</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371610799197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371610838105-376</Id><Topic><Title>THINGS I'M LEARNING ABOUT APPLE. MY NEXT COMPUTER WILL BE AN APPLE. I'LL TELL YA WHY.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371598700711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it easy to learn how to use a Mac? Every Mac is created with the guiding principle that computers should be easy to use, so you can spend more time doing what you love and less time figuring out how your computer works. If you’ve never owned a Mac, you may need a little time to get used to it. But within a week or two, chances are you’ll get along like old friends. And because all Mac applications are designed to work in the same, intuitive way, once you learn one application — iTunes, for example — you’ll quickly pick up iPhoto, Mail, or any of the other software that comes with your Mac.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371610838105</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371610866393-377</Id><Topic><Title>WELL BOARD. I'VE JUST FILED MY COMPLAINT AGAINST MSFT. W/ THE BBB. IN MY STATE ALONE 1400 COMPLAINTS.</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371596759890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:05:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mine will get me out of this bing trap and into a new os. never again will msft. Interrupt with stupid bing. i will be calling the ag, in the morning. this is commie garbage pc marketing krap, and it will cost msft mucho. the victim.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371610866393</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371610914010-378</Id><Topic><Title>hot off the press.</Title><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371590578004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft's main troubles in its traditional businesses have become clear. PC sales could drop by as much as 10% this year and a lackluster response to its Windows 8 operating system has prodded the company to begin work on a new version of the product (to be released later this year). Where the company has shown consistent strength is in its entertainment division. Its latest release, Xbox 360, managed to overcome major technical issues and offer big processing power with superior online functionality. The unit sold over 75 million units and brought more than 40 million customers to its Xbox Live online gaming service, making it one of the most acclaimed gaming consoles ever. But Microsoft's top positioning in these sectors is starting to look vulnerable, as the recently announced XBox One has been met with general disappointment in two areas: Xbox One users must maintain broadband internet connectivity and login at least once every 24 hours in order to play the games they have bought, and game publishers can block users from lending games or giving them away. In addition, rentals will not be supported when the new unit is launched. There are also privacy concerns, since large amounts of private data (videos, photos, and even things like recorded facial expressions and heart rate) are uploaded and saved on outside servers</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371610914010</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371610947011-379</Id><Topic><Title>I JUST CAME FROM A SEARCH FOR TOP TEN CLOUD PROVIDERS. NO MSFT. ANYWHERE. WOW, SO MANY FREE CLOUDS.</Title><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371598128517</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:28:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think cloud is outta msft's league... Should have golden showers for longs.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371610947011</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371610957490-380</Id><Topic><Title>Huawei to buy the corpse of Nokia, and kill windoze phone</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371609052038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go #$%$ yourself, wally.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371610957490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371611001533-381</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 enterprise take-up terrible</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371604958018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:22:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google it. Quoting: “Statistics from Net Applications also showed in April 2013 that Windows 8 had a usage share of 3.84%, however, our IT Benchmark data demonstrates that the majority of Windows 8 implementations are by consumers and not by enterprises,” said Israel Lifshitz, Founder and Chairman of SysAid. “While it is clear that Windows 7 was a highly anticipated release, businesses are not at all eager to adopt Windows 8. It will be interesting to see if the upcoming Windows 8.1 launch will be attractive enough to increase adoption among enterprises.”</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371611001533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371611237833-382</Id><Topic><Title>Huawei to buy the corpse of Nokia, and kill windoze phone</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371609052038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe, maybe not. Seems it depends on how suicidal Elop is feeling today...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371611237833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371611470685-383</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599288649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:48:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>watch out to see if there are any real ones too! :-D "I wrote "Structured Programming" for Phillips ..."</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1371611470685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371611795294-384</Id><Title>FYI THE RELEASE DATE FOR PS4 THAT HAS BEEN BLASTED 100S OF TIMES ON THIS BOARD. IS A HUGE LIE. I HAVE PROOF</Title><Msg>April 30th, 2013 Update -- More Rumors Point To October 2013 First the Assassin's Creed IV team, now Naughty Dog possibly spills the beans in regards to an October 2013 release date. Unlike Jean Guesdon, who was direct in his approach, Naughty Dog takes a different approach by what could be a subtle reference to the PS4 release date. This hint is found in their newest game The Last Of Us, one of the last titles to be released for the PlayStation 3. In a recent trailer for the game, Joel and Ellie come across a sign that states "Mandatory Evacuation Notice: 10/17/2013." While many might think this was just a date chosen at random, could this in fact be Naughty Dog releasing the PS4 date in secret to its fans? After all, Naughty Dog is one of Sony's top developers so it's likely they are privy to such knowledge. We've put the image below for your viewing pleasure! Let us know in the comments if you think this date is for real or just a joke by Naughty Dog.</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371611795294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371611889764-385</Id><Topic><Title>FYI THE RELEASE DATE FOR PS4 THAT HAS BEEN BLASTED 100S OF TIMES ON THIS BOARD. IS A HUGE LIE. I HAVE PROOF</Title><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371611795294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:16:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While the PlayStation 3 is just now hitting its stride, and has its best days still ahead of it, Sony is not one to rest on its laurels, and with the intense competition in the video game world at present, plans for the PlayStation 4's release plans are in motion now that it has been officially announced. In fact not only is the PlayStation 4 getting this treatment, but even the PlayStation 5 and PlayStation 6 are in the early stages of planning and conceptualization at Sony's R&amp;D labs. Although we've yet to see what the PS3 can fully do when really put through its paces (in fact Sony states that games</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371611889764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371611947812-386</Id><Topic><Title>FYI THE RELEASE DATE FOR PS4 THAT HAS BEEN BLASTED 100S OF TIMES ON THIS BOARD. IS A HUGE LIE. I HAVE PROOF</Title><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371611795294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:16:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>currently on the market are not even close to pushing the system to its full potential), the thought of an even more powerful console looming on the horizon has gamers worried about the holes it will leave burning in their pockets, but giddy at the confirmed capabilities of what this new behemoth of a console will be able to pull off. See the specs here. When is the PS4 coming out? The Question Everyone Wants the Answer To... As a result, the question on everyone's mind is, when will the PlayStation 4 see the light of day?!?!? Sony has officially said "Holiday 2013" which means we will have a chance to play that Playstation 4 this year! This follows the trend of Sony's previous console generations. The PlayStation 1 was first released in late 1994 in Japan and 1995 throughout the rest of the world. The PlayStation 2 hit stores in 2000, giving the PS1 a retail shelf life of 6 years from its Japanese launch. Likewise, the PlayStation 3 came out in 2006, 6 years after the release of the PS2. Following this trend that Sony has established it was not a surprise that Sony officially announced the Playstation 4 on February 20th 2013 in NYC. Popular PS4 Pages PS4 Pictures PS4 Price $ PS4 Games PS4 Specs PS4 Pre-Order PS4 Concept Designs Both the PlayStation 1 and PlayStation 2, which dominated their generations of the console wars, came to market at the same time or earlier than their competition. The PlayStation 1 was launched just after the Sega Saturn, and well before the Nintendo 64, while the PlayStation 2 was released before both the Xbox and Nintendo Gamecube. This enabled Sony to get a head start on the competition and gave developers time to build their skills at developing games for the console, to the point that even as more powerful consoles came after, games released</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371611947812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371612013739-387</Id><Topic><Title>FYI THE RELEASE DATE FOR PS4 THAT HAS BEEN BLASTED 100S OF TIMES ON THIS BOARD. IS A HUGE LIE. I HAVE PROOF</Title><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371611795294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:16:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>on the older system were just as good technically, providing no real incentive for players to move to the new consoles. This same effect has worked against the PlayStation 3 to some extent, as though considered to be far more powerful than the Xbox 360, the one year head start the 360 received has allowed developers to more quickly maximize the system's potential, resulting in games that rivaled games on the PS3 when it released. Only as the system's life spans come to an end will we likely see the PlayStation 3 come out with games that clearly trump what the 360 can do graphically. Now we can all rejoice since the PS4 is official and will be coming out in 2013. The question is will you be ready for it? Let us know what you think. Feel free to comment below. You can also join our PS4 forums to voice your opinion on everything PlayStation 4.</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371612013739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:20:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371612369824-388</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599288649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:48:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>corneriusfrake you couldn't write a decent retter to santa crause</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371612369824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:26:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371612450608-389</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599288649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:48:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get dead, wally, you #$%$.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371612450608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371612494678-390</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another bump</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1371612494678</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371612523344-391</Id><Title>DIDID YOU KNOW INTERNET EXPLORER 10 IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW....MICROSOFT BEATS EM ALL</Title><Msg>See just goes to show you sux pimps and Iturd pimps how full of it you really are</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371612523344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371612786447-392</Id><Topic><Title>The supercomputer OS war is over and Linux has won decisively</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371511295578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 19:21:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>predouchebag how much money will they make of of the OS on the super computer? If you weren't so concerned about your boi friends and sucking all the time you might just notice that they will barely get their expenses back -- Microsoft could produce a super computer OS if there was any money in it which would easily outperform your hunk o junk 'sux</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371612786447</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:33:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371612857859-393</Id><Title>WHY FATHER BLOWZIMA THAT;S A LIE. SAFARI IS #1 AND I'LL BE HAPPY TO PASTE IT 4 U, PECKERSNOT DRINKER</Title><Msg>Blatent lies like yours are easy cheesy....nobody would believe that trash... But hey...wanna prove yourself.. Bring proof. i have a nice peice of ad copy for u...ya scmbag....</Msg><Username>msft_last_always</Username><Timestamp>1371612857859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371613022410-394</Id><Topic><Title>WHY FATHER BLOWZIMA THAT;S A LIE. SAFARI IS #1 AND I'LL BE HAPPY TO PASTE IT 4 U, PECKERSNOT DRINKER</Title><Username>msft_last_always</Username><Timestamp>1371612857859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be hereshitard's twin brother.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371613022410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371613086266-395</Id><Topic><Title>DID YOU KNOW SAFARI IS THE FASTEST SEARCH ENGINE....WOW,,,,APPLE BEATS EM ALL !</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371599288649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:48:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which web browsers will work on a Mac? Every Mac includes Safari, the fastest web browser in the world. You can also use Mac versions of Firefox, Chrome, Opera, and others.....THE FACTS JACK....</Msg><Username>msft_last_always</Username><Timestamp>1371613086266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:38:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371613133847-396</Id><Topic><Title>FACT IS MSFT HAS FAILED TO COPY APPLE. VOICE RECOG. ON 8 DOESN'T LISTEN.. MUST REPEAT NON-STOP</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371599167360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:46:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is a Mac reliable? When you buy a PC, you’re buying hardware from one company and an operating system and software from other companies. Not so with a Mac. Because Apple builds both the computer and the software that comes with it, they’re literally made for each other. This means that a Mac rarely freezes or crashes. Occasionally an application might quit, but it won’t affect the rest of your system. And OS X resists most viruses, so you can do anything — without worrying about losing everything.</Msg><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371613133847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:38:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371613380225-397</Id><Title>HERE'S A FUN FACT....COST OF OPERATION. SAFARI NO VIRUSES...SAME WITH CHROME. MSFT. $40-60. PER YR.</Title><Msg>Avg. Pc life. 5-6 yrs.. Times the virus costs to defend against msft's virus factory...well about $150 more than a chromebook, and 1/2 the cost of a nice hp. So msft the dog as always on every single metric....</Msg><Username>msft_last_always</Username><Timestamp>1371613380225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:43:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371613600811-398</Id><Topic><Title>WHY FATHER BLOWZIMA THAT;S A LIE. SAFARI IS #1 AND I'LL BE HAPPY TO PASTE IT 4 U, PECKERSNOT DRINKER</Title><Username>msft_last_always</Username><Timestamp>1371612857859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't get jealous.....there's plenty to go around.....you will still get your 3 quarts...stop whining. we all know you are the peckersnot queen.</Msg><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371613600811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>