<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372566743537-1</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Drops Developer Patch Fees On Xbox 360</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1372465518665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 20:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL I'd bet Microsoft did this on the quiet because they didn't want it known that they had ever charged a fee for that.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372566743537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 00:32:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372567075129-2</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Did Zimmerman make the first move?" Probably ... look at the facts: (1) Zimmerman had called 911 numerous times on Black People. "Zimmerman prosecutors want to admit his five prior 911 calls about black suspicious characters" (2) Zimmerman carries a Firearm against Neighborhood Rules. "A manual published by the association for its "USAonWatch" program makes that very clear. "It should be emphasized to members that they do not possess police powers and they shall not carry weapons or pursue vehicles," the manual states." (3) Zimmerman followed Trayvon and confronted him. "Members should never confront suspicious persons who could be armed and dangerous." (4) Trayvon was NOT suspicious activity: "Here's why: The sheriffs' association manual lists the type of suspicious activity that should be reported to police. Among the examples: "Someone peering into car windows" and "broken doors or windows." Nowhere does it list walking while black, which is all Trayvon appeared to be doing as he made his way back to the house of his dad's fiancée after a candy run to 7-Eleven." (5) Zimmerman didn't follow the Dispatcher: "a dispatcher said he didn't need to follow the teen" ... but he did.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372567075129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 00:37:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372578149634-3</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft has failed</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372523122004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:25:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My $249 Samsung Google Chromebook is a great alternative to Windows 8 Metro. I'm using it right now. Works great with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1372578149634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 03:42:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372578418584-4</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Surface Rt Last 2 days on sale</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1372525751345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 13:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google Chromebook= Free Google Docs Included Keyboard Store Price is $249 No Windows 8 Metro = Priceless</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1372578418584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 03:46:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372589043837-5</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""Did Zimmerman make the first move?" Probably ... " Probably not by any fair measure, certainly not beyond a reasonable doubt, it's your biased guess. If one is a juror and follows American law, one can sit and have such "feelings" but one needs to weigh what is shown, not what one thinks "probably" happened, that level is left for civil verdicts. Emotional, prejudicial “feelings” are not used where an innocent man, who was maybe jumped while returning to his car as instructed, is locked up for life. "Zimmerman prosecutors want to admit his five prior 911 calls about black suspicious characters" Of course they want that, they apparently have no evidence, their best hope is to prejudice the jury. If he is a watch guy and the people who are lurking about are black he should shut up, is that what you're saying? He apparently made many, many calls, only 5 were of black suspects? Carrying a firearm is just smart, he'd likely be dead today if he didn't. You apply moron rules for yourself, do the world a favor. Ask a cop volunteering during off hours if he would go on watch without a firearm. " Zimmerman followed Trayvon and confronted him." That is contrary to testimony, English challenged moe. Trayvon said he would not run away (State witness), Trayvon not Zimmerman was using racial terms (State witness). The first words spoken per the State is "why are you following me" supporting Zimmerman's version that Trayvon turned and confronted him. "Trayvon was NOT suspicious activity:" That's your spin, nothing more, he appeared to be looking into apartments and was loitering IN THE RAIN. Criminals love the rain you know, hides their tracks. "Zimmerman didn't follow the Dispatcher:" NO! THAT PREJUDICIAL STATEMENT IS COMMON AMONG YOU NON ENGLISH SPEAKING FOREIGNORS. He was following BEFORE told they didn't want that, then he quit per his testimony. Nothing you allege he did is illegal, much less ground for prison.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372589043837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 06:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372589085404-6</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft has failed</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372523122004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 12:25:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's nice to see this assessment confirms my own long-held views in certain ways -- in particular the view that Microsoft's main goal is to prosper by hurting competitors, not by helping customers. If customers benefit, that is only incidental. One might attempt to trace this to Bill Gates' upbringing, in which he was taught to be ruthlessly hypercompetitive, but that is a bit more speculative.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372589085404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 06:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372598013491-7</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Of course they want that, they apparently have no evidence" The Evidence is all there ... Phone calls, disobeying, following someone, carrying a firearm against rules ... etc. The reasonable doubt is all there ... Zimmerman Provoked It. "he appeared to be looking into apartments and was loitering IN THE RAIN. " Even your Hannity ... (where you got all your thoughts for your original post) says he would walk next to the apartments in the rain to prevent from getting wet ... listen more closely to him. "Nothing you allege he did is illegal, much less ground for prison." According to you ... Also ... "New Evidence: No Trace of Trayvon Martin’s DNA on George Zimmerman’s Gun Evidence released in the Trayvon Martin murder case indicates that the 17-year-old did not handle his killer's gun at all despite Zimmerman's claim that he grabbed for it during their fatal struggle."</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372598013491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:13:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372598369028-8</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Phone calls, disobeying, following someone, carrying a firearm against rules ... etc." Again, third time, none of what you even ALLEGE is illegal, why the trial for non illegal things? You want to claim Zimmerman used poor judgment? In hindsight you will get some agreement. "Nothing you allege he did is illegal, much less ground for prison." According to you ... According to the law, name one thing you listed that is illegal. He had a right to follow. No evidence he disobeyed anyone, but if he did that is not illegal, rules are not law. Evidence released in the Trayvon Martin murder case indicates that the 17-year-old did not handle his killer's gun at all despite Zimmerman's claim that he grabbed for it during their fatal struggle." "Grabbed for it" is not handling it, ESL. That said, it was raining and a gun is normally lubricated, no DNA need be present if he did handle it.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372598369028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372598376345-9</Id><Title>msft could trounce appl by 2020?</Title><Msg>why not appl was trading in the 20.00 range 10 years ago before hiting 700.00 it can happen!!!!</Msg><Username>celk40</Username><Timestamp>1372598376345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:19:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372599945633-10</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also .... you might not be aware ... "Wed May 1, 2013" "Zimmerman to argue self-defense, will not seek 'stand your ground' hearing" If Zimmerman was right ... the "Stand Your Ground" law might have let him go ... But ....</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372599945633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:45:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372601308002-11</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're learning, when you cannot name a single law he violated, it is best to change the subject to some extraordinarily old news, that is nothing more than a strategy to counter what now appears to be a politically motivated witch hunt. If Zimmermen was black and Trayvon was white there would be no trial, so we do still have a ways to go on relations and fairness. I do feel bad for Trayvon's parents, that's no reason to hold a trial where no evidence is apparently available (at least none has been presented to date).</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372601308002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:08:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372602296508-12</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"when you cannot name a single law he violated" Do they arrest and charge someone with 2nd degree murder if there is No Reason or Law broken ??? "The charge of second degree murder was announced by Florida special prosecutor Angela Corey at a news conference this evening." "We have to have a reasonable certainty of conviction before filing charges," the prosecutor said."</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372602296508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372603994272-13</Id><Title>MSFT Project Spark For XBOX ONE, XBOX 360 and Windows 8....</Title><Msg>Folks Just Bing: "Microsoft Demos Project Spark Video" on C/Net".... THIS is an amazing technology that will kill POS4 or any other Gaming Platform for years to come.... WE will get our 25 Plus P/E sooner than many thought. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372603994272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372604199009-14</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only Zimmer really knows, and he is a confirmed, proven, liar to the court itself. It was dark, opinions may be faulty. One thing for sure is Martin broke no law anyone can prove that night, was unarmed, and was killed by a bullet from George. Too bad George wasn't armed, they would have had their fist fight and done. Another thing for sure is George wasn't injured much, and he should get at least manslaughter. Hopefully he will be put in a place where he can be dealt with in the same way he dealt it out. George goofed, and now wants to lie his way out of it. Almost a bigger question is why the right embraces George over Trayvon. It seems obvious they put much less value on Traynon's existence than if he had been white. There's a word for that kind of rating system.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1372604199009</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372605220025-15</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Only Zimmer really knows..." Absolutely correct. And it is the State's job to prove what, in this case, they cannot know in order to get a conviction. "...and he should get at least manslaughter" What law did he break that is proven? Answer: None. The State would have been smarter to ask for manslaughter and hope to get a conviction on emotion. Clearly by going for murder 2 they over reached a mile, but maybe they hoped the jury would return manslaughter. What you have a case to make (possibly) is civil "wrongful death". "Almost a bigger question is why the right embraces George over Trayvon." I have not seen that. Most think it a tragic event for both. Zimmerman's life is ruined. When you have a hotdog cop wanna-be run into a hothead racist punk, tough guy wanna be, on a dark rainy night, there is not going to be a good outcome.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372605220025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372605950807-16</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Do they arrest and charge someone with 2nd degree murder if there is No Reason or Law broken ???" Uhm yes, in cases of political pressure. Angela Corey is a joke, she was pressured to press charges and she caved. Unless they come up with new testimony or evidence, if Zimmerman is convicted of anything he will be a political prisoner. The judge should direct an acquittal if the prosecution had done all it can.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372605950807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372607253993-17</Id><Title>hawcreek wants Zimmerman for a romantic night of fornication apparently</Title><Msg>They can pillow talk of their hate for black people</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372607253993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372607475551-18</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>strong buy</Msg><Username>rxgolfer808</Username><Timestamp>1372607475551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372607906633-19</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT Project Spark For XBOX ONE, XBOX 360 and Windows 8....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372603994272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:53:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course folks just Google: Zune, Vista, Kin, W8, etc.,etc.,etc. and you'll understand the 13 year 11 PE! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372607906633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372608050368-20</Id><Topic><Title>Let’s get the Windows 8.1 party started....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372463120526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:45:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course folks Windows 8.2 will be released soon to deal with the obvious problems of W8.1. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372608050368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372609167759-21</Id><Title>Poor liberal juvenile kook, devoid of argument, faced with her failure in chief plays with deck</Title><Msg>that only contains race card and an idiotic level of jibberish talk. It's all she's got, and with her 8th grade maturity/mentality level it's all she'll ever have.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372609167759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372610053524-22</Id><Topic><Title>Poor liberal juvenile kook, devoid of argument, faced with her failure in chief plays with deck</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372609167759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:19:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawcreek has only online fukery to contribute</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372610053524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:34:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372610111015-23</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek wants Zimmerman for a romantic night of fornication apparently</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372607253993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:47:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go shoot yurself a black man and you might get the same cell block. Its a start for you.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372610111015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:35:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372611062833-24</Id><Topic><Title>Is Microsoft in Trouble?</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372498574376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 05:36:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft says the listen to customers. What a bunch of bulloney! Vista and Windows 8 are perfect examples of how Microsoft doesn't give a #$%$ about YOU!</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1372611062833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372611123335-25</Id><Topic><Title>Let’s get the Windows 8.1 party started....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372463120526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:45:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forget about Windows 8.x. Let's get the Windows 9 party started!</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1372611123335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372611185827-26</Id><Topic><Title>msft could trounce appl by 2020?</Title><Username>celk40</Username><Timestamp>1372598376345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:19:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSFT will be bankrupt by 2020. Nobody is buying Windows 8 or Surface.</Msg><Username>hahahacreek</Username><Timestamp>1372611185827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:53:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372614556741-27</Id><Title>bing - captcha</Title><Msg>Just another minor irritant compared to other Microsoft moves, but was going to use bing to search, while logged in (bing points), and they don't have sophisticated enough technology to determine who is a human searching, and who is trying to scam bing points. I'll search elsewhere as I consider it an insult to make me use captcha to submit a search on a search engine. Maybe I'm the one who is not so smart, as a MSFT stockholder?</Msg><Username>ckorkow</Username><Timestamp>1372614556741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 13:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372614838434-28</Id><Title>msft_victim Got a refund. Bought a Chromebook. Faster by far, no metro tiles, no false reads, touch, no prob, boots instantly, NO FRIGGIN"</Title><Msg>in your face non stop. and all for $249,... if internet and surfing the web is your thing, like me....this is the correct best of best tool. If artsy fartsy videos and personal data storage, i would go to Apple. But as to LINUX, easy I was up and posting in 2 minutes. That's including my info install, and taking the tutorial. 2 minutes. UP and no cussing. windows 8 is sooo flawed, the store gave me a full cash refund for my touchscreen Acer, and my win 8 non touch HP. HP a much better machine, but 8 is krap. period. BBB complaint filed. Now on to better boards for me...hence the new id. Victim no longer.... I went chrome. Never msft or intel ever again. Junk...pure junk. and soooooo invasive. ripp off. 8 broken. period. victim no longer......</Msg><Username>nophilordoc</Username><Timestamp>1372614838434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 13:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372614931374-29</Id><Title>Chromebook...no NO FRIGGIN" BING I HATE BING</Title><Msg>Invasive msft. horrible violations.</Msg><Username>nophilordoc</Username><Timestamp>1372614931374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 13:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372615016201-30</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT Project Spark For XBOX ONE, XBOX 360 and Windows 8....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372603994272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:53:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You see you stupid S0B, mikerego19, all that troll BS is already priced in and that you deserve to die poor for being a dumb betch. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372615016201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 13:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372615028451-31</Id><Title>Euro Obama Poster: "Yes we scan" "We are watching you" Europeans fuming</Title><Msg>LOL, too funny, even the Euros are getting the message about the poser in chief.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372615028451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 13:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372615095642-32</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT Project Spark For XBOX ONE, XBOX 360 and Windows 8....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372603994272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:53:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because Mr. Softy has its hands in so many areas, mistakes are bound to occur in some areas. But in spite of that MSFT is raking in the bucks, because they have a lot of successes which you make a habit to ignore. For example, their cloud business is on its way to becoming a monster. Furthermore, the new MSFT isn't afraid to listen to customers and fix a mistake... Windows 8.1, SBox One... You just watch how much market share they begin to take in devices with their new smart attitude to please customers.</Msg><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1372615095642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 13:58:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372615122063-33</Id><Topic><Title>Let’s get the Windows 8.1 party started....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372463120526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:45:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earnings are now only three weeks away.... Cover or die poor. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372615122063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 13:58:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372615386530-34</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is a pile of BS as by April 2014 MSFT will NOT support Windows XP, so they either move to Windows 7 or 8 or expose themselves to massive lawsuits as their systems gets compromised as they willingly and knowingly will harm their customers and employees et al.... SO if they have a legal department, which I am sure they do, what you say is just a troll's lie. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372615386530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:03:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372620072253-35</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have seen the contract where msft denies them support even if they agree to pay for it then? no?!?!!? this is just more of your usual beef stew then? :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372620072253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372620858516-36</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey it's queerneariusfrake the Troll.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1372620858516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:34:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372621810074-37</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I haven't met or seen a "black" person racist against a white persons, ever. Calling someone cracker is not even close to racism. It's akin to saying sob. Racism is sayiing Trayvon deserved to die, or George should have been allowed to go, based on what he said he did. The reason is, that has been the history of America under jim crow, to kill black men as if it's nothing, and it is that "black" people are inferior. Not different, inferior, that's racism. Like the old German guy who lost his war.Your tirades against Obama qualify, even so far as name calling a President as if he is stupid. You say something like it daily. That's why I am moving on from it, I can see it is a hopeless argument with you and your aliases.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1372621810074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372623672706-38</Id><Topic><Title>Let’s get the Windows 8.1 party started....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372463120526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:45:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course folks "Earnings are now only three weeks away...." could be taken as a warning to get out of your long position if, as expected, MSFT misses their numbers again. PLEASE DO YOUR OWN DD AND DON'T JUST BLINDLY FOLLOW MY ADVICE!! I appreciate the loyalty you all show me but, again, DO YOUR OWN DD!!!! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372623672706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372623957339-39</Id><Title>hawcreek law allows starting a fight with a black man then shooting him if you are losing.</Title><Msg>I wonder if the law could be applied the other way in some liberal areas.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372623957339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372625397772-40</Id><Topic><Title>Is Microsoft in Trouble?</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372498574376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 05:36:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mowrawn you are talking about the most successful Op systems of their day- whats pitiable and opathetic is the scam advanced by rthe open sores crowd which lures unsuspecting and low intelligence people to buy linsux</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1372625397772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372626194954-41</Id><Topic><Title>Let’s get the Windows 8.1 party started....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372463120526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 19:45:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mikeregp19, you dumb betch do you really think the long are holding or adding because of what I write here! THE longs are all well aware of the trolls like you and are making you pay for it. You will die poor and you deserve it. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372626194954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372627776690-42</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek wants Zimmerman for a romantic night of fornication apparently</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372607253993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:47:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the talking points Hawcreek had for his posts were on the Hannity Show ... and I listened to it to see how it was spun. Also, Nancy Grace seemed like a nut on the subject too.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372627776690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372627904616-43</Id><Topic><Title>Witness: Trayvon Martin was straddling George Zimmerman</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372449650502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Creep a&amp;&amp; cracker" If someone called you that ... would it bother you ?</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372627904616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372628677767-44</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was on top but who assaulted who first?</Title><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372554599157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 21:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I haven't met or seen a "black" person racist against a white persons, ever. " Pepeekook, you're a pretty fair comedian, but sometimes you overdo it a bit.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372628677767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372629369280-45</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek law allows starting a fight with a black man then shooting him if you are losing.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372623957339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:25:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...starting a fight with a black man then shooting him " Your job, Mrs. Phelps, so you choose to accept it: Prove Mr. Zimmerman started the fight in spite of no supporting evidence and if so you may have a vehicle to a manslaughter conviction based on emotion. Considering the first words communicated, as both sides agree, were the words of Trayvon confronting Zimmerman, and consider that the State's prize witness has Trayvon muttering racial slurs just prior to the confrontation, good luck with your Mission Impossible task, Mrs Phelps, your premise will self destruct in 5 seconds as illogical. You know the interesting thing about your jury rigged supposition, is that in most places even if you begin the confrontation, the confronted one has no right to kill you by bashing your head into a concrete sidewalk. If it escalates to that you DO have a right to use deadly force.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372629369280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372629565630-46</Id><Topic><Title>Witness: Trayvon Martin was straddling George Zimmerman</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372449650502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 16:00:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Creep a&amp;&amp; cracker" If someone called you that ... would it bother you ?" It would not bother me but it would allow me to realize the one uttering those words was a racist with an attitude, and possibly dangerous. Of course that only shows the thinking of Trayvon as Zimmerman did not know he was referred to with that racial slur until months later.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372629565630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:59:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372629820320-47</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek wants Zimmerman for a romantic night of fornication apparently</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372607253993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:47:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"All the talking points Hawcreek had for his posts were on the Hannity Show ... " I never watch Hannity, he uses the emotions of the right like Jesse and the like use the emotions of the left. It's a rather shallow show so I am not surprised you look to it for reference. All that said, if Hannity shared similar points, they are just the facts. I find it amusing that Obama supporters are surprised that the fact stay the same regardless of the source while the nature of their leftist Obama lies means the stories require "talking point" coordination.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372629820320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 18:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372633437442-48</Id><Title>Is Wottowoto in trouble</Title><Msg>watsamata BOZO did you get cought short a few times on MSFT as it move up 10 bucks-- gee couldnt happen to a nicer guy HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR AHR AR HAR HAR HAR AR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1372633437442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:03:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372634096666-49</Id><Topic><Title>Chromebook...no NO FRIGGIN" BING I HATE BING</Title><Username>nophilordoc</Username><Timestamp>1372614931374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 13:55:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bing is far superior to info stealing criminal GOOG, BTW chrome is one of the most insecure devices out there Congrats ! snapper head.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1372634096666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:14:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372635338254-50</Id><Title>VCSY granted patent for Method and system for providing a framework for processing markup language documents</Title><Msg>application 09/888,329 GRANTED!!</Msg><Username>pokerface072508</Username><Timestamp>1372635338254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372636402965-51</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek law allows starting a fight with a black man then shooting him if you are losing.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372623957339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:25:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deadly force is only usable in the case of reasonable fear of loss of life. Or if Zimm gets off then it must be OK to shoot if you are just losing the fight.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372636402965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372637489050-52</Id><Topic><Title>going LONG here, oh BILL GATES</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368549474411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks guys</Msg><Username>kirmoey</Username><Timestamp>1372637489050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 20:11:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372637877613-53</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek law allows starting a fight with a black man then shooting him if you are losing.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372623957339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:25:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Or if Zimm gets off then it must be OK to shoot if you are just losing the fight." Why are liberals universally uninformed? Answer: if they weren't stupid, they would be conservatives. Tell you what, mam, have a young strong guy bash your head into concrete time after time, knowing each pound could render you unconscious (and then dead), have that young man vow to kill you, and then place a gun in your hand and see what if you are in fear and what level response is warranted. As one astute analyst once said "I'd rather be tried by six than carried by six". Grow up, punk.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372637877613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 20:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372641605148-54</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek wants Zimmerman for a romantic night of fornication apparently</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372607253993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:47:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It's a rather shallow show so I am not surprised you look to it for reference." The Reference being what you Right-Wing Stooges will post.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372641605148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 21:20:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372642063221-55</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek wants Zimmerman for a romantic night of fornication apparently</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372607253993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:47:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Reference being what you...will post." Yes I realize how you hate facts, like sunlight to a vampire.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372642063221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 21:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372642150242-56</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek law allows starting a fight with a black man then shooting him if you are losing.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372623957339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:25:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems that Zimmerman had a temper to start such a fight ... "In 2005, a woman filed a petition for an injunction against Zimmerman, claiming that he came to her house and became violent when she told him to leave, the Orlando Sentinel reports. Zimmerman, 21 at the time, filed a petition of his own in response. Just a month before that, the paper reports, Zimmerman was at a bar near the University of Central Florida when a friend was arrested on suspicion of serving minors. Zimmerman became profane and pushed a law enforcement agent who tried to escort him away. He was arrested after a short struggle. That arrest had been reported previously."</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372642150242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 21:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372642802472-57</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek wants Zimmerman for a romantic night of fornication apparently</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372607253993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:47:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yes I realize how you hate facts" I post FACTS to you all the time ... you have never returned anything but Right-Wing Opinions ... That is a FACT.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372642802472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 21:40:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372643441806-58</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek law allows starting a fight with a black man then shooting him if you are losing.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372623957339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:25:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"George Zimmerman son of judge with sealed closed arrest record in Fla. 27 Mar 2012 'Now we know why George Zimmerman didn't get arrested... No Words... According to court records, George Zimmerman is the son of retired Supreme Court Magistrate Judge Robert J Zimmerman, his mother Gladys Zimmerman is a court clerk... He has three closed arrests: 7/18/05 for resisting arrest with violence and battery on a law enforcement officer div 10... 8/9/05 for domestic violence div 44... And again on 8/10/05, domestic violence"</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372643441806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 21:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372643774866-59</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek law allows starting a fight with a black man then shooting him if you are losing.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372623957339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 16:25:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Seems that Zimmerman had a temper to start such a fight ..."In 2005, a woman filed a petition for an injunction against Zimmerman" Means nothing, you need evidence here, in this case, not 7 year old innuendo that may or may not have any merit. An older neighbor girl, I think it was when she reached about 40 years old, revealed another neighbor, a friend of mine, molested her when she was 8 years old. She was positive to the day and very specific as he told it. Only problem with her story is that he was 6 months old at the time. She could have landed much potential grief on him had their ages worked. The mentally ill can make things up and have totally false memories they sincerely believe and the devious can just lie. Women have great leverage in the law in those areas to protect them from stalkers.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372643774866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 21:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372643996114-60</Id><Topic><Title>hawcreek wants Zimmerman for a romantic night of fornication apparently</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1372607253993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:47:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I post FACTS to you all the time ... you have never returned anything but Right-Wing Opinions ... That is a FACT." You have our factual roles exactly reversed, as you well know, that is fact.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372643996114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 21:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>