<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368850759960-1</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Courting New Developers, But Some Existing Ones Are Still Fuming Over Its Windows 8 Decisions</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368840032983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 21:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I'm more and more convinced that this is how it ends for Microsoft. It has an incompetent CEO/Executive Chairman that it can't get rid of, and he's a loose cannon, a bull in a china shop, bent on doing everything wrong and wrecking the company from the top down. Bill Gates, for whatever reason, can't or won't intervene. And, to the bitter end, the company has its army of shills, of which osso is only one in only one forum, trying to tell everyone that it's not so.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368850759960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 00:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368851611066-2</Id><Topic><Title>Next week events - Xbox 720, WP-8, Surface, Cloud, Skype et al....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368831546270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ossobucco you are so on the money.</Msg><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1368851611066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 00:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368852797827-3</Id><Title>How bad can the Benghazi thing be for the administration to finally throw the IRS scandal out in front of the bus?</Title><Msg>Google Doug Haman Canada Free Press</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368852797827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 00:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368869655480-4</Id><Topic><Title>How bad can the Benghazi thing be for the administration to finally throw the IRS scandal out in front of the bus?</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368852797827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 00:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if the President's team could actually be so incompetent to ring up a 4 alarm response to a two alarm event? The one thing that could suggest their "all hands to battle stations" was just an over reaction is timing just before a close election. The response, including destroying Rice's career by directing her to lie, suggests the truth hides something so nefarious that, if known, it could still bring down the President. In either case we are left with deciding if it is just more gross incompetency, already in evidence in so many places, or some twist so horrific that the public knowing the truth would complete destruction of the most corrupt presidency in history...And in either case we are not being told the truth.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368869655480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 05:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368869918419-5</Id><Topic><Title>How Many Jobs Did The Tea Party Create?</Title><Username>rightwing_fukery_hurts_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368843958533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 22:25:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"More job cuts are on the way as the river of government spending flowing through the U.S. economy continues to slow." The printed, fake money can only carry us so far for so long, eventually the overspending has to stop, voluntarily or involuntarily. The idea of a "stimulus" is by definition temporary. We have an incompetent President who depends upon it for his pretend recovery.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368869918419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 05:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368874952478-6</Id><Topic><Title>sleeping giant still rubbing its eyes</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1366826921039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 14:08:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>few eye drops-zoom</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1368874952478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 07:02:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368876224124-7</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT PE is now 18, almost twice of AAPL</Title><Username>tangos88888</Username><Timestamp>1368820056453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 15:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well MSFT is trading at 11x next years earnings estimate even after a big run up. Apple is trading at 11x next years earning estimate. The estimates for Apple are coming down fast and they will make less money next year then this. Which would you rather own a company with an 11 PE that is growing or one with an 11 PE that is slowing?</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1368876224124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 07:23:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368876743996-8</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT HIT FIVE YEAR HIGH</Title><Username>mugnmunch</Username><Timestamp>1368800003001</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 10:13:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look for an increase for the November divy. When I bought it was yielding nearly 3.5 percent and divy would keep going up. No brainer folks. Buy it put it away and look for increasing dividend checks every year.</Msg><Username>bjaythebear</Username><Timestamp>1368876743996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 07:32:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368876896122-9</Id><Topic><Title>How Many Jobs Did The Tea Party Create?</Title><Username>rightwing_fukery_hurts_usa</Username><Timestamp>1368843958533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 22:25:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The idea of a "stimulus" is by definition temporary." I'm not sure that everyone sees it that way. When I was in high school studying American history, every chapter had a summary listing legislation the Congress passed providing funds to "stimulate" this or that. That went on all through the 19th Century and the early 20th.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368876896122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 07:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368879385909-10</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft planning Xbox dashboard UI and tile changes in preparation for next-gen console (Source The Verge)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368833646355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 19:34:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new Xbox will be unveiled in two stages and release this holiday, a Microsoft executive has revealed. Microsoft's Aaron Greenberg said that the platform will be unveiled on May 21, while 'tons of exclusive games' will be shown at the E3 gaming expo. "We're really going to tell one story across two events," Greenberg told Major Nelson (via VideoGamer). "So we're going to start on the 21st, and really that's about revealing the next Xbox platform; our vision for the future of games, the future of entertainment. "We definitely have a lot of surprises planned. I know everyone knows the Infinity Ward team is hard at work on world premiering Call of Duty: Ghosts, so we're going to see what that looks like for the first time. "That's why we're inviting people to campus; we're going to bring them behind the scenes a little bit." Greenberg said that while the May 21 event is about laying the foundations, E3 will be focused on the software. "We've never done this before and so it's really exciting to be able to do that. It's a lot of laying the foundation, the best way to describe it. And then just a couple of weeks later we go to E3," he said. "E3 is all about the games. At E3, if you're a gamer, it's going to be tons of exclusives, world premieres, and obviously even beyond that we have a lot to share between then and this holiday." Reported features for the new Xbox include Kinect 2.0, 3D technology and the long-rumored Xbox TV.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368879385909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368880007414-11</Id><Topic><Title>Next week events - Xbox 720, WP-8, Surface, Cloud, Skype et al....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368831546270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IT also seems Microsoft is going to make the Xbox Extravaganza last two weeks till the Gamers' trade show, so the market excitement will take us to the end of May 2013 and get the investors and analysts all excited and focused on the "Vast Financial Impact" that Xbox-720 will have on our earnings for years to come that includes Video Streaming and Xbox-TV over and above "Exclusive Games and Features" of Xbox-720. BTW this AM I tried my X-box Music on Windows-8 and the selection and Quality is second to none. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368880007414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368881081750-12</Id><Topic><Title>How bad can the Benghazi thing be for the administration to finally throw the IRS scandal out in front of the bus?</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368852797827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 00:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's been suggested, and confirmed by some supposedly in the know that it was gun running. But I fail to see that is worse than the IRS being shown as being corrupt. Maybe they knew it was about to come out anyway and figure the people would turn to the IRS scandal and forget about Benghazi. I have to admit this administration's political abuse of the IRS is far worse than I ever imagined.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368881081750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368881639879-13</Id><Title>Still Trading at Just 11x Next Year's Estimate</Title><Msg>And MSFT is growing now. So short some more shorty. I'll see you at $50+</Msg><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1368881639879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368882244753-14</Id><Title>David and Charles Koch Buy The News to spread anti-democratic agenda</Title><Msg>David and Charles Koch have plotted a new way to spread their anti-democratic agenda: Buy our news. After spending millions distorting the truth about climate change, buying elections and using the tea party as a political tool, the Koch brothers are preparing for their next big move: Purchasing the Tribune Company, which runs newspapers across the country. We can’t let the Koch brothers turn news sources like the LA Times and Chicago Tribune into propaganda tools for corporate power. The Tribune Company needs to hear from you that any deal with the Koch brothers is a raw deal for the climate and for our democracy</Msg><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368882244753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 09:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368883053289-15</Id><Topic><Title>Next week events - Xbox 720, WP-8, Surface, Cloud, Skype et al....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368831546270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These are great input thanks for sharing. I also think that we will have more news and events in June and July running all the way to the next earnings release because we will get more press on Surface and Windows phone 8 sales numbers in US and new 25 international markets and the release of 7" Surface and more announcements on large scale windows 8 adoption by governments companies and institutions like the one Microsoft had in Texas last week with 30000 Dell tablets not to mention the new apps being announced each week. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368883053289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 09:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368883246687-16</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft planning Xbox dashboard UI and tile changes in preparation for next-gen console (Source The Verge)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368833646355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 19:34:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good news thanks and I think Microsoft has hired some good PR chiefs and is pushing all the right buttons with the customers, gaming media and investors.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368883246687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 09:20:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368883864383-17</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Courting New Developers, But Some Existing Ones Are Still Fuming Over Its Windows 8 Decisions</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368840032983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 21:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another clueless post from the resident village idiot, a high school dropout nonetheless.... You see sonny, a lot of these comments are coming from developers who moonlight as reporters as they don't have enough work and lack the skills to write code in C++, C# or in Objective-C and are used to Android's Java junk language.... Also none of these geniuses have the guts to spell out how they are going to root-out malware from Apps in a free for all open-source OS world as Intel is beginning to sense with Tizen that open source is a bad idea especially if no one is determined not to mind the shop as is the case with Goofle's Ponzi scheme. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368883864383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 09:31:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368884593964-18</Id><Topic><Title>Still Trading at Just 11x Next Year's Estimate</Title><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1368881639879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:53:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AND no one is counting the NEW revenues from Surface Pro/RT/7" replacing iPad, WP-8 getting revved up killing Android, increasing Apps inventory, monetizing Skype, Office 365 becoming standard worldwide, Cloud catching fire, Xbox going ballistic, Bing gaining market share and YES Windows 8.1 getting the job done. ADD to that the Surface Phone killing iPhone and you have the makings of a perfect storm. AS I wrote before, "when Mr. Market decides we are a growth company again", I expect P/E multiple in the range of 20-25 and you can do the math with $4-4.50 a year of earnings prospects. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368884593964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 09:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368885996602-19</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Supports Infanticide. Death Panels Next.</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368846782351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wih you, animus towards our Pres is unambiguous. those are some far out words you wrote, far out not meaning "good." No infanticide, no death panels, no nuttin' you say is right. Grandpa was already a democrat and a lot smarter than you. What are you going to do, not vote for him, or need we call the FBI as you self radicalize?</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1368885996602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368886636485-20</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Courting New Developers, But Some Existing Ones Are Still Fuming Over Its Windows 8 Decisions</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368840032983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 21:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Linux Troll article says "told Business Insider that Microsoft alienated many developers "! Well that's too bad, if they want to make a living writing software they will be compatible to MSFT software or sponge off the government like the dunce Linux trolls do.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1368886636485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368886797175-21</Id><Title>Donald Trumps I dunno</Title><Msg>He cheats people on real estate deals, gets taken to court, when on the stand is arrogant and the excuse is he can't remember and can't watch 2500 employees, no one can do that. Tea party hero. When some govt desk screws up, the GOP TP are all over Obama as if he has to have his eyes on every desk in the land. As usual double standard and the black man has to be ten times as good but still gets no respect or credit. Nothing in heaven and earth can make a TP faithful give Obama praise.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1368886797175</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:19:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368886967444-22</Id><Title>Get on this baby before it to late</Title><Msg>This baby is about to explode so don't miss out as I want as many people to make some hard cash I am not selfish so thought I share, pardon the pun</Msg><Username>meadows_field</Username><Timestamp>1368886967444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368887786570-23</Id><Title>Linux the Humping Dog</Title><Msg>The Linux desktop reminds us of a dog humping a table leg. It's both fun and disturbing to watch, but ultimately there's very little payoff from the exercise. bing it</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1368887786570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368888910229-24</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft planning Xbox dashboard UI and tile changes in preparation for next-gen console (Source The Verge)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368833646355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 19:34:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aside from all the new integration of Xbox with TV, Online Video Streaming and Cable/Satellite hookups, the most interesting development is Microsoft SmartGlass Apps integrating Xbox with Mobility devices such as Tablets and Smartphones. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368888910229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368889624668-25</Id><Title>Motley Fool</Title><Msg>Well, this must be "pump" Apple" week for these guys. Fools, you are way too obvious.</Msg><Username>applepie720</Username><Timestamp>1368889624668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 11:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368889975209-26</Id><Topic><Title>WHY Samsung Fort Knox Will NOT Work....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368752993636</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 21:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Folks there has been much speculation why all of a sudden there is no more hype on Fort Knox as it is being tested again before it goes to the Carriers for further de-bugging.... IF you remember, back in Jan 2103, DoD awarded MSFT a near $700 million contract for Windows 8 Licenses and Office 365 software et al..... SO Goofle and Android camp made some noise so the DoD later announced that Samsung Android devices will be eligible to run on DoD's IT system and that caused a lot of celebration and fanfare by Android's fanboys.... I was skeptical as we are in the middle of a Cyberwar and how in God's name we can open a back door to the Bad guys, till I read the commentary at Apple Insider that the MAIN condition is that the staff are ONLY allowed to download Apps from the DoD's own Apps store, which basically means that the smart folks at the Pentagon have forced Samsung to close the OS by using Fort Knox. SO there goes all that phony enthusiasm as Windows 8 is already approved and we will be selling a lot of WP-8 to the USG and all the related agencies. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368889975209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 11:12:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368890600337-27</Id><Topic><Title>Motley Fool</Title><Username>applepie720</Username><Timestamp>1368889624668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 11:07:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES AAPL's stock is being held up by $100 billion of buyback as MSFT is up by over 21% in the last 20 trading days after our earnings release in April, which makes it 1% per day on the average (not bad at all).... AND all this is happening while we are fighting off all the Trolls in the media and Wall Street and on a backdrop that Bill Gates selling tons of share to fund his Charity work as he has regained the title for the richest man in the world once again.... YOU see when we trade over $50.00, MSFT will be worth over $400 billion and Bill Gates over $100.00 whopping billions.... Couldn't have happened to a nicer guy! AS for Motley's, Goofle was their Pump target last week and APPL will be in the coming week. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368890600337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 11:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368890751676-28</Id><Topic><Title>Donald Trumps I dunno</Title><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1368886797175</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:19:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you at all noticed that government is descending into chaos? You have an unorganized, inexpereinced President with no managerial skills whatsoever, no experience in the real world cutting his inept teeth on our time and dime. If he had commensurate experience in the tech industry he's be laughed out of the building if he applied to be VP at IBM and yet you clueless dolts elected the failure to a second term because of hurrican Sandy and a hug from Christie..</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368890751676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 11:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368893096829-29</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Supports Infanticide. Death Panels Next.</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368846782351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As to facts: Obama voted in support of infanticide multiple times when he was in the Illinois Senate; that is an unambiguous fact! Obama is in bed with Planned Parenthood and funds them with taxpayer money. Just a few weeks ago a Planned Parenthood spokesperson testified to the Florida Legislature that infanticide is ok with them (they don't use the word, "infanticide" but that's what it is. As to "Death Panels" ... Obama calls them Independent Payer Advisory Boards. Their job is to "reduce payments to providers or eliminating payments for certain treatments and procedures altogether." These reduced payments will force providers to stop seeing Medicare patients, the same way an increased number of doctors have stopped taking Medicaid patients. This will lead to access problems, waiting lists and denied care for seniors. These death panels are made necessary because Obamacare added some 30 million new, mostly nonpaying, members to the health care system and needs a way to pay for them ... so he is raiding Medicare directly and through devices such as these death panels.</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368893096829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 12:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368893481347-30</Id><Topic><Title>What ... No Scandal ???</Title><Username>cyber_critiqer</Username><Timestamp>1368892074215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 11:47:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They pick what they like to hear, and change the meaning of it if they don't like it. We all know that method from the Hawcreek12 Team. Trying to reason with them is like throwing sand into the ocean and trying to see the effects on the water level. They never change. There was no scandal on any of it. Obama has done nothing wrong, is doing it all very well, and is probably the most honest, well qualified, President in 200 years.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1368893481347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 12:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368894077666-31</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Supports Infanticide. Death Panels Next.</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368846782351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't do "Rush" ... nor anyone else. You confirmed Lefties don't understand that it's ok to think independently and speak uncomfortable/unpopular truths.</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368894077666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 12:21:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368894119184-32</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Supports Infanticide. Death Panels Next.</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368846782351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repeat, your animus towards our President is unambiguous. You're apparently too lazy to go to health care org and quote real facts from the law. If you did that you would have no story to tell to support your Animus towards Barackabas Obamanous. You prefer to concoct dishonest, misleading, and ridiculous sentences without merit.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1368894119184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 12:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368895193276-33</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Supports Infanticide. Death Panels Next.</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368846782351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sorry you can't see the truth in these matters. It is simply a fact that Obama voted in support of infanticide when he was in the Illinois Senate; no amount of name calling or denial can change that fact. It is also simply a fact that he supports and admires Planned Parenthood whose spokesperson recently testified to the Florida Legislature that they are ok with infanticide. It is also a fact that Obamacare includes "Independent Payment Advisory Board" whose duty is to reduce or eliminate medicare payments to make up for the costs incurred by the 30 million new, non-paying members added by Obama. Clearly this massive level of reduced funds will lead to death sentences for many elderly people ... hence the IPAB is a death panel.</Msg><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368895193276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 12:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368895482994-34</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Supports Infanticide. Death Panels Next.</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368846782351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's but one example of many, Jimmy, that ObamaCare TAKES AWAY "Death Panels" by removing the previous cap on your lifetime benefits insurers used to have. That part is already in effect and I am glad it is. Nothing worse than a private insurance adjuster telling you so sad so sorry as you hit your limit and you are in the hospital. In conclusion, you're just ticked the Pres got elected, and are the type that never changes their opinion on anything. Case closed.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1368895482994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 12:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368896925441-35</Id><Topic><Title>Linux the Humping Dog</Title><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1368887786570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy a clue.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368896925441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 13:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368897066185-36</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Courting New Developers, But Some Existing Ones Are Still Fuming Over Its Windows 8 Decisions</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368840032983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 21:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More boilerplate from the resident bot.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368897066185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 13:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368897632485-37</Id><Title>S. Carolina: Haley Leaves Health Law to U.S. as Residents Remain Uninsured</Title><Msg>Advocates for the 900,000 uninsured people in South Carolina say that thousands may not be able to enroll because the state isn’t helping implement the exchange. While the Obama administration says all exchanges will open on time Oct. 1 to cover as many as 27 million people, success in reaching them may depend on states’ willingness to help. Those states are exhibiting a continuum of cooperation. “We have seen no real attempts for the state to work with the federal government at all,” Sue Berkowitz, director of the South Carolina Appleseed Legal Justice Center, a Columbia nonprofit helping the poor, said in an interview. “Not working with the feds is, in itself, a hostile move to keep people from being able to benefit.” **************************************************** SCREW THE POOR! RIGHT TEA PARTY?</Msg><Username>earl_of_del_rey</Username><Timestamp>1368897632485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 13:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368898000208-38</Id><Topic><Title>sleeping giant still rubbing its eyes</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1366826921039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 14:08:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>together-zoommmmmmmmmmm</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1368898000208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 13:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368899631942-39</Id><Topic><Title>What ... No Scandal ???</Title><Username>cyber_critiqer</Username><Timestamp>1368892074215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 11:47:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the Scandals come from the "conservative media". That darn Sean Hannity wouldn't send help in Benghazi, and allowed the IRS to target conservative groups, and tapped the AP phones...oh wait, all that happened in fact on Obama's watch, meaning, per hawcrapper rules, Obama is 100% responsible. You see, hawcraper the scandals in fact belong to Obama, the conservative press is just reporting them, now including some mainstream press...all of which is causing the Obama regime to slide into the political abyss borne of it's own dishonesty and incompetence...which is why they authorized overtime for your posts this weekend.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368899631942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 13:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368900389359-40</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Courting New Developers, But Some Existing Ones Are Still Fuming Over Its Windows 8 Decisions</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368840032983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 21:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not that any of them are paying any attention to you, but that is evidently the official attitude Microsoft has displayed up to now, and that is one of the major reasons Windows 8 is such a flop up to now, and especially the reason Microsoft Store has been such a flop. Microsoft management used to understand that Microsoft needs its community of independent developers more than they need Microsoft. If management no longer understands that, well, that is just one more sign that Microsoft is being seriously mismanaged.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368900389359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 14:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368901069171-41</Id><Topic><Title>Linux the Humping Dog</Title><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1368887786570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You remind us of wally-the-kibax.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1368901069171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 14:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368901164957-42</Id><Topic><Title>Linux the Humping Dog</Title><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1368887786570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, too ladylike for wally...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368901164957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 14:19:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368903545250-43</Id><Topic><Title>Linux the Humping Dog</Title><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1368887786570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very good analogy, just like the Sux shills that always insist on pestering honest MSFT investors by posting their trash on the wrong MB, wonton is the dog &amp; heretwat is the table leg.LOL</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368903545250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 14:59:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368904479484-44</Id><Topic><Title>Next week events - Xbox 720, WP-8, Surface, Cloud, Skype et al....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368831546270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And of course Windows 8.1 aka Windows Blue release due on June 26/2013 so to silence all the Windows 8 bashers and some.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368904479484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:14:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368906232732-45</Id><Title>This Hedge Fund Star Just Dumped Microsoft to Load Up on Apple</Title><Msg>Google it... Quoting: "Few hedge fund managers garner the type of attention that David Einhorn does just by opening his mouth. The Greenlight Capital manager's name has even become a verb. No investor wants his stocks to get "Einhorned," which is what happens when Einhorn takes a publicly bearish stance against a company, typically preceded by a short position. "Einhorn also has no qualms about criticizing companies that he's bullish on and has sizable stakes in, famously bashing Microsoft (NASDAQ: MSFT ) CEO Steve Ballmer in 2011. Just Einhorn's suggestion that Ballmer should step down sparked a rally. ... ... Well, Einhorn just dumped a major chunk of his Microsoft position while loading up on Apple in the first quarter. ...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368906232732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368906911495-46</Id><Topic><Title>This Hedge Fund Star Just Dumped Microsoft to Load Up on Apple</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368906232732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:43:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another stupid post from the flunky village idiot.... Einhorn was pimping AAPL at $700 and bashing MSFT at the same time.... SO he is losing his shirt on AAPL and was dumb enough to get out of MSFT at the wrong time as we are up 21% in 20 trading days, averaging over 1% per day.... SO the evidence shows he has made the wrong call and the media Trolls are using a proven wrong move to celebrate his bad judgement..... Kind of stupid and strange.... Einhorn has been in a #$%$ match with Ballmer, but as iPad and iPhone sales plummet in the next two quarters and AAPL trades around $200.00, he similar to Heather Bellini will be eating a lot of crow. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368906911495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368907185814-47</Id><Title>Apple Price Target: $50 Stock By 2016</Title><Msg>Downtrend still intact It is official Apple is one weak stock right now. It is supposed to be a tell when the market is up, and your down considerably to the tune of 3%. The Jim Cramer tax selling notion can now be dispelled as well. This is the new year, and for Apple shareholders the misery of the third quarter is repeating itself. bing it</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1368907185814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:59:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368907287626-48</Id><Topic><Title>sleeping giant still rubbing its eyes</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1366826921039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 14:08:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its moving</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1368907287626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 16:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368907406363-49</Id><Topic><Title>Next week events - Xbox 720, WP-8, Surface, Cloud, Skype et al....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368831546270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$45 next week, then $50 in two weeks. Off to $75 by xmas. This company has been dormant too long, on a verge of break out. w8 is an amazing software, very different from the previous msft softwares. Consumers are slowly adopting to w8, but the secret to its sucess is that no computer makers are making new machines with Windows 7 or older. Every company is making new computers with ONLY W8(verify with Best buys and Fry's E) . This tactic is to flush out all the old computers and enforce new computers buying, bad for consumers but good for computer makers. the new xbox, using hand motion to control keys and gaming is gonna be amazing. It is not just a gaming console but a center piece in every living room in the world, where internet, movies, music can be accessed. Multiple programs can be opened at once, where Dad can watch TV, while Mom surf the net, and Son blasts his Street fighter video game away with his friends. Hold on to your shares or add more. The tide has turned for msft</Msg><Username>kevinvests</Username><Timestamp>1368907406363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 16:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368908714218-50</Id><Title>The world will go nuts when Msft's market cap reaches a trillion</Title><Msg>Apple almost succeed, now msft will make that attempt. If you missed your chance of msft run 20 years ago, here is your chance.</Msg><Username>microsoftd1ck</Username><Timestamp>1368908714218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 16:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368910178840-51</Id><Topic><Title>Next week events - Xbox 720, WP-8, Surface, Cloud, Skype et al....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368831546270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see it the same way. $40 is in the bag now. This is a moneymaker with lots of room for entry now. We are talking fortunes being made.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1368910178840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 16:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368910389836-52</Id><Topic><Title>Get on this baby before it to late</Title><Username>meadows_field</Username><Timestamp>1368886967444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:22:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a one time opportunity to make fortunes that will be life-altering. Those that hesitate will kick themselves for the rest of their lives. How much more do they need to know? Every dollar that MSFT climbs is a dollar higher they will have to pay and a dollar per share they lose.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1368910389836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 16:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368910665297-53</Id><Topic><Title>David and Charles Koch Buy The News to spread anti-democratic agenda</Title><Username>lordbalzy</Username><Timestamp>1368882244753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 09:04:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lord I hope so. At least they use their own money,. the IRS uses the money from those who pay taxes and their salaries to screw them over. POS's</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1368910665297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 16:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368911412379-54</Id><Topic><Title>This Hedge Fund Star Just Dumped Microsoft to Load Up on Apple</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368906232732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:43:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More boilerplate from the village bot...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368911412379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 17:10:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368912305319-55</Id><Title>IRS concealed probe into targeting conservatives until AFTER the election</Title><Msg>Concealing such an investigation is in itself political, this is the most corrupt administration in American History and the underlings are following the corrupt leadership they see up the ladder.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368912305319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 17:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368912804545-56</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Supports Infanticide. Death Panels Next.</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368846782351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I see the truth very well. No legislator in the history of America has voted for infanticide. You have brainwashed yourself so so badly on this Obama quest. "whose duty is to reduce or eliminate medicare payments to make up for the costs incurred by the 30 million new, non-paying members added by Obama." Oh, really? Someone is paid to do that in their job description? Even they must make sure it's to offset what's "added by Obama?"That's wacky to say, let alone believe. Very wacky. There are no death panels, they don't exist. Medicare has always monitored payments, and always will. Of course, they have to do that. You have been alive long enough to know limits on your health plan have caused many people to lose their life's savings abd reduced them to poverty. Go to the site and read about Obamacare, it helps prevent that. Opposite to what you believe, there's the truth of the matter.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368912804545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 17:33:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368913365681-57</Id><Title>So David Einhorn is the Dumb Money on Apple (Source Zero Hedge)....</Title><Msg>THE village idiot posted another dumb article today and here is a great take on how wrong Einhorn was and still is on APPL (here is an interesting excerpt): "This was the more revealing takeaway from David Einhorn`s whining on CNBC over his stuck Apple position, and throwing Amazon under the bus in the process. The more these guys go on air, whether it is Carl Icahn, Bill Ackman, or David Einhorn the less attractive these guys appear for managing money. For an activist that is so fond of finding good short ideas, the fact that David Einhorn and Greenlight Capital happened to miss the best short setup of the year is hilarious, and it is not something I would want to advertise on CNBC. The bigger question to come out of all of this Apple Cash nonsense is why didn`t Greenlight Capital sell out of their entire position at $700 a share? The next question is why wasn`t GreenLight Capital shorting Apple at $700 a share? Did they view Apple as a Growth or value opportunity at over $700 a share?" Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368913365681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 17:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368913568113-58</Id><Title>IRSLawsuit</Title><Msg>IRSLawsuit is huge or little?</Msg><Username>bearishinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1368913568113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 17:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368913956738-59</Id><Topic><Title>Next week events - Xbox 720, WP-8, Surface, Cloud, Skype et al....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368831546270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have looked at Mr. Softy for 10 years and listened to investors complaining about the stock's performance along the way till early in 2013 as my value model alerted me that MSFT is a screaming STRONG BUY and I took a substantial position at $26.50.... THEN I bought Windows-8 with Intel's i5 processor from DELL and what a great set up.... IF anyone uses Windows 8, they will NOT touch anything else as it is fast, secure, and has great sound and video with excellent features and Apps. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368913956738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 17:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368915240202-60</Id><Title>Android threats to top one million by year's end....</Title><Msg>Security firm Trend Micro has predicted the number of threats targeting the Android mobile operating system will pass the one million mark by the end of 2013. The increase would represent a near tripling of the number of threats currently known to be targeting Android. Trend Micro reported that at the end of 2012 it had detected roughly 350,000 threats targeting Google's operating system. The figure means that it has taken Android just three years to boast the same number of threats it took Windows XP 14 years to reach. "2012 was a year of real evolution in traditional threat and evolution into new platforms and geographies," said Trend Micro vice president of security research, Rik Ferguson.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368915240202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 18:14:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368918087747-61</Id><Topic><Title>The world will go nuts when Msft's market cap reaches a trillion</Title><Username>microsoftd1ck</Username><Timestamp>1368908714218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 16:25:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd put it this way: If MSFT's market cap ever reaches a trillion, the world will have gone nuts.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368918087747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 19:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368918629910-62</Id><Topic><Title>Android threats to top one million by year's end....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368915240202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 18:14:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The figure means that it has taken Android just three years to boast the same number of threats it took Windows XP 14 years to reach." Um, no. The number of "threats" to XP is probably more like 8 million, according to Symantec. It's been doubling every few months for the past few years. I don't keep close track of it, there's no point. The excuse that softie shills used to give was that of course the bad guys went after XP, because it was so dominant, that's what it paid to attack. By contrast, there was little point in attacking MacOS or Linux, as so few people used it. The same argument, if it was ever valid, would apply now to Android.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368918629910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 19:10:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368919833279-63</Id><Topic><Title>Android threats to top one million by year's end....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368915240202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 18:14:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another dumb post from the village idiot.... THE $500 billion question is that MSFT has taken ownership of its software and protected its users be it the XP, Vista or W-7, while Goofle and Android lackies are no were to be found.... AND that is why Windows 8 was developed to do away with all malware, virus protection and all that Jazz. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368919833279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 19:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368919974433-64</Id><Topic><Title>sleeping giant still rubbing its eyes</Title><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1366826921039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 14:08:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>raise that to 40s</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1368919974433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 19:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368920211738-65</Id><Topic><Title>Android threats to top one million by year's end....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368915240202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 18:14:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More boilerplate from the resident bot...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368920211738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 19:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368920408698-66</Id><Topic><Title>The world will go nuts when Msft's market cap reaches a trillion</Title><Username>microsoftd1ck</Username><Timestamp>1368908714218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 16:25:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd say M$FT has laid the foundation for that event to happen &amp; sooner than you think too IMO.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368920408698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 19:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368920682451-67</Id><Topic><Title>Android threats to top one million by year's end....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368915240202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 18:14:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That little sux shill #$%$ ant wonton has been tying to pump infected GOOG junk on the MSFT board long enough !</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1368920682451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 19:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368921764928-68</Id><Topic><Title>So David Einhorn is the Dumb Money on Apple (Source Zero Hedge)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368913365681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 17:42:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Einhorn is a hypster and knows nothing about tech as he has shown with his moves on Apple. He got lucky with Lehman and is a hero in his own mind.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368921764928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 20:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368921918779-69</Id><Topic><Title>This Hedge Fund Star Just Dumped Microsoft to Load Up on Apple</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368906232732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 15:43:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's right another boilerplate of facts.... Just read Zero Hedge and see how they are lampooning your hero! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368921918779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 20:05:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368922337612-70</Id><Topic><Title>Folks: Noodles has been renamed to Poodles for....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368576961555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:16:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poodles is missing in action! Sounds like he was fired after his employers got a margin call and jumped off the Windows 8 platform. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368922337612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 20:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368922931553-71</Id><Topic><Title>Motley Fool</Title><Username>applepie720</Username><Timestamp>1368889624668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 11:07:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a great post. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368922931553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 20:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368923132597-72</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Supports Infanticide. Death Panels Next.</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368846782351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember, infanticide, filicide, viricide, sorocide, euxorcide, are all against the law...</Msg><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1368923132597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 20:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368927815060-73</Id><Topic><Title>IRS concealed probe into targeting conservatives until AFTER the election</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1368912305319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 17:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Find out where Obama ordered the IRS to do anything. Without that you are witch hunting. Can a President order the IRS to do something? Can you imagine all the little rwnj IRS whistles watching that? President Obama, "Boys and girls, you need to target the Tea party." "Yes sir master sir your honor sir" sez the IRS back. Defies logic the whole whacky idea.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1368927815060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 21:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368927821083-74</Id><Topic><Title>Still Trading at Just 11x Next Year's Estimate</Title><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1368881639879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:53:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The next 8 weeks are action packed for Microsoft starting on May 21 with Xbox-720 launch and the rest will be history when Microsoft releases its next quarterly earnings. $50 in July is quite achievable. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368927821083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 21:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368928033321-75</Id><Topic><Title>The shorts are pinning their hopes on a market correction, but....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368819691738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 15:41:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only stock repurchase here is done by short sellers or else.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368928033321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 21:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368928502567-76</Id><Topic><Title>Man were all the professional analysts, tv commentators &amp; shorts wrong onu this one.</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1368827816383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 17:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think they started playing trolls and trashed windows 8, then they believed their own lies and then Bang. I still think there is 200 million shares short since the financial times started making things up a weeks ago and we will have a good squeeze this week to get a clean slate after Xbox-720 mega event.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1368928502567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 21:55:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368928846999-77</Id><Topic><Title>Linux the Humping Dog</Title><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1368887786570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 10:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 reminds me of a room so dark, you end up sticking it in the wrong hole.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1368928846999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 22:00:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368928928739-78</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: Obama Supports Infanticide. Death Panels Next.</Title><Username>kinderjimmy9</Username><Timestamp>1368846782351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:13:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This post has been flagged as inapropriate.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1368928928739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 22:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368929020006-79</Id><Topic><Title>What ... No Scandal ???</Title><Username>cyber_critiqer</Username><Timestamp>1368892074215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 11:47:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you won't see the 'real' news until it's de-classified.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1368929020006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 22:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>