<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-28"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359358653077-1</Id><Title>China considering end to 13-year ban on video game consoles: report</Title><Msg>SHANGHAI (Reuters) - China is considering lifting a decade-long ban on video game consoles, the official China Daily newspaper reported on Monday, sending shares of major hardware makers such as Sony Corp and Nintendo Co Ltd surging. In November, Sony's PlayStation 3 received a quality certification from a Chinese safety standards body, prompting speculation that Beijing would lift the ban, which the government said was imposed in 2000 to safeguard children's mental and physical development. "We are reviewing the policy and have conducted some surveys and held discussions with other ministries on the possibility of opening up the game console market," the China Daily quoted an unnamed source from the Ministry of Culture as saying. "However, since the ban was issued by seven ministries more than a decade ago, we will need approval from all parties to lift it." An official at the ministry's cultural market department, which is responsible for the legislation, denied the report. "The ministry is not considering lifting the ban," the official, who identified himself only as Bai, told Reuters.</Msg><Username>dell_stk</Username><Timestamp>1359358653077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 02:37:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359364413680-2</Id><Title>Surface RT at Best Buy on line sold out</Title><Msg>this could be a good sign that Surface computers are gain nice traction. also, Surface computers are heading to Cosco, and Surface Pros are launching in about 10 days!!!! No wonder, Bill Gates was saying late Friday - Win 8 and Surface are doing well!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359364413680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 04:13:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359364638491-3</Id><Topic><Title>500 Million Windows XP MUST migrate to Windows 7 or 8 in 12 months....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359247110947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expect sale and profit contributions from this masive transiton to be a huge driver for MSFt shares over coming year. Also, new products like WIn8 and Surface computers and new Offcie are positioning MSFT for 10-20% bottom line expansion over coming 1-5 years!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359364638491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 04:17:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359364723285-4</Id><Topic><Title>Prediction of Direction of MSFT shares on 1/28/13?</Title><Username>johntjohnt_2000</Username><Timestamp>1359333519492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:38:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i am expecting msft to reach 30 around Feb. 10, 2013!!!! New Surface Pro and new Office!!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359364723285</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 04:18:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359369873795-5</Id><Topic><Title>Osama was offered to Clinton at least 6 times before 9/11</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1359332611373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:23:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>False.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1359369873795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 05:44:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359375820554-6</Id><Topic><Title>World's First Microsoft® Mediaroom</Title><Username>edwinabertawdmyhjna7520</Username><Timestamp>1302456627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-04-10 13:30:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just joined too.</Msg><Username>williamharry708</Username><Timestamp>1359375820554</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 07:23:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359381668945-7</Id><Topic><Title>500 Million Windows XP MUST migrate to Windows 7 or 8 in 12 months....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359247110947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Add to that a growing economy in the US, China and soon Europe and we will have a great year.... It is also worth noting that for each $1 of Rev. our Earnings gain 90 Cents and that is a huge profit margin as "all" the development costs have already been absorbed.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359381668945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:01:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359382132846-8</Id><Topic><Title>Osama was offered to Clinton at least 6 times before 9/11</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1359332611373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:23:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not really. Clinton didn't want to pay for, and take on terrorism at its early stage which would have saved the country trillions of dollars. Allowing terrorism to build out its intrastructure around the world has created a monumental task for the Western World. That an liberalism always fails pathetically at the ground level. Liberalism depends on lawyer lying at the top that easily sways the masses of their ignorant base members....politely called the non-informed.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359382132846</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:08:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359382418484-9</Id><Topic><Title>500 Million Windows XP MUST migrate to Windows 7 or 8 in 12 months....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359247110947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is awesome, MSFT can easily double in next 1-2 years.</Msg><Username>dell_stk</Username><Timestamp>1359382418484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:13:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359382571769-10</Id><Title>Remember China the bad guy</Title><Msg>as described by liberals? Liberals said we should not do business with China. Forget that their inexpensive products were desperately needed by the poor, and even the middle class to stretch their disposable dollars, and create wealth. It was about protectionism for union workers. Now China is in a recession, and is having difficutly getting out of a recession because of the terrible economy created by Obama, and the left forcing us deep in debt. China needs the USA as an important consumer of their products, and our dollars are going to service our huge debt, that Obama wants to INCREASE with higher spending! The thing that can bring on a world war.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359382571769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:16:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359382928684-11</Id><Topic><Title>Remember China the bad guy</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359382571769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repubs lost demos won,4 more years! live with it hawkfreak.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1359382928684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:22:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359383478379-12</Id><Topic><Title>Sueface Computers are now heading to Cosco</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359295136431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 08:58:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"you are like a hemmorhoid that never goes away, a pain in the azs" That's right, I'm not going away, bozo. Good to know it bothers you. "no one cares...." Contradicting yourself, bozo. You just now told me that YOU care.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1359383478379</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:31:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359383815675-13</Id><Topic><Title>Just watched Koch funded NOVA on Doomsday Volcanoes</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1359338143729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:55:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rignt on. Not to to mention that we are long overdue for Yellowstone megavolcano eruption.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1359383815675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:36:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359384165352-14</Id><Title>Windows 8 pro</Title><Msg>Just curios, have any shareholders actually used windows 8? What the hell is going on at Microsoft? I read the reviews and they were mostly horror stories. I figured I'd upgrade one of my systems and see what the fuss was all about. It's bad. Really really bad. My opinion. If you haven't actually worked with the new OS, I urge you to do so as an investor. This is worse than vista.</Msg><Username>applesupertramp</Username><Timestamp>1359384165352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:42:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359385077110-15</Id><Title>MSFT recent update</Title><Msg>Huge Gains, Multi Day Runs and Legendary Picks! paste to your browser-- http://finance.yahoo.com/mbview/threadview/?&amp;bn=30ec85b4-d1ce-32fe-a71c-f56c94fe758b&amp;tid=1359384851669-dc48a0cd-2a0f-4b62-9c60-0c2812dda1cf</Msg><Username>knilffucashley</Username><Timestamp>1359385077110</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:57:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359385180695-16</Id><Topic><Title>Dubya Bush Got Out Smareted By Osama On 9/11/2001. Obama Is Smarter Than America's Enemies.</Title><Username>monsignor_whiteowl</Username><Timestamp>1359384419504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:46:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have inside information: The Libyan ambassador told his staff, "Don't worry fellas. President Obama will protect us. After all, he is Commander in Chief".</Msg><Username>lrseab</Username><Timestamp>1359385180695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:59:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359385373777-17</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT recent update</Title><Username>knilffucashley</Username><Timestamp>1359385077110</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:57:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee, guy. You are recommending that web site????? Does your mother know what you are up to?</Msg><Username>lrseab</Username><Timestamp>1359385373777</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:02:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359386367326-18</Id><Topic><Title>Dubya Bush Got Out Smareted By Osama On 9/11/2001. Obama Is Smarter Than America's Enemies.</Title><Username>monsignor_whiteowl</Username><Timestamp>1359384419504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:46:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me understand. Bill Clinton lets our guard down. Al Qaeda organizes under his watch and whacks us on 9/11 under GWB’s watch. GWB then whacks al Qaeda in Afghanistan. Some group fire bombs the American embassy in Libya and kills the American ambassador and three other Americans. Obama scratches his head and asks Hillary, “Do you know who did this?” “Gee, no. I haven’t a clue. Who knows? Maybe it was a bunch of rowdies who got bored watching YouTube”. I’ll bet if Obama ever finds out who killed our ambassador, he will give a tough speech and will warn them that they better not try that again!</Msg><Username>lrseab</Username><Timestamp>1359386367326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:19:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359386608307-19</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 pro</Title><Username>applesupertramp</Username><Timestamp>1359384165352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:42:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I use WIN8 &amp; it's a great OS,comparing WIN8 to Vista IMO proves you're a real dummkopf.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1359386608307</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:23:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359386621165-20</Id><Topic><Title>Just watched Koch funded NOVA on Doomsday Volcanoes</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1359338143729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 20:55:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sound reasoning, since there are other dangers we cannot control then there is no point in trying to control the ones we can. Lets just dump our nuclear waste into the Mississippi river.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359386621165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:23:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359386734309-21</Id><Topic><Title>Any time the market rises under a prograssive president it must be maniipulated</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359161678918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 19:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anything other than old white men in charge</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359386734309</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:25:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359386934121-22</Id><Topic><Title>People who like Presidents who ignore the Constitution like Lincoln and Obama</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1359324205362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now we see more of the true Hawfeeces. The Confederacy, and segregation, feels good to him, boy. Sorry, Sherman isn't my hero, wrong yet again. You proved nothing. You never prve anything with your half told, words picked out of context, ramblings. Quarter told. Explain Pres Obama's violation of the Constitution, let's see how much you leave out. Of course the Supremes need to decide, before the acusation is settled. That's how it works in my country. Start with the notion of the legitimacy, and need, of Presidential apointments. Anyone reading about the matter in a truthful way, will conclude Obama, as always, was right on.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1359386934121</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:28:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359387291127-23</Id><Title>Get latest Information on PLSB</Title><Msg>PLSB has been on the uptrend from .40-70 and is looking to really catch steam. I'm initiating a long position as they are a LEGITIMATE company with good #'s. There have been buyout talks and its one year Target has been set at $4-5.</Msg><Username>knilffucashley</Username><Timestamp>1359387291127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:34:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359387430040-24</Id><Title>good news on MMGW</Title><Msg>Actual scientific study provides evidence that warming may not be as severe as initially predicted. ""Bayesian estimation of climate sensitivity based on a simple climate model fitted to observations of hemispheric temperatures and global ocean heat content"" The analysis uses the short period of time where warming has appeared to level off as brought up by hawcreek. However this work is done by actual scientists. I bet a dollar creek cannot define Bayesian without copy and pasting from wiki.. Still this is one hopeful paper among the mass of less optimistic papers. Gee if all scientists are for hire as the mmgw deniers suggest i wonder who paid for this study??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359387430040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:37:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359388258247-25</Id><Title>We will close above $30.00 this week on our way to....</Title><Msg>$50.00 a share. Stay tuned as the market wakes up and smells the $$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359388258247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:50:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359388295478-26</Id><Topic><Title>Remember China the bad guy</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359382571769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney was on a course, day one he said, to destroy relations with China with his stupidity. At the same moment, literally, his company was closing a plant in Illinois and shipping it to China, 170 workers lost their jobs. Meanwile, in the same very town in Illinois, Pres Obama saved 1000 jobs due to restricting cheap Chinese tires. I remember looking at tires a couple years ago, and saw made in China. I asked for not made in China. The only one losing money was the tire retailer, the cost was just as high for me as a US made tire, and less quality. That made in China lettering is not easy to see on black rubber, most people would take what the retailer talks them in to. Pres Obama, being the patriot he is, fixed that a lot, and his focus is on the truth of the matter, not politics for elections. You see, feeces, you're wrong yet again. So early in your prime time posting week too.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1359388295478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:51:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359390611181-27</Id><Topic><Title>Remember China the bad guy</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359382571769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A conversation between the president of Solyndra and Obama: “Mr. President, our company needs some money” “How much do you need?” “About a half billion dollars” “Why don’t you try to get the money from private investors?” “We did, but they tell us that it is a terrible investment.” “OK. I’ll reach in the pockets of taxpayers and give it to you. After all, its only play money. But you have to contribute to my campaign big-time. ,” “No problem, Mr. President.”</Msg><Username>lrseab</Username><Timestamp>1359390611181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:30:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359390681597-28</Id><Topic><Title>good news on MMGW</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359387430040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:37:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Warming, shwarming, global warming happens, just not man induced global warming. That was exposed as a lie via factual data many times over. Liberals will now move on to another scam to fund their socialism, and corruption.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359390681597</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:31:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359390815927-29</Id><Topic><Title>People who like Presidents who ignore the Constitution like Lincoln and Obama</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1359324205362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has violated the constitution for fascist reasons. Quite diffrerent than the Constitution that Lincoln upheld.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359390815927</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:33:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359390982571-30</Id><Topic><Title>People who like Presidents who ignore the Constitution like Lincoln and Obama</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1359324205362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:03:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You point it out clearly. The Pres was right on. The Repubs are violating. The Pres has the right, just like the white Pres's, to appont. There are no White's Only Presidential appts, and I don't think you read past the faux news headlines because you can't explain. Supremes will say. What'd your imaginary wife have at McD's this AM? And when did you take her? Because you are always here. Thanks for answering to the name Hawfeces, feeces.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1359390982571</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:36:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359391109017-31</Id><Title>Is there a minute in a day when Feeces isn't here posting?</Title><Msg>That's my nickname for him now, hope it sticks. He answers to it. Hawr hawr hawrfeeces</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1359391109017</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:38:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359391226043-32</Id><Topic><Title>good news on MMGW</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359387430040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:37:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The climate has been in a continuous change for billions of years, but something remarkable is happening. In this decade, man now has the ability to prevent the climate from changing simply by shutting down American manufacturing. If fact, we can prevent climate change without the need to shut down manufacturing in India and China. That Obama is one smart dude.</Msg><Username>lrseab</Username><Timestamp>1359391226043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:40:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359391965452-33</Id><Title>Get latest Information on PLSB</Title><Msg>PLSB is likely to double short term and be worth $3-5+ mid term. They have revenues, a hot sexy product, great packaging and just everything going for them.</Msg><Username>knilffucashley</Username><Timestamp>1359391965452</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:52:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359392687465-34</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 pro</Title><Username>applesupertramp</Username><Timestamp>1359384165352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 09:42:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another dissatisfied customer! Funny how MSFT won't admit how bad Windows 8 sales really are.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1359392687465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:04:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359392894862-35</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT at Best Buy on line sold out</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359364413680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 04:13:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More likely that Surface RT tablets were discontinued and Best Buy won't stock them anymore.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1359392894862</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:08:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359392980770-36</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft problems are over , but for how long ?</Title><Username>myers.marlene</Username><Timestamp>1359392335176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 is a BIG problem for Microsoft. Nobody wants it.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1359392980770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:09:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359393047221-37</Id><Topic><Title>500 Million Windows XP MUST migrate to Windows 7 or 8 in 12 months....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359247110947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2013 is our YEAR, STOCK PILE UP MSFT.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1359393047221</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359393186135-38</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft problems are over , but for how long ?</Title><Username>myers.marlene</Username><Timestamp>1359392335176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A person's or a company's problems are over when it dies. Good to hear you think Microsoft is dead.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1359393186135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:13:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359393583748-39</Id><Title>News - Windows 8 is currently the fourth most popular OS in the world</Title><Msg>Win 8 doubters will be big losers!!! Windows 8 has managed to overtake Mac OS X 10.8 to become the fourth most popular operating system in the world, according to figures provided by Net Applications for the week of January 20. While Windows 7 continues to be the king of the OS world with a share of 45.77 percent, Windows XP has lost a few points to eventually reach 38.18 percent. Windows Vista takes the third place with 5.01 percent, while Windows 8 comes next with 2.45 percent. One week ago, Windows 8 had a market share of 2.25 percent, while Mac OS X posted a share of 2.43 percent, according to data released by the same company.</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359393583748</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:19:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359393678594-40</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft problems are over , but for how long ?</Title><Username>myers.marlene</Username><Timestamp>1359392335176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of my stocks have big problems or I would not have purchased them. And that is why I bought this last week. Some time back I sold (slowly) all my PCYC because it really looks like they have something big against blood cancers. I do not need the headache of owning a stock with bright prospects. Bought it yrs ago following crash after a drug trial went bad.</Msg><Username>x2073</Username><Timestamp>1359393678594</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:21:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359393875749-41</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT at Best Buy on line sold out</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359364413680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 04:13:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all other Surface models are in stock at Best Buy, so your theory cannot be true. I think Best Buy woudl love to stockk their upcomignsurface Pro like mad!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359393875749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:24:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359394332536-42</Id><Title>nice price action</Title><Msg>Its good. Ofcourse charts are useless but it is still nice to see what is going on.</Msg><Username>x2073</Username><Timestamp>1359394332536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:32:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359394357303-43</Id><Title>Short at $28.20</Title><Msg>MSFT goes up too quick, so I am betting that it will drops down to the mid $26 range again. I will cover for a small profit around $27.00 - $27.50 range.</Msg><Username>whatever_if_u_say_so</Username><Timestamp>1359394357303</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:32:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359394483374-44</Id><Topic><Title>Short at $28.20</Title><Username>whatever_if_u_say_so</Username><Timestamp>1359394357303</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:32:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why not @ 28.23 uuu missed da three sense eh</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1359394483374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:34:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359394575042-45</Id><Topic><Title>nice price action</Title><Username>x2073</Username><Timestamp>1359394332536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:32:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>30s 3 months out div increase in 2013</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1359394575042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:36:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359394673335-46</Id><Topic><Title>nice price action</Title><Username>x2073</Username><Timestamp>1359394332536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:32:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>especially when the nice price action has been the case for quite a few days now. in fact, the stock has bottomed out since it otuched base at about 26.5. if the bottoming out is true, we should be able to reach 30 or so , hopefulkly before Feb. 9!!!! Earnings are great and series of new products are driving massiev growth. Street are expecting eps groth over comig two quaters at more than 15% yoy!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359394673335</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:37:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359394822014-47</Id><Topic><Title>Short at $28.20</Title><Username>whatever_if_u_say_so</Username><Timestamp>1359394357303</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:32:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good luck. however, i think the momentum is massivley against you!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359394822014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:40:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359394870701-48</Id><Topic><Title>Joseph Goebbels, Secret Billionaires &amp; Their Parellel With The Koch Bros</Title><Username>monsignor_whiteowl</Username><Timestamp>1359391356785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:42:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By definition, the son of a Muslim father is a Muslim. Not that there's anything wrong with that. Is there?</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1359394870701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:41:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359394939407-49</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft problems are over , but for how long ?</Title><Username>myers.marlene</Username><Timestamp>1359392335176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>News out today show Win 8 now the 4th most popular operation system worldwide, even though WIn 8 is out only 3 months ago. Win 8 doubters will be big losers for sure!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359394939407</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:42:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359394984452-50</Id><Topic><Title>Joseph Goebbels, Secret Billionaires &amp; Their Parellel With The Koch Bros</Title><Username>monsignor_whiteowl</Username><Timestamp>1359391356785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:42:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Islam is a religion, moe. Father is a Muslim but the son was raised christian, moe.</Msg><Username>bogglepuffer</Username><Timestamp>1359394984452</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:43:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359395110263-51</Id><Topic><Title>We will close above $30.00 this week on our way to....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359388258247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your thinkging has good logic. S&amp;P 500 has average pe about 17 times. MSFt forward earnings at 3.2 over coming year, so 17 x 3.2 = $55!!!! It is just amazing how wrongly the street is trading MSFt shares. Buying here is like an opportunity of a life time!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359395110263</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:45:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359395176794-52</Id><Topic><Title>Joseph Goebbels, Secret Billionaires &amp; Their Parellel With The Koch Bros</Title><Username>monsignor_whiteowl</Username><Timestamp>1359391356785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:42:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like all monotheistic religions, Islam is an exclusive faith. As the son of the Muslim father, Senator Obama was born a Muslim under Muslim law as it is universally understood. It makes no difference that, as Senator Obama has written, his father said he renounced his religion. Likewise, under Muslim law based on the Koran his mother’s Christian background is irrelevant. -NY Times</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1359395176794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:46:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359395504554-53</Id><Topic><Title>Joseph Goebbels, Secret Billionaires &amp; Their Parellel With The Koch Bros</Title><Username>monsignor_whiteowl</Username><Timestamp>1359391356785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:42:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>under Muslim law Muslim law is irrelavent.</Msg><Username>captain_snotty</Username><Timestamp>1359395504554</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:51:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359395793742-54</Id><Topic><Title>Joseph Goebbels, Secret Billionaires &amp; Their Parellel With The Koch Bros</Title><Username>monsignor_whiteowl</Username><Timestamp>1359391356785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:42:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to a Muslim. Let's face it, he was born a Muslim. He adopted Christianity as a cover, because it is far more politically palatable. Accept reality for once.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1359395793742</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 12:56:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359396042527-55</Id><Topic><Title>We will close above $30.00 this week on our way to....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359388258247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree as MSFT and the rest of the Tech sector became the victim to APPL's hype and now that the reality is hitting the fans, people would be looking at MSFT as the ONLY Software company that its existance is crucial to not only the US economy, but the World's economy.... With the expiration of Windows XP this year, improving world economy and introduction of Surface Pro, our EPS would be over $4.00 and just under $5.00 in 2013 and that based on S&amp;P multiple should easily get us over $50.00 and perhaps $60.00.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359396042527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:00:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359397168441-56</Id><Topic><Title>60 MINUTES devotes time and segment to Obama / Hillary infomercial sales pitch</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1359396897901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:14:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He "owes her one." After all, her horndog husband did a lot to get O'Bama elected the second time around.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1359397168441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:19:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359400014916-57</Id><Topic><Title>500 Million Windows XP MUST migrate to Windows 7 or 8 in 12 months....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359247110947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The stock could trade between $50-60 by the Q3/2013.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1359400014916</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 14:06:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359400440519-58</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft problems are over , but for how long ?</Title><Username>myers.marlene</Username><Timestamp>1359392335176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good one! thx</Msg><Username>johnmarston503</Username><Timestamp>1359400440519</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 14:14:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359400999328-59</Id><Topic><Title>Obama frustrated with Fox, wants to control 100% of the media rather than 90%</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1359396756747</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:12:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Diaper Boy says, "Ditto Rush Limpballs.</Msg><Username>zernike_polynomials</Username><Timestamp>1359400999328</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 14:23:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359401266246-60</Id><Topic><Title>500 Million Windows XP MUST migrate to Windows 7 or 8 in 12 months....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359247110947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 19:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Linux does not have all the applications I use. Switching would not help me.</Msg><Username>stkctr22</Username><Timestamp>1359401266246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 14:27:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359402696224-61</Id><Topic><Title>We will close above $30.00 this week on our way to....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359388258247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have mentioned several times that MSFT could easily double in 1-2 years. This is one of the most undervalued stock.</Msg><Username>dell_stk</Username><Timestamp>1359402696224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 14:51:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359403450708-62</Id><Topic><Title>We will close above $30.00 this week on our way to....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359388258247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When we see the IT spending numbers hit the wire, this will fly north of $40.00 in a flash.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359403450708</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:04:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359403718330-63</Id><Topic><Title>We will close above $30.00 this week on our way to....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359388258247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No doubt about MSFT hitting $40, its just a matter of how soon. I cannot believe that MSFT is still trading at these low values.</Msg><Username>dell_stk</Username><Timestamp>1359403718330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:08:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359403785732-64</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives ought to compromise, forget Rush Limbaugh</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1359397343945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:22:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAHA So that's the socialists new strategy. If only they can get Limbaugh, and Fox out of the way, they've got the rest of the media on board.....clear sailin for socialism. Good luck cybermonkey, there are still decent folks in thsi country you valueless leftists have to deal wtih.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359403785732</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:09:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359405644752-65</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives ought to compromise, forget Rush Limbaugh</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1359397343945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:22:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Compromiimg iswhat got us into this mess in the first place. As Reagan found out, he increased taxes but the dems never cut spending as they promised. Just like Democrats got the big stimulus and was squandered with pork. Still didn't learn anything. And now they whine about poor Sandy victims and what do they do. Load up the Sandy bill with more pork. You should be ashamed of that instead of crying to conservatives to compromise.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1359405644752</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:40:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359405710008-66</Id><Title>Can't believe how can anybody compare chrome book with win8, LIL.</Title><Msg>WIN8 surface pro is a substitute for the desktop and laptop that is running Windows. Chrome book is a toy and can be used by students in elementary schools and general browsing.</Msg><Username>wallellaw</Username><Timestamp>1359405710008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:41:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359408604388-67</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT at Best Buy on line sold out</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359364413680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 04:13:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checked for myself, and you're absolutely right -- SOLD OUT!! All reviews rated it just a hair under 5 stars. Good news, and I believe the Pro will be even better.</Msg><Username>tmkawaba</Username><Timestamp>1359408604388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 16:30:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359408895004-68</Id><Title>What the Mus Broherhood is saying about Obama and Benghazi</Title><Msg>. The Muslim Brotherhood contact in Egypt is convinced that Obama left the four Americans to die as “compensation” for the offense Muslims suffered over a “youtube video.” Quite frankly it is not a stretch to say that Obama did not want to jeopardize his campaign with a rescue mission. So he shrugged. In his mind that is a small price to pay for the reelection of a black man from Chicago. Libera lmedia spoke barely a peep over the manipulation of a terrorist attack that killed your brothers!</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1359408895004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 16:34:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359408955729-69</Id><Topic><Title>Surface RT at Best Buy on line sold out</Title><Username>bwu106</Username><Timestamp>1359364413680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 04:13:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fake reviews. All but a couple only have one review, obviously trumped-up IDs to shill for MS. They hire agencies to do this. Transparent sham, that only fools the most gullible. As for being "sold out" -- haha.... that's what happens when a product is a dismal failure and production is limited and halted early.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1359408955729</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 16:35:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359409878382-70</Id><Title>MSFT needs to buy YAHOO...name their OS Yahoo.......</Title><Msg>Thats why google is so popular..........its just the marketing gimic of the names...chrome, ice-cream sandwich and androit.............and MSFT is so old fashion..MS8....Do it MSFT...buy Yahoo.....besides it also has a great gateway...</Msg><Username>denn56k</Username><Timestamp>1359409878382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 16:51:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359411452899-71</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft problems are over , but for how long ?</Title><Username>myers.marlene</Username><Timestamp>1359392335176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 11:58:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very well written. I subscribed</Msg><Username>stevenhill681</Username><Timestamp>1359411452899</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 17:17:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359411463581-72</Id><Topic><Title>Economists growing more upbeat about year ahead</Title><Username>martin_mildred</Username><Timestamp>1359403092779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 14:58:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very well written. I subscribed</Msg><Username>stevenhill681</Username><Timestamp>1359411463581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 17:17:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359411789321-73</Id><Title>How come ABC didn't ask Sen. Menendez about sleeping with underage prostiutes?</Title><Msg>Days after documents surfaced that suggested New Jersey Democratic Senator Bob Menendez paid for sexual favors in the Dominican Republic — including some from girls as young as 16 — few in Washington are offering new clues about what appears to be an ongoing federal investigation. The documents included emails between FBI Special Agent Regino Chavez and a Dominican source. In one email, Chavez told the source that “we have been able to confirm most of” the information he had provided about Menendez and the prostitutes. “We know that you are providing accurate information.” (RELATED: Emails show FBI investigating Menendez for sleeping with underage Dominican prostitutes) More liberal #$%$</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1359411789321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 17:23:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359411929760-74</Id><Topic><Title>We will close above $30.00 this week on our way to....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359388258247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are 1 billion users of Windows worldwide and 500 million are still on Windows XP which we will stop supporting this year.... I expect 750 million new licenses sold this year, you can do the math and see how the Windows division is going to explode as 90 cents on each dollar of Revenue go to the bottom line or a margin of 90%.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1359411929760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 17:25:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359411933704-75</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives ought to compromise, forget Rush Limbaugh</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1359397343945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:22:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thus spaketh alter ego #2, of the Hawcreek12 Empire of Fools.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1359411933704</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 17:25:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359412091951-76</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives ought to compromise, forget Rush Limbaugh</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1359397343945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:22:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's beyond reason any sane person could listen to limpbaugh and not vomit and laugh at the same time. Out and out 1900's style jim crow racism exposed in the open.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1359412091951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 17:28:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359412690885-77</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives ought to compromise, forget Rush Limbaugh</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1359397343945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:22:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems Hawteam klan has a way to stick three ups or downs now. Now there are always three, was two. He is quite an expert on the tricks of getting around yahoo rules. Hannitized, that's a good one. The real person has come out, like with romney, the outside of a faux news believer, is fake.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1359412690885</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 17:38:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359413861127-78</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives ought to compromise, forget Rush Limbaugh</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1359397343945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:22:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Hawc is smart enough to get around yahoo rules. Well I always knew he was a smarter man than I and you too it seems, as you just admitted. BTW, what the ef does "the outside of a faux news believer, is fake" mean? As usual your gibberish is rather amateurish.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1359413861127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 17:57:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359415241249-79</Id><Title>Microsoft earnings shed no new light on Windows 8 sales</Title><Msg>Google it....</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1359415241249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 18:20:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359415421824-80</Id><Topic><Title>Can't believe how can anybody compare chrome book with win8, LIL.</Title><Username>wallellaw</Username><Timestamp>1359405710008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:41:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Chrome book is a toy" That is what softie shills say about any product they feel threatened by. I understand Chrome book is beginning to catch on in some quarters.....</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1359415421824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 18:23:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359416776854-81</Id><Topic><Title>Can't believe how can anybody compare chrome book with win8, LIL.</Title><Username>wallellaw</Username><Timestamp>1359405710008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:41:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chrom is more useless than the ipads</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1359416776854</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 18:46:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359417527636-82</Id><Title>Yahoo - Search Revenue Up</Title><Msg>Nice partnership w/Microsoft - no need for MSFT to buy Yahoo, instead, the latter simply needs to drive traffic to their site, and MSFT cashes in....Small change to the bottom-line is still good for the LONGS!</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1359417527636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 18:58:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359417720250-83</Id><Title>Chrome, Apple and MSFT</Title><Msg>MSFT should not underestimate Chrome/Google - they need to keep Windows users and not have them migrate to Google. That said, with 60 billion in cash, MSFT is not going away easily. No doubt Google is great, and so is Apple, but MSFT not far behind. Partnerships w/Nokia helping, and soon, Dell might be in the bag.....</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1359417720250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:02:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359417773318-84</Id><Title>Google buys MSFT</Title><Msg>unthinkable?</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1359417773318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:02:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359417954924-85</Id><Topic><Title>good news on MMGW</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359387430040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:37:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""You realize a "new study" does not decrease the chances of warming, it's just a new study?"" No i don't realize this. Wut makes U realize this.</Msg><Username>david_robert_watkins</Username><Timestamp>1359417954924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:05:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359418085749-86</Id><Title>HPQ buys MSFT</Title><Msg>possible?</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1359418085749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:08:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359418094053-87</Id><Title>agree, that gateway is Marissa....msft could do a stock for stock swap...one for one or a bit more without using any cash...</Title><Msg>just take in the 6 billion in cash at yahoo, add 4.6 billion to revenue and 1 billion more in profits...and start attacking google and Facebooker.....</Msg><Username>mawsii1</Username><Timestamp>1359418094053</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:08:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359418247219-88</Id><Topic><Title>good news on MMGW</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359387430040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:37:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL he doesn't understand what is meant by the word chances. I suppose my weatherman is insane when he says chances for storms are reduced for todays forecast. Maybe he should check with the board scientist????</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359418247219</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359419196764-89</Id><Topic><Title>agree, that gateway is Marissa....msft could do a stock for stock swap...one for one or a bit more without using any cash...</Title><Username>mawsii1</Username><Timestamp>1359418094053</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:08:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure if Wall St will see this as a good buy, YAHOO's business-model is far, far behind. But if it makes the shares go up, sure, why not!</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1359419196764</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:26:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359419521875-90</Id><Topic><Title>Can't believe how can anybody compare chrome book with win8, LIL.</Title><Username>wallellaw</Username><Timestamp>1359405710008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:41:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WIN8 is a serious all in one machine,chrome is a joke like the 600 + aborted other nightmare versions of linix.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1359419521875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:32:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359419594934-91</Id><Title>If MSFT buys YHOO</Title><Msg>MICROYAHOO will be a solid # 2 in search, and Marissa can help unseat her former employer, all in due time!</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1359419594934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:33:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359420517581-92</Id><Topic><Title>good news on MMGW</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359387430040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:37:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more evidence of fuzzy type one thinking, The truth is what i decide to claim. LOL</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359420517581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:48:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359424825945-93</Id><Topic><Title>Can't believe how can anybody compare chrome book with win8, LIL.</Title><Username>wallellaw</Username><Timestamp>1359405710008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:41:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a phucktard.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1359424825945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 21:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359424939655-94</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft earnings shed no new light on Windows 8 sales</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1359415241249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 18:20:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>M$ playing games with the figures.....channel stuffing most likley.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic5</Username><Timestamp>1359424939655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 21:02:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359428474146-95</Id><Topic><Title>good news on MMGW</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359387430040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 10:37:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow, where did you say that</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1359428474146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 22:01:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359430147128-96</Id><Topic><Title>Google buys MSFT</Title><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1359417773318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:02:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not likely today, but in a few years, who knows? If Dell is on the auction block today, why not Microsoft down the road?</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1359430147128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 22:29:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359431269261-97</Id><Topic><Title>Google buys MSFT</Title><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1359417773318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:02:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What assets will MS have? By the time they sell it, Windows and Office will be memories of a dark and ugly time past. Well, they do own a lot of buildings I guess. Make a nice Goog campus, if the evil spirits don't corrupt them.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1359431269261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 22:47:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359431472487-98</Id><Topic><Title>Google buys MSFT</Title><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1359417773318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:02:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, like Nokia or Novell, Microsoft might have some unexpired patents that haven't been invalidated in court.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1359431472487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 22:51:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359435514032-99</Id><Topic><Title>Google buys MSFT</Title><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1359417773318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 19:02:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmm lets MSFT does 75 billion gross a year this past 12 mos and will be doing 100 billion in a couple of years. Net will move from this years 25 billion to 35-40 billion tough titty there ghosanon- I guess you ex cons just have to lie about something eh</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1359435514032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 23:58:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>