<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373010100215-1</Id><Topic><Title>mjna DUMP dont lose your money, i made 400% month</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368989019609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ERFD</Msg><Username>adampenske</Username><Timestamp>1373010100215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 03:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373010742385-2</Id><Topic><Title>going LONG here!! up 3k</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368549513779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MKLI</Msg><Username>adampenske</Username><Timestamp>1373010742385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 03:52:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373010748363-3</Id><Topic><Title>going LONG here, oh BILL GATES</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368549474411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VFTY</Msg><Username>adampenske</Username><Timestamp>1373010748363</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 03:52:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373011848935-4</Id><Topic><Title>100 million dollar Africa trip and what did we get fot it:?</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372980946257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:35:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since you continually want to live in the past. Why don't you mention the Vietnam War that Kennedy and Johnson got us in and the thousands of lives lost. BTW it's time for you to change your ID again as this is the last useless post I'm going to open under this one. Redundant stupidity always shows up no matter what you call yourself. Your talking points have gone beyond dull.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1373011848935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 04:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373012108907-5</Id><Topic><Title>A Sequester Fizzle for Military Fireworks This Fourth of July - THANKS TEA PARTY</Title><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1372978886212</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:01:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just think how many fireworks we could have had with the money spent on the African apology trip. Tell us again what besides an apology to Africa did we get for a hundred million. No one seems to know. Hope you don't post it under world's ID because she is history.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1373012108907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 04:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373020514065-6</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget, republican conservatives were against a women's</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1372946071827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ultra conservatives will never win the presidency again.....</Msg><Username>beemerbe</Username><Timestamp>1373020514065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373021050759-7</Id><Title>Background checks for guns</Title><Msg>If the argument that there is no point in having background checks for gun owners is valid because criminals don't obey the law, would the same argument be valid for doing away with drunk driving laws because drunk drivers don't obey the law ???</Msg><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1373021050759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373025538624-8</Id><Topic><Title>Background checks for guns</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1373021050759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:44:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have background checks to buy guns, I guess you think we should have background checks for all to buy alcohol and that the drunks will then not get alcohol? LOL at your totally flawed logic and analogy, Lugi.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1373025538624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 07:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373030640345-9</Id><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: win 8 is unusable garbage.</Title><Msg>My venerable Lenovo Thinkpad T420S died after being dropped on the way through airport security at the beginning of a trip to Ireland. It was working fine, but the case shattered, and the damage included jamming the CPU fan, and the repair cost was way more than it was worth. So, I bought a new one - a core i7 Asus with 8G RAM, 1Tb disk and NVidia GT650M graphics on a 1920x1080 ful HD screen, and great audio (Bang &amp; Olufsen). It came with bloody awful windoze 8, so i now count as a purchaser for M$. I'll try for a refund of the windoze tax, but I already wiped the HDD and installed Linux (SuSE 12.3). UEFI secure boot is a pain in the bum, but once I switched it off Linux installs and boots like lightning. The only oddity is having to have /boot/UEFI as a windoze FAT partition, but I didn't have time to fix all the issues (even if possible), as I needed to get back to work. I played with w8 for a while before nuking it....suspicions confirmed....it is APALLING. I was going to dual boot, just to see how it went, but a short time with w8 convinced me that it is a waste of disk space, so it's gone. Everything works great -even the Nouveau driver is pretty solid and capable nowadays - even got full compositing on KDE . Once agaiin. no M$ in my life!</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373030640345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373030662635-10</Id><Topic><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: win 8 is unusable garbage.</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373030640345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windoze is garbage</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373030662635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373030850166-11</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget, republican conservatives were against a women's</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1372946071827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget, Democrats were against the abolition of slavery.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1373030850166</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373031041238-12</Id><Topic><Title>DRAM $3.7 ..12-MONTH TARGET: $30+...REASONS: 1) RAISING 2013 MEMORY PRICES, 2) NEW MEMORY/SOFTWARE MANUFACTURING DEAL WITH AMD, 3) LO FLOAT</Title><Username>accountislate</Username><Timestamp>1372273549925</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-26 15:05:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In mid May 2013 AMD and Dataram Corp. (NASDAQ: DRAM) separately announced their deal with each other for DRAM to manufacture the new super fast AMD Radeon Gamer Series RG2133 memory modules for the fast growing global gaming business. Additionally, AMD is using DRAM's RAMDisk technology to drive all of its Radeon products. Even without this huge AMD deal, DRAM was on the verge of returning to profitability because of improving fundamentals in the memory industry (DRAM's bread and butter up to now). Since the end of last quarter ended January 31, 2013, memory prices have jumped an additional 50%. Together with improving memory bsuiness and the new AMD windfall which started in May 2013, DRAM is poised to explode because it's current market cap is only $7 million and it's trading below 0.2 X sales compared to a 1.5 sector average. Here are a couple of customer reviews of the DRAM-manufactured RG2133 memory modules (Newegg website): Customer Reviews of the AMD Radeon RG2133 Gamer Series 16GB (4 x 4GB) – Newegg @ $154 A - 5 Star Review Easily overclocked/superfast Pros: fast and reliable top of the line ram. Thinking of getting more for the second PC i'm building. Cons: N/A Other Thoughts: Really fast. A definite increase in browser speed and minuscule fps gain. If you're in the department for some new ram, this AMD ram takes the cake IMO 3 out of 3 people found this review helpful. Did you? B - 5 Star Review Great Memory from AMD Pros: AMP support for AMD systems.Low profile head spreader and legit design, detected running at 30C in my case. Memory testing yields 100% solid performance, no errors in 2133 with advertised timings. Cons: Expensive? You can find significantly cheaper but I'm a sucker for AMD products NOTE... DRAM was $30+ two years ago with less earnings potential and diversification</Msg><Username>dianakibsion</Username><Timestamp>1373031041238</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373031267710-13</Id><Topic><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: win 8 is unusable garbage.</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373030640345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad you didn't get the free Windows Blue beta upgrade to W8 because you need WINDOWS to trade stocks and for the business world. Instead you made your new pc a IDIOT like you. NTFS was launched with Windows NT and is a far more advanced and secure disk file system than FAT32. However, it is not widely compatible with other computers and operating systems, so not only is your pc a IDIOT, it's less secure than NTFS so you win the Turkey. CONGRADALATIONS STUPID.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1373031267710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373031426073-14</Id><Title>Bulls Look for More Gains From Microsoft</Title><Msg>"Microsoft has been on a tear since mid-April, and option activity was heavy to the bullish side going into yesterday's holiday." "optionMONSTER's Heat Seeker tracking program detected strong activity in the September 37 calls with less than 45 minutes left in Wednesday's shortened session, as big chunks traded for $0.32. More than 5,100 of the contracts changed hands, almost double the previous open interest, indicating that these are new positions. " Bing It.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1373031426073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373031853496-15</Id><Title>Microsoft Tries to Avoid Another Hardware Failure</Title><Msg>Google it. Quoting: "Facing lackluster performance from the Microsoft (NASDAQ: MSFT ) Surface RT and Surface Pro, the company is hoping that, by turning to businesses through resellers like CDW, sales can improve. The Microsoft-branded tablets face stiff competition from both Apple and Google, and sales figures have shown it. In addition to opening distribution channels, Mr. Softy is rolling out a program to encourage developers to work on new apps in an effort to become more competitive."</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1373031853496</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:44:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373032002919-16</Id><Title>Breaking: Zombie-Like Security Flaw in Almost Every Android Phone</Title><Msg>"Almost every Android phone has a big, gaping security weakness...essentially, according to BlueBox, almost every Android phone made in the past four years...is just a few steps away from becoming a George Romero film, thanks to a weakness that can "turn any legitimate application into a malicious Trojan". It just gets worse and worse for droid phone owners.</Msg><Username>scooponcoop</Username><Timestamp>1373032002919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373032132023-17</Id><Topic><Title>osso-di.ldo was 100% wrong, unsurprisingly</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372953038228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mention 10 pounds of s h I t in a 5 pound bag and it pops right up. A perfectly executed "wally"...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1373032132023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:48:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373033661593-18</Id><Topic><Title>Background checks for guns</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1373021050759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:44:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, the argument against background checks is just as stupid. You do need a background check both to buy alcohol and to drive. What the stubborn holdovers from the 19th century don't admit to, or comprehend in their simple thinking, is it saves lives, not all lives. That should be enough reason. The gun nuts only hold onto these odd arguments because Obama is for checks. They live in this fairy tale land where he is King and is planning to use his powers to do all sorts of mischief to them. That's why we call them nuts.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1373033661593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:14:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373035253036-19</Id><Topic><Title>osso-di.ldo was 100% wrong, unsurprisingly</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372953038228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey its predouchebag again! PD you are a poor excuse for phands - he would be here posting but obviously swallowed too much spnk last night HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR H</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373035253036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:40:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373035459362-20</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Tries to Avoid Another Hardware Failure</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1373031853496</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:44:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wotopimp still bashing Microsoft- as if that were the only purpose for mankind since the dawn of the computer age.-- BOZO why don't you face up to it- Microsoft is going to prevail - you will be dead and buried and MSFT will be soaring upward in spite of all the kkraaap you threw at them HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373035459362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373035644018-21</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget, republican conservatives were against a women's</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1372946071827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget Democrats were against the abolition of slavery since the 20th century on the other hand Republicans have been in favor of reinstituting slavery since Nixon's day Oh one other thing wotto the pimp is a LIAR and would do well to keep his trap shut</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373035644018</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373037307296-22</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget, republican conservatives were against a women's</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1372946071827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does this subject pertain to the MSFT or even the Market?!?! Buzz off then!</Msg><Username>joet52632001</Username><Timestamp>1373037307296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373039524073-23</Id><Topic><Title>Background checks for guns</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1373021050759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:44:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You do need a background check both to buy alcohol and to drive. " In what country?</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1373039524073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373039602498-24</Id><Topic><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: win 8 is unusable garbage.</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373030640345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should have called me first. For the same price, I'd have sold you my old (still runs) Tandy 1000!</Msg><Username>zingermaster</Username><Timestamp>1373039602498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373041413131-25</Id><Topic><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: win 8 is unusable garbage.</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373030640345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, #$%$..I got rid of the windoze infection, and now I'm getting a refund from Asus - they just agreed to. NTFS is outdated, insecure garbage, and why M$ require FAT for the UEFI stuff is beyond primitive. Why M$ can't use decent. modern set ups like ext4 or BTRFS, or quite a few others is unbelievable.....but then M$ doesn't do modern technology.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373041413131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:23:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373041478784-26</Id><Topic><Title>these alerts will make you explode</Title><Username>haneymason841</Username><Timestamp>1372952395446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:39:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean "explode" like fireworks, or "explode" as in expand one's thinking processes? You realize of course, the NSA is giving your post added scrutiny because of your inclusion of the word "explode". in the subject line. But not to worry, they'd do the same thing if you included the word "explode" in the body of the message, which is now up to about one-third dozen. And they'd even investigate if you wrote that MSFT's stock price will explode and crash due to strategic business blunders, or explode upward in price due to dazzling deal decisions. There; that's six times I've mentioned the word "explode" in the body of this post.....Seven!, seven times I mentioned .......ha, ha, you thought I was gonna say ex.... whoops, almost said it again. Does that count as 7-1/2?</Msg><Username>zingermaster</Username><Timestamp>1373041478784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373041536997-27</Id><Topic><Title>At a tiny 0.53%, Windoze 8 adoption levels in the enterprise are shockingly low</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370388335249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reminder bump</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373041536997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373042080011-28</Id><Title>Google Will Eat Microsoft's Lunch</Title><Msg>Google it. Quoting: "In several articles (here, here, here, and here) we have been pondering the future of Intel (INTC) and Microsoft's (MSFT) Windows, both companies have seen their core market, personal computers, coming under threat from mobile and hybrid devices working with processors based on the design of ARM (ARMH) and operating systems from Apple (AAPL) and Google (GOOG). "We have described how Intel and Microsoft are fighting back to get more traction in these new mobile and hybrid markets, but we weren't too optimistic. There is considerable momentum behind iOC and Android, and some network effects, complicating the life of Microsoft. CPU's based on ARM designs are, at least up to now, cheaper and more energy efficient than those of Intel. "What we haven't mentioned yet is that Android is also invading into the territory of the PC and laptop. Well, we did marvel at the upcoming Asus Transformer (the hybrid that defined the category of hybrids, that is, an ARM/Android based tablet, but it has a base with more connections, a second battery, and a keyboard, clicking them together delivers a laptop, sort off), but there is more going on here. "On a smartphone and a tablet, the ARM/Android combination provides a useful "computing" experience for most users. One can surf the web, watch videos, communicate, and there are a growing, and already bewildering amount of applications (apps) that can do all sorts of things. "The first thing to note is that for an increasing amount of people, this is their first and/or most important computing experience, and that experience is making people less hungry for buying laptops and desktops, as the declining sales testify." _________________________ There is much more. Please see the original article....</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1373042080011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:34:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373045846922-29</Id><Title>Windows Phone Nonexistent in Marketplace</Title><Msg>Only used by serf geeks in Redmond. "No Room for Rivals: Android, iOS Maintain Smartphone Dominance" Search for it.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1373045846922</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:37:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373046234921-30</Id><Title>Folks - 11 days till $50 you stupid S0B's !!!</Title><Msg>ossobucco2012 • Jun 18, 2013 7:52 PM Flag We will trade over $50.00 in 4 weeks. Osso Sentiment: Strong Buy</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373046234921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:43:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373046327720-31</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not yet - waiting for W8.2 you stupid S0B.. Dr. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373046327720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373047470372-32</Id><Topic><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: win 8 is unusable garbage.</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373030640345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"now I'm getting a refund from Asus" Try reading your first post this thread, S,,,K,,,A,,,N,,,K,,,, Lenovo Thinkpad T420S is not a Asus and you said a FAT partition, which is old technology. ERTBSDSS IS THE LATEST disk format and MSFT uses it! Atleast Get your lies right....HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1373047470372</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373049877191-33</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The BSOD was eliminated on Vista already- you are 3 generations behind on software- where are you on brains</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373049877191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373049909434-34</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey basher- why not stay out of discussions where you aren't welcome-- by anybody--ok?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373049909434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373049987996-35</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the noodres!! corneriusfrake the noodres!!!!!!! and get off this board</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373049987996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373050718833-36</Id><Title>Don't miss this one GIMO 11 million float / ipo you can now trade options !! IT'S RUNNING !!</Title><Msg>MAJOR BUY BY CRAMER !!</Msg><Username>wthomas862</Username><Timestamp>1373050718833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:58:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373052103380-37</Id><Topic><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: win 8 is unusable garbage.</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373030640345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pigeon s h I t for brains ESL f u c k up. Re read it, moron.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1373052103380</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373052145060-38</Id><Topic><Title>Folks - 11 days till $50 you stupid S0B's !!!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1373046234921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:43:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry it ain't happening</Msg><Username>joet52632001</Username><Timestamp>1373052145060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:22:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373052351373-39</Id><Title>WeHAVE A MAJOR BREAKOUT AT HAND "" gimo "" 11 million float</Title><Msg>JUST BROKE $30</Msg><Username>wthomas862</Username><Timestamp>1373052351373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373055303822-40</Id><Topic><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: win 8 is unusable garbage.</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373030640345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your synopsis is that of a imbecile &amp; your abridgement is appalling. That's why u linux rats never get anywhere in life. while you can repeat things, you have no comprehension of what you are saying. therefore, ur "iq" is under acceptable limits for "human", so the truth must be stated!</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1373055303822</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373057103209-41</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Phone Nonexistent in Marketplace</Title><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1373045846922</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:37:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft down 0.2% for the survey peroid. Not much, but it's nearly one tenth of what it had.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1373057103209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:45:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373057401560-42</Id><Topic><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: win 8 is unusable garbage.</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1373030640345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol! What an indecipherable snot bubble. Speak English, doofus.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1373057401560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373058490295-43</Id><Topic><Title>Google Will Eat Microsoft's Lunch</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1373042080011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:34:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yo we got some lunch for you wotopimp- its a little snotty tho</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373058490295</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 17:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373058620340-44</Id><Topic><Title>At a tiny 0.53%, Windoze 8 adoption levels in the enterprise are shockingly low</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370388335249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>time for you to be laying out plans for your nightly gai romp of the dives and waterfront sh.tholes isn't it phands??</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373058620340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 17:10:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373058927330-45</Id><Topic><Title>Background checks for guns</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1373021050759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:44:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Im sure he misspoke as to the need for background checks to buy booze. However if there is any doubt about the purchasers age then some kind of check will be required. Your problem hawfaeces is that you think that you should be able to buy guns when most of the professional people would deny you the right to own a gun. Why - because mental defectives shouldn't be allowed to own guns</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373058927330</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 17:15:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373059882058-46</Id><Title>The new msn web page may have the best modern layout in Window Blue or 8 in rtm</Title><Msg>The page full of all the news in the tiles for finance or just the main page tells the worlds story instantly. That has to be the best page on the net as far as getting information quick.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1373059882058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 17:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373061129358-47</Id><Topic><Title>Background checks for guns</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1373021050759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:44:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"mental defectives shouldn't be allowed to own guns" Have you noticed that the quality of Hawcreeks posts have gone down over the years ?</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1373061129358</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 17:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373070450643-48</Id><Topic><Title>The new msn web page may have the best modern layout in Window Blue or 8 in rtm</Title><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1373059882058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 17:31:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSN still exists?</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1373070450643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 20:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373071328102-49</Id><Title>Hawcreek Team Losing The Battle ...</Title><Msg>"Wall St. gains as jobs data signals stronger economy" America coming back from the Bush Financial Disaster and Great Recession.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1373071328102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 20:42:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373072287890-50</Id><Title>I do like</Title><Msg>2 jews though. I do like Barry Manilow and Neil Diamond.</Msg><Username>order_in_the_quartz</Username><Timestamp>1373072287890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 20:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373081711814-51</Id><Title>What was hawcreek`s ``last straw``</Title><Msg>there was a definite last straw somewhere.</Msg><Username>ima_spent_force</Username><Timestamp>1373081711814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 23:35:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>