<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357970440195-1</Id><Topic><Title>about the second amendment nonsense</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357948720675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 18:58:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**** How about it, lets legalize ANFO You mean it's NOT legal now? OOOOPS!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1357970440195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:00:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357970581297-2</Id><Topic><Title>Climate Panel Says Coast, Midwest at Risk of Extreme Weather</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1357943112456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 17:25:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ consensus from #$%$ conspirator #$%$-heads. No biggie. Where did I leave ny AR-15 and "legal" ANFO???</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1357970581297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:03:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357972953545-3</Id><Topic><Title>about the second amendment nonsense</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357948720675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 18:58:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I have blown up a truck load" I'll bet, but when, because you are always here. When did you get your truck load and go blow it up? date and time. If you have to go look up when you started posting here 16/7 you are lying. When you blow up a truck load of something, you tend to remember when. Have you cleaned anything in the past five years, or just made messes? "who then get too powerful and try to steal from us." See how stupid that is to say? A Pres isn't King George. A Pres gets two terms, you know that? A Pres has a congress to deal with, who interfere with things like the 250k limit. The writers of the 2nd had no such thoughts. They weere worried about the King, you can't understand that? Do you know that was a big fear back then? Maybe you also need to look at the 1st and a few other amendments. And, no way, no how, did the Pres lie about the 250k limit, f he could have he would have. You still don't get simple meanings of words, home schooled by mama? You see,again, the Pres isn't King, unlike Grover and the NRA, he is a democratically elected official.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1357972953545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:42:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357993738830-4</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this the answer you learned when working at the NUTSA Godtard Message Board Troll Center? Next time I'm in Auburn I'll lay a Wreath on Bob's memorial for you.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1357993738830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 07:28:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357995115483-5</Id><Topic><Title>CFury moe-ron asks middle school math questions, leaving out critical aspects which makes the question</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1357961829069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 22:37:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's pretty sure that if you lean far enough to the right, even the force of gravitation can be changed. The theory didn't pan out too well when it was applied to the attempt to attract voters to install the white collar criminal moe-ron he wanted into "his" White House. He's still looking for a "Physical" explanation.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1357995115483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 07:51:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357996620622-6</Id><Topic><Title>WOW that was a lot of buyers, MSFT going a lot higher TIC TOC can't wait for Monday</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1357938129430</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 16:02:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple’s (AAPL) staggering success over the past few years can be attributed to the combination of several key factors. Great leadership is one, great products is another. Apple’s deep pockets and monstrous marketing budget have played an equal role in the company’s success but according to a new report, Apple may be losing its grip on an important demographic. Among teens, Apple is no longer cool. The news comes from the Buzz Marketing Group, an agency that specializes in youth marketing. Popularity is always a double-edged sword with teenagers and according to the sentiment observed by Buzz, Apple is now too popular to be popular. Replacing iPhones and iPads as the object of teens’ desire is Microsoft’s (MSFT) Surface tablet and Galaxy smartphones from Samsung (005930). “Teens are telling us Apple is done,” Buzz Marketing Group’s Tina Wells told Forbes. Surface is the future. $30 by March. $50 by Dec 13</Msg><Username>marketanalyst2003</Username><Timestamp>1357996620622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:17:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357999178319-7</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your response was as idiotic as any of the other responses that pop into your adult diaper from time to time. "the example given before was positioning oneself on a spring scale" --Hilarious! Proving conclusively that if you lean far enough to the right any kind nonsense can result.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1357999178319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:59:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357999864067-8</Id><Title>INSIDERS DUMPING SHARES</Title><Msg>Insider Transactions Reported MARQUARDT DAVID : Nov. 28, 2012 Sell 300,000 MSFT SALE at $27.07 per share. (Proceeds of $8,121,000)</Msg><Username>macdaddy333</Username><Timestamp>1357999864067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:11:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358001774803-9</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Name him and shame him. Tough week of trolling, isn't it? Maybe you should refer me to the spring scale section of "desmogblog" or "real [pseudo]science".</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358001774803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:42:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358002559755-10</Id><Title>I bought a Surface and Windows 8 for my PC!</Title><Msg>Both are FANTASTIC! FAN TASTIC!</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1358002559755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:55:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358003326965-11</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In reality numbers are often rounded in arbitrary ways. You can't even tell unless you study the numbers. A recent study says that about 3.8% of the US population is LGBT, or about 9 million people. If one figures that the US population is about 305 million then: 305 million * 0.038 = 11.59 million gays. Which should properly be rounded up to 12 million. You have to dig around to find they applied their percentage to the presumed adult population above age 18. I looked this up and it works out to like 8.8 million adult gays, which they round up to 9 million. Do we assume there are no gay children? Or that they don't count? Or maybe that we can "cure" them?</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1358003326965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:08:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358003912574-12</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's another statistic for you. Republicans are going on and on about their Hispanic Stratedgy. During election 2012 Mitt Romney lost by about 2 million votes. (If I recall 1.5 million voted for "Other" and Obama got a 50.5% majority, the 0.5% being 500k or 600 k votes.) So if there are 9 million adult gays, how many do you think voted for Mitt Romney? I bet Close to NONE. Now suppose Romney got 1/3rd of the gay vote, about 3 million votes. Bingo, Romney wins in 2012! All Obama did to get ALL of the gay vote was SAY he supported gay marriage. He didn't actually DO ANYTHING! Nor did he promise to DO ANYTHING. He just talked blither blather. We are hearing constant political chatter about the Republican Hispanic Strategy and NO TALK AT ALL about the Republican Gay Strategy! How does that affect/effect or impact your significant digits?</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1358003912574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:18:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358004191243-13</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He doesn't understand the question. As basic as it is he still doesn't understand it. I am tempted to explain it too him but i am having tooo much fun messing with him.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358004191243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:23:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358004281689-14</Id><Topic><Title>Climate Panel Says Coast, Midwest at Risk of Extreme Weather</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1357943112456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 17:25:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shove your AR15 up your ess and keep pulling the trigger....until you can't anymore.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1358004281689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:24:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358004397546-15</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" *TYPICALLY* averaging multiple readings of a single data point gives one a better result " I guess you would answer the question in favor of averaging then ???</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358004397546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:26:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358005010712-16</Id><Title>creek believes averaging provides the most likely better result -- maybe ?</Title><Msg>"given a list of measurements for a single quantity which strategy provides the most likely best estimate of the true value. 1 Averaging the measurements 2 Using the rules of significant digits" *********************** One more time CFury, just to rub you nose in your own arrogant ignorance. Your question displays your ignorance as it is like asking "which gives the better ride a Ford car or tires". The car ride is still always limited by using tires and the best car cannot improve uneven out of balance tires. As I schooled you on the formula you posted but did not understand *TYPICALLY* averaging multiple readings of a single data point gives one a better result and can *IMPLY* an increase in a significant digit. THERE ARE EXCEPTIONS such as where methodology of the reading induces repeated error, the example given before was positioning oneself on a spring scale. If you tend to lean and that leaning causes a 1% error and that error is repeated each reading averaging will not help. Conclusion: Your question is a math moe-ron bit of nonsense because when averaging one must adhere to significant digits rules as well. Averaging once read data does not increase significant digits for the whole because simply put, you are in essence "averaging" a single number which obviously always results in that number. Combining that number with other such once read numbers does increase accuracy wrt significant digits. If you had made it past a good tenth grad math level you would quit making a fool of yourself. Less ******************************* AS usual he couches his answer in riddles to avoid taking a stand to a very simple question. It appears he favors averaging for the answer since he says ((*TYPICALLY* it gives a better result)) He is however too much coward to answer directly Once again with the "once read data" thing, does anybody know what the fakcer means by that??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358005010712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:36:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358005116816-17</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So if there is no answer why should a person take multiple readings of a quantity if there is no use in doing so??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358005116816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:38:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358005481355-18</Id><Title>Only hawcreek could answer then deny an answer exists.</Title><Msg>"given a list of measurements for a single quantity which strategy provides the most likely best estimate of the true value. 1 Averaging the measurements 2 Using the rules of significant digits" The board scientist with an enguneer digree says this question has no answer ????? Really ???? I though it was common for scientists and maybe even some engunears to take multiple measurements of things. Why would they do this if the board whacko says he doesn't know what to do with the multiple readings. Maybe the board whacko is just kinda slow at reasoning ??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358005481355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:44:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358005515439-19</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Suppose cfunny takes six hot water enemas as follows: 1. One cup (4 oz) short of 6 quarts of water at 105.6 degrees F, with soapy water 2. 6 quarts of water at 115.3 degrees F, with soapy water 3. 6 quarts of water at 114.7 degrees F, with clear water 4. 6 quarts of water at 108.3 degrees F, with clear water 5. 8 quarts of water at 117.9 degrees F, with clear water Do you think the cfunny will care if the average temperature was 112.7131964809 degrees F or will about about 112.7 degrees F or 113 degrees F be an adequate average? Will he think of it as significant that one of the enemas was almost 118 degrees F? Or will he insist that it was only 117.9 degrees F. This is an experiment we could really try!</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1358005515439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:45:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358005777471-20</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cfury claims to be a great scientist! I propose this is an experiment he should agree to! We can all watch on Skype and post the results on YouTube!</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1358005777471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:49:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358005802992-21</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying that neither method can be used for providing an estimate of the measured quantity??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358005802992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:50:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358005843210-22</Id><Topic><Title>I bought a Surface and Windows 8 for my PC!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1358002559755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:55:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why didn't you just wait for the Surface Pro, both rolled into one device, no more deciding what device to take with you, all in one.</Msg><Username>bill_california_paseo</Username><Timestamp>1358005843210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:50:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358006426114-23</Id><Topic><Title>Only hawcreek could answer then deny an answer exists.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358005481355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:44:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>K lets rephrase this so maybe you can understand it. If your client wanted to know how tall one of your pile driving cranes was as it sits in some position and you asked 5 of your best flunkies to go out with a tape measure and measure the height and they all reported their numbers to you. Would you Pick the measurement of your favorite boi to report. Average the readings then apply significant digits rules to the average to report. Average the readings and then report this value Or something else like consult an astrologer ?? Email rush limbaugh What number would you report.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358006426114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:00:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358006817297-24</Id><Topic><Title>S.O.P. for CFury after a sound spanking (he's done it a hundred times) is to retreat to a corner</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358006549467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:02:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me rephrase the question for you. given a list of measurements for a single quantity which strategy provides the most likely best estimate of the true value. 1 Averaging the measurements 2 Averaging the measurements then applying the rules of significant digits to the average Which answer is most likely closer to the true answer ?? I misunderstood how stewpid U R , pretending to not know that i meant apply sig digs to the average for option 2 Now that this is cleared up do you think you have the pair to stand up and actually answer ????</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358006817297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:06:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358007231059-25</Id><Title>can i post anything at all</Title><Msg>how about it yahooooo</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358007231059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:13:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358007462049-26</Id><Title>try this one creeeeeeeeeek</Title><Msg>how now brown cow took an average of his farts</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358007462049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:17:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358007495887-27</Id><Title>try this one creeeeeeek</Title><Msg>this is the future for msft</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358007495887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:18:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358007587333-28</Id><Title>try this one creeeeeeeek</Title><Msg>are you a human of a machine that prevents the average of the significant digits</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358007587333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:19:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358007794560-29</Id><Topic><Title>S.O.P. for CFury after a sound spanking (he's done it a hundred times) is to retreat to a corner</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358006549467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:02:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah but your highness the two items are no longer as you say tires and cars ?? now we get down to your more basic misunderstanding of the question.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358007794560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:23:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358007852823-30</Id><Topic><Title>It appears the CFury bot had a main b-buss undervolt fatal logic board malfunction</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358007794374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:23:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when the censor turns on i enjoy testing it to see if it is human.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358007852823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:24:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358007953457-31</Id><Topic><Title>S.O.P. for CFury after a sound spanking (he's done it a hundred times) is to retreat to a corner</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358006549467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:02:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[[One cannot say that averaging the measurements (of once read data points) and carrying that answer to added digits provides a better more accurate answer.]] I didn't ask you that, go reread the question then try again.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358007953457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:25:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358008294626-32</Id><Title>simple math question rewritten so some of the dimmer can understand it</Title><Msg>Let me rephrase the question. given a list of measurements for a single quantity which strategy provides the most likely best estimate of the true value. 1 Averaging the measurements 2 Averaging the measurements then applying the rules of significant digits to the average Which answer is most likely closer to the true answer ?? Maybe an example would help. If a civil engunear weighed his collection of pet rocks every day for five days for a graduate lab course in rock weighing which value should he report to his perfessur for the weight of his rock collection. A pick the number he likes cause its purty. B Average the weights he recorded and report this. C Apply the rules of significant digits to the average from B and report this. D Any other option for the 5 readings</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358008294626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:31:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358008415776-33</Id><Topic><Title>It appears the CFury bot had a main b-buss undervolt fatal logic board malfunction</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358007794374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:23:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you're going to start mucking around with spring steel in your old age perhaps you should be more concerned with the effects of anthropogenic global warming than you are about the persistent rightward slant your positions take. CFuryurself12 will probably take care of himself quite nicely without your "help", thenkyewverymuch.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358008415776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:33:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358008485196-34</Id><Topic><Title>simple math question rewritten so some of the dimmer can understand it</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358008294626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:31:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody must be copy pasting for you. I've got a very good measurement of how dim your bulb is from reading previous posts. It is readily apparant that after you run out of fingers and toes, numbers don't mean anything to you.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358008485196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:34:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358008705205-35</Id><Topic><Title>simple math question rewritten so some of the dimmer can understand it</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358008294626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:31:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>E Leave the rocks in his head and insist that the Perfessur told him that his rock arrangement would lead to a persistent bias so he might as well not bother doing his work and should simply continue posting right-wingnut twaddle on financial message boards as he has non-stop for at least the last twelve years.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358008705205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:38:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358008822024-36</Id><Topic><Title>simple math question rewritten so some of the dimmer can understand it</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358008294626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:31:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you have an answer to the question??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358008822024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:40:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358009029300-37</Id><Topic><Title>simple math question rewritten so some of the dimmer can understand it</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358008294626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:31:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One would think that such a talented business leader could find more productive use of his time. Only two conclusions are possible. 1 He is talented but doesn't believe in his talent so he underachieves and wastes his time here. 2 He fails at everything else and the message board is his fallback. I vote for 2</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358009029300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:43:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358009143735-38</Id><Topic><Title>CFury called on his nonsense gibberish undefined unanswerable question poses a new</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358008959623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:42:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes it is a 'new' question as i assumed you understood my meaning. And NO you didn't answer the new question, which is very basic and no engunear should have trouble with it.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358009143735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:45:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358010164409-39</Id><Topic><Title>CFury called on his nonsense gibberish undefined unanswerable question poses a new</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358008959623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:42:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hint: focus on the word "Likely" in the question. Also what is actually done in practice, what number would you give if you took multiple readings?? It cannot get any simpler than that can it, something that is done every day by engunears is suspect.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358010164409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:02:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358011450837-40</Id><Topic><Title>since it is the weekend lets put this simple math problem back up</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357949056455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 19:04:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republican Party needs a high colonic enema with hot soapy water!</Msg><Username>chronosthegrimreaper</Username><Timestamp>1358011450837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:24:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358012669827-41</Id><Topic><Title>Only hawcreek could answer then deny an answer exists.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358005481355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:44:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ditto, Rush! What's the quantization error on flunkie? Show your work.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358012669827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:44:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358018220924-42</Id><Topic><Title>Is Anyone Making Money WIth MSFT?</Title><Username>harmoncohen986</Username><Timestamp>1358014635474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:17:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know- bought at the mid 26s because it looks cheap to me- I don't know how the current quarter earnings will play out BUT believe going forward, things will be good</Msg><Username>mikemclaug</Username><Timestamp>1358018220924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:17:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358021081859-43</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Ban Scenerio ...</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1358010997529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:16:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should drop your adult diaper, shove the barrel up your sssa, and keep pulling the trigger until you run out.</Msg><Username>hi_speed_jebus_motors</Username><Timestamp>1358021081859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 15:04:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358024045170-44</Id><Topic><Title>CFury called on his nonsense gibberish undefined unanswerable question poses a new</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358008959623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:42:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for demonstrating that you do not understand the problem. the word "Likely" in the problem statement is extremely significant. It remains true that you do not understand averaging. Engunear school must be poor training for the real world. Interesting example though. What if we programmed one of those new fangled computers to generate numbers and then add random error and then used both methods to obtain an estimate. In this case the true number would be known and the relative merits would stand out for both cases. We could even run this computur program a thousand times to see which result turned out to be more accurate and how often the winner won each round. Is this something you can understand ???</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358024045170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 15:54:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358024974158-45</Id><Topic><Title>Is Anyone Making Money WIth MSFT?</Title><Username>harmoncohen986</Username><Timestamp>1358014635474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:17:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can be extraordinary! gains of 100% - 300%</Msg><Username>jeanettesolomon709</Username><Timestamp>1358024974158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:09:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358028508936-46</Id><Topic><Title>Is Anyone Making Money WIth MSFT?</Title><Username>harmoncohen986</Username><Timestamp>1358014635474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:17:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed, tried both window RT and window pro at BJ's - new concept but no more difficult than what you do on your cell phone....of course, window RT will only work with certain apps while window pro will work with all apps - that said, new concept that might be unpopular but again, it's nice and if people adjust, this can take off. I know a lady bought a $399 Toshiba with window RT. So, bring on all the bad news and I wonder if those are already priced in ie that's why it is in the $26 dollar range. MSFT is now expanding and with BALLMER hopefully moving out of MSFT, that could easily trigger a 10 - 30% increase! IMHO</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1358028508936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:08:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358029280599-47</Id><Topic><Title>can i post anything at all</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358007231059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:13:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO!</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1358029280599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:21:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358032600083-48</Id><Topic><Title>I bought a Surface and Windows 8 for my PC!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1358002559755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:55:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 is here to stay. The people have no other choice... Its that or buy an Apple mac.. They rather choose MS due to the affordability.. The game is over for Apple...The Apple fad is dying out</Msg><Username>ossweekly</Username><Timestamp>1358032600083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:16:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358033813465-49</Id><Topic><Title>about the second amendment nonsense</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357948720675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 18:58:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It intended to say right to bare arms, but you know the NRA perverted that to mean something for them. It was about dress code in colonial America originally.</Msg><Username>hawrcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358033813465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:36:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358034380048-50</Id><Topic><Title>This needs it's own topic line: CFury insists averaging improves accuracy over sticking with significant numbers</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358031364182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:56:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>[[I say there is no way for that to be consistently true with independent data points, i.e. it cannot be a rule and THAT is precisely why we even have significant digits]] Nobody said this at all, that is why i advised you to consider the word "Likely" in the problem definition. I have to give you a few honesty points as it does seem that you are trying. you included two examples of a potential calculation of the results using each method. How about picking a true value then adding random errors to create hypothetical 'measurements' then applying both methods on these noisy measurements and see which strategy creates the closer answer more often.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358034380048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:46:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358034615326-51</Id><Topic><Title>about the second amendment nonsense</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357948720675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 18:58:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well do try to keep up with the discussion. Are you for or against allowing citizens to buy ANFO and detonators.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358034615326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:50:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358035036453-52</Id><Title>shouldn't we educate the public of the construction of</Title><Msg>explosively formed projectiles so that we could fight a tyrannical government</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358035036453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:57:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358035100336-53</Id><Title>shouldn't we teach people how to rig a cellphone to trigger a bomb</Title><Msg>so that we would be ready to put down an oppressive government</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358035100336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358035242105-54</Id><Title>People have the right to buy all the C4 explosive they want</Title><Msg>Its the only way to defend against an oppressive government.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358035242105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:00:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358035389547-55</Id><Topic><Title>about the second amendment nonsense</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1357948720675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 18:58:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ANFO (or something similar) was used by Timothy McVeigh. He killed 168 people. Now I understand that Tea Party selohssa like you admire McVeigh. Explosives and assault rifles are your substitute for balls. Ooooo I'm scared. I suggest you shove your semi-auto fiream up your sssa and empty the mother.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1358035389547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:03:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358035737582-56</Id><Topic><Title>This needs it's own topic line: CFury insists averaging improves accuracy over sticking with significant numbers</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358031364182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:56:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow you blew a fuse, must be getting close to teaching you something. Why do you pretend the everyday experience of measuring something multiple times and combining these measurements in some way such that a more accurate value is expected is something foreign and not understandable. You still do NOT understand the question. I even though engunears learned a little math. And what do you mean by a single point?? Do you not understand the concept that physically measurable quantity has a true constant value but can only be measured in the presence of errors? Do you know that you are making a fool of yourself??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358035737582</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:08:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358037097909-57</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Ban Scenerio ...</Title><Username>cyber_critiquer</Username><Timestamp>1358010997529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:16:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Creek is too much a gentlemen to say this, but I'm not. #$%$!!!!</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1358037097909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:31:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358037442600-58</Id><Topic><Title>People have the right to buy all the C4 explosive they want</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358035242105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:00:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>C4 explosives don't kill, people do. Obama has only four years to get his tyrannical government in order, and his military at your door taking your guns. It is wise to stock up on military killing machines before then. You know how those people are, fast moving when you least expect. Hopefully next time we get a nice safe white in there. If only there were good guys at every corner, beach, sunrise service, ball game, with c4 explosives, there would be no more bad guys trying to use them to hurt our children anymore. It would be a dream world then, no violence , everyone safe.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1358037442600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:37:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358038024703-59</Id><Topic><Title>I bought a Surface and Windows 8 for my PC!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1358002559755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:55:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't wait anymore for my windows PRO. Hopefully in two weeks should have. Also bought WIN8 and love it so far with quick boot and live tiles.</Msg><Username>mystk7</Username><Timestamp>1358038024703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:47:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358038602487-60</Id><Topic><Title>This needs it's own topic line: CFury insists averaging improves accuracy over sticking with significant numbers</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358031364182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:56:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is the point when you realize you have an error, i have seen it before. So i will continue to explain to the board that you are a mathematical idjut and you prove it by not understanding averaging. Why do you pretend the everyday experience of measuring something multiple times and combining these measurements in some way such that a more accurate value is expected is something foreign and not understandable.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358038602487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:56:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358038920173-61</Id><Title>creek doesn't believe there is any benefit to taking multiple readings of a quantity</Title><Msg>and averaging them to obtain a better (more accurate ) result. Is this something they teach in engunearin skool. If so that might explain some of the downfall our country is experiencing.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358038920173</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:02:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358040404523-62</Id><Topic><Title>This needs it's own topic line: CFury insists averaging improves accuracy over sticking with significant numbers</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358031364182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:56:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is the kinda poop you pull when you have no answer. don't worry i will give you plenty of opportunity to prove that you are not a moe ron</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358040404523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:26:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358040605896-63</Id><Topic><Title>creek doesn't believe there is any benefit to taking multiple readings of a quantity</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358038920173</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:02:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>somewhere in inginearin skool they taught him that when averaging numbers to always trim back the result of the average to correspond to the worst measurement. They probably didn't teach him that but that is what he came away with. What is wrong with education in this country??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358040605896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:30:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358041032790-64</Id><Title>Really some other chime in here and say who is crazy</Title><Msg>Creek cannot answer as what would be the best procedure for processing a group of measurements of the same physical quantity so that one can calculate an value that is most likely to be the closer the the true value than the other methods. I thought this sort of thing was done all the time. Don't people who go to colige learn in their fisics classes to average their measurements. Board scientists thinks its a waste of time, WHY ??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358041032790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:37:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358041220399-65</Id><Topic><Title>creek doesn't believe there is any benefit to taking multiple readings of a quantity</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358038920173</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:02:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AGAIN i advise you to consider the word "likely" used in the original question. I really hate to explain the question to you for two reasons. 1 It might ruin my fun making you look like an idy ot. 2 you still might not get it which would be even more embarrassing for U.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358041220399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:40:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358041424581-66</Id><Title>I will prove that averaging is more accurate than applying sig digs to averages</Title><Msg>I have to go and do the rounds on 7 west not but i will be back And then i will show you why using the average is almost always closer to the truth than applying significant digits rules to the average.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358041424581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:43:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358042499917-67</Id><Title>a challenge on significant digits issues by the board scientist</Title><Msg>Creek says {If you weren't a math id-iot you would understand likely makes no difference. There is no case where averaging results in a more accurate number than significant digits or implied significant digits, none, not one} Suppose the true value of a quantity is 10 But i measured 10.069877 7.1240874 8.6227156 10.791516 9.8271631 The actual average is 9.2870717 using sig digs the average should be 9 the average is closer to the true value in this case so creek is directly proven wrong per the last post.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358042499917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:01:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358046268403-68</Id><Topic><Title>a challenge on significant digits issues by the board scientist</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358042499917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:01:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well i guess he was wrong about this one eh??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358046268403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:04:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358046578172-69</Id><Topic><Title>I will prove that averaging is more accurate than applying sig digs to averages</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358041424581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>before i begin with the proof i would like the esteemed board civil enginear to accept or reject the following hypothesis. measurement errors are random, and further using the central limit theorem a sum of these errors approaches a gaussian statistical distribution. Now this seems fairly straight forward for anybody who has studied mathematics but i want to cover my bases before i proceed. So how about it board enginear can you agree with this step??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358046578172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:09:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358046816485-70</Id><Topic><Title>I will prove that averaging is more accurate than applying sig digs to averages</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358041424581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did i say that he doesn't understand the question?? Yes i believe so, and i am vindicated by this precious post where he finds an 'example' of where it does not work. Can you believe he STILL does not get the real question which is NOT whether one particular answer is possible or not but what the probabilities of each method being closer to the exact answer is the real question.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358046816485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:13:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358047361116-71</Id><Topic><Title>a challenge on significant digits issues by the board scientist</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358042499917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:01:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are not correct. You measured to at least six significant digits past the decimal point so your answer (average) could have at least six significant digits too. Remember that you logically (and mathematically) would not know that the "true value" is 10 and only 2 significant digits. Your calculated mean (average) is 9.2870717. According to significant digits maybe you should round that to 9.287072. If you required a real world accuracy of seven significant digits after the decimal then I think you would express your "real" mean as 10.0000000. Or maybe 10.000000. If you are building electronic parts or space ship parts or nuclear fission gizzmos maybe seven significant digits would be important. Expressing your "true value" as 10 would imply that 10 +/- 0.5 is OK! (Thus a range of 9.5 to 10.5.) This might be OK for estimating jelly beans in a box, but might be wholly inadequate for precision mechanics. (I worked around actuaries and statisticians for many years.) I suppose there are valid scientific measurements where billionths can be accurately measured. In most real world cases billionths are not reasonably measurable. Or meaningful. In insurance it is common to round to the nearest whole dollar. In reinsurance we sometimes needed to calculate reinsurance rates to the nearest penny and sometimes to the nearest 1/10th penny to get useful reinsurance premiums. Note that in your example, if we rounded your calculated average to 9.3 we would have a more accurate estimate approaching your given "true value" (e.g. mean) of 10.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1358047361116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:22:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358047908181-72</Id><Topic><Title>I will prove that averaging is more accurate than applying sig digs to averages</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358041424581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a real world example for you. Suppose a carpenter has 16 pieces of 2X4, each longer that 16 inches, and wishes to cut each to be 16 inches long. He takes 2X4 one, measures 16 inches and saws off at the measured point. To save measuring time, he takes 2X4 one and uses it to measure and cut 2X4 two. Then uses 2X4 two to measure and cut 2X4 three. Then 2X4 three to measure and cut 2X4 four, and so on to the nth 2X4 sixteen. Do you think 2X4 sixteen will be the same length as 2X4 one? Will the error among the resulting 2X4s be random and gaussian? Just asking.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1358047908181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358047992743-73</Id><Topic><Title>I will prove that averaging is more accurate than applying sig digs to averages</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358041424581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, Mighty Math Guru, we are awaiting your brilliant proof of everything!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1358047992743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:33:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358048279438-74</Id><Topic><Title>a challenge on significant digits issues by the board scientist</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358042499917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:01:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You pat yourself on the back too quickly. Careful you don't break your arm!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1358048279438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:37:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358048971925-75</Id><Topic><Title>I bought a Surface and Windows 8 for my PC!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1358002559755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:55:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tried Surface RT today at BJ's - 1st time with Windows 8, not as bad as critics say it is - biggest issue people are having is shutting it down - that was easy enough to do after playing with it. Agreed, APPLE has a challenger on its hands, but of course, SURFACE PRO is more than APPLE but it will be popular with business users, and that will be the difference. MSFT is not going away, while APPLE stock is going down. APPLE has a great product with IPAD, but MSFT is ready to challenge. GO MSFT!</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1358048971925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:49:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358049204057-76</Id><Title>Surface PRO coming soon</Title><Msg>more expensive but will be great for business pro - that said, businesses won't blink an eye to spend the $899 IPAD is a great tool, but MSFT is catching up. LONG on MSFT, and WINDOWS 8 will be a success, although it won't be overnight. SMARTPHONES share also going up with NOKIA, Samsung and HTC - MSFT is not dead and on the contrary it's coming back to LIFE. Easily over $30 by year-end 2013 with SURFACE PRO, XBOX 720, and Ballmer leaving for the NBA. Unless we have another 2007 crash....then everything goes down!</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1358049204057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:53:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358049302237-77</Id><Topic><Title>Really some other chime in here and say who is crazy</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358041032790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:37:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Personally, I agree with this. If your measuring device is good to only 0.1 grams +/- 0.05 grams what is the point of claiming increased significant digits to 0.3333333333333333333 grams? Even though that is, accurately 1/3rd gram. Or because some math calculation results in an irrational number claiming that increases your significant digits. Or that if 5000 monkeys each weigh 100 bunches of bananas is it really meaningful to claim that the "true" mean for a bunch of bananas is 2.38768476 pounds. Even if you CAN calculate that value with gaussian statistics. Now if your filling ships with bananas, it MIGHT be important to estimate that an average bunch of bananas is about 2.3877 pounds thus X many bunches of bananas will safely carry in a 20.6 metric ton hold. (We wouldn't want the ship to founder, would we?) But for most practical purposes saying a bunch of bananas is about 2.4 pounds or 2.39 pounds is adequate.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1358049302237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:55:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358049699107-78</Id><Title>MSFT - Smartphones, Gaming, still the platform of choice for OS, Skype</Title><Msg>MSFT is now more embedded in our lives, from phones, to gaming console, and SKYPE will be a great addition down the road and of course, windows still dominates over 90% market share. This is a company that is alive and kicking, and not going away any time soon! GO MSFT!</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1358049699107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:01:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358049792809-79</Id><Title>MSFT at near 52 week low</Title><Msg>with plenty of cash and a low PE, and a dividend to entice, there should be more LONGS than shorts - and I anticipate share price increase for 2013 b/c of great product line! GO MSFT!</Msg><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1358049792809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:03:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358050929798-80</Id><Topic><Title>a challenge on significant digits issues by the board scientist</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358042499917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:01:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I haven't seen this ID since the last time i made crreeed look idyotic</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358050929798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:22:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358051109166-81</Id><Topic><Title>This needs it's own topic line: CFury insists averaging improves accuracy over sticking with significant numbers</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358031364182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:56:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**** How about picking a true value then adding random errors to create hypothetical 'measurements' What you are proposing is scientific fraud! The whole POINT of random averages and the law of large numbers and central limits theorem is that YOU DO NOT KNOW the "true" mean and in most cases CAN NOT KNOW the "true" mean. The whole point of your random measurements and statistical calculations is to ESTIMATE the value of the "true" mean within a range of confidence! There are perhaps 100 billion stars in our galaxy: what is the average mass of a star in our galaxy? There is no way for sure we can know! We measure a random selection of stars in our galaxy, estimate their average mas and declare, within a certain range of confidence, that an average mass of a star in our galaxy is 5.36 solar masses. Then somebody finds a bunch of stars that are way bigger! So we re-estimate, and so on. There is no way we can ever get the "true" average. Here you go, we produce 10,000 cases of jelly beans per day. Each case has a gross of boxes of jelly beans. On average, how many jelly beans are in each box. We want to assure our customers that there are at least 10 jelly beans in a box and not more than 13 jelly beans in a box at least 90% of the time. Remember that we are producing 10,000 new cases of jelly beans every day! We won't ever know what the "true" mean is! We must just estimate it within a range of confidence. Here's another one: In a certain auto rating territory, within a state, we have 3375 insureds covered for collision insurance. Last year there were 1182 accidents invoking collision coverage for a total paid loss of $2,805,645.94. What will the average loss per policy be NEXT year? You can only ESTIMATE the answer within a range of confidence! (Trust me, people using fancy statistics lose on this one every year!)</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1358051109166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:25:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358051614965-82</Id><Topic><Title>This needs it's own topic line: CFury insists averaging improves accuracy over sticking with significant numbers</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358031364182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:56:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bullwinkle this post belongs in the special ed or short bus contribution, but thanks for playing</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358051614965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:33:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358051758227-83</Id><Topic><Title>a challenge on significant digits issues by the board scientist</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358042499917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:01:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, that was several years ago and you goofballs are still rehashing the same trash. Trust me, to 99.99% of the people on this message board it is meaningless nonsense.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1358051758227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:35:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358051766068-84</Id><Topic><Title>Really some other chime in here and say who is crazy</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358041032790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:37:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny you never show unless the hopelessly ignorent hawcreek is backed into a corner. It is good of you to care about his mental state, but it is not good for you to shield him from reality.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358051766068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:36:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358051941831-85</Id><Topic><Title>a challenge on significant digits issues by the board scientist</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358042499917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:01:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well the interesting thing is the coincidence of your return with the board scientist being publicly humiliated. Seems like the last time you showed up he was also being publicly humiliated. Is the rescue of hawcreek your only function??? It seems so</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358051941831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:39:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358053127463-86</Id><Topic><Title>a challenge on significant digits issues by the board scientist</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358042499917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:01:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think I originally started this "thread" by asking how satellites could determine the temperature on the ground to the millionth of a degree, e.g. 9.9999999 since most thermometers are incapable of that refined a measurement. I noticed a lot of satellite temperatures are to the seventh digit after the decimal point. Global warming is usually expressed to the 10th degree C: 0.4 degrees C in the last 100 years (or maybe 0.7 degrees C depending on whose story you're reading.) In my experience 1/10th degree is the limit for most ground based thermometers. At the time you gave an adequate answer that there were statistical methods &amp; proofs for calculating more refined "significant digits" then may have existed in the original data. I still question weather that makes any practical difference in the real world, if your equipment is not capable of measuring it. Saying that warming has increased by 0.3 degrees C (0.7 - 0.4 = 0.3) but doesn't mean much to me since the implied range is 0.25 to 0.35 with an average of 0.3 degrees C.) Then we compare that to the measured temperature (which is maybe 23.4 degrees C[guessing]) and find that our "variation" is 668.6 to 936.0 times less significant than our measured temperature. I am sorry, I wonder if this is really meaningful.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1358053127463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:58:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358053181400-87</Id><Topic><Title>Surface PRO coming soon</Title><Username>ezloan2go</Username><Timestamp>1358049204057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:53:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSFT has been a disaster ever since Balmer took charge. He needs to go. And then MSFT might......might have a chance.</Msg><Username>alphashort</Username><Timestamp>1358053181400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:59:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>