<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371355561266-1</Id><Topic><Title>YOU NOW HAVE MY ATTENTION. I BOUGHT 8. AM HAVING TO USE VITS OLD OS. WHY CONFIG. UPDATES.</Title><Username>rudealfo</Username><Timestamp>1370404804503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:00:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Echo-bots everywhere below. If this is somebody's idea of a joke, it's not funny, it's just stupid.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371355561266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:06:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371356357683-2</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Courting New Developers, But Some Existing Ones Are Still Fuming Over Its Windows 8 Decisions</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368840032983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 21:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not that any of them are paying any attention to you, but that is evidently the official attitude Microsoft has displayed up to now, and that is one of the major reasons Windows 8 is such a flop up to now, and especially the reason Microsoft Store has been such a flop. Microsoft management used to understand that Microsoft needs its community of independent developers more than they need Microsoft. If management no longer understands that, well, that is just one more sign that Microsoft is being seriously mismanaged.</Msg><Username>trollers_nightmare</Username><Timestamp>1371356357683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371356762764-3</Id><Title>JUST AS THE SP. CLEARLY SHOWS MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS THE MARKET. AS ALWAYS. AND PRODUCTS</Title><Msg>Lack development or originality. msft.'s management's biggest flaw, is the insiders play it all for them... To hold over comp'd jobs for paltry results. Never grows... Or returns for investors. proof. The yield leaves longtime longs yielding less than inflation. And waaaaaaaaay below apple or goog. Or even broad market. So as an investment on every metric. msft. stinks. lags. Horrible investment. For 13 years and countin. a game console won't change anything. too too too little. As always. msft underdelivers. Period.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371356762764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:26:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371360954899-4</Id><Title>Windows will be the Apple Smasher!</Title><Msg>A friend was demonstrating Windows phone &amp; Windows 8 on a PC &amp; tablet. Seems you can have Microsoft Office on all three! Phone, PC &amp; tablet. And have them all linked! This is how to get real work done! This is REALLY cool! If you want fidigit over how icons should look, get Apple. If you want to get real work done, get Windows!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.alsharpton</Username><Timestamp>1371360954899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 01:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371362179167-5</Id><Topic><Title>Windows will be the Apple Smasher!</Title><Username>travisthechimp.alsharpton</Username><Timestamp>1371360954899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 01:35:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You ain't talking about 8. nobody with a touchscreen 8 system. all the misreads and gesture errors alone, not to mention flying tiles and no reads, margins and charms getting in the way while you try 2 navigate. too many do overs. very very very time consuming doing everything over. any school kid will get frustrated. but a business person will put that aside and revert to a different system. Like chrome or apple. Too flawed and slow. then the auto-scroll while composing..then add...never mind. this is way flawed. google windows 8 complaints.</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371362179167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 01:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371363028799-6</Id><Title>LADIES AND GENTS, WE HAD A REAL LIVE SUBSPECIES TRAVIS THE LOON POST. READ IT'S WHOLE HISTORY,</Title><Msg>Fascinating right wing rants. Amazing. 113 tea party unrelated to investing posts. faaar out. these tea party spam posters are all over the social medias just spreading vile comments, hate, and fear. amazing.</Msg><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371363028799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371363146284-7</Id><Title>ALABAMA RESEARCH SHOWED VIEWERS OF FOX NEWS HAD FAR LOWER IQ'S AND COMPREHENSION. BY TRAVIS</Title><Msg>Read his posts... Truely reflects a cancer on our medias and society.</Msg><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371363146284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:12:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371365083767-8</Id><Topic><Title>LADIES AND GENTS, WE HAD A REAL LIVE SUBSPECIES TRAVIS THE LOON POST. READ IT'S WHOLE HISTORY,</Title><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371363028799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why they're losing ground. It isn't cool to be dumb hate mongers.They don't get i so they're a dying breed. All they got is warped logic form FOX News and hatred. They don't have a clue as to how to promote positive thinking. They say they believe in Jesus; but tough luck for everyone who can't take care of themselves or needs help. Helping others is a bad thing. Especially if they happen to be a minority. They claim all such people are deadbeats. Is that supposed to be Jesus' message? They're hypocrites and sound like they were spawned by the Devil. They're voice is diminishing. The only people listening are other Tea Baggers. They're more like annoying mosquitoes.</Msg><Username>rumi1one</Username><Timestamp>1371365083767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371368635129-9</Id><Topic><Title>LADIES AND GENTS, WE HAD A REAL LIVE SUBSPECIES TRAVIS THE LOON POST. READ IT'S WHOLE HISTORY,</Title><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371363028799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you NZealanders always need to scream?</Msg><Username>logge_0dd</Username><Timestamp>1371368635129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 03:43:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371373739039-10</Id><Topic><Title>Windows will be the Apple Smasher!</Title><Username>travisthechimp.alsharpton</Username><Timestamp>1371360954899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 01:35:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 is the new Vista! I hate Windows 8 so much, I switched to a Samsung Google Chromebook running Chrome OS on an ARM processor and NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371373739039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 05:08:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371373927020-11</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 continues to fail</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370287653415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 is great for Apple, Google and Samsung. Sent from a Samsung Google Chromebook with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371373927020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 05:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371374627722-12</Id><Topic><Title>HP AND GOOGLE TEAM UP.. "IT IN A BOX". MSFT IN TROUBLE. NSA SUITS. ORSEN WELLS "BIG MSFT BROTHER"</Title><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1370994049094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:40:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why I switched to a Samsung Google Chromebook with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371374627722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 05:23:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371374752225-13</Id><Title>Amazon's Bestselling Laptop</Title><Msg>Amazon's bestselling laptop does NOT run Windows 8. It's the Samsung Google Chromebook with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371374752225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 05:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371379273508-14</Id><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Msg>They should have stuck with an average of 95 or something that is not on the surface of it a lie. The "study" purported H.Q. to be from Alabama actually has a Washington D.C. call back number. Because of ND contracts they cannot reveal the actual study or who funded it. Now, gullible Obama bois, try to think for a minute, how would one survey watched network AND learn that viewers actual I,Q.?????? Well I just sold a pile of real estate so I sent $50K to a research/detective firm in D.C. which found it was not actually Fox viewers tallied but how Obama supporters PERCEIVED Fox viewers. Further, since I was paying for an investigation and a new survey it was discovered that Fox viewers actually had an I.Q. of 104 4% above national average. An additional question found that 69% of those who support Obama found lying an acceptable vehicle to the end of agenda advancement. 62% realize Obama lies with some regularity. 65% want recent scandals swept under the rug so that the welfare checks can continue. The last two questions were the killers though, my study found 22% of Obama supporters were unemployed, almost three times the official national average and of those unemployed Obama defenders the average I.Q. was 87. My study is real and scientifically done, trust me, gullible morons.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371383572764-15</Id><Topic><Title>Bestselling Laptop</Title><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371288268007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 05:24:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon's #1 bestselling laptop is the Samsung running Windows 8, IE 10 and Microsoft Office. The Google Doc mishmash of an office system suite sucks air- and is no match for Microsoft office. One thing you need to remember about pricing your products- Sh.t may be free but you still cant give it away</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371383572764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 07:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371383614340-16</Id><Topic><Title>Bestselling Laptop</Title><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371288268007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 05:24:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't penguins go around picking sh.t all day?? let us know</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371383614340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 07:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371385570379-17</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"dound Fox vierers" Now you know why they found Fox viewers the dumbest!</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1371385570379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371385910164-18</Id><Title>Windows 8, PC shipment decline is worst EVER</Title><Msg>Google it. Published two months ago. Quoting: "At this point, unfortunately, it seems clear that the Windows 8 launch not only failed to provide a positive boost to the PC market, but appears to have slowed the market", Bob O'Donnell, IDC vice president, says. Holy Moley, Windows 8 slowed the market? You want to know why Ballmer booted Sinfosky out the door? O'Donnell offers chilling indictment. "While some consumers appreciate the new form factors and touch capabilities of Windows 8, the radical changes to the UI, removal of the familiar Start button, and the costs associated with touch have made PCs a less attractive alternative to dedicated tablets and other competitive devices", he says. "Microsoft will have to make some very tough decisions moving forward if it wants to help reinvigorate the PC market".</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371385910164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371385989833-19</Id><Title>Exclusive Games - XBox One leads PS4 2 to 1</Title><Msg>Why do gamers buy a box? To play games of course. With XBox One having twice as many exclusive games, you have to figure in the end that alone will lead to XBox One dominating the market. And with MSFT's moves to appease developers, I think Mister Softy's lead in the exclusive game category will grow, leaving Sony and PS4 in the dust. I understand the knee jerk reaction of the market is to favor PS4 over XBox One due to restrictions MSFT has put in place... But in the end there is NOTHING more restrictive than not having the best games to play. And that is one restriction PS4 will likely never be able to overcome versus XBox One. With the undisputed lead in exclusive games, MSFT put restrictions in place because they can. When push comes to shove, I think most gamers will want the box with the best games. That will be XBox One all the way.</Msg><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371385989833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371387049743-20</Id><Topic><Title>Windows will be the Apple Smasher!</Title><Username>travisthechimp.alsharpton</Username><Timestamp>1371360954899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 01:35:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huh? Vista is a great O/S!</Msg><Username>mc_penner_2006</Username><Timestamp>1371387049743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371387196095-21</Id><Title>AAPL put out a new version of QuickTime which SUCKS!</Title><Msg>Why do they even make suckie software?</Msg><Username>mc_penner_2006</Username><Timestamp>1371387196095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371387997250-22</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Now you know why they found Fox viewers the dumbest!" Not too sure what that means, if you are suggesting thinking faster than accurate touch typing indicates a lower I.Q?... actually the opposite is true. And if you were selecting me as an example, I seldom watch Fox, I watch Brian Williams because I want to know what the enemies of America are saying. Then from time to time Lester Holt substitutes for Williams and is far more fair and a better anchor and NBC just gives news but I can count on Williams to slant it far left. Besides as to low I.Q. I always figure out your new aliases in a post of two, pigeon.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371387997250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371389421334-23</Id><Topic><Title>Any math people out there?</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371240814183</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 16:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong V(n)=f(n) not the iteration</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1371389421334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371389680973-24</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is no secret that conservatives are lower in intelligence. Have you ever listened to any of them, nothing but dumb talking points and no understanding.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1371389680973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:34:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371390442267-25</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kind of like your posts Cfur. Dumb talking points.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371390442267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:47:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371391505599-26</Id><Topic><Title>Windows will be the Apple Smasher!</Title><Username>travisthechimp.alsharpton</Username><Timestamp>1371360954899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 01:35:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>papa wewe is the new penguin only twice as stupid if that's possible, this message brought to you by the OS DE FACTO WinDoz8 with no stinking penguin inside!</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371391505599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371392023980-27</Id><Topic><Title>Any math people out there?</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371240814183</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 16:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Theoretically...never.</Msg><Username>faretheenotbad</Username><Timestamp>1371392023980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:13:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371392515788-28</Id><Topic><Title>SONY POS4 IS ONLY AVAILABLE ON DEC 31/2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371348729734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sony is going to lose money on the POS4 and if I were a Sony shareholder, I would be very worried.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371392515788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371392600978-29</Id><Topic><Title>SO folks higher multiple for MSFT is surely on the table....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370630218480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:36:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The earnings will be hear soon.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371392600978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371392636819-30</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 IMPRESSIVE</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1371224494771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:41:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371392636819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371392697085-31</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT valuation....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367458331128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just look at the CRM evaporate with all the GS's BS.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371392697085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371392751547-32</Id><Topic><Title>WHY GS Is Betting Against MSFT....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369342746864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes this is all about Cloud Azure and is already sold out.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371392751547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371392782390-33</Id><Topic><Title>WHY Windows will win this round as well....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368147359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371392782390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371392929242-34</Id><Topic><Title>XBOX ONE - The Day The World Changed Forever....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369158573053</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is funny as POS4 is listed to be shipped on Dec. 31/2013 on the Amazon (Not to be ready for Xmas or Black Friday). And there goes all the BS and hype by Sony as they even don't have a product to run their games on.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371392929242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371392983567-35</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft and Best Buy Partner on Windows Stores (Bloomberg)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371149056377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 14:44:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This will be all ready for back to school in August.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371392983567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371393026379-36</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It is no secret that ..." It is no secret that you are not the one to comment on the intelligence of others, I've read your posts and your failed attempts at displays of erudition.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371393026379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371393061952-37</Id><Topic><Title>Office 365 Available for iPhone. First Apple switches to Bing. And now this. The impact on earnings from both will be huge.</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371209508742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 07:31:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This will boost the earnings by "another" 30 cents a share.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371393061952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:31:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371393134616-38</Id><Topic><Title>Sony Playstaion Is A Glorified VCR....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370999660289</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 21:14:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it won't be ready for Black Friday or even Xmas.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371393134616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371393382730-39</Id><Topic><Title>Developers, Publishers and Microsoft....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371053182625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sony is going to lose money on POS4 for pricing it below cost and alienating the developers and Xbox-1 with more than twice the number of exclusive games, Kinect and of course Cloud will put POS4 out of its misery soon now that the POS4 design is incomplete and will be delivered only on the New Year's eve missing Black Friday and Xmas. What a laugh.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371393382730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371393554664-40</Id><Topic><Title>Oppenheimer raised Microsoft PT to $39 from $34.</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1370607137497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:12:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a code word for $100 a share.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371393554664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371395547828-41</Id><Topic><Title>SONY POS4 IS ONLY AVAILABLE ON DEC 31/2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371348729734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes Sony is in trouble and this is a good indication..... For those who want to confirm POS4's delivery, jut go to the Amazon website. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371395547828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371395782929-42</Id><Topic><Title>SONY POS4 IS ONLY AVAILABLE ON DEC 31/2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371348729734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Xmas - right around the time MSFT hits $250. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371395782929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371395854964-43</Id><Topic><Title>Exclusive Games - XBox One leads PS4 2 to 1</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371385989833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:33:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree as XBOX ONE has Kinect built in as well and offers 15 great exclusives such as the NFL, NBA and all the production from the Spielberg Studios and Sony will be the loser at the end as they have a loser mentality/strategy pricing POS4 below cost, it is not ready and the latest info suggests that it will be shipped on Dec 31/2013 or New Year 2014.... Kind of stupid move all this week by Sony to fight off XBOX ONE with more BS. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371395854964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371395963767-44</Id><Topic><Title>SO folks higher multiple for MSFT is surely on the table....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370630218480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:36:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes and $300 by New Years. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371395963767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371401444391-45</Id><Topic><Title>SO folks higher multiple for MSFT is surely on the table....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370630218480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:36:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes the shorts' BS is the same as March 2013 and we all know how that worked out for them after our Q1/2013 earnings release. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371401444391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371401821889-46</Id><Title>Analysis: Fed-induced selloff has investors hunting for bargains (Reuters)....</Title><Msg>SO folks as I pointed out two weeks ago, Buy on Bernanke Dip as the Bond Buying program will stretch well into 2014.... Just Bing the title above. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371401821889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:57:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371401936618-47</Id><Topic><Title>Buy On This Bernanke Dip ALL YOU CAN....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369324689535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just Bing: "Analysis: Fed-induced selloff has investors hunting for bargains"..... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371401936618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371403076280-48</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kind of like your posts agolferbogie / Hawcreek / Obama_nation, etc. Dumb talking points.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371403076280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371403205743-49</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I just sold a pile of real estate so I sent $50K" "Fox viewers actually had an I.Q. of 104 4% above national average." Gee, you got ripped-off .... I guess that is the Low IQ Conservative way.</Msg><Username>atomic_brassiere</Username><Timestamp>1371403205743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:20:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371403500887-50</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is no secret that conservatives are lower in intelligence. Have you ever listened to any of them, nothing but dumb talking points and no understanding.</Msg><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371403500887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371403665247-51</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8, PC shipment decline is worst EVER</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371385910164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:31:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google it. Published two months ago. Quoting: "At this point, unfortunately, it seems clear that the Windows 8 launch not only failed to provide a positive boost to the PC market, but appears to have slowed the market", Bob O'Donnell, IDC vice president, says. Holy Moley, Windows 8 slowed the market? You want to know why Ballmer booted Sinfosky out the door? O'Donnell offers chilling indictment. "While some consumers appreciate the new form factors and touch capabilities of Windows 8, the radical changes to the UI, removal of the familiar Start button, and the costs associated with touch have made PCs a less attractive alternative to dedicated tablets and other competitive devices", he says. "Microsoft will have to make some very tough decisions moving forward if it wants to help reinvigorate the PC market". Less</Msg><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371403665247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371403789057-52</Id><Topic><Title>Amazon's Bestselling Laptop</Title><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1371374752225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 05:25:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon's bestselling laptop does NOT run Windows 8. It's the Samsung Google Chromebook with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371403789057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371403839246-53</Id><Topic><Title>HP AND GOOGLE TEAM UP.. "IT IN A BOX". MSFT IN TROUBLE. NSA SUITS. ORSEN WELLS "BIG MSFT BROTHER"</Title><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1370994049094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:40:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why I switched to a Samsung Google Chromebook with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371403839246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371403885473-54</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 continues to fail</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370287653415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 is great for Apple, Google and Samsung. Sent from a Samsung Google Chromebook with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371403885473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371403919561-55</Id><Topic><Title>Windows will be the Apple Smasher!</Title><Username>travisthechimp.alsharpton</Username><Timestamp>1371360954899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 01:35:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Windows 8 is the new Vista! I hate Windows 8 so much, I switched to a Samsung Google Chromebook running Chrome OS on an ARM processor and NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371403919561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371403938721-56</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't think for yourself, I see, Friday.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371403938721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:32:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404087383-57</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Faux news study shows clearly... Right wing nut jobs.. Mentally challanged.</Msg><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371404087383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404202050-58</Id><Topic><Title>LADIES AND GENTS, WE HAD A REAL LIVE SUBSPECIES TRAVIS THE LOON POST. READ IT'S WHOLE HISTORY,</Title><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371363028799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why they're losing ground. It isn't cool to be dumb hate mongers.They don't get i so they're a dying breed. All they got is warped logic form FOX News and hatred. They don't have a clue as to how to promote positive thinking. They say they believe in Jesus; but tough luck for everyone who can't take care of themselves or needs help. Helping others is a bad thing. Especially if they happen to be a minority. They claim all such people are deadbeats. Is that supposed to be Jesus' message? They're hypocrites and sound like they were spawned by the Devil. They're voice is diminishing. The only people listening are other Tea Baggers. They're more like annoying mosquitoes</Msg><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371404202050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:36:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404267098-59</Id><Topic><Title>ALABAMA RESEARCH SHOWED VIEWERS OF FOX NEWS HAD FAR LOWER IQ'S AND COMPREHENSION. BY TRAVIS</Title><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371363146284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:12:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TRUE TRUE....PUT LIPSTICK ON IT. LOL....</Msg><Username>rollin_correction</Username><Timestamp>1371404267098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404307297-60</Id><Topic><Title>LADIES AND GENTS, WE HAD A REAL LIVE SUBSPECIES TRAVIS THE LOON POST. READ IT'S WHOLE HISTORY,</Title><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371363028799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fascinating right wing rants. Amazing. 113 tea party unrelated to investing posts. faaar out. these tea party spam posters are all over the social medias just spreading vile comments, hate, and fear. amazing.</Msg><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371404307297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404360694-61</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Is Courting New Developers, But Some Existing Ones Are Still Fuming Over Its Windows 8 Decisions</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1368840032983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 21:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You ain't talking about 8. nobody with a touchscreen 8 system. all the misreads and gesture errors alone, not to mention flying tiles and no reads, margins and charms getting in the way while you try 2 navigate. too many do overs. very very very time consuming doing everything over. any school kid will get frustrated. but a business person will put that aside and revert to a different system. Like chrome or apple. Too flawed and slow. then the auto-scroll while composing..then add...never mind. this is way flawed. google windows 8 complaints.</Msg><Username>didya_hear</Username><Timestamp>1371404360694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:39:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404409759-62</Id><Topic><Title>JUST AS THE SP. CLEARLY SHOWS MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS THE MARKET. AS ALWAYS. AND PRODUCTS</Title><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371356762764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:26:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lack development or originality. msft.'s management's biggest flaw, is the insiders play it all for them... To hold over comp'd jobs for paltry results. Never grows... Or returns for investors. proof. The yield leaves longtime longs yielding less than inflation. And waaaaaaaaay below apple or goog. Or even broad market. So as an investment on every metric. msft. stinks. lags. Horrible investment. For 13 years and countin. a game console won't change anything. too too too little. As always. msft underdelivers. Period.</Msg><Username>sargentfriday</Username><Timestamp>1371404409759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371404593859-63</Id><Title>If we all had super strict gun laws, we could be like Chicago</Title><Msg>6 shot within 25 minutes in the Burroughs, could godfather Rahm maybe bring that to the nation? "More than two dozen people were shot Saturday afternoon into Father's Day Sunday across the city, according to authorities. Of the 26 people shot, six died either at the crime scenes or at local hospitals. The youngest was 16. One of the men killed was an armed man shot by police after he raised a 9-millimeter handgun in their direction after bailing from a moving car, authorities said."</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371404593859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404708271-64</Id><Topic><Title>ACTUALLY. MSFT PE IS 18. QUITE HIGH. OVER THE CURRENT S&amp;P AVG. AND LOW YIELD. SO DOWN GOES SP.</Title><Username>joeeddy69</Username><Timestamp>1371349664077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Msft p/e is 18. faux news iq challanged see it diff. but hey... They are always wrong. google it.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371404708271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404755614-65</Id><Topic><Title>ANYONE TRYING TO SELL A CONSOLE IS IN TROUBLE. IT'S MOBILE STUPID !!!!!</Title><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371349837115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:30:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at the stock performance for every game oem...and they all stink.. So when you shills wish to brag console... I laugh.. It's purely obfuscation for 8 being unfunished.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371404755614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404806134-66</Id><Topic><Title>HEY WHEN PUMPERS CANNOT ADDRESS IT ISSUES WITH 8, THEY ARE UNQUALIFIED TO JUDGE. I'M POSTING</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370400205808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:43:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8 stinks all know...goes lower.....and bing is a virus. Period.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371404806134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404842834-67</Id><Topic><Title>Xpox One pricing paves way for Sony PS4 success</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371159575598</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 17:39:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumpity....xpox1 is doomed</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371404842834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:47:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404849665-68</Id><Topic><Title>ACTUALLY. MSFT PE IS 18. QUITE HIGH. OVER THE CURRENT S&amp;P AVG. AND LOW YIELD. SO DOWN GOES SP.</Title><Username>joeeddy69</Username><Timestamp>1371349664077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As msft is a perinnial under-performer. best market in history. msft. Goes down. Why. Old in decline... And fully diluted. too many shares distributed. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371404849665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404862651-69</Id><Topic><Title>Sony sucker-punches Xbox on price, specs, DRM-free gaming</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371096608613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 00:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump again.......</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371404862651</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404873637-70</Id><Topic><Title>M$ admits they lost the console war with Xpox One</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371257635356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 20:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another bump</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371404873637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404916459-71</Id><Topic><Title>At a tiny 0.53%, Windoze 8 adoption levels in the enterprise are shockingly low</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370388335249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This never gets tiring</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371404916459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371405458601-72</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Faux news study shows clearly... Right wing nut jobs.. Mentally challanged." Anyone watching the talking point, made up left wing "Faux" News is "challenged" i.e. not as smart as "challanged" . Those watching Fox News get the story first and fair and straight. I get my news from many sources so I don't need Fox, I watch NBC to see the lies the left is making to cover for the Failure in Chief.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371405458601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371405641695-73</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A few weeks ago one of the most popular Google searches was "Who is Ben Gazzy?" Those weren't Fox viewers. Those were more Obama useful idiots.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371405641695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371405685290-74</Id><Topic><Title>ACTUALLY. MSFT PE IS 18. QUITE HIGH. OVER THE CURRENT S&amp;P AVG. AND LOW YIELD. SO DOWN GOES SP.</Title><Username>joeeddy69</Username><Timestamp>1371349664077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha ha ha... Pe is 18. Fool all know that...this is not 2014. wake up fool.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371405685290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371405798362-75</Id><Topic><Title>HEY WHEN PUMPERS CANNOT ADDRESS IT ISSUES WITH 8, THEY ARE UNQUALIFIED TO JUDGE. I'M POSTING</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370400205808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:43:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8 can't touch chrome. and all know it. Amzn best retailer sez chrome.. Best seller.... Google it.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371405798362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371405850367-76</Id><Topic><Title>YOU NOW HAVE MY ATTENTION. I BOUGHT 8. AM HAVING TO USE VITS OLD OS. WHY CONFIG. UPDATES.</Title><Username>rudealfo</Username><Timestamp>1370404804503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:00:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Msft took over my pc. Even with my custom task schedule....myy my....they write software to make us think we own our new $800.00 machine.....only to find...no no no...msft...takes over even against my wishes.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371405850367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:04:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371405917086-77</Id><Topic><Title>SARAH LIPSTICK, DEER IN THE HEADLIGHTS LIAR .....PAHLIN....TOPS AT FUAX NEWS. AGAIN.. HA HA WHAT A DOPE.</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371346343869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 21:32:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you say she balled glenn beck.. I knew it.. I heard she blewrush. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371405917086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371406612793-78</Id><Topic><Title>At a tiny 0.53%, Windoze 8 adoption levels in the enterprise are shockingly low</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370388335249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AGREED....</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371406612793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371406705077-79</Id><Topic><Title>LADIES AND GENTS, WE HAD A REAL LIVE SUBSPECIES TRAVIS THE LOON POST. READ IT'S WHOLE HISTORY,</Title><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371363028799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why they're losing ground. It isn't cool to be dumb hate mongers.They don't get i so they're a dying breed. All they got is warped logic form FOX News and hatred. They don't have a clue as to how to promote positive thinking. They say they believe in Jesus; but tough luck for everyone who can't take care of themselves or needs help. Helping others is a bad thing. Especially if they happen to be a minority. They claim all such people are deadbeats. Is that supposed to be Jesus' message? They're hypocrites and sound like they were spawned by the Devil. They're voice is diminishing. The only people listening are other Tea Baggers. They're more like annoying mosquitoes</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371406705077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:18:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371406836575-80</Id><Topic><Title>Any math people out there?</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371240814183</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 16:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes - of course. That was a given. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371406836575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:20:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371407149736-81</Id><Title>FOR NON FOX NEWS VIEWERS. ( AS THEY CAN'T READ.)</Title><Msg>Alec Baldwin, Matt Damon and John Cusack are among an array of A-list actors starring in a new video urging President Barack Obama to "set the world's course" for an end to nuclear weapons at next week's G8 Summit in Northern Ireland. "Some argue that the spread of these weapons cannot be stopped, cannot be checked," actor Robert De Niro says in the video. "Such fatalism is a deadly adversary," Damon responds. Whoopi Goldberg, Morgan Freeman, Naomi Watts and Christoph Waltz also appear in the two-and-a-half minute spot. The video was produced by Global Zero, a Washington, D.C.-based grassroots organization whose mission is "to eliminate all nuclear weapons by 2030." The message from national security experts and citizens around the world is clear: the only way to eliminate the global nuclear danger is to eliminate all nuclear weapons, Michael Douglas says. It's time to set the world's course to zero. To do so, Global Zero said in a press release, President Obama "will have to go beyond the bilateral process President Reagan started of U.S.-Soviet/Russian arms reductions and bring the other leading nuclear powers into international arms negotiations for the first time in history." The group also sent an open letter to Obama recalling a 2009 speech in which the president committed to their cause.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371407149736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371407757788-82</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that what you dound. that spelling or typo's or reverse amortization formulas are the sign of smarts... What a stupid premise. more to caring about typos or stupid numbers formulas having nothing to do with iq. more to education or givingash.-----t. nobody cares. you trying to play smart... Is great entertainment...</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371407757788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371407792792-83</Id><Topic><Title>Sony sucker-punches Xbox on price, specs, DRM-free gaming</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371096608613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 00:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People only think they want PS4 because it's a little cheaper. Wait until they realize all the awesome exclusive games are on XBox One. Then everyone will be chiming in how great XBox One is and worth a few extra bucks. BTW PS4 might not even be available until after the holidays, ROFLMAO XBox One will be here for Black Friday.</Msg><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371407792792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:36:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371407815548-84</Id><Topic><Title>JUST AS THE SP. CLEARLY SHOWS MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS THE MARKET. AS ALWAYS. AND PRODUCTS</Title><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371356762764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:26:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lack development or originality. msft.'s management's biggest flaw, is the insiders play it all for them... To hold over comp'd jobs for paltry results. Never grows... Or returns for investors. proof. The yield leaves longtime longs yielding less than inflation. And waaaaaaaaay below apple or goog. Or even broad market. So as an investment on every metric. msft. stinks. lags. Horrible investment. For 13 years and countin. a game console won't change anything. too too too little. As always. msft underdelivers. Period.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371407815548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371407916035-85</Id><Topic><Title>Sony sucker-punches Xbox on price, specs, DRM-free gaming</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371096608613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 00:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually if you dd games at cnet or gme or amzn... Then you would know msft is 7th in titles.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371407916035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371408053605-86</Id><Title>No Wonder Sony Charging Less for PS4. Low Number of Exclusive Games</Title><Msg>XBox One has way more games people want. XBox One will sell more games to their users compared to Sony. And MSFT will end up selling way more more boxes than Sony, because XBox One already has 2x as many exclusive games. And that gap will only widen.</Msg><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371408053605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:40:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371408154848-87</Id><Title>OHMYMAMMA'SCARE</Title><Msg>JUSTTHINK ABOUT IT !!</Msg><Username>littlejohnmccain</Username><Timestamp>1371408154848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371408157513-88</Id><Title>INSIDERS OWN 10% OF THIS DEBT. RIDDEN CO. YET RECIEVE 50% OF PROFITS. EXEC. COMP FOR PISSPOOR PERFORMANCE. 2 DECADES NOW.</Title><Msg>AND MSFT ISN'T #1 IN ANY CATEGORY.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408157513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371408173034-89</Id><Topic><Title>NBC just featured a former Interior Designer now working at McDonalds</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371250133114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 18:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawcrapper loves his food stamps. When Bernanke said Obamas policies do not support a recovery that told the story. Obama is placing this debt on the next two generations. Liberals made promises for the vote, now even Illinois's pension plans at 900B in debt, so one of these days those pensioners checks are going to a fraction of what was promised, very much like Greece. The horde yells and is enraged with hate while hearing the truth</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371408173034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371408189426-90</Id><Topic><Title>Exclusive Games - XBox One leads PS4 2 to 1</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371385989833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:33:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wall Street will figure it out soon enough. XBox One has all the games. No wonder Sony box is cheaper. Who wants to buy a box with 50% less of the top games choices?</Msg><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371408189426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:43:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371408406896-91</Id><Title>AS I WAS SAYING... MSFT IS A SCAM. HIGH PAY....POOR RESULTS. PC SALES DOWN HUGE. WIN. 8 TO BLAME</Title><Msg>And repubs claims false. a huge recession follows every repub. Prez. For past 50 years....and all know it...</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371408406896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371408465883-92</Id><Topic><Title>Exclusive Games - XBox One leads PS4 2 to 1</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371385989833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:33:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But you are an excremental kibax. Even M$ were talking up the xpox for everything EXCEPT gaming.</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371408465883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:47:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371408519554-93</Id><Title>MSFT 7TH IN GAMES. GOOGLE IT. XBOX A PIMPLE ON A GNATS..AS--- WON'T SAVE MSFT. TOO FLAWED.</Title><Msg>NO NEW GAME HAS KINECT. TELL YA ANYTHING?????</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371408519554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371408528246-94</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"nobody cares..." There it is, always comes out sooner or later the common mental disorder factor for the Obama supporter with dozens of aliases who is also a Microsoft lying moron. He thinks he/she speaks for "everyone" which is a sure sign of visions of grandeur, mental illness. It's the same for all but a couple of Obama supporting idiots here.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371408528246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371408562593-95</Id><Topic><Title>M$ admits they lost the console war with Xpox One</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371257635356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 20:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>re-bump....</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371408562593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371408643881-96</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, hawKKKunt....projecting much? Why don't you FOAD, Dunning-Kruger Orbo buyer?</Msg><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371408643881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371408696646-97</Id><Topic><Title>FOR NON FOX NEWS VIEWERS. ( AS THEY CAN'T READ.)</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371407149736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suspect you're right on this one, probably a majority of non Fox viewers can't read. Some can, I don't typically watch Fox and I can read, but the majority of the left wing / low information / useful idiots for Obama probably can read a few words, but here they display little ability to comprehend.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371408696646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:51:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371408887238-98</Id><Title>Anyone else notice the Obama useful idiots are becoming more angry and strident by the day?</Title><Msg>For a long while his demolition of America went on unabated and with the non objecting tacit support of too many not paying attention. Now the Obama useful idiots finally realize they are losing the PR spin gambit that worked for them for so long.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371408887238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371408987534-99</Id><Topic><Title>FOR NON FOX NEWS VIEWERS. ( AS THEY CAN'T READ.)</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371407149736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See there is a great example. you didn't understand the post. so you read it bassackwards....from now on... More misspelled words so you can rant. obviously you are incapable of comprehension...which is a sign of your low iq.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371408987534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:56:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371409123859-100</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you admit msft hires dimwits like yourself to pump garbage... I agree.</Msg><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371409123859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371409287590-101</Id><Topic><Title>Do a little "study" on the research that dound Fox vierers with lower I.Q.s</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371379273508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There it is, always comes out sooner or later the common mental disorder factor for the Obama supporter with dozens of aliases who is also a Microsoft lying moron.</Msg><Username>gottaloveobama</Username><Timestamp>1371409287590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371409416730-102</Id><Topic><Title>LADIES AND GENTS, WE HAD A REAL LIVE SUBSPECIES TRAVIS THE LOON POST. READ IT'S WHOLE HISTORY,</Title><Username>tellya_anything</Username><Timestamp>1371363028799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why they're losing ground. It isn't cool to be dumb hate mongers.They don't get i so they're a dying breed. All they got is warped logic form FOX News and hatred. They don't have a clue as to how to promote positive thinking. They say they believe in Jesus; but tough luck for everyone who can't take care of themselves or needs help. Helping others is a bad thing. Especially if they happen to be a minority. They claim all such people are deadbeats. Is that supposed to be Jesus' message? They're hypocrites and sound like they were spawned by the Devil. They're voice is diminishing. The only people listening are other Tea Baggers. They're more like annoying mosquitoes</Msg><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371409416730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371409462472-103</Id><Topic><Title>At a tiny 0.53%, Windoze 8 adoption levels in the enterprise are shockingly low</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370388335249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'M NOT SURPRIZED.. AS 8 STINKS... AND WII IS #1</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371409462472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371409509723-104</Id><Topic><Title>SARAH LIPSTICK, DEER IN THE HEADLIGHTS LIAR .....PAHLIN....TOPS AT FUAX NEWS. AGAIN.. HA HA WHAT A DOPE.</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371346343869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 21:32:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you say she balled glenn beck.. I knew it.. I heard she blewrush. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>gottaloveobama</Username><Timestamp>1371409509723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371409650578-105</Id><Title>PUMPERS ATTEMPT TO CLAIM, MSFT WILL GO WAY UP, AT SAME TIME CLAIM MARKET CRASH, AND ECON. IN SHAMBLES.</Title><Msg>Typical tea bag nonsense. not based in a reality format.</Msg><Username>gottaloveobama</Username><Timestamp>1371409650578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371409856419-106</Id><Topic><Title>JUST AS THE SP. CLEARLY SHOWS MSFT UNDER-PERFORMS THE MARKET. AS ALWAYS. AND PRODUCTS</Title><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371356762764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:26:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lack development or originality. msft.'s management's biggest flaw, is the insiders play it all for them... To hold over comp'd jobs for paltry results. Never grows... Or returns for investors. proof. The yield leaves longtime longs yielding less than inflation. And waaaaaaaaay below apple or goog. Or even broad market. So as an investment on every metric. msft. stinks. lags. Horrible investment. For 13 years and countin. a game console won't change anything. too too too little. As always. msft underdelivers. Period.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371409856419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:10:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371410142133-107</Id><Topic><Title>FOR NON FOX NEWS VIEWERS. ( AS THEY CAN'T READ.)</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371407149736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One might care about their acting, but why would anyone care about their politics?</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1371410142133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371410407960-108</Id><Title>BUSH LEFT MILLIONS IN FORECLOSURE. AND UNEMPLOYED...OBAMA HAS LED US TO HERE. I SALUTE</Title><Msg>Funny as we are a democracy and democrats lead us out of the greatest financial meltdown in history. majority favor democrats and obama. see ratings for proof. obama leads with 54%. bush 23%. at his horrible scam with chris cox, greenspun, hank paulsen, and the repub. Lead congress. what do ya think.... America knows better after nixon, reagan, and 2 bushes. never again... Wait til midterms... Aaaaggghhh the repub. Posers in congress. who have done zip... Will get the usa...boot.</Msg><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371410407960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:20:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371410976528-109</Id><Topic><Title>BUSH LEFT MILLIONS IN FORECLOSURE. AND UNEMPLOYED...OBAMA HAS LED US TO HERE. I SALUTE</Title><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371410407960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:20:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post your OT political sewage on an appropriate board</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371410976528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371411527441-110</Id><Title>Bush left millions with the Clinton/Frank/Waters mortgage legacy, anyone who claims different is</Title><Msg>a liar or a useful idiot for Obama. And the useful idiots are getting comically animated as the Liar in Chief is exposed as the poser he is.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371411527441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371411734363-111</Id><Topic><Title>BUSH LEFT MILLIONS IN FORECLOSURE. AND UNEMPLOYED...OBAMA HAS LED US TO HERE. I SALUTE</Title><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371410407960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:20:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oooh but willie.. U love the constant barrage of right wing whackjob posts here 24/7. you never complaina about that.. Do ya.. Tea-bagger. Or is that just bagholder. Either way...as was posted.. Keep it up.. And recieve the same in return.... Cost of pumping waaaay up since willie and the crew attacked the msft-victim. who posted win. 8 poor unfinished...and broken. 1 post. And you all attacked. not smart. costs have incresed for msft. To pay lame pumpers. Lol... Right back atcha..</Msg><Username>trollers_nightmare</Username><Timestamp>1371411734363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371411931914-112</Id><Title>ACTUALLY IT WAS GREENSPUN, COX, PAULSEN AND BOEHNER.. YA LIAR. CLINTO WAS THE BEST. AND ALL KNOW IT.</Title><Msg>Bush the worst. well known. mission accomplished. usa broken... Bush wouldn't have been in office if jeb bush hadn't cheated america out of a fair election. gore won. On all metrics.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371411931914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:45:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371412199448-113</Id><Title>WHY the shorts are afraid of Dr. Osso....</Title><Msg>Folks it makes me laugh as now there are several bogus aliases similar to mine.... And it only suggests one thing: "Fear".... SO hang tough and Buy on this Dip. Stay Long and Prosper. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371412199448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371412297002-114</Id><Topic><Title>Buy On This Bernanke Dip ALL YOU CAN....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369324689535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes we will have another volatile week with the G8 and the Fed talk till Wed.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371412297002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371412339359-115</Id><Title>Don't Forget Microsoft Makes Money on Every Single Android Or Chrome OS Phone made by Foxconn</Title><Msg>That is a lot of income from the patent infringement that Foxconn has to pay to Microsoft.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371412339359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:52:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371412349899-116</Id><Topic><Title>Analysis: Fed-induced selloff has investors hunting for bargains (Reuters)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371401821889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is another must read. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371412349899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371412430783-117</Id><Title>Rapp The NSA</Title><Msg>They have cameras on the corners, And drones are coming to our door, They are reading through our emails, And tapping phones to find out more. They have scanners at the airport, In public buildings too, Stop and search is legal And theres nothing we can do. Whistleblowers are arrested, And reporters stand accused, Newspapers are all threatened, And our civil rights refused. They say its for security, To keep us safe from harm. Now were all suspected terrorists, But no cause for real alarm. So, put a bar code on your forehead And phone chip up your #$%$, There is no need for worry, If youre only cutting cl#$%$! indisckize They have cameras on the corners, And drones are coming to our door, They are reading through our emails, And tapping phones to find out more. They have scanners at the airport, In public buildings too, Stop and search is legal And theres nothing we can do. Whistleblowers are arrested, And reporters stand accused, Newspapers are all threatened, And our civil rights refused. They say its for security, To keep us safe from harm. Now were all suspected terrorists, But no cause for real alarm. So, put a bar code on your forehead And phone chip up your #$%$, There is no need for worry, If youre only cutting cl#$%$! indisckize They have cameras on the corners, And drones are coming to our door, They are reading through our emails, And tapping phones to find out more. They have scanners at the airport, In public buildings too, Stop and search is legal And theres nothing we can do. Whistleblowers are arrested, And reporters stand accused, Newspapers are all threatened, And our civil rights refused. They say its for security, To keep us safe from harm. Now were all suspected terrorists, But no cause for real alarm. So, put a bar code on your forehead And phone chip up your #$%$, There is no need for worry, If youre only cutting cl#$%$! indisckize</Msg><Username>repsrealty</Username><Timestamp>1371412430783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371412442947-118</Id><Topic><Title>WHY the shorts are afraid of Dr. Osso....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371412199448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:49:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes I noticed them and is easy to locate the real Osso. Thanks for the heads up.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371412442947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371412814735-119</Id><Topic><Title>AS I WAS SAYING... MSFT IS A SCAM. HIGH PAY....POOR RESULTS. PC SALES DOWN HUGE. WIN. 8 TO BLAME</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371408406896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:46:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And repubs claims false. a huge recession follows every repub. Prez. For past 50 years....and all know it...</Msg><Username>wishin_aint_investin</Username><Timestamp>1371412814735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371412959400-120</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371344552048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 21:02:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ignore earnings, past, present and future. Just buy more shares. There is no downside! I get stock awarded to me for free and then just sell the shares and make a profit off of the money investors keep pumping into the stock. Doesn't matter to me if, or whether, the price goes up or down. I just dance! S. Ballmer</Msg><Username>fan_tazer</Username><Timestamp>1371412959400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371413062970-121</Id><Topic><Title>Sony sucker-punches Xbox on price, specs, DRM-free gaming</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1371096608613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 00:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually if you dd games at cnet or gme or amzn... Then you would know msft is 7th in titles. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371413062970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371413307804-122</Id><Topic><Title>OH ASSO.. MSFT P/E IS 17.7 CURRENTLY. U R A LIAR. SEE SCOTTRADE OR YAHOO FINANCE. BUT U NEED TO PU;; HEAD OUT FIRST</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371350481594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:41:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your path is strewn with rose petals! and what about buco? i know he's not the real you but is he another real phony bucco? or may he be a phony real bucco? or both? please help even more than you do already! go l2!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1371413307804</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371413440601-123</Id><Title>Where is that obnoxious toxic shetbag Troll heretwat?</Title><Msg>Hiding behind one of his many twisted hate aliases no doubt.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371413440601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:10:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371413538423-124</Id><Topic><Title>At a tiny 0.53%, Windoze 8 adoption levels in the enterprise are shockingly low</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370388335249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THOSE ARE FACTS....</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371413538423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371413576181-125</Id><Topic><Title>SARAH LIPSTICK, DEER IN THE HEADLIGHTS LIAR .....PAHLIN....TOPS AT FUAX NEWS. AGAIN.. HA HA WHAT A DOPE.</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371346343869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 21:32:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you say she balled glenn beck.. I knew it.. I heard she blewrush.</Msg><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371413576181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:12:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371413617692-126</Id><Topic><Title>Beware phony Osso's!!!</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1371351372127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:56:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bees wear false profits!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1371413617692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371413625580-127</Id><Topic><Title>YOU NOW HAVE MY ATTENTION. I BOUGHT 8. AM HAVING TO USE VITS OLD OS. WHY CONFIG. UPDATES.</Title><Username>rudealfo</Username><Timestamp>1370404804503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:00:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Msft took over my pc. Even with my custom task schedule....myy my....they write software to make us think we own our new $800.00 machine.....only to find...no no no...msft...takes over even against my wishes.</Msg><Username>gottaloveobama</Username><Timestamp>1371413625580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371413678552-128</Id><Topic><Title>HEY WHEN PUMPERS CANNOT ADDRESS IT ISSUES WITH 8, THEY ARE UNQUALIFIED TO JUDGE. I'M POSTING</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370400205808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:43:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8 can't touch chrome. and all know it. Amzn best retailer sez chrome.. Best seller.... Google it. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>isee_clearly</Username><Timestamp>1371413678552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371413740219-129</Id><Topic><Title>ACTUALLY. MSFT PE IS 18. QUITE HIGH. OVER THE CURRENT S&amp;P AVG. AND LOW YIELD. SO DOWN GOES SP.</Title><Username>joeeddy69</Username><Timestamp>1371349664077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P/e is 18. see market research for proof... Way to high. goes. To 11 by way of sp. Decline.</Msg><Username>factz_dontlie</Username><Timestamp>1371413740219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414034060-130</Id><Topic><Title>ACTUALLY. MSFT PE IS 18. QUITE HIGH. OVER THE CURRENT S&amp;P AVG. AND LOW YIELD. SO DOWN GOES SP.</Title><Username>joeeddy69</Username><Timestamp>1371349664077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>M$FT is severely undervalued by any measure we're going to $40+ in a heart beat.............</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371414034060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414060973-131</Id><Topic><Title>AS I WAS SAYING... MSFT IS A SCAM. HIGH PAY....POOR RESULTS. PC SALES DOWN HUGE. WIN. 8 TO BLAME</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371408406896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:46:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And repubs claims false. a huge recession follows every repub. Prez. For past 50 years....and all know it... Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371414060973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414111697-132</Id><Topic><Title>SARAH LIPSTICK, DEER IN THE HEADLIGHTS LIAR .....PAHLIN....TOPS AT FUAX NEWS. AGAIN.. HA HA WHAT A DOPE.</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371346343869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 21:32:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy, you Obama flunkie idiots are a crude bunch. Could it be that you are troubled by Obama's lack of achievements? I guess it is an embarrassment to see your president daily advertising his incompetence. He had to have Power, Rice and Clinton to tell him he was embarrassing himself by not being able to make a decision on Syria. ....And fool, you can only wish you could have Sarah.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371414111697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414143665-133</Id><Topic><Title>BUSH LEFT MILLIONS IN FORECLOSURE. AND UNEMPLOYED...OBAMA HAS LED US TO HERE. I SALUTE</Title><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371410407960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:20:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oooh but willie.. U love the constant barrage of right wing whackjob posts here 24/7. you never complaina about that.. Do ya.. Tea-bagger. Or is that just bagholder. Either way...as was posted.. Keep it up.. And recieve the same in return.... Cost of pumping waaaay up since willie and the crew attacked the msft-victim. who posted win. 8 poor unfinished...and broken. 1 post. And you all attacked. not smart. costs have incresed for msft. To pay lame pumpers. Lol... Right back atcha..</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371414143665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414295348-134</Id><Topic><Title>AS I WAS SAYING... MSFT IS A SCAM. HIGH PAY....POOR RESULTS. PC SALES DOWN HUGE. WIN. 8 TO BLAME</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371408406896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:46:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yada yada you repeat the same same old tired mindless script, we already had our recession/depression dog boi................</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371414295348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:24:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414471648-135</Id><Topic><Title>Bernstein Raised MSFT to $42 from $40....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368642251966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:24:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can see the short trolls are bashing MSFT P/E as they should read this post. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371414471648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371414485752-136</Id><Title>How did a man so devoid of professional accomplishment beguile you dummies...</Title><Msg>into thinking he could manage the world's largest economy, direct the world's most powerful military etc.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371414485752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414535612-137</Id><Topic><Title>BUSH LEFT MILLIONS IN FORECLOSURE. AND UNEMPLOYED...OBAMA HAS LED US TO HERE. I SALUTE</Title><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371410407960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:20:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oooooh but dog boi M$FT &amp; investors are good for the economy, instead of a #$%$ parasite Troll like you.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371414535612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:28:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414549041-138</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT valuation....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367458331128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More reading for the Short Trolls..... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371414549041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414676464-139</Id><Topic><Title>Oppenheimer raised Microsoft PT to $39 from $34.</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1370607137497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:12:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another warning to the short Trolls. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371414676464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414842469-140</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Announces Upcoming Event for the Financial Community....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369868126810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 18:55:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More reading for the troll shorts. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371414842469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414953739-141</Id><Topic><Title>Exclusive Games - XBox One leads PS4 2 to 1</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371385989833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:33:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You had your first good week short MSFT in like 2 months. Loooooooooooser!</Msg><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1371414953739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:35:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371415002404-142</Id><Topic><Title>No Wonder Sony Charging Less for PS4. Low Number of Exclusive Games</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371408053605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:40:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly... And shorts don't want to hear it. they keep trying to bury your posts. I wonder why that is?</Msg><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1371415002404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:36:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371415275939-143</Id><Topic><Title>Where is that obnoxious toxic shetbag Troll heretwat?</Title><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371413440601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:10:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1371415275939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371416196996-144</Id><Topic><Title>How did a man so devoid of professional accomplishment beguile you dummies...</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371414485752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You voted for Bush and you got what he gave you ... Financial Disaster and Great Recession</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1371416196996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371416264618-145</Id><Topic><Title>SONY POS4 IS ONLY AVAILABLE ON DEC 31/2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371348729734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes Amazon says ship Dec 31/2013.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371416264618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371416604190-146</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Announces Upcoming Event for the Financial Community....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369868126810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 18:55:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excuse you. this is more dilution. Hardly good for longs. But you wouldn't understand the diff.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371416604190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:03:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371416757773-147</Id><Topic><Title>BUSH LEFT MILLIONS IN FORECLOSURE. AND UNEMPLOYED...OBAMA HAS LED US TO HERE. I SALUTE</Title><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371410407960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:20:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ooooh please buy this trash... oh please buy this dog...ohhh no don't look at a chart. it's the democrats making msft. a 13 year dog.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371416757773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371416838318-148</Id><Topic><Title>AS I WAS SAYING... MSFT IS A SCAM. HIGH PAY....POOR RESULTS. PC SALES DOWN HUGE. WIN. 8 TO BLAME</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371408406896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:46:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aaahhh so you admit obama has led a recovery. period.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371416838318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371416916761-149</Id><Topic><Title>BUSH LEFT MILLIONS IN FORECLOSURE. AND UNEMPLOYED...OBAMA HAS LED US TO HERE. I SALUTE</Title><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371410407960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:20:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oooh but willie.. U love the constant barrage of right wing whackjob posts here 24/7. you never complaina about that.. Do ya.. Tea-bagger. Or is that just bagholder. Either way...as was posted.. Keep it up.. And recieve the same in return.... Cost of pumping waaaay up since willie and the crew attacked the msft-victim. who posted win. 8 poor unfinished...and broken. 1 post. And you all attacked. not smart. costs have incresed for msft. To pay lame pumpers. Lol... Right back atcha..</Msg><Username>want_refund</Username><Timestamp>1371416916761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371416972296-150</Id><Topic><Title>YOU NOW HAVE MY ATTENTION. I BOUGHT 8. AM HAVING TO USE VITS OLD OS. WHY CONFIG. UPDATES.</Title><Username>rudealfo</Username><Timestamp>1370404804503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:00:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Msft took over my pc. Even with my custom task schedule....myy my....they write software to make us think we own our new $800.00 machine.....only to find...no no no...msft...takes over even against my wishes. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>worst_system</Username><Timestamp>1371416972296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371417069568-151</Id><Topic><Title>OH ASSO.. MSFT P/E IS 17.7 CURRENTLY. U R A LIAR. SEE SCOTTRADE OR YAHOO FINANCE. BUT U NEED TO PU;; HEAD OUT FIRST</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371350481594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:41:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes 18 is curr. pe. and waaaay too high for this old dead money</Msg><Username>want_refund</Username><Timestamp>1371417069568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371417180764-152</Id><Topic><Title>ANYONE CAN GO TO CNET OR GOOGLE SUPERCOMPUTERS. NOT 1 RUN MSFT. ALL LINUX. FACTS.</Title><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371350893290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:48:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But hey msft... Has always lied lied lied... Just like bing or kinect. look it up.. Not on a msn...thing or bing. As msft....lies.</Msg><Username>worst_system</Username><Timestamp>1371417180764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371417228571-153</Id><Topic><Title>ANYONE TRYING TO SELL A CONSOLE IS IN TROUBLE. IT'S MOBILE STUPID !!!!!</Title><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371349837115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:30:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>disaster8_box  18 hours ago 2 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 1 Reply ANYONE TRYING TO SELL A CONSOLE IS IN TROUBLE. IT'S MOBILE STUPID !!!!! Look at the stock performance for every game oem...and they all stink.. So when you shills wish to brag console... I laugh.. It's purely obfuscation for 8 being unfunished.</Msg><Username>worst_system</Username><Timestamp>1371417228571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371417304597-154</Id><Topic><Title>At a tiny 0.53%, Windoze 8 adoption levels in the enterprise are shockingly low</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370388335249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES THAT'S THE FACTS.....DUDE.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371417304597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371417397972-155</Id><Topic><Title>HEY WHEN PUMPERS CANNOT ADDRESS IT ISSUES WITH 8, THEY ARE UNQUALIFIED TO JUDGE. I'M POSTING</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1370400205808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:43:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On my 6 year old vista hp... Why... Cuz windoze 8 took over and is configuring updates and i cant use my 2 week old hp with 8. so unfair to download many gb. Of disk space i just bought. Monopoly....or socialisim....either way... This is junk...and vista is even better than clunky 8. They just take over. Hostile takeover... On my machine....never again !!!!</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371417397972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371417980850-156</Id><Topic><Title>How did a man so devoid of professional accomplishment beguile you dummies...</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371414485752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the man could not have gotten a CEO job at the least of the F500 companies</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371417980850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371418877374-157</Id><Topic><Title>How did a man so devoid of professional accomplishment beguile you dummies...</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1371414485752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know....you are soooo right, ballmer sucked offa gates. Riding his coattails....breathing sp. 4 u. bretheing in that huge brown cloud of methane...hence why all his hair fell out what a loser. keeping all the shares and all the money for decades deluded investors wait for any return while ballsinmouth sucks the life out of innovation.</Msg><Username>msft_last_always</Username><Timestamp>1371418877374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371418883625-158</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Announces Upcoming Event for the Financial Community....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369868126810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 18:55:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget to add the revenue from the Patent infringement settlement from Foxconn in China. Foxconn makes Google, Apple, XBox, Surface, Future Surface Phone, etc. For every single Android or Chrome OS phone made they have to pay Microsoft. This is significant income. Microsoft makes more than Google. Google does it for search. The settlement was approved and it has been in place. Also there are two Microsoft Stores. One for PC's and one for mobile. Both generate income.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371418883625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:41:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371419012811-159</Id><Title>Samsung analysts ask hard questions as S4 marketing charm wears off....</Title><Msg>Folks the analysts have reduced the S4 volume by 30% as WP_8 is going to kill Android and iPhone on the high end and start developing the lower end with Lumia 521.... Just Bing the Title above. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419012811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419051591-160</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Announces Upcoming Event for the Financial Community....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369868126810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 18:55:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EXCUSE U... THOSE ARE LOSS CENTERS.</Msg><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371419051591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419176194-161</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung analysts ask hard questions as S4 marketing charm wears off....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419012811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:43:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just google it... Samsung best in phones. galaxy 3 goodle it.. #1 sp. #$%$</Msg><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371419176194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:46:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419218129-162</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Announces Upcoming Event for the Financial Community....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369868126810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 18:55:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No the shorts are the loss centers you idiot. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419218129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:46:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371419243082-163</Id><Title>ASSO IS THIS THE BOARD U ALL WANT...KEPP IT UP...CLOWNS... 8 SUCKETH</Title><Msg>Keep it cummin'.. And watch the cost of pumpin'</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371419243082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419327123-164</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung analysts ask hard questions as S4 marketing charm wears off....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419012811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:43:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dream on and educate yourself and Samsung is heading Deep South. Goofle is in real trouble as Bing is making major headway in Search. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419327123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:48:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419404456-165</Id><Topic><Title>No Wonder Sony Charging Less for PS4. Low Number of Exclusive Games</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371408053605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:40:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is more than that. Sony does not come with motion sensing. That is extra. Microsoft has HD Skype. Microsoft has W8 interface style and web searching in a split screen. Microsoft has exclusive content from Stephen Spielberg &amp; NFL. Microsoft has XBOX music, movies and facial recognition. Microsoft has social networking that allows a user to see if their friends are on line and what they are playing. Microsoft has a blu ray player. Microsoft senses weight, heart rate and the slightest wrist movement wirelessly. The heart rate &amp; weight is going to produce some pretty amazing workout apps I believe. Microsoft will allow Windows 8 apps to run and have connectivity via Nokia phones or it may be Microsoft Surface Phone then. There is no comparison and the XBOX ONE will be the hot item this Christmas. It will be the item they are fighting over on Black Friday.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371419404456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419448283-166</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung analysts ask hard questions as S4 marketing charm wears off....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419012811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:43:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No bing is hype the numbers by virus attacks through ie-10 and os 8 and all know it... Goes lower.</Msg><Username>msft_virus_bing</Username><Timestamp>1371419448283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419465785-167</Id><Topic><Title>ASSO IS THIS THE BOARD U ALL WANT...KEPP IT UP...CLOWNS... 8 SUCKETH</Title><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371419243082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:47:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will be begging for Mercy again as you have done so often here; you stupid S0B. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419465785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419538819-168</Id><Topic><Title>WHY the shorts are afraid of Dr. Osso....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371412199448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:49:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are hopeless losers. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419538819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419578666-169</Id><Topic><Title>No Wonder Sony Charging Less for PS4. Low Number of Exclusive Games</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371408053605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:40:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No those are lies. Blatent misleads. facts are not 1 msft 2013 games has kinect capabilities. try 2 prove otherwise salesfool. cheerlosers are just lying bagholders. see a chart.</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371419578666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:52:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419622215-170</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung analysts ask hard questions as S4 marketing charm wears off....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419012811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:43:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bing is now over 30% of the traffic and soon will be at par with Goofle; you stupido. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419622215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419651830-171</Id><Topic><Title>AS I WAS SAYING... MSFT IS A SCAM. HIGH PAY....POOR RESULTS. PC SALES DOWN HUGE. WIN. 8 TO BLAME</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371408406896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:46:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aaahhh so you admit obama has led a recovery. period. Sentiment: Strong Sell</Msg><Username>msft_last_always</Username><Timestamp>1371419651830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419665202-172</Id><Topic><Title>Bernstein Raised MSFT to $42 from $40....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368642251966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:24:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been in Microsoft Stock since the beginning. I believe when the XBOX ONE effect hits that earning cycle there will be a significant surprise. I think it will jump $4 immediately on the surprise and continue up to the 46 - 55 range. If tapering set's in by Fed in end of year, that may prevent a continuing rise.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371419665202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419732785-173</Id><Topic><Title>No Wonder Sony Charging Less for PS4. Low Number of Exclusive Games</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371408053605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:40:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sony is desperate as they are way behind in technology and are selling below cost just to say in the game.... A very sad situation indeed. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419732785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419931995-174</Id><Topic><Title>SONY POS4 IS ONLY AVAILABLE ON DEC 31/2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371348729734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes just Bing it; it is very easy to confirm. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419931995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:58:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371420072499-175</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT valuation....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367458331128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XBOX ONE is a gaming, entertainment, Windows 8 PC all in one. People do not realize that it is actually going to look and perform like your Windows 8 computer except it controls your TV. The voice commands will be irresistible. The Stephen Spielberg looks pretty impressive and I am not into that at all. Seeing the experience and how it makes you feel like you are there was interesting anyway. The NFL experience is the big one. Every football fan will get this. Where I live, you have to pay the cable people extra to see the home team. You have to get a NFL package if you want all the games. Microsoft nailed it with the NFL exclusive. That will sell the hell out of this plus the massive demand by gamers. There is one more thing, businesses will by it also for the easy as 123 group conferencing in HD. Does anyone know how much businesses pay to have that done??? This will sell big.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1371420072499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371420111300-176</Id><Topic><Title>ACTUALLY. MSFT PE IS 18. QUITE HIGH. OVER THE CURRENT S&amp;P AVG. AND LOW YIELD. SO DOWN GOES SP.</Title><Username>joeeddy69</Username><Timestamp>1371349664077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The performance these paid msft employees are predicting... Hasn't happened in 13 years. greatest market ever msft under-performs. see apple or google chart. see dow chart. this is dead money.</Msg><Username>msft_last_always</Username><Timestamp>1371420111300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371420300614-177</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT valuation....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367458331128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know folks wll hate yelling at the tv. As i hate yelling at my acer windows 8. or hp that's not touch like my acer.. But still 8 is sooooo flawed. You tv will be as confused as any pc with 8. Too many misreads. As 8 is still being ironed out. not finished and many misreads and flaws. period.</Msg><Username>wii_ps4_best</Username><Timestamp>1371420300614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371420821612-178</Id><Title>FACT IS MSFT HAS FAILED TO COPY APPLE. VOICE RECOG. ON 8 DOESN'T LISTEN.. MUST REPEAT NON-STOP</Title><Msg>As is the touch feature......soooo mis read.. Miss read.. Over and over. you will need great patience if you get stuck in 8. waaaay worse than vista. i own both.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371420821612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371420838677-179</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT valuation....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1367458331128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are so phony it is hard to describe as Windows 8 is the ultimate OS and anyone who uses it will never touch anything else.... Also we have 500 million Windows XP that are migrating to 8 or 7 and that combined with WP-8 and Tablets are going to rev up the Windows Division profits several folds and some this quarter. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371420838677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371421020176-180</Id><Title>EVERYONE KNOWS 8BLOWS.....AND XBOX LAST.... AS IS PHONE....GO SAMSUNG.....</Title><Msg>Google and apple have doubled. Msft. Is a horrible investment. like a cd. zero growth.. And for 13 years. see a chart. For proof. !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371421020176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371421921923-181</Id><Topic><Title>WHY Windows will win this round as well....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368147359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 20:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time for a re-read.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371421921923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:32:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371422379028-182</Id><Title>MSFT HASN'T DISTINGUISHED ITSELF IN OVER A DECADE. AND IT'S SP. SHOWS IT. STILL 26-36. BIG DEAL.</Title><Msg>Apple went to 700 + making money for it's longtime longs. msft longtime longs=bagholders. see a chart. For the true history of this scam.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371422379028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371422586094-183</Id><Title>HELL is more crowded tonight- but Beelzibub dances with glee</Title><Msg>Thomas Penfield Jackson, Judge in Microsoft Antitrust Case, Dead at 76</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371422586094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371422811406-184</Id><Topic><Title>HELL is more crowded tonight- but Beelzibub dances with glee</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371422586094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:43:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sick and twisted right wing nut job tea party..insanity... Check into therapy u sicko.</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371422811406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371422901917-185</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT HASN'T DISTINGUISHED ITSELF IN OVER A DECADE. AND IT'S SP. SHOWS IT. STILL 26-36. BIG DEAL.</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371422379028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pretty shortsided evaluation don't you think- know another stock paying 3+ % yield? holding 92% of the desktop/laptop gaining in tablets big time with Surface Pro and all the clones gaining in phones big time with NOKIA, HUAWEI, etc</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371422901917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371422981835-186</Id><Topic><Title>HELL is more crowded tonight- but Beelzibub dances with glee</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371422586094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:43:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you want to talk about it bubb?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371422981835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371423119146-187</Id><Topic><Title>HELL is more crowded tonight- but Beelzibub dances with glee</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371422586094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:43:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh talking to you, how exciting.... I would rather put needles in my eyes... But as i know what you attempt. i have 10 years exp. At mb. Sooo sure old prev-priest... I 'll play ya douchbag</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371423119146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371423529334-188</Id><Topic><Title>HELL is more crowded tonight- but Beelzibub dances with glee</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371422586094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:43:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why don't you swallow that mouthful of spnk that you just got from your boyfriend eh</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371423529334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371423567306-189</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT HASN'T DISTINGUISHED ITSELF IN OVER A DECADE. AND IT'S SP. SHOWS IT. STILL 26-36. BIG DEAL.</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371422379028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Msft is just like nok. old white elephant going extinct. oh and chrome is selling leader... And 92% is a very old out dated wrong number.. Period. ask cnet. Or market reasurch sp. 4 ufu.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371423567306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371423572939-190</Id><Topic><Title>HELL is more crowded tonight- but Beelzibub dances with glee</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371422586094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:43:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW if you have 10 years experience it would have to be at sucking</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371423572939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:59:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371423703082-191</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT HASN'T DISTINGUISHED ITSELF IN OVER A DECADE. AND IT'S SP. SHOWS IT. STILL 26-36. BIG DEAL.</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371422379028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the only thing going extinct is the HIV carriers like you and all your boyfriends</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371423703082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:01:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371423922560-192</Id><Topic><Title>Analysis: Fed-induced selloff has investors hunting for bargains (Reuters)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371401821889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES Buy On This Dip. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371423922560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371424410623-193</Id><Topic><Title>WHY the shorts are afraid of Dr. Osso....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371412199448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:49:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of them has any IT background and/or has never used Windows 8.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371424410623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:13:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371424494478-194</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft - Announcing Build June 26-28/2013</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370306273296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Folks this is a big event and is all sold out.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371424494478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:14:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371424574541-195</Id><Topic><Title>WHY GS Is Betting Against MSFT....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369342746864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>June 26-28 Developers conference. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371424574541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371424655620-196</Id><Topic><Title>CRM is getting killed as Heather Bellini has $55.00 PT with P/E of 110!</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370356368972</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:32:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just wait till we have the Developers conference on June 26-28.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371424655620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371425229868-197</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT HASN'T DISTINGUISHED ITSELF IN OVER A DECADE. AND IT'S SP. SHOWS IT. STILL 26-36. BIG DEAL.</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371422379028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW.. U A DOUCHEBAG...</Msg><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371425229868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371425293347-198</Id><Topic><Title>Analysis: Fed-induced selloff has investors hunting for bargains (Reuters)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371401821889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AND MULTIPLY YOUR LOSSES... WHAT A STUPID IDEA.</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371425293347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:28:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371425315935-199</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT HASN'T DISTINGUISHED ITSELF IN OVER A DECADE. AND IT'S SP. SHOWS IT. STILL 26-36. BIG DEAL.</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371422379028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STINKS.. OLD AND DEAD...</Msg><Username>eight_suckz</Username><Timestamp>1371425315935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371425582035-200</Id><Topic><Title>BUSH LEFT MILLIONS IN FORECLOSURE. AND UNEMPLOYED...OBAMA HAS LED US TO HERE. I SALUTE</Title><Username>obama_savedus</Username><Timestamp>1371410407960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:20:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ha ha ha....</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371425582035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:33:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371425598985-201</Id><Topic><Title>AS I WAS SAYING... MSFT IS A SCAM. HIGH PAY....POOR RESULTS. PC SALES DOWN HUGE. WIN. 8 TO BLAME</Title><Username>ossobucco2112</Username><Timestamp>1371408406896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:46:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep yep... ha ha</Msg><Username>disaster8_box</Username><Timestamp>1371425598985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371427264287-202</Id><Title>GAP DOWN MONDAY TRADERS.... U HEARD IT HERE FIRST. LONGS.. GRAB. SCROT. CUZ.. GONG LOWER CHEERLOSERS</Title><Msg>YA...FRIG....IN...!!! HOO!.. SELL YOU LOSERS.. FUND MGRS. 1/2 YR... GONE.. SELL SELL SELL.WATCH. !!!</Msg><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371427264287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:01:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371427272785-203</Id><Topic><Title>Analysis: Fed-induced selloff has investors hunting for bargains (Reuters)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371401821889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So far the shorts have been the big losers getting caught on the wrong side of the trade.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371427272785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371427391819-204</Id><Topic><Title>SONY POS4 IS ONLY AVAILABLE ON DEC 31/2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371348729734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sony will tank in July 2013 when the news is confirmed that there is no POS4 coming this Xmas.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371427391819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371427507296-205</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung analysts ask hard questions as S4 marketing charm wears off....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371419012811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:43:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AND that is 3 million S4 handsets going to Nokia.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371427507296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371427574405-206</Id><Topic><Title>Bernstein Raised MSFT to $42 from $40....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368642251966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:24:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371427574405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:06:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371427689923-207</Id><Topic><Title>No Wonder Sony Charging Less for PS4. Low Number of Exclusive Games</Title><Username>oncmillionaire</Username><Timestamp>1371408053605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:40:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts are already panicking. They all will cover tomorrow.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1371427689923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:08:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371428288559-208</Id><Topic><Title>GAP DOWN MONDAY TRADERS.... U HEARD IT HERE FIRST. LONGS.. GRAB. SCROT. CUZ.. GONG LOWER CHEERLOSERS</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371427264287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I HEARD ABOUT YOU PAID PUMPERS....</Msg><Username>provendog</Username><Timestamp>1371428288559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:18:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371428349615-209</Id><Topic><Title>GAP DOWN MONDAY TRADERS.... U HEARD IT HERE FIRST. LONGS.. GRAB. SCROT. CUZ.. GONG LOWER CHEERLOSERS</Title><Username>msft_victim</Username><Timestamp>1371427264287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OUCH... WAIT TILL MONDAYPUNKZ</Msg><Username>dumpreits</Username><Timestamp>1371428349615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371428409255-210</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT HASN'T DISTINGUISHED ITSELF IN OVER A DECADE. AND IT'S SP. SHOWS IT. STILL 26-36. BIG DEAL.</Title><Username>ossobuco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371422379028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH SEE ACHART.. OR BE STUPID.</Msg><Username>msft_a_dog</Username><Timestamp>1371428409255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371428711234-211</Id><Title>Shorts: Cover Or...</Title><Msg>Die Poor. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371428711234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371430151599-212</Id><Topic><Title>ValueAct: Microsoft Could Potentially Become The Worlds Largest Company....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368453132061</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 09:52:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time for re-read.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371430151599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371430487787-213</Id><Topic><Title>Fed Hurdle of 4 Straight 200,000 Payrolls Sets Bernanke View (Source Bloomberg).....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370624302919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another reminder.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371430487787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371430567538-214</Id><Topic><Title>8 Things Windows 8 Tablets Can Do That The iPad Can't....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370103697299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:21:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reading time again.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371430567538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371430740719-215</Id><Topic><Title>Microsfot Cloud, Smart Phones, China</Title><Username>douglas7white</Username><Timestamp>1369232118183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:15:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a reminder.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371430740719</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:59:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371430835601-216</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft BUY Recommendation update 2013.06.11.</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370954308316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 08:38:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a reminder folks.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371430835601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 21:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371430913725-217</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Steps Up Cloud Services in Japan (WSJ)</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369308907955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 07:35:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More good reading folks.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371430913725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 21:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371431200318-218</Id><Topic><Title>Fed Hurdle of 4 Straight 200,000 Payrolls Sets Bernanke View (Source Bloomberg).....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370624302919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 12:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So we can't "grow without printing more money than we're growing, when has that got to end?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371431200318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 21:06:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371433277231-219</Id><Title>Windows 8, Surface Pro, Windows Phone and Office 2013 are the right tools for the right time!</Title><Msg>We find this truth to be self evident!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1371433277231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 21:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371433415716-220</Id><Title>President BarryBoi sends first triios to Syria</Title><Msg>300 advisers and a no fly zone over Russian held SAMs. So we will be in a hot war, we can not win, over Syria with Russia &amp; China.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1371433415716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 21:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>