<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372830690886-1</Id><Topic><Title>Cloud Security Is Another Enterprise Market Microsoft Is Going After....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372728678880</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:31:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bing it? what does that mean?</Msg><Username>wallstreet.thief</Username><Timestamp>1372830690886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 01:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372832314695-2</Id><Topic><Title>Bottom Line: Windows OS Systems Have 91.51% of All OS Used on the Planet</Title><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1372708156374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 15:49:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not a "stubborn fact", it's what one questionable but unaccountably popular site continues to report. The Oracle deal signals only that Oracle is in trouble.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372832314695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 02:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372834762500-3</Id><Title>Watching Google Take Over The World</Title><Msg>Google it. This is only about browsers, and to me it's a bit simplistic, i.e. lacking in nuance and subtlety; but one point is clear -- IE is no longer the dominant browser. Microsoft's effort to bring it back was too little and far too late. IE is the canary in the coal mine...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372834762500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 02:59:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372836899310-4</Id><Title>Analyst: Nokia must adopt Android before it's too late</Title><Msg>Google it. Quoting: "After Nokia's shares dropped by 2.6 per cent, Bernstein Research's Pierre Ferragu claimed the company's balance sheet is "in a rather tight net cash position" and its stock is overvalued, Barrons reports. Ferragu reckons Nokia will have to "take the pill before one cannot afford to do so anymore" and start making mobiles that use Google's Android operating system. " "[Nokia] is facing two structural challenges: its exposure to the disappearing feature phone market and the lack of traction of Windows Phones," Ferragu writes. "Both could cost Nokia a lot of cash in the near term, in restructuring, marketing/distribution support, and operational losses, which means it could be too late to address the problem in a couple of years." "That's right, he thinks things are so bad Nokia might not be around in a couple of years unless it changes tack. "Ferragu says the situation is "urgent", and that he "wouldn't be surprised to see Nokia adopting Android as its new low-end platform by year end." "The numbers don't sound good, from looking at Ferragu's calculations. But would Nokia ever adopt Android? The Finnish phone firm hasn't ruled it out."</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372836899310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 03:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372837118532-5</Id><Topic><Title>$50 in 2 weeks....</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372793801048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 15:36:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Laughter, they say, is the best medicine. Not my forte, but yes...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372837118532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 03:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372845696243-6</Id><Topic><Title>We got you boy here now. VIVA ZNGA. thank you suckers</Title><Username>globalalex2000</Username><Timestamp>1372807149913</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 19:19:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is that high priced purchase going to do for you? You going to have a set top box of Farmville? A that is not willing to make a change when his boss what him to is not the ideal ceo in most circumstances. Maybe he should put his money where his mouth is and start his own company. If your boss says remove this it has to change because the public demands it and we cannot risk what do you do? Throw a hissy fit! That is ceo material?</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1372845696243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 06:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372850603681-7</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings ONLY 16 Days Away....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372806138484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 19:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good news for AAPL. 54% of new 'thin and light' laptops sold are MacBook Air models with the new Haswell processor. Only 46% are Windows 8 Ultrabooks.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1372850603681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372851134848-8</Id><Topic><Title>SELL NOW!!!</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1365608654809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 11:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earnings won't be good this quarter. Even worse next quarter. Microsoft's only hope Windows 8.1 Haswell ultrabooks and surface in during the holiday season. Too bad Apple already has Haswell Macbook Air laptos for sale right now, and they are priced competitively with Windows 8 Ultrabooks. Macbook Air doesn't have Metro Tiles and you can install Windows 7 with Boot Camp or Parallels. XBox already #$%$ off users. Windows phone market share is smaller Ballmer's weenie. This turd will sink below 30 by next month for sure.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1372851134848</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372851164346-9</Id><Title>Did Microsoft loose the XBOX head or gain Customer 101</Title><Msg>Microsoft listened to twiiter, facebook,message boards and every critic out there. Instead of risking a slow launch of XBOX One Ballmer said change DRM (games selling restriction) &amp; always on. The head of XBOX literally throws a hissy fit. It is done. Now the code has to be changed. Anyone who does it knows it is just time and the time is paid by Microsoft. So did they loose the head of XBOX or become more customer aware and win millions of more buyers? It is not easy to please everyone and this time the consumer one.</Msg><Username>ineedastock</Username><Timestamp>1372851164346</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372851226201-10</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Azure Cloud Services</Title><Username>quasar_king</Username><Timestamp>1372791820955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 15:03:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can do the same thing with Google Docs for FREE.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1372851226201</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:33:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372851795467-11</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Azure Cloud Services</Title><Username>quasar_king</Username><Timestamp>1372791820955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 15:03:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What company would put their resources on some server somewhere " I suppose the stupid Linux idiots would but they don't have anything important to save in the "Cloud" anyway. The "Cloud" is for storing movies &amp; music and not for your personal data.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1372851795467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372856077034-12</Id><Title>Check Out These Stock Picks</Title><Msg>Best stock tips there are. These guys really know their stuff. Every single pick of theirs always skyrockets. Don’t miss out. Text the word Alert without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT to join</Msg><Username>wittn824</Username><Timestamp>1372856077034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372856211222-13</Id><Topic><Title>MS "Probes" New Business Opportunities via Skype</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1372784705008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 13:05:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still miss the point. "There has been an increase in reports of the sexual abuse of children being streamed live over the internet on services like Skype, it has today been revealed Live footage of children being abused is becoming increasingly available over the internet on services like Skype, child exploitation experts have today warned."</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1372856211222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372857316997-14</Id><Topic><Title>SELL NOW!!!</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1365608654809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 11:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"More money losing trash talk" This from the most obnoxious and prolific message board spamming, know it all little c o c k s u c k e r anyone's ever seen here. S T F U, you smart a s s piece of s h i t. No one is listening to you and no one believes a word you say outside of your pimp pals.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1372857316997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372857464237-15</Id><Topic><Title>$50 in 2 weeks....</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372793801048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 15:36:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! 20I2, you're the best TFAD we've had here in a long time.</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1372857464237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372861285763-16</Id><Title>After insulting us in Africa, where is Obama headed next?</Title><Msg>What kind of president goes overseas to warn the locals about the people who elected him? Yet, that was pretty much the message he delivered in Capetown "folks come here and they're automatically benefiting Africans. And that includes the U.S." Somehow the president's thinking, Americans are prone to dishonesty and out to cheat Africans. Only a leader with deep misgivings about America's role in the world evidenced in everything from his own apology tours to the first lady's admission that she wasn't proud of America until her husband won the presidential nomination , would say such a thing anywhere. IBD</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372861285763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372861648766-17</Id><Topic><Title>After insulting us in Africa, where is Obama headed next?</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372861285763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:21:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not keeping up with his travels but I did note that Yahoo News reported the other day he will not visit the country of his birth while in Africa ;-)</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372861648766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372861792154-18</Id><Title>Obamacare not to be enforced until 2015 for business. There are two messages there</Title><Msg>(1) They know it's a train wreck. (2) Getting mid term votes for the dolt in chief is more important than your health. Low information voters will not appreciate the train wreck until it hits them after the mid terms.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372861792154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372862001303-19</Id><Title>Market action, the pretend demand on no volume and the world falling apart is like really bad theater</Title><Msg>Over acted, with dialog too loud, and unbelievable premises.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372862001303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372863319458-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare not to be enforced until 2015 for business. There are two messages there</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372861792154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:29:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(1) Hawcreek is Anti-Obama. (2) Hawcreek is a Right-Wing Stooge.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372863319458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372863406196-21</Id><Topic><Title>After insulting us in Africa, where is Obama headed next?</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372861285763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:21:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"After insulting us in Africa" Who is "US" ?</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372863406196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:56:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372864678226-22</Id><Title>All Hell's Going to Break Loose</Title><Msg>...when the jury finds Zimmerman not guilty of second degree murder, because he didn't commit second degree murder. Even if he is found guilty of anything, he will get minimal time/probation. The anticipated chaos that is coming soon very well may be started in America's urban centers by this verdict. Not sure how it expands to the suburban and more rural areas though. We (my community, Smith, &amp; Wesson) generally don't put up with that kind of lawlessness. When the mobs are finally prevalent in the U.S., that's all she wrote.</Msg><Username>plmartin2012</Username><Timestamp>1372864678226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372865559376-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare not to be enforced until 2015 for business. There are two messages there</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372861792154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:29:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The law, as Congress wrote it, explicitly commands that the employer mandate provision take effect in January 2014. The perversely named "Affordable" Care Act does not permit the government to grant a reprieve or an extension. Yet with the usual blatantly illegal move, the Obama administration is simply choosing not to enforce the parts of the law that are causing visible problems, thereby ignoring the legislative and judicial branches of the government. BTW, that's called tyranny, and we were warned about it a long time ago.</Msg><Username>plmartintexas2012</Username><Timestamp>1372865559376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:32:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372866878831-24</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare not to be enforced until 2015 for business. There are two messages there</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372861792154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:29:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many medical companies have other computer system updates to do before Obamacare kicks in ... ICD-9 to ICD-10 conversions ... which has been extended to 10/1/2014 (It was originally supposed to be done already) ... but many places are behind ... due to other law changes too, like Medicare "D". "On October 1, 2014, the ICD-9 code sets used to report medical diagnoses and inpatient procedures will be replaced by ICD-10 code sets." "With ObamaCare the federal government is requiring that all hospitals and physicians use the new ICD-10 code system which goes from 15,000 codes to 68,000 codes." Besides, the USA was already behind the rest of the world using these ICD-10 codes. "ICD 10 codes are already prevalent around the world by industrialized countries, as well as many developing countries, such as Australia, Canada, France, Germany, South Korea, Netherlands, Sweden and Thailand, to name a few. The switch from ICD 9 to ICD 10 was inevitable.” So, Thank Obama for bringing the USA up-to-date.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372866878831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372868993183-25</Id><Topic><Title>WHY GS Is Betting Against MSFT....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369342746864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"June 26-28 Developers conference." One week later, typical MS cheek and chicanery. "This isn't the first time Microsoft has changed its TechNet program to stem the tide of pirated software coming from the relatively inexpensive TechNet program. Apparently, though, it's just easier to kill off the whole program and let developers and admins buy their own licenses. The timing of the revelation, one week after the Microsoft Build developer conference, is interesting. Such news would have surely caused some grumbles at the conference. While Microsoft is well within its rights to try to control pirated software, the changes to TechNet will cause a higher barrier-to-entry for some developers who might actually need longer-term licenses for a low cost." LOL! Thanks for the help, boys and girls. Now, get the f u c k out or pay up big bucks to help us build our c r a p ware. Typical...</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1372868993183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372869923823-26</Id><Title>DOW 15,000 is the magical manipulative perfect psychological price</Title><Msg>Strange that no matter what the true value of stocks in the DOW or issues du jour their valuation aggregates to 15,000...until it don't no mo.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372869923823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:45:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372870052165-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare not to be enforced until 2015 for business. There are two messages there</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372861792154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:29:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Martin you just don't understand, it's going into effect January 2014, they jus gonna look the other way about enforcement until after the election. The dolt in chief has made his intentions and priorities clear, it's always 100% about him.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372870052165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:47:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372870161705-28</Id><Title>13 days till $50 ! You stupid S0B's</Title><Msg>ossobucco2012 • Jun 18, 2013 7:52 PM Flag We will trade over $50.00 in 4 weeks. Osso Sentiment: Strong Buy</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372870161705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372870769055-29</Id><Topic><Title>Watching Google Take Over The World</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372834762500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 02:59:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so the advertisements aren't working? :-D why do they advertise it?</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372870769055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:59:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372870869669-30</Id><Topic><Title>13 days till $50 ! You stupid S0B's</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372870161705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a stupid SOB. Everybody hates Windows 8 Metro and PCs aren't selling. Just wait til the next IDC report. PC sales were down 14% in the first quarter, thanks to Windows 8. Analysts predict PC sales will be down at least 5% more in the 2nd quarter. 54% of new 'thin and light' laptops sold are MacBook Air models without Windows 8 Metro. Also, Asus is selling Ubuntu laptops as an alternative to Windows 8. Just ordered mine today.</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1372870869669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372870911323-31</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Nokia must adopt Android before it's too late</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372836899310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 03:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, the guys over on the nok board always hate ferragu. it's bad enough that he works for an american company. but the worst part is he's always right!!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372870911323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372870937841-32</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare not to be enforced until 2015 for business. There are two messages there</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372861792154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:29:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The dolt in chief has made his intentions and priorities clear" And they were Very Clear ... he did bring America out of the Bush Financial Disaster and Great Recession.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372870937841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871075602-33</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Azure Cloud Services</Title><Username>quasar_king</Username><Timestamp>1372791820955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 15:03:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so, no hope for msft in the enterprise cloud business? :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372871075602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871493215-34</Id><Topic><Title>$50 in 2 weeks....</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372793801048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 15:36:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're welcome! go l2!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372871493215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871641822-35</Id><Topic><Title>Windows Azure Cloud Services</Title><Username>quasar_king</Username><Timestamp>1372791820955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 15:03:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"so, no hope for msft in the enterprise cloud business?" There are Business Development products that use the cloud. But if there was ever a disruption in Internet Connectivity or that host where your data is, you are SOL, because that product is not available for installing as a stand alone on your PC and your data is on Cloud-9. If you like to gamble with your business, the Cloud is it, your business can dissipate just like a Cloud does.</Msg><Username>quasar_king</Username><Timestamp>1372871641822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871665291-36</Id><Topic><Title>WHY GS Is Betting Against MSFT....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369342746864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you think their new partnership with oracle will kill them? :haha:</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372871665291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372871739560-37</Id><Title>Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is failing.</Title><Msg>Me an my crew need some more #$%$ for the wall.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nati0n</Username><Timestamp>1372871739560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871782557-38</Id><Topic><Title>WHY GS Is Betting Against MSFT....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369342746864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump! ! ! !</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372871782557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871887508-39</Id><Topic><Title>13 days till $50 ! You stupid S0B's</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372870161705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe it hits $50 in after hours? ;-)</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372871887508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372872009689-40</Id><Title>Only 47% to go for $50 !</Title><Msg>Just a reminder folks - only 47% to go for $50 by July 16th as per my below prediction you stupid S0B's. Don't let shorts and journalists lie to you! 13 DAYS TO $50 !!! Dr. Osso ***************************************************************************************************************************** "ossobucco2012 • Jun 18, 2013 7:52 PM Flag We will trade over $50.00 in 4 weeks. Osso Sentiment: Strong Buy"</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372872009689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872125915-41</Id><Topic><Title>13 days till $50 ! You stupid S0B's</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372870161705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True but W8.2 will solve all these problems you stupid S0B. Dr. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372872125915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872168755-42</Id><Topic><Title>13 days till $50 ! You stupid S0B's</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372870161705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fingers are crossed you stupid S0B. Dr. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372872168755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872436353-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare not to be enforced until 2015 for business. There are two messages there</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372861792154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:29:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"... he did bring America out of the Bush Financial Disaster and Great Recession." Nope, that's your spin. Spending $3 to get $1 is not growth, moe</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372872436353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872521679-44</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is failing.</Title><Username>an_obama_nati0n</Username><Timestamp>1372871739560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is failing" You accidently left out "NOT" Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is NOT failing?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372872521679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372872836793-45</Id><Title>dont miss this, Alerts on stocks that run!!</Title><Msg>I can’t believe how easy it was. I signed up for their free service and my trading has greatly improved. Can’t believe I was missing out. Text the word Alert without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>simmonsjuan854</Username><Timestamp>1372872836793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873134457-46</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst: Nokia must adopt Android before it's too late</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372836899310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 03:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was an item on Bloomberg TV the other day connection Nokia and Android, but I didn't catch the details. I tried to follow up through the web site but found nothing. Still, Nokia/Android seems to be in the air.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372873134457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873487210-47</Id><Topic><Title>dont miss this, Alerts on stocks that run!!</Title><Username>simmonsjuan854</Username><Timestamp>1372872836793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks! I've been looking for something to help me pick a winner you stupid S0B! But this really is an improvement over my last system - ME!! Dr. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372873487210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873574627-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare not to be enforced until 2015 for business. There are two messages there</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372861792154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:29:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nope, that's your spin." That is FACT ... something the Hawcreek Team Hates. "Spending $3 to get $1 is not growth, moe" "Nope, that's your spin."</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372873574627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873593027-49</Id><Topic><Title>13 days till $50 ! You stupid S0B's</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372870161705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>7 cents less to go for $50 you stupid S0B's. Dr. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372873593027</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372873683911-50</Id><Title>BLOOMBERG: UN Charts ‘Unprecedented’ Global Warming Since 2000</Title><Msg>The decade through 2010 was the warmest for both hemispheres and for land and sea, the UN’s World Meteorological Organization said today in an e-mailed report examining climate trends for the beginning of the millennium. Almost 94 percent of countries logged their warmest 10 years on record, it said. UN Charts Unprecedented Global Warming as Sea-Level Rise Doubles UN Charts Unprecedented Global Warming as Sea-Level Rise Doubles The report underlines the challenge the globe faces in containing temperature gains since industrialization to the 2-degree Celsius (3.6 Fahrenheit) ceiling set by UN climate-treaty negotiators. “The decadal rate of increase between 1991-2000 and 2001-2010 was unprecedented,” WMO Secretary-General Michel Jarraud said in a statement. “Rising concentrations of heat-trapping greenhouse gases are changing our climate, with far-reaching implications for our environment and our oceans.” The report underlines the challenge the globe faces in containing temperature gains since industrialization to the 2-degree Celsius (3.6 Fahrenheit) ceiling set by UN climate-treaty negotiators. The planet is on course to warm by 4 degrees by 2100 because emissions are still rising, the World Bank says. RUSH LIMPBALLS, THE KOCH BROS AND EA BAGGERS WILL FIND A CONSPIRACY THEORY THERE SOMEWHERE!</Msg><Username>i_farted_in_church</Username><Timestamp>1372873683911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873728382-51</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare not to be enforced until 2015 for business. There are two messages there</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372861792154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:29:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep on topic you stupid S0B's. $50 by July 16th. Dr. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372873728382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372874316748-52</Id><Topic><Title>WHY GS Is Betting Against MSFT....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1369342746864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every GS employee spends their entire day betting at StockGaming.</Msg><Username>maxkissime</Username><Timestamp>1372874316748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372874356814-53</Id><Title>Microsoft must solve its Nokia, BlackBerry prisoner’s dilemma</Title><Msg>Google it. Quoting: "With Nokia now at 80 per cent of the Windows Phone market, rapidly approaching 100 per cent, the two dangers to Microsoft’s smartphone business are: "1. Nokia switches emphasis to Android – or something else, for that matter: "Whoops! Nokia has been saying that they don’t have a “Plan B” – beyond Windows Phone. Maybe they hadn’t – in 2011 or early 2012. But now? If you don’t believe Nokia has an active Plan B in place, you are naive. "Most likely, such a Plan B would involve Android. Perhaps it involves acquiring BlackBerry. Perhaps it would involve acquiring Research in Motion and making a great Android phone with a BlackBerry keyboard. The possibilities are endless. Either way, Microsoft is screwed. "2. Nokia gets acquired. "Whoops again! Whether Huawei, Lenovo, Samsung or HP, Microsoft’s only remaining outlet for Windows Phones may be gone. Microsoft would be screwed. "In this light it doesn’t take a lot to scare Microsoft into acquiring Nokia. Problem is, even if Nokia isn’t acquired, it can still abandon Windows Phone."</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1372874356814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372874489496-54</Id><Topic><Title>Check Out These Stock Picks</Title><Username>wittn824</Username><Timestamp>1372856077034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:54:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>someone is making a bid on DRIV.</Msg><Username>stockfox123</Username><Timestamp>1372874489496</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:01:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372875547377-55</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is failing.</Title><Username>an_obama_nati0n</Username><Timestamp>1372871739560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is NOT failing?" Didn't FAUX Opinions tell you that Obama bailed out America from the Bush Financial Disaster and Great Recession ?? I bet Rush and Hannity didn't tell you that either. Here Are The FACTS: "The financial crisis of 2007–2008, also known as the Global Financial Crisis and 2008 financial crisis, is considered by many economists to be the worst financial crisis since the Great Depression of the 1930s." Now ... Thank Obama: The U.S. economy has made enormous progress since the dark days of early 2009. Eighteen months ago, the global financial system was on the brink of collapse and the U.S. was suffering its worst economic downturn since the 1930s. Real GDP was falling at about a 6% annual rate, and monthly job losses averaged close to 750,000. Today, the financial system is operating much more normally, real GDP is advancing at a nearly 3% pace, and job growth has resumed, albeit at an insufficient pace.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372875547377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372875805423-56</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is failing.</Title><Username>an_obama_nati0n</Username><Timestamp>1372871739560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAHAHA For a guy that spent 3 yrs. in the 5 th grade you failed again.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372875805423</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:23:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372876849301-57</Id><Title>where my bears at?</Title><Msg>thinking down to $30 by end of July</Msg><Username>philosophize_me_capt</Username><Timestamp>1372876849301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372877640420-58</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is failing.</Title><Username>an_obama_nati0n</Username><Timestamp>1372871739560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Presidential Leadership Index fell 11.7% over the last month to 43.2.That's the lowest level and sharpest drop since Pres. Obama took office. A sluggish economy and Obama's focus on lower priority issues and the scandals are all taking a toll. Americans see the US. standing in the world at a 2 year low. We don't have to pretend anything. Facts are facts.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372877640420</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372878257739-59</Id><Topic><Title>Check Out These Stock Picks</Title><Username>wittn824</Username><Timestamp>1372856077034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:54:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your on tgt but not buying enough-hence costing u big bucks</Msg><Username>raggwead</Username><Timestamp>1372878257739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372878513934-60</Id><Title>Skype disruption prompts confusion during witness testimony Wednesday</Title><Msg>google the subject line Great product that Skype. [/sarcasm] Why aren't the shills calling this "innovative"?</Msg><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1372878513934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372879067832-61</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is failing.</Title><Username>an_obama_nati0n</Username><Timestamp>1372871739560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The survey was conducted by TechnoMetrica and took place June 24-29 among 857 adults." Now, further research shows: "Investor's Business Daily and their polling agency, Technometrica Institute of Policy and Politics (IBD/TIPP)." "TIPP does polls available only to IBD, which produces deeply biased reports based on TIPP surveys with no direct or full link to that surveyor's questions or methods of acquiring its samples. Their practices and results are of doubtful value, to say the least."</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372879067832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372879069673-62</Id><Topic><Title>Skype disruption prompts confusion during witness testimony Wednesday</Title><Username>predisposable_nym_01</Username><Timestamp>1372878513934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:08:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he douhebag- why don't you tell us what you have that's better? you c.....ucker</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1372879069673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372879299841-63</Id><Title>Quiz to ponder over the 4th: What will predictably happen "unexpectedly" on Friday?</Title><Msg>Predictable unexpected, along with spending $3 to get $1 and pretending that's "growth" marks the tenure of the current dolt in chief in the White House.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372879299841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372879320797-64</Id><Title>Wotto Bozo must solve his Nokia, BlackBerry prisoner’s dilemma</Title><Msg>google it watto if you keep pumping your BS--then Huawei WP phone users will be highly peod best you switch to a different stock board</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1372879320797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372879755539-65</Id><Topic><Title>Quiz to ponder over the 4th: What will predictably happen "unexpectedly" on Friday?</Title><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372879299841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What will predictably happen "unexpectedly" on Friday?" Prediction - You will post Anti-Obama, Right-Wing Wacko Stuff. Unexpectedly - You will realize that you are FOS on your own without others proving it.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372879755539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372880044223-66</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's already happening. The adults are back in the room.</Msg><Username>roirop</Username><Timestamp>1372880044223</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372880706283-67</Id><Title>Signs in Tahir Square you don't see on MSNBC</Title><Msg>WAKE UP AMERICA. OBAMA SUPPORTS A FASCIST REGIME IN EGYPT OBAMA SUPPORTS TERROISM OBAMA YOU JERK, YOUR DEAL WITH MUSLIM BROTHERHOOD IS UNSUCCESSFUL Looks like the thrill is gone.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372880706283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:45:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372880722637-68</Id><Topic><Title>At a tiny 0.53%, Windoze 8 adoption levels in the enterprise are shockingly low</Title><Username>phands.theheretic6</Username><Timestamp>1370388335249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump again</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372880722637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:45:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372881368492-69</Id><Topic><Title>Signs in Tahir Square you don't see on MSNBC</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372880706283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:45:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop Listening To FAUX Opinions and their Spin-Offs ... Here is news: "OBAMA CALLS EGYPT’S MORSI AND SAYS U.S. ‘DOES NOT SUPPORT’ EITHER SIDE"</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372881368492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372881954026-70</Id><Topic><Title>Signs in Tahir Square you don't see on MSNBC</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372880706283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:45:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you get anymore dishonest? Morsi and the Muslim Brotherhood is the Mid-East equivalent of the Koch Bros and the Christian Coalition. Conservatism, religious dogma and rule by wealth in the Mideast or in America sucks.</Msg><Username>veronica_meester</Username><Timestamp>1372881954026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:05:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372883627915-71</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JUST A REMINDER FOLKS ! DR. OSSO KNOWS BEST!!! Osso @@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ ossobucco2012 Jun 23, 2013 2:22 PM Following the volatility in the market MSFT will hit $40 in no time and trade over $50 after the earnings. Osso Sentiment: Strong Buy</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372883627915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372885619420-72</Id><Topic><Title>Signs in Tahir Square you don't see on MSNBC</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372880706283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:45:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In case you missed it Sybil: From The Article: "After all, Obama's Muslim outreach speech at Cairo University four years ago last month purposely snubbed a conspicuously absent Mubarak, and practically gave Egyptians America's blessing to oust our most vital Arab ally. What the Press did NOT tell the American people was that, in that speech to a room full of Fanatical, Jihadi-Leaning Muslims, the President of the U.S, #$%$-BARAK Insane Obama told the crowd, IN ARABIC: "I am one of you</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372885619420</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372885685385-73</Id><Title>No $50 by July 4th !</Title><Msg>Stupid S0B journalists in shorts have held us back again! Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372885685385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:08:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372890204427-74</Id><Topic><Title>This will be brutal...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1366295219103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 10:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ONLY two weeks to earnings and it would be brutal for the crash test dummy shorts again.... Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372890204427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372890465498-75</Id><Topic><Title>No $50 by July 4th !</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372885685385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:08:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm celebrating Independence Day and independence from Microsoft by ordering an Asus Linux laptop with NO Metro Tiles!</Msg><Username>penguinx64</Username><Timestamp>1372890465498</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372890500129-76</Id><Topic><Title>Cloud Security Is Another Enterprise Market Microsoft Is Going After....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372728678880</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 21:31:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes we will deal with all this BS on the earnings release day as usual. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372890500129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:28:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372890614039-77</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft Says Fortune 500 Firms Are Loving Its Amazon Cloud Killer (Source Business Insider)....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371492135165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 14:02:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expect the first surge of Azure Cloud revenue on our quarterly earnings in two weeks. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372890614039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372890702299-78</Id><Topic><Title>THE Imminent and Tragic Death of iPhone, iPad and Android....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1368187729573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 08:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now we can add AMZN and CRM to our Death List. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372890702299</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372890861310-79</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL has 390,000 corporate clients who would use Windows Azure Cloud starting Monday June 24/2013....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371854733346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This would end AMZN for good. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372890861310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372891072137-80</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft - Announcing Build June 26-28/2013</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370306273296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SO now we have deals with both ORCL and SAP on Cloud both on Big Data and Manufacturing environment. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372891072137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:37:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372891088287-81</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is failing.</Title><Username>an_obama_nati0n</Username><Timestamp>1372871739560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are no ideas left that you haven't repeated over and over for the past year or more. I can't think of anything Obama has non pretend failed at. It's good though you are being more truthful and admit it was all made up.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1372891088287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372891128795-82</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft BUY Recommendation update 2013.06.11.</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1370954308316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 08:38:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time for the shorts to read and weep. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1372891128795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372892738539-83</Id><Title>I must admit</Title><Msg>all in all we are better off now under Obama. I was fighting this idea so long but today my Ma paid me a visit and said I need to lower my blood pressure. I think it's like rhythm, they have this ability,this vitality, to get things done even when they aren't capable of knowing how. I'll ask my Ma about this idea next week when she visits me. So, for now, I will mellow on the fellow.</Msg><Username>an_obama_natlon</Username><Timestamp>1372892738539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372894460537-84</Id><Topic><Title>I must admit</Title><Username>an_obama_natlon</Username><Timestamp>1372892738539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have trouble digesting simple number facts do you? Two, and two still ain't 4 for you yet?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372894460537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372896501701-85</Id><Topic><Title>I must admit</Title><Username>an_obama_natlon</Username><Timestamp>1372892738539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I must admit, that fake name looks better than the one you tried earlier, are you really that concerned with the facts I offer?</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372896501701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372896788277-86</Id><Topic><Title>I must admit</Title><Username>an_obama_natlon</Username><Timestamp>1372892738539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"are you really that concerned with the facts I offer?" We are concerned that you can't tell the difference between Facts, Opinions and Fabricated BS ... of which the last two are your specialties.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372896788277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372897719528-87</Id><Title>Microsoft and Best Buy Partner on Windows Stores in 600 locations</Title><Msg>Since the announcement on June 13 Microsoft has been opening up new Windows stores in the US and Canada all to be ready for the new school year in September. They will be selling all Microsoft products including Surface Pro, Phones and Xbox. A very smart move indeed.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1372897719528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372897882280-88</Id><Topic><Title>This will be brutal...</Title><Username>mikerego19</Username><Timestamp>1366295219103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 10:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes this is the typical nonsense from the felons who short stocks in general citing past trends and the real dangers of being long no matter the fundamentals. Have seen it all and this one is very amusing. Thanks</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1372897882280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372898034764-89</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are mikerego as Osso thinks you are a first class loser.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1372898034764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:33:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372907403066-90</Id><Topic><Title>I must admit</Title><Username>an_obama_natlon</Username><Timestamp>1372892738539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We are concerned " there is that "we" again, the multiple aliases change, the delusional visions of grandeur shines through, time after time.</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372907403066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 23:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372909494752-91</Id><Topic><Title>I must admit</Title><Username>an_obama_natlon</Username><Timestamp>1372892738539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"there is that "we" again" "WE" are the American People ... as a nation divider, where do you fit in ?</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372909494752</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 23:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>