<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372913091842-1</Id><Topic><Title>I must admit</Title><Username>an_obama_natlon</Username><Timestamp>1372892738539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't know what you are talking about, I haven't tried anyting earlier. To your question, no, because your opinions aren't facts.. If you remove the last two words in your sentence, yes.</Msg><Username>an_obama_natlon</Username><Timestamp>1372913091842</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:44:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372913810068-2</Id><Title>Frist Snowden now Egypt - Obama foreign policy is weak</Title><Msg>US is a laughingstock, no longer superpower to the world</Msg><Username>helping_you_out_99</Username><Timestamp>1372913810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:56:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372914907205-3</Id><Topic><Title>going LONG here!! up 3k</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368549513779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HGFJ</Msg><Username>chris_lamby</Username><Timestamp>1372914907205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 01:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372914922035-4</Id><Topic><Title>going LONG here, oh BILL GATES</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368549474411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EDLH</Msg><Username>chris_lamby</Username><Timestamp>1372914922035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 01:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372934411706-5</Id><Topic><Title>Frist Snowden now Egypt - Obama foreign policy is weak</Title><Username>helping_you_out_99</Username><Timestamp>1372913810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The American Presidency is too large for any man. A competent leader surrounds himself with competent help but first knows how to identify competent help. Obama is not a manager, he is not a leader and had no experience to add those to his emply. Instead he choose fellow incompetents with like Marxist thinking and we are in a mess of non leadership as is the world which still foolishly looks to the U.S. for guidance. It's funny that Chris Christie was the darling of the left when he hugged Obama but was virtually ignored when he noted the fact that "Obama is not a leader".</Msg><Username>an_obama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1372934411706</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 06:40:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372940522703-6</Id><Topic><Title>No $50 by July 4th !</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372885685385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:08:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who needs Microsoft? Sent from my Samsung Google Chromebook with NO WinTel Inside!</Msg><Username>papa.weelee</Username><Timestamp>1372940522703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:22:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372943062165-7</Id><Topic><Title>Frist Snowden now Egypt - Obama foreign policy is weak</Title><Username>helping_you_out_99</Username><Timestamp>1372913810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that is the failed ntotion the far left kooks wanted to convey. Obama was their Messiah that could convey it. We no longer want to be a Super Power. We want to be a member of the "International community". We now like our enemies. Problem is, our enemies don't like us, want to kill us, and see the oppurtunity to do so because the war now weak, and getting weaker with Obama, and the left in control.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372943062165</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372946071827-8</Id><Title>Don't forget, republican conservatives were against a women's</Title><Msg>right to vote, Social Security, Medicare, the forty hour work week, sick time, vacations, civil rights and on and on. They want to be elected to the U.S. Presidency with a record like that, wow !!!!! Now they're doing everything they can to alienate todays modern women voter, crazy...</Msg><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1372946071827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372946273843-9</Id><Topic><Title>Frist Snowden now Egypt - Obama foreign policy is weak</Title><Username>helping_you_out_99</Username><Timestamp>1372913810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is highly regarded, it's the tea party that they mock and laugh at. Ignorant, right wing America is not found elsewhere, even among so called third world countries, the general population is smarter than the American right wing. Name what weakness Obama has in rgard to both snowden and egypt. You just put criticism of Obama out there with no sense behind it.</Msg><Username>ghosanonon</Username><Timestamp>1372946273843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:57:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372952395446-10</Id><Title>these alerts will make you explode</Title><Msg>Guaranteed spot on picks. Can’t believe I didn’t sign up earlier. Text the word Alerts without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>haneymason841</Username><Timestamp>1372952395446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372953038228-11</Id><Title>osso-di.ldo was 100% wrong, unsurprisingly</Title><Msg>$40 by end of May? WRONG $50 by 4th July? WRONG Over $35 "any time" now? WRONG What a bag of excrement.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372953038228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:50:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372954206244-12</Id><Title>The Most Bizarre Steve Ballmerism Ever is a Doozy</Title><Msg>Ballmer is proven to be a total #$%$...he knows NOTHING about real-world conputing... ------------------------------- Here is Mr. Ballmer's statement: How many of us have gone to a meeting with somebody who brought a tablet and then when it comes time to actually take notes, writes them down on pencil and paper. Or can't get at the spreadsheet...or try to use it in terminal emulator mode...or take [a long time] to set up and turn their tablet into something that approximates a PC." The answer is, actually, not many. The reason is that tablet customers are a lot smarter about how to use their devices than Mr. Ballmer would like his own customers to believe. If he can get them to buy into the idea that tablets are just too hard to use in meetings, perhaps the Surface, which runs Windows and MS Office, will sell better. This is a classic, zany Ballmerism: say something that makes you look incredibly stupid to the opposing camp, and say it in earnest, and maybe some of the people in your own camp, out of sheer contrariness, will have something to seize upon and believe. -------------------------------</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372954206244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372955562601-13</Id><Topic><Title>Frist Snowden now Egypt - Obama foreign policy is weak</Title><Username>helping_you_out_99</Username><Timestamp>1372913810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the GOP is about job #1, and putting competent folks that are well qualified in key positions." The Republicans got Bush in that Key Position and look what we got ... Financial Disaster and Great Recession ... And, did you notice that the American People didn't want another Republican in a Key Position ... they lost 2 Presidential Elections.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372955562601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372955719276-14</Id><Title>Using the UI from my phone on my PC is like using the controls on my lawn mower to drive my car:-</Title><Msg>sure it can be done, but why would I? w8 is a total disaster.</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372955719276</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372956642136-15</Id><Title>Let Us Remember The Thousands Dead Due To Republican Negligence On 9/11/2001</Title><Msg>On the birthday of our beloved country let us remember the Thousands who died on 9/11/2001 and in two unnecessary unfunded wars, all due to Republican negligence and mismanagement. (not to mention the trillions of dollars wasted)</Msg><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1372956642136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372956734789-16</Id><Topic><Title>Frist Snowden now Egypt - Obama foreign policy is weak</Title><Username>helping_you_out_99</Username><Timestamp>1372913810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well I was in Europe the last couple of weeks and at the Brandenburg Gate the day after Obama made his speech. The complaint I heard is it took them two days to erect the platform for his 20 minute speech and they weren't impressed. Also in Stockholm, I heard "He was given the Nobel Peace Prize because he wasn't Bush" and now are disillusioned that he uses drones against terrorists, hasn't closed Guantanamo and hasn't repudiated every Bush Cheney security policy No mention of the Tea Party or the American right wing, much less mock and laugh. I'd say you are the ignorant one who still worships the idol with clay feet. The rest of the world has at last figured it out.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372956734789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372957480599-17</Id><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: windoze 8 is garbage</Title><Msg>My venerable Lenovo Thinkpad T420S died after being dropped on the way through airport security at the beginning of a trip to Ireland. It was working fine, but the case shattered, and the damage included jamming the CPU fan, and the repair cost was way more than it was worth. So, I bought a new one - a core i7 Asus with 8G RAM, 1Tb disk and NVidia GT650M graphics on a 1920x1080 ful HD screen, and great audio (Bang &amp; Olufsen). It came with bloody awful windoze 8, so I now count as a purchaser for M$. I'll try for a refund of the windoze tax, but I already wiped the HDD and installed Linux (SuSE 12.3). UEFI secure boot is a pain in the butt, but once I switched it off, Linux installs and boots like lightning. The only oddity is having to have /boot/UEFI as a windoze FAT partition, but I didn't have time to fix all the issues (even if possible), as I needed to get back to work. I played with w8 for a while before nuking it....suspicions confirmed....it is APALLING. I was going to dial boot, just to see how it went, but a short time with w8 convinced me that it is a waste of disk space, so it's gone. Everything works great -even the open source NVidia Nouveau driver is pretty solid and capable nowadays - even got full compositing on KDE . Once again. no M$ in my life!</Msg><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372957480599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372957605046-18</Id><Title>Liberals are an ideological movement who...</Title><Msg>want to use other people's money to advance their desires and think they know how to rule the world. They are the elites, in their own minds, who view humanity's every challenge as an opportunity for government intervention. Yet, again, they must use those with conservative values who do not suck off the government, but maintain it. All they have actually done is kill the will to work and provide for oneself. Brainwashing the masses to be happy with a mediocre lifestyle. Just like in Europe where long lines to get health care as long as it is free suffice even though some pay a 25%.VAT tax. Sounds like a preview of coming attractions.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372957605046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372957793513-19</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals are an ideological movement who...</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372957605046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:06:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you get that from Glen Beck ?</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372957793513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372958002118-20</Id><Topic><Title>Frist Snowden now Egypt - Obama foreign policy is weak</Title><Username>helping_you_out_99</Username><Timestamp>1372913810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The complaint I heard is it took them two days to erect the platform for his 20 minute speech and they weren't impressed." I wouldn't be impressed with the 2 day slowness of the workers either .... Anyone who isn't Bush that starts wars based on BS should be given the Nobel Peace Prize.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372958002118</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372958325760-21</Id><Topic><Title>Let Us Remember The Thousands Dead Due To Republican Negligence On 9/11/2001</Title><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1372956642136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So we went to war in Iraq based on Lies ... WMD's. That was the Primary Reason. "Bush Admits WMD "Main Reason" for Iraq; Press Ignores Admission" "Now, look, I -- part of the reason we went into Iraq: was -- the main reason we went into Iraq: at the time was we thought he had weapons of mass destruction. It turns out he didn't, but he had the capacity to make weapons of mass destruction." And 1000's of soldiers died for "We Thought".</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372958325760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:18:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372958341710-22</Id><Topic><Title>Frist Snowden now Egypt - Obama foreign policy is weak</Title><Username>helping_you_out_99</Username><Timestamp>1372913810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"disillusioned that he uses drones against terrorists" I'm not. "I heard" is the usual right wing ignoramous proof.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1372958341710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:19:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372958556425-23</Id><Topic><Title>Frist Snowden now Egypt - Obama foreign policy is weak</Title><Username>helping_you_out_99</Username><Timestamp>1372913810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You haven't named anything Obama's foreign policy is weak at. All you can do is say it is weak, which is very weak, hahahahaha</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1372958556425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:22:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372958900903-24</Id><Topic><Title>Let Us Remember The Thousands Dead Due To Republican Negligence On 9/11/2001</Title><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1372956642136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember Vietnam too, and when a package has "made in Vietnam" on it at a store, don't buy it.</Msg><Username>lithiumniobate</Username><Timestamp>1372958900903</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:28:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372959182545-25</Id><Topic><Title>Frist Snowden now Egypt - Obama foreign policy is weak</Title><Username>helping_you_out_99</Username><Timestamp>1372913810068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 00:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pepedidiot, it's a good thing you live in a country that takes care of it's idiots because it is evident you are too dumb and lazy to provide for yourself.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372959182545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:33:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372959924820-26</Id><Topic><Title>Let Us Remember The Thousands Dead Due To Republican Negligence On 9/11/2001</Title><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1372956642136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, it was a Republican Congress and Administration that effed up. WMDs was a lie from day one.</Msg><Username>lawn_brat</Username><Timestamp>1372959924820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:45:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372962475012-27</Id><Topic><Title>Let Us Remember The Thousands Dead Due To Republican Negligence On 9/11/2001</Title><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1372956642136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry to burst your bubble, but 9-11-2001 was a joint intelligence agency false flag with unknown operatives carrying it out. Nobody knows ANY details as there was no investigation. The mafia cannot investigate themselves. 15 of the 19 so called hijackers were escorted through the Saudi Arabian Consulate office by CIA case officers. Military stand down and never an indictment for OBL.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1372962475012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:27:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372962540775-28</Id><Topic><Title>Let Us Remember The Thousands Dead Due To Republican Negligence On 9/11/2001</Title><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1372956642136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>American unjustly and illegally attacked North Vietnam. I guess you only read military news. The Mf'ers who carried out this false flag even ADMITTED on TV, it was a false flag.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1372962540775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372963518372-29</Id><Topic><Title>Let Us Remember The Thousands Dead Due To Republican Negligence On 9/11/2001</Title><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1372956642136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"American unjustly and illegally attacked North Vietnam." Americans, not American is correct English. The South Vietnamese weren't idly standing by. Go read some history books starting with the Eisenhower administration when it started. I didn't even know there was "military news."</Msg><Username>lithiumniobate</Username><Timestamp>1372963518372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:45:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372963781300-30</Id><Topic><Title>Anybody got any other ideas of how we can pretend Obama is failing.</Title><Username>an_obama_nati0n</Username><Timestamp>1372871739560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why pretend, when by comparison to all other U.S. Presidents, he ranks right alongside Benedict Arnold.</Msg><Username>zingermaster</Username><Timestamp>1372963781300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372966982138-31</Id><Title>Economically, Could Obama Be America's Best President?</Title><Msg>Forbes - 5/16/2013 "Significantly, in 2000 America had a budget surplus. By 2009 surpluses were long gone and the country was racking up historic deficits as taxes were cut while simultaneously outlays for defense skyrocketed to cover costs of wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. Additionally, banks were on the edge of failing due to unregulated real estate speculation and massive derivative losses." "Although we hear almost no one in the Obama administration taking credit for record index highs, they should. Because the President deserves attention for how well this economy has done during his leadership." "Today the Congressional Budget Office is reporting a $200B decrease in the deficit almost entirely due to increased revenue from a growing economy and higher taxes on the wealthiest Americans. The deficit is now only 4% of the GDP, down from over 10% at the end of Bush’s administration – and projections are for it to be only 2% by 2015 (before Obama leaves office.) "</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372966982138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372967343686-32</Id><Topic><Title>Economically, Could Obama Be America's Best President?</Title><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372966982138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:43:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For his crony rich contributor buddies for sure. For the workin stiff he's shafted them. Many are now the workin poor if they do have a job. Obama has created 53 straight months of unemployment over 7.6%, and June new job numbers were poor again...unemployment will continue to rise. Bush dropped unemployment to 4.5% regarded as full employment the moment he got the pinko Democrats to pass his tax cut bill. Easy to compare, and see the difference in good policy.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372967343686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372968323721-33</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget, republican conservatives were against a women's</Title><Username>tocrazyright</Username><Timestamp>1372946071827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what you say is so true........</Msg><Username>therwnjneedhelp</Username><Timestamp>1372968323721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372969335908-34</Id><Topic><Title>Economically, Could Obama Be America's Best President?</Title><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372966982138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:43:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Bush dropped unemployment to 4.5% regarded as full employment the moment he got the pinko Democrats to pass his tax cut bill. " You Right-Wing Stooges always post Pre Financial Disaster and Great Recession stuff. "Using nonseasonally adjusted numbers, the unemployment rate was already 8.5% when Obama took office, and it is 7.6% today".</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372969335908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372969652239-35</Id><Topic><Title>Economically, Could Obama Be America's Best President?</Title><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372966982138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:43:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush didn't visit the downlowclubs like OIDIOT!</Msg><Username>shwdl</Username><Timestamp>1372969652239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372970105743-36</Id><Topic><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: windoze 8 is garbage</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372957480599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:04:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad you didn't get the free Windows Blue beta upgrade to W8 because you need WINDOWS to trade stocks and for the business world. Instead you made your new pc a IDIOT like you. NTFS was launched with Windows NT and is a far more advanced and secure disk file system than FAT32. However, it is not widely compatible with other computers and operating systems, so not only is your pc a IDIOT, it's less secure than NTFS so you win the Turkey. CONGRADALATIONS STUPID.</Msg><Username>misterreality14</Username><Timestamp>1372970105743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:35:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372971294709-37</Id><Topic><Title>500% in profit just this MONTH</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368250132474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 01:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARFM</Msg><Username>chris_lamby</Username><Timestamp>1372971294709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372971660109-38</Id><Title>Commercials can reveal so much.....VCSY Granted Emily patent</Title><Msg>Commercials can tell us so much "Is it cool if I date Emily when you're........(parachute opens-VCSY LIVES!).....................Never mind!" Watch the Microsoft Windows Phone commercial with the skydivers</Msg><Username>pokerface072508</Username><Timestamp>1372971660109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:01:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972698788-39</Id><Topic><Title>Making money is to easy when your...</Title><Username>rogerwalker513</Username><Timestamp>1371786380089</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 23:46:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TRUE</Msg><Username>chris_lamby</Username><Timestamp>1372972698788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972750388-40</Id><Topic><Title>Just had to buy a new laptop at short notice: windoze 8 is garbage</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372957480599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:04:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you smell bird droppings? smells very strong right here ...</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372972750388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972794293-41</Id><Topic><Title>Commercials can reveal so much.....VCSY Granted Emily patent</Title><Username>pokerface072508</Username><Timestamp>1372971660109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:01:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your post was the wrong color. i have fixed that now ...</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372972794293</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972919879-42</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>careful they don't step on you!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372972919879</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372973282929-43</Id><Topic><Title>Making money is to easy when your...</Title><Username>rogerwalker513</Username><Timestamp>1371786380089</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 23:46:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WPNV</Msg><Username>merri.evans</Username><Timestamp>1372973282929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:28:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372973390469-44</Id><Topic><Title>No $50 by July 4th !</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372885685385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:08:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>make them wear leggings! and no more journals, vlogs only!!</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372973390469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:29:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372973518654-45</Id><Topic><Title>mjna DUMP dont lose your money, i made 400% month</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368989019609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very good deal</Msg><Username>merri.evans</Username><Timestamp>1372973518654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372973698716-46</Id><Topic><Title>osso-di.ldo was 100% wrong, unsurprisingly</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372953038228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>problem! bag is too small to hold whole load. :-D</Msg><Username>corneliusflake</Username><Timestamp>1372973698716</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:34:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372974205360-47</Id><Topic><Title>osso-di.ldo was 100% wrong, unsurprisingly</Title><Username>the.heretic7</Username><Timestamp>1372953038228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cornerius frake not know his prace- making noodres and the raundry</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1372974205360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372974414679-48</Id><Title>Psssst</Title><Msg>SNGX - major buy in by billionaire investor last week. Hurry though. You can thank me later.</Msg><Username>wealthywanger</Username><Timestamp>1372974414679</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:46:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372975268960-49</Id><Topic><Title>going LONG here!! up 3k</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368549513779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wonderful</Msg><Username>merri.evans</Username><Timestamp>1372975268960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372975309829-50</Id><Topic><Title>going LONG here, oh BILL GATES</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368549474411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WENP</Msg><Username>merri.evans</Username><Timestamp>1372975309829</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:01:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372976315702-51</Id><Topic><Title>500% in profit just this MONTH</Title><Username>stockmr</Username><Timestamp>1368250132474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 01:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>exquisite</Msg><Username>merri.evans</Username><Timestamp>1372976315702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:18:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372978886212-52</Id><Title>A Sequester Fizzle for Military Fireworks This Fourth of July - THANKS TEA PARTY</Title><Msg>A Sequester Fizzle for Military Fireworks This Fourth of July Several military bases have canceled their firework celebrations this Fourth of July due to sequestration. THE TEA PARTY HOUSE ARE KOCH SUCKERS!!!</Msg><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1372978886212</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:01:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372980946257-53</Id><Title>100 million dollar Africa trip and what did we get fot it:?</Title><Msg>Besides and apology tour. For 100 million dollars we could have had all kinds of military fireworks. Thanks Obama.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372980946257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:35:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372981992384-54</Id><Title>Most Undervalued Stock on NASDAQ</Title><Msg>Concurrent (CCUR) currently $7.44 has only 8.754mm s/o, a market cap of $65.13mm, cash of $22.37mm, no debt, and an enterprise value of $42.76mm. CCUR's enterprise value is only 0.68X revenues of $63.23mm, 6X operating cash flow of $7.13mm, and 7.64X free cash flow of $5.6mm. CCUR's EPS was up 175% last quarter and it just raised its dividend by 100% to $0.48 per share for a yield of 6.45%. CCUR is the leader of some of the world's hottest technologies! CCUR leads the video on demand (VOD) delivery business with over 2.4mm streams deployed worldwide and 4 of America's 6 largest cable TV operators as clients. The #2 VOD technology vendor Seachange (SEAC) closed yesterday at $11.83 and is about to break its 52-week high of $12.10. SEAC has an enterprise value of $273.2mm or 1.75X revenues of $156.11mm, 15.67X operating cash flow of $17.43mm, and 20.12X free cash flow of $13.58mm. An enterprise value of 1.75X revenues would value CCUR at $15.20 per share. An enterprise value of 15.67X operating cash flow will value CCUR at $15.32 per share. An enterprise value of 20.12X free cash flow will value CCUR at $15.43 per share. CCUR also has the leading Big Data Analytics software being used by pay-TV operators. CCUR tracks the behavior of 35mm pay-TV subscribers and has processed 15 billion media transactions. Big Data Analytics is the hottest space on Wall Street. Tableau Software (DATA) recently had its IPO at $31 and hit a new 52-week high yesterday of $61.45 for a gain of 98%. DATA's enterprise value is currently 24X revenues vs. CCUR's enterprise value of 0.68X revenues!</Msg><Username>asj48493</Username><Timestamp>1372981992384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372982317691-55</Id><Topic><Title>Economically, Could Obama Be America's Best President?</Title><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372966982138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:43:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty compelling evidence. I will ask Ma when she visits next week. No one called me today, and I was right here in my room, oh well. I used to have calls on all holidays before Obama got in with his false marxist votes.</Msg><Username>an_obama_natlon</Username><Timestamp>1372982317691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:58:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372984726762-56</Id><Topic><Title>Economically, Could Obama Be America's Best President?</Title><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372966982138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:43:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I used to have calls on all holidays before Obama got in with his false marxist votes." What ? FAUX Opinions, Rush, Hannity has not called you ? I guess you had to talk to your aliases all day .... Sooooooooooooooooooooo Funny.</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372984726762</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 20:38:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372984826386-57</Id><Topic><Title>100 million dollar Africa trip and what did we get fot it:?</Title><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1372980946257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:35:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Much more than the BILLIONS Bush spend on his wars ....</Msg><Username>hawcreeks_world</Username><Timestamp>1372984826386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 20:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372986511530-58</Id><Topic><Title>Psssst</Title><Username>wealthywanger</Username><Timestamp>1372974414679</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:46:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the remainder of 2013 numerous catalysts are currently in store for SNGX. Investors can expect a decision regarding the company's BARDA funding application for Orbishield™ (likely prior to the summer's end). It appears that numerous advantages exist for Orbishield™ including being in pill form rather than injectable, not needing refrigeration (due to utilizing SNGX's Thermostability platform) and having prior shown efficacy and safety as an active ingredient in animal studies. Following the contract decision, in the later half of the year we can expect the start of Phase II trials for SNGX's Oral Mucositis, the start for Pediatric Crohn's Phase II/III trials and the start of Phase II cGVHD trials. Between SNGX's large pipeline of pharmaceuticals and biodefense candidates coupled with the overwhelming amount of orphan and fast track designations received, I see SNGX as a highly diversified biotech with a great chance of success in the future.</Msg><Username>wealthywanger</Username><Timestamp>1372986511530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372989025575-59</Id><Title>MSFT will hit $45 to $55 at the end of this year!!!!</Title><Msg>The big move up will start at Q report in 12 days. Good luck all longs!!!</Msg><Username>sss150</Username><Timestamp>1372989025575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:50:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372989641338-60</Id><Topic><Title>Commercials can reveal so much.....VCSY Granted Emily patent</Title><Username>pokerface072508</Username><Timestamp>1372971660109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:01:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By: moonpunk 04 Jul 2013, 05:46 PM CDT Msg. 377436 of 377442 (Reply to 377430 by govcsy) gov - they have to have a distraction or they will explode. Their safety valves are under such pressure they need to desperately redirect attention away from the trend showing VCSY building every day toward a larger purpose. They've been planning a diversion campaign for a long time and now they're putting it into action. Danny is not the story here. I am not the story here. Emily is the story. Four powerful patents that destroy the traditional software culture represented by the people backing tepe, al, stockwabbit, johnnny and mirror. These are their hacks - low dollar thugs willing to contract for years to attempt to undermine the public discussion concerning what VCSY has. Now is when they need the maximum effort to redirect reader attention away from the intellectual property and off into a controversy they can use to fill the board up with hundreds of inconsequential small minded rants - phony indignation for somebody "damaging VCSY" while they've practiced the art of damage on VCSY for ten years. Last night and today show just how scary the future is for them. They spent hours in hysteria. Today they woke up realizing they overplayed that angst and it showed as panic. Now look how re-aligned they are. Al is calm and reasonable. The rest are claiming they "won" some sort of ridiculous semantic battle. The truth is tomorrow looms ahead of them and if the trend continues they're facing a brand new bunch of readers poking around for VCSY information. Attempting to counter the thugs' efforts is pointless but necessary. It looks to the readers like a typical penny stock discussion about a company collapsed from the dotcom era. That's good. Readers won't take rosy scenarios and wonderful technology stories as true. They expect a basher ravaged forum here with chaotic screaming and raucous hysterics. We achieved our end by passing the real discussion over to</Msg><Username>pokerface072508</Username><Timestamp>1372989641338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372992850567-61</Id><Topic><Title>Gartner Recommends Windows 8.1 For Full Scale Enterprise Deployment....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1371901921464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has Microsoft finally got rid of the blue screen of death in Windows 8.1?</Msg><Username>stockgaming.com</Username><Timestamp>1372992850567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>