<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358571762972-1</Id><Topic><Title>Proven: Obama was the liar when he said his Obamacare would reduce costs</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358566870187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:41:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama doesn't lie, but you do. Never have seen one Obama lie yet, and don't expect to. Your posts are meaningless. Do more research, but for the truth of matters, You probably are the biggest liar most of us have ever come across in our lives. Thank God we can turn you off. Big weekend of telling stories about Obama for you ahead, to what end is unknown. You can try to unelect Obama the rest of your life, nothing is unelecting him, and he isn't running again. How many times do people have to tell you things before you hear.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1358571762972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:02:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358574187044-2</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is really taking off now, In phones , tablets, New PC and in upgrades , GOOD JOB MSFT</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1358437451993</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:44:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why would anyone in their right mind who is NOT a short waste his life posting on this board. but I guess we always knew you were living in cloud cookoo land at that wotopimp</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358574187044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:43:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358592859796-3</Id><Topic><Title>The liberal New York Times November 19, 1989</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358558339258</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 20:18:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Initially run by the father of that fellow who recently tried to buy the Presidency, old what's-his-name the BSing Mormon. His campaign wanted to call him a "car guy", kind of like Joe Isuzu.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358592859796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 05:54:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358594136871-4</Id><Title>Microsoft the dinosaur</Title><Msg>You can how Microsoft managers think. They think they can still succeed by doing things the way they did in the Eighties, when most people had no idea what a computer was. They could cobble together a product that was somewhere in the neighborhood of what it ought to be, and based on user feedback they could adjust it, bit by bit, in the direction of what customers needed. They could spend ten years improving Windows that way, until finally it became a more or less usable product. That's not good enough any more...</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1358594136871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:15:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358594956120-5</Id><Topic><Title>Microsoft the dinosaur</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1358594136871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:15:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You can how Microsoft managers think" How what? Go back to kinder garden you illiterate bastid..</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1358594956120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:29:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358601583436-6</Id><Title>What Microsoft Could Learn From McDonald’s</Title><Msg>Google it.... Quoting: "Does Microsoft think of itself as a premium brand? Personally, I’ve always been loyal to Windows PCs solely because their cost is so low..... "Microsoft should take a look at McDonald’s strategy. The fast food restaurant has seen enormous success by heavily marketing inexpensive products (e.g. the Dollar Menu) and by promoting low-grade items (e.g. the McRib). Not every diner is looking for a five-star meal. I’m not slamming McDonald’s, of course – I commend the company for its rational business model and expert promotional campaigns like the McRib tour. And, to be thorough, I should point out that the company offers menu options aside from just their Dollar Menu and just the McRib. McDonald’s sells products at various price points including “premium salads” and “premium roast coffee,” and these pricier foods have their place even alongside a Dollar Menu. The company, however, doesn’t lose sight of their target demographic, and neither should Microsoft. "If Microsoft fails to gain traction in the tablet market, the consequences could be dire. Now that Windows 8 seems to be universally hated, and with critics advising PC users to stay with Windows 7, consumers have less incentive to purchase a new PC with the new ecosystem. Microsoft needs to catch consumer interest in its new tablet, and its bait needs to be a low price that users expect."</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1358601583436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:19:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358602412171-7</Id><Topic><Title>Proven: Obama is the lr when he said your taxes would not rise</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358566795898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:39:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll bet you wonder why all you have in life is this stupid message board and the inane garbage you post on it incessantly.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358602412171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:33:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358602437781-8</Id><Title>Is Linux For Losers?</Title><Msg>Is Linux For Losers? NEW YORK , Daniel Lyons - Theo de Raadt is a pioneer of the open source software movement and a huge proponent of free software. But he is no fan of the open source Linux operating system. "It's terrible," De Raadt says. "Everyone using it don't realize how bad it is. And the Linux people will just stick with it and add to it rather than stepping back and saying, 'This is garbage and we should fix it.'" "You know what I found? Right in the kernel, in the heart of the operating system, I found a developer's comment that said, 'Does this belong here?' "Lok says. "What kind of confidence does that inspire? Torvalds, via e-mail, says De Raadt is "difficult" and declined to comment further. Bing it.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1358602437781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:33:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358605337339-9</Id><Topic><Title>Proven: Obama is the lr when he said your taxes would not rise</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358566795898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:39:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stuff it, punk. Go fill a Mangrove.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358605337339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:22:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358605476899-10</Id><Topic><Title>Public Opinion Of The Republican Controlled House - ( o )</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1358564364588</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:59:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Approval of the Republican Party = 14%ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....ha...ha....</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1358605476899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:24:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358605948277-11</Id><Topic><Title>What Microsoft Could Learn From McDonald’s</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1358601583436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:19:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IF they fail to gain traction? They invented the tablet over a decade ago and are getting less than 1% of tablet sales. This isn't a potential situation, it's a given.</Msg><Username>fan_tazer</Username><Timestamp>1358605948277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:32:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358607097137-12</Id><Topic><Title>Proven: Obama is the lr when he said your taxes would not rise</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358566795898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:39:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have a long cry. Get over your lost love Willard. He was just toying with your affections and didn't care much for you anyway. And try to figure out why you should take advantage of the mental health counselling that comes along with your high-line medical insurance you pay so much of your hard earned wealth for.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358607097137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:51:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358607165277-13</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT is really a strong stock with a great dividend!</Title><Username>dogeater2013</Username><Timestamp>1358568404529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 23:06:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure you did,&amp; that's why you infest a chat board LOL,go eat another #$%$ boy.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1358607165277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:52:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358607288792-14</Id><Topic><Title>Proven: Obama is the lr when he said your taxes would not rise</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358566795898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:39:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've got to be as dumb as a libdem to think the mIddle class and the poor wouldn't pay a huge price for Obama's support for huge socialist, govt spending that he wants to increase, not decline. The workin stiff that gets a W-2 form pays the bulk of the taxes.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358607288792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:54:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358607447882-15</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street will squeeze MSFT shorts on Thursday just like they did GE's. This is how bankers make their money</Title><Username>rdctwo2</Username><Timestamp>1358606526234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:42:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In this terrible govt debt mode that the Obama regime' has us in, and will only get worse, shorts have the big upper hand. Catastrophic news will continue to come out.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358607447882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:57:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358608167656-16</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT is really a strong stock with a great dividend!</Title><Username>dogeater2013</Username><Timestamp>1358568404529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 23:06:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AND I'M THE EASTER BUNNY.</Msg><Username>nostra_dumbass666</Username><Timestamp>1358608167656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:09:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610624896-17</Id><Topic><Title>Proven: Obama is the lr when he said your taxes would not rise</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358566795898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:39:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee, one of Hawfreak's imaginary lovers chimes right in with a "deep insight". Should we put up a sign-in sheet? Paging Mr. golfiebooger... Mr. golfiebooger, call on line three.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358610624896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:50:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358611853508-18</Id><Title>Troll Alert! hawdiaper On Another Non-Stop Troll. Did you change out your load from yesterday?</Title><Msg>hawdiaper, you urine soaked troll, do you think you are improving the approval rating of the Republican Party? It's at its lowest since 2008 when it was at record lows. Or does a urine soaked troll like you have the opposite effect? Something for you to 'thimk' about!</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1358611853508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:10:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358612918933-19</Id><Topic><Title>Proven: Obama is the lr when he said your taxes would not rise</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358566795898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:39:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He didn't lie, you do. Your interpretations are as far fetched as moon colonies before 2020. Try all your life and you won't find one lie from the President, not one.. What he said was 100% true and correct. Blame your friends for it. I've about had enough of you again. You are full of hot air, and seem to think what you do here serves a purpose. You'd do just as well to go throw sand into the ocean all day as what you do here. At least come up with some new ideas besides Obama isn't the one to vote for. We already voted for him, you miss that? The worst is when you show yourself as to what your agenda is with the comment about pigment challenged people. AND he is drinking Whites Only water right now. In summary, get lost loser, get a life.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1358612918933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:28:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613842137-20</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>adammedlin953</Username><Timestamp>1358459471099</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:51:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good one</Msg><Username>markharrison196</Username><Timestamp>1358613842137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:44:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358615022054-21</Id><Title>Let's all pine for the days of the Confederacy, then the rise of the KKK....</Title><Msg>...the Jim Crow laws and the good old days of segregation. Separate but equal was the cry of the old former Confederacy. The black schools became separate but they were anything but equal. When Dems like John Kennedy, then later, Lyndon Johnson, busted up the segregation of the old South, those Southern Blue Dog Democrats became Republicans. They switched parties. The Republican Party to this day is the party of separation. It used to be the party of choice in the south. Thanks to changing demographics, oh, the times they are a changin'. Florida a Blue state? North Carolina a Blue state?, Georgia was just 2% away from becoming a Blue state. Texas is predicted to go Blue by 2016 due to the growing Hispanic population. These are troubling times in the Kingdom of Bitter Old Republican Red Necks.</Msg><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1358615022054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:03:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358615511357-22</Id><Title>Modern America and Social Justice</Title><Msg>I was listening to a song by Steeleye Span called “Fighting for Strangers.” My nephew just joined the US Marine Corps. In part he has no reasonable employment options available, due to the Obama (non)Economy. In part he is following the advice of conservative talk show hosts to no go into debt to go to college or university, but instead to join the military and earn college benefits to use later. I was thinking, “Does it really make sense for a conservative, white, Christian, boy, from the south, to go fight in a failing war for an incompetent, black radical, nonChristian, antiAmerican President?” How does that suit your sense of "social justice." For that matter, how does this apply to young blacks who have maybe twice the unemployment rate and more dismal opportunities, due to the same incompetent, black president that they helped to re-elect because he was black?</Msg><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1358615511357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:11:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358615991897-23</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone else notice how racist and condescending some white Obama supporters really are.???</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358615590606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:13:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No hadn't notice this. Where do you find these people ?? BTW are you seeking help for your worsening illness.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358615991897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:19:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616138201-24</Id><Topic><Title>Troll Alert! hawdiaper On Another Non-Stop Troll. Did you change out your load from yesterday?</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1358611853508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:10:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has to get 100 posts before a new diaper can be procured. When the posting rate ramps up that's because he is sitting in a load.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358616138201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:22:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358616669957-25</Id><Title>carbon traders looking to China for profit.</Title><Msg>Bloomberg "Carbon Traders Stung by Rout Try Again in China" nvestors from Climate Change Capital in London to Climate Bridge Ltd. in Melbourne said this month they are seeking involvement in what may become the world’s largest emissions market. Beijing’s worst-recorded air pollution has renewed pressure on the government, which aims to cut carbon dioxide emissions by as much as 45 percent before 2020. I bet they just don't know what the swamp scientist knows about global warming.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358616669957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:31:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616969940-26</Id><Topic><Title>Modern America and Social Justice</Title><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1358615511357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:11:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean the war started by bush??</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358616969940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:36:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358617847479-27</Id><Topic><Title>Modern America and Social Justice</Title><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1358615511357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:11:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was your point "I am a stupid liberal?" The war was started by terrorists, radical Muslims that Obama won't identify even though they declared war on us. The thing Bush started was a robust, record economy..52 straight months of incredible economic growth initiated by the tax cuts. So Obama's plan? Let's raise taxes and created 8 years of recession conditions, and bankruptcy a real possiblity.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358617847479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:50:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358617971163-28</Id><Topic><Title>Why would anyone, even jokingly, deny Obama lies</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358615279795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:07:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has lied so much, and so consistently that it would be a shocker if he ever told the truth. And when he does spew the truth once in a great while that is not what he wants, and supports behind closed doors.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358617971163</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:52:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619302849-29</Id><Topic><Title>MIcrosoft jacking up the price of Windows 8</Title><Username>stockdox</Username><Timestamp>1358546347111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 16:59:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most analysts don't really know what they are talking about, at least they appeared to be driven by their positions in the stock. Logic tells me that W8 is awesome, "awarded best invention of 2012". Msft has two ways of making huge profits from W8. 1) Raise up the price of W8 so high that none of the pc makers can afford it; msft in turn monopolizes the hybrid laptop/touchpad business. 2) Priced the w8 to affordable range, msft will profit from the sells of w8 and Surface Pro, but the downside is that msft can NOT monopolize the hybrid business. Msft has to compete against 10 or so PC makers mass producing all of these hybrids. So why did I say the analysts have no clue on what they are saying? Because everyone of them says, "the success of msft depends on how many W8 they can sell". The answer is NO!!!!!! it depends on which of those two routes they choose to persue. I think msft is choosing both routes, wanting to price w8 high enough to get as much as they can out of it, at the same time keep the competition to Surface Pro to a limit.</Msg><Username>cameleonman</Username><Timestamp>1358619302849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:15:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619473673-30</Id><Topic><Title>What Microsoft Could Learn From McDonald’s</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1358601583436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:19:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, it doesn't look good for Microsoft. But Microsoft NEEDS to get into mobile, so they will keep trying for as long as the company exists, which won't be forever, but may be several years.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1358619473673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:17:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619826974-31</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone else notice how racist and condescending some white Obama supporters really are.???</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358615590606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:13:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you keep arguing with that priK?</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1358619826974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:23:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358620115905-32</Id><Topic><Title>Let's all pine for the days of the Confederacy, then the rise of the KKK....</Title><Username>rightwing_rethink</Username><Timestamp>1358615022054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:03:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These are troubling times in the Kingdom of Bitter Old Republican Red Necks INDEED!</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1358620115905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:28:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358620631971-33</Id><Topic><Title>What Microsoft Could Learn From McDonald’s</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1358601583436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:19:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They won't make it. Mobile users demand simplicity, reliability, snappy performance, and a vast ecosystem for apps and accessories. MS serves up bloat, weird UIs, flaky performance, and a very limited ecosystem they had to pay/bribe people, including their own moonlighting employees, to create.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1358620631971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:37:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358620803987-34</Id><Topic><Title>How to catch a herd of wild animals</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358617824166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:50:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brilliant post. I think 3 walls are up already.</Msg><Username>ghosananon</Username><Timestamp>1358620803987</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:40:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358621008423-35</Id><Topic><Title>What Microsoft Could Learn From McDonald’s</Title><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1358601583436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:19:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tend to agree. Besides the points you mention, there is the fact that Microsoft is very late to the party, so the decision has already been made. Nothing Microsoft does is likely to make much difference, unless it's what the author of the article suggested -- lower its prices.</Msg><Username>wottowwottow</Username><Timestamp>1358621008423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:43:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358622861121-36</Id><Topic><Title>Proven: Obama is the lr when he said your taxes would not rise</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358566795898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:39:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try to understand- hawfaeces is a paranoid schizophrenic with some pretty rigid delusions. About all that a truly Christian person can do is try and find compassion for him. After all some of the more liberal life philosophys from Christianity to rationalism and especially determinism tell us that in short - we all play the hand we are dealt in life. Hawfaeces is no more responsible for his mental illness than Obama is for the color of his skin. Weather his illness was inherited or if he acquired it we are still required to practice Christian love and forgiveness and compassion. No doubt wild horses couldn't drag Haw in to the shrink to get him started on some kind of therapy so we will just have to put up with him as long as he isn't obviously dangerous. Lets hope the very young and impressionable do not have the misfortune of reading his hate and lies</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358622861121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:14:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358623181555-37</Id><Topic><Title>Proven: Obama is the lr when he said your taxes would not rise</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358566795898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:39:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBTW I didnt mean to denegrate Obamas skin color but only to allude to his being a black person.</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358623181555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:19:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358623333920-38</Id><Title>First Black Woman On The SCOTUS Soon</Title><Msg>It was important that Obama won. There will be 2 appointments to the SCOTUS within the next 4 years. No more, "Corporations are people and money is freedom of speech." Say buh-bye to the Koch-Rove-Norquist headlock on big money Olegarchy.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1358623333920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:22:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358623476612-39</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone else notice how racist and condescending some white Obama supporters really are.???</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358615590606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:13:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, but we'll keep an eye out for that. Remarkable how nobody's noticed that in spite of your exceedingly active fantasy life as some sort of engineero-constructo-investo-super-multi-millionare with brilliant insights into the mechanics of bathroom scales and powerful mathematical tools at your fingertips to apply to their behavior (proving, by the way, that with only a few months of remedial work, you'll be all ready for that freshman Chemistry for non-science majors course you appear to be lusting after) you have a surprising abundance of time to post what appears to be a poorly digested mash of stale wingnut talking points "freshened" with snippets from the latest Limbaugh sermon to the faithful. I guess that's what makes you such a successful message board troll, what with the extent and frequency of your appearances here by popular demand. Is the veal any good this week, by the way? And the kid in the third row wants to know if you can make that funny noise with your butt again, he was too shy to ask himself, but he thinks it's really awesome how you get that wet sound almost every time.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358623476612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:24:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358624304626-40</Id><Title>Anyone notice how Hawfreak pretends to confuse "uppityness" with "racism"?</Title><Msg>Either that or he doesn't want to make un-American Marxists (non-KKK members) too ashamed of their insufficient bigotry.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358624304626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:38:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358624515368-41</Id><Title>How to catch a wild #$%$.</Title><Msg>Leave a fresh pack of adult diapers in your Have-a-Heart trap. If you're not of the bleedin-heart liberal persuasion you can just leave them under a deadfall.</Msg><Username>nd1005</Username><Timestamp>1358624515368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:41:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358627912716-42</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone else notice how racist and condescending some white Obama supporters really are.???</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358615590606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:13:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get a fresh diaper. Just trying to be helpful, not condescending. What, can't afford a new pack until your EBT card is refilled? What a shame.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358627912716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:38:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358628174607-43</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone notice how Hawfreak pretends to confuse "uppityness" with "racism"?</Title><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358624304626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:38:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Garbage. Try the "REAL 'Murcan" BS again. It's got more punch. This troll just makes you seem whiny and doesn't get any rage up in the audience. You'd think with twelve years at this gig you'd have a better sense of what gets the food thrown at you.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358628174607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:42:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358632295152-44</Id><Title>Communists are everywhere</Title><Msg>Them Beatles were communists. And such a long hair. Long hair = communists.</Msg><Username>old_white_man_in_diapers</Username><Timestamp>1358632295152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:51:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632689323-45</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone else notice how racist and condescending some white Obama supporters really are.???</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358615590606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:13:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm with you brother. Darn right Obama is dark. All he can do is dance like the rest of them peoples. Does he believe in the virtues of the AR15 semi-auto? Most commies fear the AR15. They want to drink from the same water fountain as whites.</Msg><Username>old_white_man_in_diapers</Username><Timestamp>1358632689323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:58:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358633050089-46</Id><Title>Some Democrats Are Known Communists</Title><Msg>Those communists want to feed the poor! Those evil basturds.</Msg><Username>old_white_man_in_diapers</Username><Timestamp>1358633050089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:04:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358633202443-47</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone else notice how racist and condescending some white Obama supporters really are.???</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358615590606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:13:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nuthin better to do.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358633202443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:06:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358633367617-48</Id><Title>Attends is the best thing since sliced bread</Title><Msg>Now these babies can hold a load for days.</Msg><Username>old_white_man_in_diapers</Username><Timestamp>1358633367617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:09:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358633409552-49</Id><Topic><Title>Modern America and Social Justice</Title><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1358615511357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:11:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why is it Obamas war as the OP implied</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358633409552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:10:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358633601572-50</Id><Topic><Title>Modern America and Social Justice</Title><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1358615511357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:11:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nuthin' but communists in the Marines now days anyway. I've known many bright Marines that were known to be known communists. The Lord is the important thing. Of course he had long hair and a beard, another known communist no doubt about it.</Msg><Username>old_white_man_in_diapers</Username><Timestamp>1358633601572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:13:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358633798145-51</Id><Title>Who is not a known Communist? Rush Limbaugh!</Title><Msg>He doesn't have long hair. Rush has hardly no hair at all. bald = not a known communist Plus he's fat. fat = not a known communist.</Msg><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1358633798145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:16:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358633996126-52</Id><Topic><Title>Who is not a known Communist? Rush Limbaugh!</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1358633798145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:16:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WRONG. Rush wore a red shirt. red = known communist blue shirt = not a known communist</Msg><Username>old_white_man_in_diapers</Username><Timestamp>1358633996126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:19:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358634373015-53</Id><Topic><Title>Modern America and Social Justice</Title><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1358615511357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:11:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the OP said it was Obamas war. Another RWNJ said it was the terrorsts war. Did you have a point.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358634373015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:26:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358634868301-54</Id><Topic><Title>When a man campaigns with a Red Poster and then makes openly Marxist policy statements</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358634259870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:24:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm with you brother. Known communists are everywhere. Hey, how 'bout them Attends, eh? They can hold a load for days.</Msg><Username>old_white_man_in_diapers</Username><Timestamp>1358634868301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:34:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358635296537-55</Id><Topic><Title>Modern America and Social Justice</Title><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1358615511357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:11:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never said anything about Afghanistan. Neither did the OP. Obama did not start the Afghan war it is not his war. Do you now believe the Afghan war is unjust, unwarrented , unwinnable?? Do you have anything to say per the OP topic.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358635296537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:41:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358635845311-56</Id><Topic><Title>carbon traders looking to China for profit.</Title><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358616669957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:31:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the government directly taxed carbon would that be better</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358635845311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:50:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358638022615-57</Id><Topic><Title>Modern America and Social Justice</Title><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1358615511357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:11:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's Obama's war because he bought it with his policies and four years of his time playing golf. Do you think it OK for a president to play tthe most golf in history while he is sending our young troops to die for his failed war?</Msg><Username>goodgod000000001</Username><Timestamp>1358638022615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:27:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640254243-58</Id><Topic><Title>Attends is the best thing since sliced bread</Title><Username>old_white_man_in_diapers</Username><Timestamp>1358633367617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:09:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder how the babies like them?</Msg><Username>bill_california_paseo</Username><Timestamp>1358640254243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:04:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358641749320-59</Id><Topic><Title>Modern America and Social Justice</Title><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1358615511357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:11:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I get it. So he agreed with the administration (bush) and that makes it his war. Lots of beer belly fat farts at the local tavern agreed also. Is it "their" war also. What was YOUR opinion at the time Obama supported the war?? I bet you were for it. Is it your war ?? The ownership following you're reasoning should belong mostly to those who had the most power to control the issue of going to war, and that clearly was bush.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358641749320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:29:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358642957626-60</Id><Topic><Title>Afghanistan is Obama's war and Old White men is CFury</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358642391318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:39:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bzzzzzt. Wrong on both counts. Try again, whiny sixth-grader.</Msg><Username>truth_in_government</Username><Timestamp>1358642957626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:49:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358643356023-61</Id><Topic><Title>Afghanistan is Obama's war and Old White men is CFury</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358642391318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:39:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He said that in the context of already being there, right ?? And he is definitely wrong that we should have fought this war but then again it was in play when he took office was it not?? The real question which cannot be answered is whether he would have started this war under identical circumstances. I do know that at the time all neaocons were raging to war somewhere. You yourdammmedself supported this war vigorously on this very message board years ago.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358643356023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:55:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358644570927-62</Id><Topic><Title>Communists are everywhere</Title><Username>old_white_man_in_diapers</Username><Timestamp>1358632295152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have the right to bear Communists, Kruschev, yeah that was a typical looking liberal with long hair, just like a Beatle he was.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1358644570927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:16:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358644916926-63</Id><Topic><Title>Communists are everywhere</Title><Username>old_white_man_in_diapers</Username><Timestamp>1358632295152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I need to add from the tea party photos I have seen, most of the men look like Krushchev, and the wives even more so. Since they look like that, tea partiers= Communists.</Msg><Username>peppeek</Username><Timestamp>1358644916926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:21:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358646830016-64</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 is all about Internet security. This will drive business demand.</Title><Username>rdctwo2</Username><Timestamp>1358630619389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:23:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and will moved to linux as the evil empire is notourious for lacking security.</Msg><Username>shortinfygetrich</Username><Timestamp>1358646830016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:53:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358647299240-65</Id><Title>earth to evil empire no ones wants your malware jacking the price very much so</Title><Msg>is the ceo that clueless? hello your monopoly is on a dying platform. this will only cause peps to buy google lap tops.</Msg><Username>shortinfygetrich</Username><Timestamp>1358647299240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:01:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358647918200-66</Id><Topic><Title>Proven: Obama was the liar when he said his Obamacare would reduce costs</Title><Username>hawcreek12</Username><Timestamp>1358566870187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:41:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe they will now rise LESS than before the new healthcare act; time will tell, lets wait and see!!!!</Msg><Username>mikemclaug</Username><Timestamp>1358647918200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:11:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358652517425-67</Id><Title>serious question for hawcreek</Title><Msg>Creek your popularity has waned here on this board. In considering your motivation for posting here i can only think of two reasons for it. 1 A genuine political motive whereby you hope to effect change through your posts. 2 A narcissistic need to prove your ideas in order to validate a self concept of yourself, ( needy personality ). At this point it seems very likely that neither of these objectives will be fulfilled on the MSFT board. Your ideas are stale and constantly ridiculed and your posts have no effect. In other words you are over exposed here and your goals might be much more successfully approached on a different venue. You might for instance start a new identity somewhere with some of your thoughts that were closerer to reality and that got good support here but you now can leave out some of the nonsense that tarnished you're reputation here. You can at times sound intelligent but this elixir is used up here, so branch out and start preaching where people will read your posts and like them. Preferable in a market where the audience is not very smart.</Msg><Username>cfuryurself</Username><Timestamp>1358652517425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:28:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358657939500-68</Id><Topic><Title>earth to evil empire no ones wants your malware jacking the price very much so</Title><Username>shortinfygetrich</Username><Timestamp>1358647299240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:01:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love legal monopolies that are growing BIGGER like M$FT. IDIOT shorts like you are doomed.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1358657939500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 23:58:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>