<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-23"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353654459600-1</Id><Title>Fracking industry keeps eye on Obama - Next month, the EPA is expected to release a draft of its long-awaited report on suspected links between water pollution &amp; fracking</Title><Msg>Fracking industry keeps eye on Obama EPA report could doom its future Comments (6) By Ben Wolfgang The Washington Times Thursday, November 22, 2012 The drilling process that has brought U.S. energy independence within reach faces renewed scrutiny from the Obama administration and an uncertain future in many states. Oil and gas industry leaders remain enthusiastic yet cautious that hydraulic fracturing, commonly known as “fracking,” will be fully embraced by the newly re-elected President Obama and state leaders. Fracking is a controversial but highly successful practice that has unlocked massive amounts of fuel. Endorsements from Mr. Obama and state leaders would make fracking the cornerstone of U.S. energy policy for decades to come. Industry leaders won’t have to wait long for their first clue to what the future holds. Next month, the Environmental Protection Agency is expected to release a draft of its long-awaited report on suspected links between water pollution and fracking, which uses huge amounts of water, combined with sand and chemical mixtures, to crack underground rock and release trapped oil and gas. The completed EPA study won’t be finished until 2014, but the draft will provide an early indication to which energy path the Obama administration will take in the next four years. Many in the energy sector, along with congressional Republicans, fear the report will paint fracking in a negative light and give the White House political cover for cracking down on it in the name of science, something environmentalists have hoped for since Mr. Obama came into office in 2009. But economics may outweigh environmental arguments. Energy leaders now, more than ever, are portraying oil and gas production as a key way of generating tax revenue, spurring job creation and saving the nation from going off the looming “fiscal cliff.” “It’s going to take tax reform, but we can’t tax our way out of this. It’s going to take entitlement reform, but we can’t save our way out of this. And we’re not going to be able to grow out of this. We need another [way] to make this achievable, and we believe that’s energy,” said Karen A. Harbert, president and CEO of the U.S. Chamber of Commerce's Institute for 21st Century Energy. “Every dollar that we generate from energy is a dollar that we don’t have to take out of the Defense Department, the entitlement area, or increase taxes.” Ms. Harbert and others remain optimistic that the White House will recognize that, and they are heartened by what they heard from the president during his campaign. While Republicans and some industry analysts at times have doubted his sincerity, Mr. Obama voiced strong support for expanded oil and gas drilling throughout his race against Republican challenger Mitt Romney. Politically, it has become increasingly difficult to oppose such expansion, especially in light of research that shows drilling will be vital to the effort to free the U.S. from reliance on Middle Eastern oil. The International Energy Agency last week predicted that the U.S. will become the world’s largest oil producer by the next decade, overtaking Saudi Arabia and putting the nation on course to be energy self-sufficient by 2030. The shift is driven by increases in oil extraction and the production of natural gas, which since 2007 has gone up from 20.2 trillion cubic feet per year to more than 24 trillion cubic feet and likely will go even higher. The new energy reality, unimaginable even five years ago and driven primarily by fracking, puts pressure on the Obama administration to fully embrace the extraction method and avoid taking steps that could hamper it, analysts say. “We believe you cannot be for the potential energy development in the U.S. and be against hydraulic fracturing,” said Jack Gerard, president of the American Petroleum Institute. As the White House weighs its options, fights over fracking are heating up in state capitals. North Carolina Gov.-elect Pat McCrory, a Republican, recently said he plans to get his state “in the energy business,” signaling that he will take a different path from that of his predecessor, Gov. Bev Perdue, who vetoed legislation to allow fracking. New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo must decide whether to allow the practice in the Empire State, though he continues to equivocate, and it’s unclear when he will make a decision. Last month, a coalition of environmental groups sued California to stop fracking, claiming that the toll it may take on water supplies has not been fully studied. Meanwhile, states such as Pennsylvania and North Dakota continue to expand drilling, creating tens of thousands of jobs and pumping millions of dollars into local economies. Any federal action to limit fracking would pour cold water on the growth in those states and give fresh ammunition to the vocal environmental opposition in New York, California and elsewhere. Although some new federal rules and oversight are almost inevitable, many analysts say, the administration can’t turn back the tide. “It’s clear that the EPA, the Interior Department, may impose some more regulations on... washingtontimesDOTcom/news/2012/nov/22/fracking-industry-keeps-eye-on-obama/?page=all#pagebreak</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353654459600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 02:07:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353654540037-2</Id><Title>Next month, the Environmental Protection Agency is expected to release a draft of its long-awaited report on suspected links between water pollution and fracking,</Title><Msg>... Next month, the Environmental Protection Agency is expected to release a draft of its long-awaited report on suspected links between water pollution and fracking, ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353654540037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 02:09:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353685579008-3</Id><Title>WOW</Title><Msg>Dow up over 100, Exxon up a whole 34 cents. Wrapping up its fourth straight year of dreadful underperformance. Remains nearly 10 points below spring of 2008 price. Problem is awful management. XTO acquisition will be a textbook case of management idiocy .</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1353685579008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:46:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353692816518-4</Id><Title>Enbridge Plans C$1.8 Bln Link Between Alberta Pipeline Hubs</Title><Msg>Enbridge Plans C$1.8 Bln Link Between Alberta Pipeline Hubs Posted 11/23/2012 8:40 AM by MidnightTrader Enbridge Inc (ENB TO) said on Thursday it will build a C$1.8 billion ($1.8 billion) pipeline to ship 570,000 barrels per day of oil between Alberta's two main storage hubs at Edmonton and Hardisty to accommodate rising output from the oil sands, Reuters reported. It said the company plans a 179-km (111-mile), 36-inch (91-cm) line that will carry crude from Edmonton to Hardisty, the starting point for Enbridge's Alberta Clipper pipeline, which takes 796,000 bpd of oil to Superior, Wisconsin, as well as TransCanada Corp's (TRP TO) 590,000-bpd Keystone pipeline and its planned Keystone XL line. Edmonton is the terminus for a number of pipelines serving oil sands projects in Northern Alberta, where production is expected nearly to double to 3.1 million bpd by 2020. Enbridge said it expects to file for regulatory approval of the project by the end of the year. If approved, construction of the new line could begin in early 2014, with service starting by the middle of 2015. Along with the new pipeline, which will be expandable to 800,000 bpd, Enbridge also plans new storage tanks and other facilities at both hubs. Enbridge shares fell 10 Canadian cents to C$38.70 on the Toronto Stock communityDOTnasdaqDOTcom/News/2012-11/market-chatter-enbridge-plans-c18-bln-link-between-alberta-pipeline-hubs.aspx?storyid=192380</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353692816518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 12:46:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353695137146-5</Id><Title>odds of energy prices rising is 14.5%, past 200 years</Title><Msg>1871-1873, 1916-1920, 1947-1948, 1973-1981, 1999-2012 comprise the 29 years out of 200 that energy price rose in a statistically or economically meaningful way. The rest of the time they were falling relative to inflation, and certainly after accounting for efficiency gains. The odds of losing a game of Russian Roulette (16.67%) are better than a bet on rising energy prices paying off long term. The oil bubble price bubble is just the latest of a string of bubbles the past decade that will collapse. Oil companies are not positioned to profit from falling oil price either. They have divested much of their downstream operations in an attempt to book profit, and meet the costs of investing in high cost oil reserves, and LNG projects, while paying out high dividends and buy back stock. The companies have become upstream oil plays and their share price will collapse utterly when oil does.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353695137146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:25:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353704644857-6</Id><Topic><Title>aka Raul_10spain is Chris O'Donough a cowardly racist</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1353633626596</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 20:20:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So who's the always angry one?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353704644857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 16:04:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353704840144-7</Id><Topic><Title>WOW</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1353685579008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:46:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>S&amp;P closed up 1.3%; XOM up 1.23%; CVX up 1.32%. You see a lot of significance there in one day's abbreviated trading?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353704840144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 16:07:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353706230882-8</Id><Topic><Title>WOW</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1353685579008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 10:46:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I mentioned several days ago to wait until the fiscal cliff negotiations collapse to short stocks again - that applies to Exxon Mobil as well. I would chalk today up to a short covering rally by those who were too impatient, or too stupid to read the ebb and flow of the negotiations.There have been no negotiations worthy of note as Obama has been Asia, so they have not had a chance to collapse. Given the lack of news the media paints a happy face across the headlines. Smart speculators would take that as an opportunity to sell their holdings if they have not already done so.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353706230882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 16:30:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353706539151-9</Id><Topic><Title>aka Raul_10spain is Chris O'Donough a cowardly racist</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1353633626596</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 20:20:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a theatrical trick - you should be able to identify it if you think hard enough on it.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353706539151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 16:35:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353707598651-10</Id><Topic><Title>odds of energy prices rising is 14.5%, past 200 years</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353695137146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One could also divide the history into two segments for a closer analysis: pre and post Ronald Reagan. The result is a 9.5% chance of a rising energy price before Reagan was elected, and a 45.2% chance of a rising energy price in the years after he and his ilk were elected. The possible reasons for the 5 fold increase in the chance of an energy price rise in the years after Reagan elected are many. Mainly they come down to a deterioration of government investments in education and energy technologies, and the diversion of university curriculum toward fields such as business, accounting, finance, law, physical education, political science, etc, at the expense of mathematics, physics, chemistry, and engineering. Infrastructure has not been a priority of small government neo-cons either and so while other countries make improvements to improve their efficiency, the U.S. lags behind. Lower tax rates after 1980 also encouraged more speculation of all sorts and the trillions devoted to that pursuit find their way into commodities, thus allowing commodity prices to be bid up. Eventually the speculators will get blown out at a loss when the high energy price causes the economy to crash, but that takes time. In any event, even with these factors in play, the chance of winning a bet on energy prices rising since 1980 is still worse than a coin toss. The neo-cons have been defeated now too. The big government approach, which in the past promised much faster technological progress, at least in the areas that matter most to the economy, like energy, is now ascendant - that bodes poorly for energy price speculators long term. Higher taxes paid by speculators reduces their ranks and that is helpful too...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353707598651</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 16:53:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353708576740-11</Id><Topic><Title>odds of energy prices rising is 14.5%, past 200 years</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353695137146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 13:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To be complete one should not that the chance of energy prices rising has increased to 45.2% since the election of Ronald Reagan, which is 5 times higher than it was in the 170 years before his election. That is still worse than a coin toss. There reasons for increasing tendency of energy prices to rise since Reagan are fairly simply. Lower tax rates beget more speculators and speculators run up the prices of all assets - and they've made commodities an asset where it never was before. There has also been a diversion of educational resources toward finance, business, law, political science, physical education, and fields and away from the science which is natural outcome of the government taking its finger partly off the scale, a finger that had been on the science end to support Cold War programs... A slower pace of technological progress in the hard sciences tends to drive up energy prices all else equal, as it reduces the pace of supply growth and efficiency on the demand side. The neo-cons have lost now so you can expect the government's finger to go back on the scale...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353708576740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 17:09:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353718458075-12</Id><Title>What's at stake in Doha climate talks</Title><Msg>What's at stake in Doha climate talks Negotiators look beyond the Kyoto Protocol and focus on 2020. Jeff Tollefson 23 November 2012 PHOTO Countries are split on whether any future agreement on reducing greenhouse gas emission should be legally binding or voluntary. L. Stone/Corbis Diplomats from around the world will gather for the United Nations (UN) climate talks next week in Doha, Qatar, where negotiators hope to agree a second phase of the Kyoto Protocol and lay the groundwork for a new global treaty that will take force by 2020. Nature takes a look at what is expected from the 18th annual Conference of the Parties (COP 18), which runs from 26 November to 7 December. What is happening with the Kyoto Protocol? At last year’s meeting in Durban, South Africa, the big showdown was over the future of Kyoto, and the talks very nearly imploded. Most industrialized countries were ready to move beyond the protocol and negotiate a new treaty altogether once the current commitment period comes to a close at the end of the year. But in the end, a block of developing countries allied itself with Europe and successfully fought for a second round of commitments. This means that parties to the protocol must now register their commitments — political pledges at the moment — within a legally binding agreement. The goal for COP 18 is to complete that process and define the terms of the second commitment period, 'Kyoto II', which could last between five and eight years. Who will be involved in Kyoto II? The United States never ratified the Kyoto Protocol and has made it clear that it has no interest in going down that track now. Japan, Russia and Canada have all ducked out of a second round, but the ground is still shifting. Earlier this month New Zealand dropped out, and Australia announced that it would take part. As for the developing countries, where virtually all of the growth in emissions is taking place, the Kyoto framework requires nothing in the way of emissions reductions from them. As a result, the legal obligations under Kyoto II would apply to a small share of the global emissions — less than 15% of the total, according to UN officials. How does Kyoto II relate to the new treaty that is being negotiated? For now, Kyoto II will serve as little more than an interim measure, but many developing countries would like to make it the basis of the future treaty. But the main focus of the talks is what comes next. The UN climate negotiators have committed to signing a new treaty by 2015, to take effect by 2020 — or possibly earlier if countries pushing for more ambitious action, such as the Maldives, get their way. What will this agreement look like? It’s too early to say. Climate negotiators began to break down the dichotomy between developed and developing countries at the summit in Copenhagen, Denmark, in 2009. Not only did most countries step forward with pledges, but emerging giants such as China and Brazil signed a controversial agreement — dubbed the Copenhagen Accord — with the United States and other major industrialized countries that sought to assemble climate pledges under an entirely new framework. Affirmed a year later in Cancun, Mexico, this framework agreement incorporates signatories' climate commitments, but it is not legally binding. The legal force of the coming treaty is a key question. What does 'legally binding' mean? There are certain penalties for noncompliance with the Kyoto Protocol, including formal judgements and fines, but they are targeted at countries that want to participate. But there are few repercussions if a country drops out altogether — as Canada did last year. So public pressure will always be crucial for ensuring that countries do what they say they are going to do. The Durban talks very nearly foundered on these questions last year. In the end, negotiators abandoned the words “legally binding” in favour of a vague commitment to negotiate “a protocol, another legal instrument or an agreed outcome with legal force”. This leaves the door wide open. So far, the question has often been framed as a choice between a legally binding Kyoto-style framework and a voluntary Copenhagen-style framework, but many wonder whether there could be something in between. Negotiators in Doha will be exploring these questions as they create a road map to 2015. What else is on the COP 18 agenda? Negotiators will also seek to push forward work on climate adaptation and deforestation and will be wrangling over financial commitments. Developed countries seem to be largely on track to meet their Copenhagen commitments to fast-track US$30 billion in climate aid from 2010–12, according to the Washington-based World Resources Institute, but assessments vary. It is also unclear how they will ramp up funding to the committed $100 billion annually by 2020. What about the goal of limiting global warming to 2 ºC? There is widespread acknowledgement that the world is on a path to miss that target. A recent assessment conducted on behalf of the World Bank suggests that the world is currently on track for 4 degrees of warming, with potentially disastrous consequences. This week the United Nations Environment Programme issued its annual Emissions Gap report and found that emissions are set to rise to 58 gigatonnes of carbon dioxide equivalent by 2020 under a "business-as-usual" scenario, which is roughly 14 gigatonnes higher than they need to be in order to maintain a "likely" chance of staying below 2 degrees of warming. Current policies will help reduce the size of the gap, but UNEP nonetheless estimates that these efforts will fall short by 8-13 gigatonnes in 2020. In Doha, all eyes will be on the world’s largest greenhouse-gas emitters — the United States and China — following the re-election of President Barack Obama and the appointment of Xi Jinping as the new leader of China's Communist Party. But climate policies are not expected to change substantially in either country. More broadly, there is little evidence that the global political ambitionfor aggressive action combating climate change is going to increase any time soon. natureDOTcom/news/what-s-at-stake-in-doha-climate-talks-1.11844</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353718458075</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 19:54:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>