<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344054673000-1</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. solar plan creates energy zones, excludes sensitive lands</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343870954000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 21:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>High energy zone: http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-hg5vw-fjW8o/T_q3o4zki-I/AAAAAAAAAiY/DU0CPP-sENw/s1600/CSP+-+Power+Tower.jpg</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1344054673000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 00:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344080377000-2</Id><Title>Strong Up-Move After Weak Opening, XOM</Title><Msg>So why are we seeing maybe such a big turn for XOM? Volume was stunning today pouring in at 13983205. Focus on XOM as maybe a bigger theme to the industry. How come? XOM is moving forward as they showed up a lot of capital and cleaned up their act for the year. If you look at this market in general, people look at it as a cyclical market but its more of a volatile growth story. Its been that way historically where from 2000 the stock market hasn't gone anywhere. My opinion is to capture the gains on XOM for the short term and keep your ears to the floor when the quarterly report is published. Full report on XOM can be found here: http://bullexchange.info</Msg><Username>vegaaguilar496</Username><Timestamp>1344080377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 07:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344087770000-3</Id><Title>USDA announces more biofuel payments across US</Title><Msg>USDA announces more biofuel payments across US Aug. 2, 2012 Comments 0 USDA announced payments for 125 advanced biofuel producers across the country to support the production and expansion of advanced biofuels from a wide variety of non-food sources, including waste products. "Advanced biofuels are a key component of President Obama's 'all-of-the-above' energy strategy to reduce the Nation's reliance on foreign oil and take control of America's energy future," said Vilsack. "These payments represent help spur an alternative fuels industry using renewable feedstocks grown in America, broadening the range of feedstock options available to biofuels producers, helping to create an economy built to last." The funding is being provided through USDA's Bioenergy Program for Advanced Biofuels, which was established in the 2008 Farm Bill. Under this program, payments are made to eligible producers based on the amount of biofuels a recipient produces from renewable biomass, other than corn kernel starch. Examples of eligible feedstocks include but are not limited to: crop residue; animal, food and yard waste material; vegetable oil; and animal fat. Through this and other programs, USDA is working to support the research, investment and infrastructure necessary to build a biofuels industry that creates jobs and broadens the range of feedstocks used to produce renewable fuel. For example, in Somerset, Ky., Somerset Hardwood Flooring will receive a $7,040 payment for producing wood pellets from residual sawdust from its hardwood flooring manufacturing process. The company produces about 40 tons of wood pellets annually. FPE Renewables, LLC, based in Lyden, Wash., generates nearly two million kilowatt hours of electricity annually. The firm will receive a payment of $9,612 for producing biogas primarily from dairy waste, which is converted to electricity. In West Point, Va., Virginia Biodiesel Refinery, LLC, will receive a payment of $7,900 for making biodiesel from recycled cooking oil and soybean oil. Increased biofuel production plays a relatively minor role in retail food price changes because the growing diversity of feedstock used to produce biodiesel allows for flexibility and helps relieve market pressures. Biodiesel is made from an increasingly diverse mix of non-food feedstocks, including recycled cooking oil, agricultural oils and animal fats, allowing most biodiesel producers to select from a choice of feedstocks if prices rise or supplies are limited. Therefore, the industry's impact in commodity markets is significantly reduced. As the market expands for home-grown renewable energy, American farmers and producers will create even more good-paying jobs that can't be exported. The biofuels industry in the U.S. currently employs about 400,000 people and is expected to employ around a million people in the U.S. by 2022. USDA today is announcing $19.4 million in payments to 125 local producers and business-owners. Below is a complete list of the 111 producers (by state) receiving payments of more than $500 for production of advanced biofuels. (Producers receiving payments in the amount of $500 or less are not included in the list.) http://westernfarmpress.com/government/usda-announces-more-biofuel-payments-across-us</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344087770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344089202000-4</Id><Title>Ethanol production nationally is at a two-year low</Title><Msg>Ethanol production nationally is at a two-year low http://www.talkstock.com/tm.asp?m=424502&amp;mpage=1&#424503;</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344089202000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344090812000-5</Id><Title>XOM FORM 10-Q FOR THE QUARTERLY PERIOD ENDED JUNE 30, 2012</Title><Msg>EXXON MOBIL CORPORATION FORM 10-Q FOR THE QUARTERLY PERIOD ENDED JUNE 30, 2012 http://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/34088/000003408812000036/xom10q2q12.htm XOM Chart http://bigcharts.marketwatch.com/advchart/frames/frames.asp?show=&amp;insttype=Stock&amp;symb=xom&amp;time=6&amp;startdate=1%2F4%2F1999&amp;enddate=1%2F8%2F2012&amp;freq=1&amp;compidx=aaaaa%3A0&amp;comptemptext=&amp;comp=&amp;ma=4&amp;maval=9+15+50&amp;uf=7168&amp;lf=1&amp;lf2=4&amp;lf3=2&amp;type=4&amp;style=320&amp;size=3&amp;timeFrameToggle=false&amp;compareToToggle=false&amp;indicatorsToggle=false&amp;chartStyleToggle=false&amp;state=11&amp;x=0&amp;y=0 Analyst Estimates http://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/xom/analystestimates</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344090812000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344102005000-6</Id><Title>Sunrise Powerlink will eventually carry more than 1,000 MW of clean energy</Title><Msg>Brown Dedicates New Power Transmission Line 4 Comments July 31, 2012 06:00 am Mark Truppner, MML Reporter ALPINE - Governor Jerry Brown dedicated the Sunrise Powerlink transmission line in San Diego County, which will deliver millions of kilowatt hours of renewable energy, strengthen grid reliability during hot summer months and help California meet its renewable energy goals. Brown was Tuesday's KVML "Newsmaker of the Day". "The Sunrise Powerlink is an extraordinarily sophisticated technology that will bring solar and wind energy from the Imperial Valley to San Diego," said Brown. "Most immediately, it will help keep the lights on during this year's hot summer with the San Onofre Nuclear Power Plant offline." The 117-mile, Sunrise Powerlink will eventually carry more than 1,000 megawatts of clean energy from solar and wind farms in the Imperial Valley to San Diego - enough to power over 650,000 homes. The transmission project - the first major new lines to connect to San Diego in over 25 years - will enable the local utility, San Diego Gas &amp; Electric, to meet Governor Brown's 33-percent renewables delivery goal by 2020. In April 2011, the Governor signed legislation requiring that one-third of the state's electricity come from renewable sources by 2020, the highest renewable energy goal in the U.S. The Sunrise Powerlink consists of more than 110 miles of overhead 500kV and 230kV transmission towers and transmission lines, six miles of underground 230kV cables and a 40-acre, 500kV transmission substation. The California Public Utilities Commission, the U.S. Bureau of Land Management and the U.S. Forest Service all reviewed and approved the Sunrise Powerlink project before construction started. Following an extensive environmental review and permitting process, the project broke ground in December 2010. On June 17, 2012 the transmission line was fully energized and control was officially transferred to the California Independent System Operator (Cal-ISO). Construction of the Sunrise Powerlink adhered to some of the most rigorous environmental and cultural mitigation measures ever placed on a construction project of this type. The measures include enacting one of the largest natural land preservation efforts in the region's history; identifying Native American cultural sites and preserving artifacts; creating no-fly zones around golden eagle nesting sites; establishing a 13-mile construction-free zone in Bighorn sheep habitat during lambing season; and deploying 400 environmental monitors to worksites. The ceremony was held at the Suncrest Substation in Alpine, California. Governor Brown was joined by state, federal, local and business leaders for the dedication. http://www.mymotherlode.com/news/local/1726110/Brown-Dedicates-New-Power-Transmission-Line.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344102005000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344120338000-7</Id><Title>Economic conditions pointing downward</Title><Msg>So much for that jobs report. Times are tough like no other. You would think the corruptions would stop, but it continues, continues until it implodes. It is a self inflicting virus that will devour inside out. Some want to blame Republicans or Democrats. This is unrealistic since both mismanaged the country and now we are in the mist of greater slowdown. If it has changed than why do we see the same repeat offenders like Knight Capital, HBSC, and MF Global. These are just a few. Under S&amp;L crisis, the Keating 5 is where so much of this corruption did start and we continue to make it worse. Obama has no idea how to fix it he since he is a school boy that is someone who does not even have an idea to run lemonade stand. Since he pumped so much money in his pet program like Solyndra and it udderly failed in front of eyes like a puff of smoke. Yep that fast. But as I step back the Republican are to blame as well. Shame on McCain and his S&amp;L cover. So as the politicians are pointing fingers most of the sheep will follow their sect over the cliff. But this is what politicians want you the sheep to part of the class warfare.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1344120338000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344121448000-8</Id><Title>Strategy for China. What strategy?</Title><Msg>I see nothing happening to IRan or a potential war happening soon. What I do see is a stalemate. The oil prices will rise due to the disruption of the UN embargo and the maybe a closure of the strait of Hormuz. Obama is the perfect candidate since he will do nothing and the price of oil will go to the stratosphere. So I would be a heavy investor in Oil or Oil Services at this point until it implodes. We are long way from the price pressures to the consumer. On the other side of the coin China will have to live with higher manufacturing(energy) cost and food. This could hurt China for the long run and could bring jobs back to America.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1344121448000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344122631000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Sunrise Powerlink will eventually carry more than 1,000 MW of clean energy</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344102005000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:40:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, they built some powerlines!!! BFD.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1344122631000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344130438000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Strategy for China. What strategy?</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1344121448000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chinese energy costs are nearly 13% of their GDP, split about half on oil products and half on electricity. By point of comparison, the USA has not been able to afford even 10% of GDP going to energy in the past, and this with vastly larger stores of wealth to support the outlay. Much of Chinese GDP is totally fabricated, too, reflecting nothing more than the expense of road building and other infrastructure, not real income. China's road building in its rural areas, the source of much of its GDP, has severely weakened its economy by diverting capital to low payoff or negative payoff uses. The debt run up to pay for the infrastructure is real enough, but the income from it far less so. The USA did the same thing China is doing now in the 1880s when the Railroads embarked on a race to cover the western United States with new routes. The routes did not have enough traffic to cover the capital cost and led to the bankruptcy of most railroads in the United States. The result was the depression of the 1890s...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1344130438000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 21:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344132003000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Economic conditions pointing downward</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1344120338000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since the Europeans wrapped up their first Kyoto emissions trading scheme in 2007 and embarked on their next one, their stock markets have lost nearly 45% of its value and some even more. The result of the scheme was to punish industrial which uses large amounts of energy, effectively capping their GDP. The banking system does not handle a situation of no GDP growth, or more importantly the impossibility of GDP growth, very well. So the result was the collapse observed. It can get much worse and will. The USA's economy got sucked into the vortex of the European economic crash, a situation that was worsened by the oil price price spike, itself caused by the overheated Chinese economy, in turn caused by the wholesale flight of industrial production from Europe to China. There is a limit to how much China can grow by sucking industrial output out of Europe, and building up domestic infrastructure.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1344132003000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:00:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>