<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-23"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348392809099-1</Id><Title>Mitt</Title><Msg>Mitt has made an art of the brain-fart.</Msg><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1348392809099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 05:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348393571297-2</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt</Title><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1348392809099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 05:33:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GFY you commie POS #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348393571297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 05:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348393755709-3</Id><Topic><Title>Please wake UP AMERICA</Title><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348364236414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 21:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you know why you cant be Pres. if your not a citizen. Look at the mess nobumba and dumbo voters got us in. Nobumba should be jailed and tried for treason.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348393755709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 05:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348393886378-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Presidential Race is Over</Title><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348177091783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:38:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MAxidopey better hope so, if not his checks will stop and my big fat boot will kick his commie #$%$ out of here.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348393886378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 05:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348401520359-5</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt</Title><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1348392809099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 05:33:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its going so bad that the Republican Party will rid Romney of Stuart Stevens. Appointing himself as speechwriter, strategist, ad producer, etc has made the campaign incredibly inept.</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1348401520359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 07:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348406551355-6</Id><Title>DuPont set to move ahead with cellulosic ethanol refinery</Title><Msg>DuPont set to move ahead with refinery 5:08 PM, Sep 22, 2012 1 Comments Written by Cori Anne Natoli The News Journal Zeroing in on a megatrend to reduce dependance on fossil fuels, the DuPont Co. soon will embark on a $200 million undertaking to bring a new technology to market by building a 28 million-gallon-a-year cellulosic ethanol refinery. The DuPont Cellulosic Ethanol Nevada, Iowa site will use about 360 tons of locally bought biomass each year. For those having doubts whether the technology – criticized by some – is coming, DuPont says it’s imminent. “I think it’s important to stress that this is real and I’m sure people have doubts about cellulosic ethanol but it is real and it is coming,” said Jan Koninckx, global business director for DuPont Biofuels. “We are developing technology that enables the biofuels industry to grow.” The firm will demonstrate the technology at its coming Nevada site by licensing it to suppliers and in some instances, partnering with them. “It’s not our objective to be the biggest biofuel producer in the world, but instead we want to enable many players in this industry to participate,” Koninckx said. “We think this is a technology that has nothing but benefits in greenhouse gas reduction and the creation of jobs with these plants.” The 210-year-old Wilmington-based firm is rooted in developing and applying market-based science to address global megatrends and cellulosic ethanol fits squarely into that mission, Koninckx said of the technology, 10 years in the making. When compared to gasoline, cellulosic ethanol, made from corn stover, reduces greenhouse gases by more than 60 to 100 percent, according to DuPont, which says its commercial scale biorefinery in Iowa will be one of the first such commercial scale facilities worldwide. DuPont is naturally supportive of federal mandates for biofuel production, namely the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency’s Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS) mandate, which has come under fire amidst a devastating drought that has deteriorated crops and helped to spiked corn prices. “We understand the impact of the drought very well and we feel their (farmers) pain and we feel empathy for them,” Koninckx said. “I understand that situation. … The RFS is a visionary piece of legislation in that they described a specific vision for the future.” Prior to the federal mandate, Brazil was the leader in biofuels, he said. Waiving federal mandates for biofuel production would send a signal to investors and Wall Street that supportive legislation is no longer solid, not to mention large companies such as DuPont have spent hundreds of millions in developing next generation fuels. Chicken processors such as Mountaire Farms and Perdue, and legislators have been petitioning the EPA to waive the federal requirement in the face of an unforgiving drought and already pinched economy. Waiving the requirement could create a drop in corn prices, used for poultry and other livestock feed, and ease financial pressures. A 30-day public comment period will end Oct. 11, on the controversial RFS mandate. The EPA then has 90 days to make a decision. delawareonline</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348406551355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348410213240-7</Id><Title>Northern Gateway Pipeline hearings continue in Edmonton - for the first time backers of the project were given the chance to cross examine those opposing it</Title><Msg>Northern Gateway Pipeline hearings continue in Edmonton Global News : Saturday, September 22, 2012 4:51 PM Hearings dealing with the Northern Gateway Pipeline continued in Edmonton, Saturday, and for the first time backers of the project were given the chance to cross examine those opposing it. The pipeline would run nearly 1,200 kilometres from Bruderheim to Kitimat, on the BC coast. The project would allow bitumen to be sold to Asian markets. Over the past few weeks, groups opposed to the pipeline have been voicing their concerns to an independent joint review panel. Among them, the Alberta Federation of Labour, which contends the project would move jobs out of the province. "Our concern is that once it's built, it will become a bitumen superhighway, taking not only raw bitumen from the oil sands out of the province to places like China and the United States, but along with that bitumen we're afraid that it's also going to transport literally tens of thousands of jobs in upgrading and refining," said Gil McGowan, President of the Alberta Federation of Labour. "The project doesn't preclude refining. We will be able to move synthetic or diluted bitumen, or more conventional oil, so there's nothing to prevent refining from happening. Certainly the very value is in accessing large markets and if refining proves profitable or economic at some point, we can certainly move those products as well," explained John Carruthers, President of Enbridge Northern Gateway Pipelines. The independent panel is set to make its decision on whether the pipeline should go ahead by December 2013. While the panel's input will carry weight, the final say goes to the Federal Cabinet. It's decision is expected in the summer of 2014. globaltvedmonton</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348410213240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:23:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348419620015-8</Id><Topic><Title>Please wake UP AMERICA</Title><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348364236414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 21:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Women of America: You are being spoon-fed the pablum of your demise by a pathological liar.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1348419620015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:00:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348424583513-9</Id><Title>Romney–Obama Energy Policy Differences Clear as Day</Title><Msg>Romney–Obama Energy Policy Differences Clear as Day September 23, 2012 By Zachary Shahan 7 Comments There’s one clear reason why we cover politics the way we do here on CleanTechnica — one side is dead-set on promoting dirty energy while it stifles clean energy. Here’s an extended excerpt from a good, recent post on sister site The Inspired Economist on this matter: One surefire way to understand policy direction is to look at the people those candidates appoint to offices that are not just talking heads, but actual “rubber hits the road” decision makers. Nowhere is this distinction more clear than in the energy sector. President Obama’s Energy Secretary is Dr. Steven Chu. Chu is a Nobel Prize winning physicist, headed the Lawrence Berkeley Lab, and has taught physics at Stanford. One of his main accomplishments in his four years as Energy Secretary include creating a requirement that new appliances decrease or eliminate the amount of vampire power they use (energy used while plugged in but not turned on–about 15% of the total energy used, and a total waste). Chu has also written and directed policy aimed at improving the nation’s electricity grid, something that most scholars believe can help change the landscape for allowing more renewables, and better decisions by energy users to decrease their consumption–and their bills. He has also actively promoted weather stripping, caulking and other energy efficiency measures, and pushed for tax incentives for these programs. (Editor’s note: he’s also implemented some great programs to bring down solar and wind power costs.) In contrast, Republican Candidate Mitt Romney’s energy advisor to this point is Harold Hamm, CEO of an oil services company, who lobbied aggressively in front of congress to maintain the $4.1 billion in subsidies that taxpayers give to oil companies every year. With both candidates saying that the election couldn’t be a clearer choice for the direction of the country, I’d have to say, I agree entirely. When it comes to energy policy, we have an extremely clear choice. Clean Technica</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348424583513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348432737869-10</Id><Topic><Title>Romney–Obama Energy Policy Differences Clear as Day</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348424583513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:23:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROTFLOL! Here,I'll give it to you in simpler language. BUILD THE FRICKIN' PIPLINE NUMBNUTS.THAT'S what creates jobs,not that Solyndra #$%$.And what could POSSIBLY be his excuse for draggin' aaz on Nat Gas. Puleeeezzeee.This guy had four years to create real energy jobs while FOOD STAMP and DISABILITY clams went UP by FIFTY PERCENT.You think people suddenly became disabled?? They couldn't find jobs! Disability was the last resort that keeps them off the street.It's nauseating.Obama couldn't grow a chia pet,let alone a national economy.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348432737869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 16:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348433088120-11</Id><Topic><Title>Please wake UP AMERICA</Title><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348364236414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 21:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bibi AND The Kurds.........a nation of 35 million intensely pro-US and pro Israel MUSLIMS in the heart of the middle east.What you never heard of 'em? LOL. Of course not,you ain't interested.Obama hasn't done much for 'em.But Romney = Candi Rice = Help for the Kurds and their 200,000 soldiers - The Pesh Merga.Their favorite pastime? Kickin' the stuffing out of the Iranians.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348433088120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 16:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348435101956-12</Id><Title>Denmark gets first power from Anholt wind park - aims to cover half its power needs with wind turbines by 2020</Title><Msg>Denmark gets first power from Anholt wind park Fri Sep 21, 2012 11:52am GMT COPENHAGEN, Sept 21 (Reuters) - Danish utility DONG Energy has brought the first turbine onstream at Anholt, set to be the country's biggest offshore wind park with a total capacity of 400 megawatts. The Anholt development will deliver enough power for 400,000 households, or 4 percent of Denmark's power consumption, when it is completed in a year's time, state-controlled DONG Energy said on Friday. Denmark, already the world leader in wind energy with around a quarter of its electricity from wind farms, aims to cover half its power needs with wind turbines by 2020. It also aims to get 30 percent of overall energy consumption from renewables by 2020, and Anholt will make a significant contribution to those goals, DONG Energy said. The wind farm, located off the island of Anholt in the Kattegat between Denmark and Sweden, will have 111 Siemens turbines with a capacity of 3.6 MW each. While DONG Energy has not disclosed the cost of the project, estimates are around 10 billion Danish crowns ($1.74 billion). DONG Energy, the oil, gas and electricity producer, owns 50 percent and is the operator of the Anholt development, while pension insurance groups PensionDenmark and PKA own 30 percent and 20 percent respectively. The pension providers bought their stakes in March 2011, marking a new step in DONG Energy's efforts to bring new kinds of investors into wind power projects and diversify its own risk as wind farm developer and owner. ($1 = 5.7558 Danish crowns) reuters</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348435101956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348436312716-13</Id><Title>Idaho Power WIND Energy Agreement Must Be Honored Regardless Of Circumstance, Says Regulator - FERC's decision was a major victory 4 Idaho's WIND industry</Title><Msg>Idaho Power Wind Energy Agreement Must Be Honored Regardless Of Circumstance, Says Regulator AP | By REBECCA BOONE Posted: 09/20/2012 6:19 pm EDT BOISE, Idaho (AP) — Idaho Power's long-term purchase agreement with wind farms requires the utility to buy electricity from the farms even when demand for power is low, the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission said Thursday. Idaho Power officials have contended that the Public Utilities Regulatory Policies Act, or PURPA, should allow the company to halt contractually required electricity purchases during periods of light load, such as at night in the spring and fall. The utility company said the requirement to buy from wind farms even during times of low demand forces it to back down other energy generators like coal-fired plants, and bringing the other systems back up when demand increases costs the utility more. Those costs are passed on to consumers, the company said. But wind developers maintain that PURPA only allows utilities to limit wind farms' output during operational emergencies, and that Idaho Power is trying to sway public opinion by unfairly basing its cost arguments on historically low natural gas prices. Longer-term pricing models are the proper comparison, the wind farms argue. Idaho Power spokesman Brad Bowlin said the company was examining FERC's order and evaluating options. Steve Eisenberg, the managing director of RP Wind ID LLC, the managing partner of Idaho Wind Partners 1, said the wind farms were pleased with the decision. "We applaud FERC's decision today, which upholds the sanctity of our qualified facility power purchase agreements with Idaho Power," Eisenberg said. Idaho Power's curtailment plan first went to the state regulatory agency, the Idaho Public Utilities Commission, for review. Commission staffers testified that limiting wind power during times of light load is allowable under commission rules and under precedent-setting decisions in similar cases. But wind farms, fearing that they'd get an unfavorable decision from the state regulator, appealed to the federal commission. State regulators argued to FERC officers that the matter simply wasn't ripe for federal review because the state commission hadn't yet ruled. Idaho Wind Partners 1, which has 11 subsidiary project companies in Idaho, told the federal commission that the Idaho Power plan would violate PURPA and expose the wind farms to immediate financial harm. Each of the farms has a 20-year agreement with Idaho Power that has already been approved by state regulators. The federal regulatory commission found that PURPA doesn't allow a utility company to unilaterally curtail electricity purchases during times of light load. Moreover, the commission emphasized, those purchases are part of long-term power purchase agreements, and when those agreements are created they reflect the costs that each party anticipates over the life of the contract in a variety of circumstances, including light loads. In other words, Idaho Power likely considered those costs — or at least should have — when it entered the agreements with the wind farms in the first place. Peter Richardson, a renewable energy attorney in Boise, said FERC's decision was a major victory for Idaho's wind industry. Also on HuffPost: Wind Turbines Around The World IMAGE 1 of 27 [fullscreen] huffingtonpost</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348436312716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348441384697-14</Id><Title>Obama Campaign In Trouble</Title><Msg>There has been nothing but bad news for the Romney campaign for several weeks.When his troubles began,soon after the Dem convention Obama took a clear lead.By now,he should have opened up a sizeable lead over Romney.But it hasn't happened.Instead,despite the volume of negative news for Romney the race has actually tightened. As of Sept. 23rd RASMUSSEN has them tied nationally.In the 11 swing states Romney trails Obama by only 1 pt - 46-45 with 6% undecided. Obama is gonna have to pull a magic trick in every one of those debates.Romney will have loads of ammo to throw at Obama.Dems who think this Presidents record is anything less than totally vulnerable to criticism are in for a nasty surprise.Romney will offer a full menu of ideas.He'll use the debates to deal with the issue of "where's the beef?".His real job is to deflect Obama's character attacks,which will be delivered as smooth as silk.For once in his life Romney is going to have to be deft.He will be. The pressure is on Obama.The country is not happy and his re-election hinges on one thing - his smooth personality.If he shows any cracks during the debates he's a goner.Romney can afford minor mistakes.The voters want an alternative.Provided has can present a platform of ideas they can understand he can weather a few stumbles and still win.And if his people can conjure one or two good zingers they could put Obama on the ropes before the end of the debates.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348441384697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348441704181-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney–Obama Energy Policy Differences Clear as Day</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348424583513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:23:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Add to that: The federal government has empounded millions of acres of oil rich land and, removed the management of that land from the public trust. The environmental wackos (representing a paultry 2-3% of voters) have screamed loud enough to bring down our economy, while their own "footprint" is more destructive than those who would produce energy independence responsibly. How are we doing America? Better yet, WHAT are we doing?</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1348441704181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:08:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348443041968-16</Id><Title>Super Typhoon 18W Jelawat Warning &amp; Tropical Storms MIRIAM &amp; NADINE</Title><Msg>Super Typhoon 18W Jelawat Warning &amp; Tropical Storms MIRIAM &amp; NADINE Multiple URLs available at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348443041968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348445756645-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Campaign In Trouble</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348441384697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"[Obama] should have opened up a sizeable lead over Romney. But it hasn't happened." Not true. You lie. Your desperation is very welcomed.</Msg><Username>casey_iii</Username><Timestamp>1348445756645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348446176637-18</Id><Title>Latest anti-drilling claims are so much laughing gas : NY Daily News</Title><Msg>In their desperation to block Gov. Cuomo from giving the okay for fracking in New York, die-hard opponents of the natural gas drilling technology are floating laugh-out-loud-funny health and environmental threats. Most hilariously, the enviro-activists have demanded that state officials explore an alleged link between fracking and — we kid you not — syphilis. They argue that a drilling boom would draw an influx of male workers from other states who would engage in activities of a kind that would spread sexually transmitted diseases. They also contend that a boom would trigger a housing crunch, adding to homelessness and the health ailments that go along with it. And that increased truck traffic would not only lead to more road fatalities, but would also — again, no kidding — discourage people from getting the outdoor exercise they need to stay fit. This is absurd. If New York starts saying no to entire industries on the grounds they might trigger population changes, rising home prices and truck traffic, it might as well turn out the lights. Have the people pushing these theories considered the health effects of unemployment and poverty — which are all too common in the parts of New York targeted for drilling? Have they forgotten the public health upsides of harvesting natural gas — which burns far more cleanly than other fossil fuels? What fracking opponents really want is not a study of imagined risks, but many more months of wheel-spinning in Albany — and additional fodder for litigation. Hydraulic fracturing, or hydrofracking, involves pumping millions of gallons of chemical-laced water deep into the earth at high pressure to release trapped natural gas. For four years, the state Department of Environmental Conservation has analyzed the extent of true health concerns, such as the potential for air and water pollution. As a result, the DEC has proposed what everyone acknowledges are some of the tightest regulations in the nation — including an absolute ban on drilling in the entire region surrounding New York City’s reservoirs. The opponents tried to push DEC Commissioner Joseph Martens into hiring a public health consultant to check out the danger of venereal diseases and all the rest. Smartly, he went only so far as to ask Health Commissioner Nirav Shah to review whether DEC has appropriately considered health concerns. If faux seriousness is what it takes to head off lawsuits, so be it. Stifling laughter is a small price to pay for progress toward fracking approval.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348446176637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348446292663-19</Id><Title>The Middle East is in flames, but 'Islam is a religion of peace'?</Title><Msg>CHARLOTTE, September 22, 2012 ― Have you ever wondered why Muslims are compelled to declare that Islam is a “religion of peace” following a terrorist attack or rampant violence by enraged believers? No other religion in the world is ever forced to defend itself in such a manner. Only Islam. That is because every other religion on the planet is inherently “peaceful.” Islam is not. Surely the events of recent weeks throughout Egypt, Libya, Pakistan and other Middle Eastern countries should be some indication to even the most ambivalent observer that such extreme reactions are indicative of the ferocity that festers within Islam. This is not new. Many Americans believe that such responses are the consequence of hatred of the West. The truth is that the current problems are merely the latest examples of fourteen hundred years of conflict that began in the 7th century. Author and filmmaker Gregory M. Davis sums it up in two paragraphs: “The spectacular acts of Islamic terrorism in the late twentieth and early twenty-first centuries are only recent manifestations of a global war of conquest that Islam has been waging since the days of Muhammad. “Over the course of its fourteen-hundred year history on three continents, Islam has demonstrated that it is essentially and enduringly violent. This is the simple, glaring truth that stares the world in the face today, but which few seem willing to contemplate. However difficult to accept, the fact is that we are in a global religious conflict with an adversary who intends to destroy or conquer us and who has been hard at work at both for fourteen centuries.” Whenever and wherever Islamic violence occurs, Muslim apologists come out of the woodwork to decry its savagery by stating that the Koran explicitly denounces the killing of innocent people and that all human life is valuable. As evidence for their claim they cite Sura 5:32 of the Koran, which says, “whoever killed a human being…shall be regarded as having killed all mankind; and that whoever saved a human life shall be regarded as having saved all mankind.” Peaceful, right? Ahhh, but here’s the catch. Verse 5:32 in the above form is taken out of context. Here is the full sura as written in the Koran, “That was why We laid down for the Israelites that whoever killed a human being, except as punishment for murder or other villainy in the land, shall be regarded as having killed all mankind; and that whoever saved a human life shall be regarded as having saved all mankind.” The chapter continues immediately with the following, “Our apostles brought them veritable proofs: yet many among them, even after that, did prodigious evil in the land.” “Those that make war against God and His apostle and spread disorder in the land shall be slain or crucified or have their hands and feet cut off on alternate sides, or be banished from the land. They shall be held up to shame in this world and sternly punished in the hereafter….” As Davis points out in a few terse words, “Engaging in violence against non-Muslims is not a fringe idea but a central tenet of Islam.” Islamic actions in recent days and the above quotes from the Koran bear that out. The media continually questions how an inane video by an obscure filmmaker on YouTube could result in the overreaction and violence that has erupted in the Middle East. First, it should be understood from the outset that most of the protestors who have taken to the streets have not even seen the video in question. They are responding primarily on hearsay, which, for them, is enough. Beyond that, we are not dealing with a contemporary problem, but one that has been on-going for centuries and which will continue so long as Muslims cling to the basic principles that were taught by Muhammad. As Davis explains, “The Prophet especially disliked the many poets who ridiculed his new religion and his claim to prophethood – a theme that recurs today in the violent reactions of Muslims to any perceived mockery of Islam.” While the YouTube film is more than mere “perceived mockery,” the point is that we are dealing with fourteen centuries of upheaval. What we need to understand is that the so-called “moderate Muslims” which make up a high percentage of the Islamic faith, are not relevant to the argument any more than non-Nazi Germans were relevant to Hitler’s rise to power. The minority of radical Muslims that follow Islam to the letter are in control, and it is they who are perpetuating the firestorm that confronts us. Much has been written lately about the moderation of the Muslim Brotherhood in Egypt, but one of its founders, Sayyid Qutb, a leading 20th century theorist of Muslim ideals also claimed that Islam was a “religion of peace” in his book Islam and Universal Peace. What Qutb said and what he meant are entirely different as Gregory Davis explains, “Islam seeks the subjugation of the entire earth under Islamic law. When Islamic law becomes universally triumphant, peace will reign; therefore Islam is a religion of peace.” In other words, “religion of peace” is purely and simply “spin” in its most obtuse form.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348446292663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:24:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348446345335-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Campaign In Trouble</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348441384697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The pressure is on Romney. The country is not happy and his election hinges on one thing - the inability of rightwingers to understand anything. Romney can afford minor mistakes and major mistakes as we have just seen in terms of the rightwing vote as that don't care or understand. Leftwing voters are apathetic, and will now be motivated to vote. 14% tax is way too low. Romney's desperation is so high as to show this very damning point just to show he pays tax. Its all over.</Msg><Username>casey_iii</Username><Timestamp>1348446345335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348446364142-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Middle East is in flames, but 'Islam is a religion of peace'?</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348446292663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:24:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a key factor in understanding the concept “peaceful Islam”, and it is a dire warning to the West which has blindly and naively believed, especially under the leadership of Barack Obama and Secretary of State Hillary Clinton, that negotiation with the Muslim world is possible. Davis sums it up in one final statement. “If the West persists in the false hope of solving the problem of Muslim violence once and for all (through democracy, capitalism, multiculturalism, sensitivity, or whatever the next political vogue will be), it risks being unable to contain it, and thus may bring down upon itself otherwise unavoidable future disasters.” While that parenthetical list may desirable, and though it expresses Western morality and ideals, it does not work within the reality of Islamic radicalism and violence. Our only hope is through strength or the Western world cannot survive against this “religion of peace.”</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348446364142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348446864879-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Campaign In Trouble</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348441384697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The nonsense in your post indicates the hopelessness in your cause.</Msg><Username>luke_oflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1348446864879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348447352235-23</Id><Title>Hidden Cam Clip Has More Views Than Official Romney Videos on YouTube</Title><Msg>Bwahahahahaha!!!</Msg><Username>cries_foul</Username><Timestamp>1348447352235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348447468397-24</Id><Topic><Title>Hidden Cam Clip Has More Views Than Official Romney Videos on YouTube</Title><Username>cries_foul</Username><Timestamp>1348447352235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:42:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. It's all over.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348447468397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:44:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348449167543-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Campaign In Trouble</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348441384697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! An Obama supporter who thinks any opposing opinion is a "lie".Bizarre.And yes,he should have ten point lead by now.But it ain't happening.In my OPINION his campaign is in trouble.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348449167543</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348449278833-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Campaign In Trouble</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348441384697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More hilarity from a totally unsubstantive response.In other words - you all agree.Of course.Because it's obvious his campaign can't gain traction,even with Romney crippled by bad press.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348449278833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348449758974-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Middle East is in flames, but 'Islam is a religion of peace'?</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348446292663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:24:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Muslims who preach race hate and violence are HERETICS.Once upon a time Christianity was subverted in the same way.It didn't even begin to change until the reformation. There are 35 million Kurdish muslims in the mid east - intensely pro american,close with Israel,democratic by nature,economically progressive and tolerant of other faiths.There's no reason to support Palestinian independence,they are not our friends and never have been.The Kurds have ALWAYS been our friends.It's way beyond high time we made their cause our cause instead of the Palestinians.While the Palestinians are allied with Iran the Kurds at at war with Iran. And,it totally exposes everyone's hypocricy,particularly the Syrians,Turks and Iranians who call for Palestinian independence while killing and oppressing the Kurds. DUMP PALESTINE FREE KURDISTAN</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348449758974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348450095947-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney–Obama Energy Policy Differences Clear as Day</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348424583513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:23:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great point. Gotta love these hypocrits running around with cell phones and tablets,each one consuming as much energy as a REFIDGERATOR.But drill and create jobs?/ Oh no,musn't have that.The stupidity is breathtaking.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348450095947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348450731035-29</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Campaign In Trouble</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348441384697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Incredible hypocrisy. You guys are the best at it. You are also wrong. You guys are even better at that.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348450731035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348450832622-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Campaign In Trouble</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348441384697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The trouble the Obama campaign has is that it no longer needs to campaign.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1348450832622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348458757256-31</Id><Title>Gore seeks November splash with event - “dirty weather” is weather that’s enabled by emissions from fossil fuels &amp; “misinformation” about climate change</Title><Msg>Gore seeks November splash with event By Ben Geman - 09/23/12 03:35 PM ET Al Gore hopes to show links between climate change and the effects of extreme weather worldwide with an online and social media-fueled event built around the idea of “dirty weather.” Gore’s advocacy group, the Climate Reality Project, announced Sunday that its second multi-media “24 Hours of Reality” event will occur Nov. 14-15 and bear the title “The Dirty Weather Report.” “We are in a new era where the . . . extreme weather that is occurring is not fully caused by the natural cycles of time and natural events, but by dirty energy, so it is really important to articulate that and name it more precisely,” said Maggie Fox, the CEO of the Climate Reality Project, in an interview Saturday. Organizers call the November event part of an effort to counter the lobbying and financial power of oil and coal interests by using social media and other tools to engage people directly. Gore said on Sunday that “dirty weather” is weather that’s enabled by emissions from fossil fuels and “misinformation” about climate change. “This crisis has to be understood in order to be stopped. The misinformation includes messaging that it is not happening, that we can’t solve it, that we can’t afford to act,” Gore said in a videotaped announcement. “However, together with your help and the full force of our 21st Century technology and media, we can stop the misinformation and the dirty weather, and we can solve the climate crisis,” he said in remarks to a conference in New York City on technology and social change. The live-streamed online event in November is slated to provide content from nations all over the world, and will encourage participation through social media sites including Twitter. It will include expert commentary, as well as “crowd-sourced videos about how weather is altering our lives and homes, and profiles of communities developing solutions to the climate crisis,” the group said. The strong push to use social media to boost interest in addressing climate change comes as advocates are playing defense politically in Washington, D.C. Climate change legislation is dead – at least for now – on Capitol Hill, and Republicans are pushing to block Environmental Protection Agency greenhouse gas regulations. Organizers hope to build political momentum with the event, which will occur just a week after November’s U.S. elections. Fox said “24 Hours of Reality” is “explicitly intended to connect people everywhere and activate them to take action and to advocate for system-wide solutions with their elected officials.” Gore announced the event to the Social Good Summit that’s taking place in New York City. The summit is aimed at exploring ways to harness new media and technology to address environmental problems, poverty and development, disease and other issues. Environmentalists are citing extreme weather – including recent heat waves and drought in the U.S. – to seek to show that climate change is not an abstract, future problem, but rather something that’s already underway with damaging effects. Climate experts say that while individual weather events can’t be laid at the feet of climate change, more frequent and intense drought, violent storms and extreme heat waves are expected in a warming world.   And some scientists are now ditching the caveat about individual weather events.    James Hansen, director of NASA’s Goddard Institute for Space Studies, and colleagues published a paper in August that claims certain heat waves and droughts in recent years are the direct result of climate change. “We find ourselves living in what the scientists call a 'new normal' of more extreme weather that is happening all over the world with increasing frequency,” Gore said Sunday. “The results – fire, floods, drought, crop and livestock devastation, refugees, just to mention a few – impact everyone, everywhere,” he said. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348458757256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>