<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-16"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350364035430-1</Id><Title>Twenty in Congress want new study on LNG shipments</Title><Msg>Twenty in Congress want new study on LNG shipments By Bob DowningPublished: October 15, 2012 Twenty members of Congress want U.S. Energy Secretary Steven Chu to complete a detailed Environmental Impact Statement before the United States proceeds to export liquified natural gas (LNG). Among those signing the letter was U.S. Rep. Dennis Kucinich, D-Lakewood. Here is the press release put out by the letter singers, who were led by U.S. Jared Polis of Colorado and Maurice Hinchey of New York: WASHINGTON—With experts stating that increased liquid natural gas (LNG) exports will expand the use of hydraulic fracturing (or “fracking”) in gas drilling, Congressman Jared Polis (CO-02) and Congressman Maurice Hinchey (NY-22) wrote to U.S. Energy Secretary Steven Chu today urging the completion of an Environmental Impact Statement before approving LNG exports. Polis and Hinchey’s letter was signed by 18 of their colleagues. According to the Energy Information Administration, 63 percent of the export demand for LNG would be met by increased production, 85 percent of which involves production from unconventional techniques, such as fracking. Fracking in densely populated areas would further threaten families and homes with cancer-causing pollution and noise. Signers include: Polis, Hinchey, Raúl Grijalva (AZ), Bob Filner (CA), Charles Rangel (NY), John Olver (MA), Barbara Lee (CA), Gerald Connolly (VA), Pete Stark (CA), José Serrano (NY), Paul Tonko (NY), Betty McCollum (MN), Chellie Pingree (ME), Sam Farr (CA), Michael Honda (CA), Janice Schakowsky (IL), Carolyn Maloney (NY), Dennis Kucinich (OH), Steven Rothman (NJ), and Steve Cohen (TN). The text of the letter follows. Dear Secretary Chu: As the Department of Energy’s Office of Fossil Energy (DOE/FE) considers proposals to export liquefied natural gas (LNG), we urge the DOE/FE to consider the potential environmental impacts of increased U.S. gas production pursuant to the National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA). Specifically, we request that the DOE/FE prepare an Environmental Impact Statement (EIS) to determine how LNG exports may potentially increase environmental risks in communities where natural gas is extracted. We are concerned that exporting more LNG would lead to greater hydraulic fracturing, or “fracking,” activity thus threatening the health of local residents and jobs. For instance, increased natural gas production in communities across the nation could negatively impact farmers, residents, and local property values. The potential benefits from increased trade should be weighed against the increased health costs of additional fracking. Under NEPA, “all agencies of the Federal Government” must prepare an EIS for every “major Federal action significantly affecting the quality of the human environment.” Even though exporting nearly one-third of our domestic gas production certainly constitutes a major Federal action, the DOE has not yet conducted an EIS. A comprehensive EIS is essential to understanding the upstream public health and environmental effects resulting from increased domestic fracking. Further, an EIS ensures that decision-makers are fully analyzing the environmental risks posed by exporting LNG. Before issuing any additional permits for the construction of LNG export facilities, we respectfully request that the DOE/FE complete a comprehensive EIS. Such a review would inform your agency's decision and address the environmental and health impacts in our communities that may result from the opportunity to increase LNG exports. ohio</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350364035430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 01:07:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350367156834-2</Id><Title>Why Does XOM get tax breaks?</Title><Msg>The richest company in the world gets tax breaks and Mitt says that's fine as long as they fire Big Bird and get rid of PBS. Only a millionare or mentally handicapped person would vote for Mitt.</Msg><Username>jpaulgettytoo</Username><Timestamp>1350367156834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 01:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350377669665-3</Id><Topic><Title>California pump prices to plunge [Oil &amp; Gas News]</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350359505472</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 23:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let the freaks pay. They are stupid.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350377669665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 04:54:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350377700515-4</Id><Topic><Title>FACT RYAN ASKED JOE BIDEN FOR 2009 STIMULAS MONEY !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1350327195385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 14:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ commie wahleee.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350377700515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 04:55:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350377750646-5</Id><Topic><Title>FACT RYAN ASKED JOE BIDEN FOR 2009 STIMULAS MONEY !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1350327195385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 14:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Left wing freak commie.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350377750646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 04:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350377975510-6</Id><Topic><Title>So is the State of Florida</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350332334355</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:18:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxipad and good luck get all thumbs down. Thats whats going to happen to the commie dumbocraps come election time. BYE bye maxi dopey and wahleee your leaving.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350377975510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 04:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350378127829-7</Id><Topic><Title>Invest just invents "facts"</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350348121126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:42:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You left low IQ freaks do to much dope and maxi dopey is as poor as it comes. Not even 2 nickels to rub together. The commie trio is getting kicked in their #$%$ into the ocean soon.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350378127829</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 05:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350385420316-8</Id><Title>Iran Plotting to Spill Oil in Strait of Hormuz, Magazine Claims</Title><Msg>http://www.cnbc.com/id/49426899</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1350385420316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 07:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350387618760-9</Id><Title>76% of union members say they are voting for mitt romney! to help save america</Title><Msg>..........................</Msg><Username>unionsaveamerica</Username><Timestamp>1350387618760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 07:40:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350389430698-10</Id><Topic><Title>76% of union members say they are voting for mitt romney! to help save america</Title><Username>unionsaveamerica</Username><Timestamp>1350387618760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 07:40:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bottom line is their jobs will survive under Romney. REMEMBER Romney=Freedom nobumba=Communism</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350389430698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350389920615-11</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Clinton should consider this.</Title><Username>asu_eht_evol_i</Username><Timestamp>1350356675336</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 23:04:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, though not for the same reasons. I recall Hillary campaining for Obama in the 2008 elections. She stated the most important thing was making sure a democrat was elected president. So should it be any surprise that she would lie and throw herself under the bus to cover for Obama? Not a surprise to me at all. When the facts are laid out and hard evidence is found that Obama and/or Biden were made aware of the requests for added security in Benghazi, it'll be too late to change. Why would anyone not want change now? Obama said he'd lower that healthcare insurance by 2500.00 and instead it is 3000.00 higher. Obama said he'd cut the defecit in half, and instead he quadrupled it. Obama said the stimulus bill would keep unemployment under 6.5% and instead it went above 10%. Why on earth should anyone believe Obama and his crew of professional liars??????</Msg><Username>yankeeddandy</Username><Timestamp>1350389920615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350390381230-12</Id><Topic><Title>FACT RYAN ASKED JOE BIDEN FOR 2009 STIMULAS MONEY !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1350327195385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 14:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what if Ryan did ask for stimuless money? The stimuless bill is funded by federal tax payer dollars. The people of the state of Wisconsin, whom Ryan represents, are entitled to benefit from money that they are forced to pay. If Ryan did not ask for some of the stimuless money, he would basically be allowing the federal gov't to tax his people and give the money to other states. That wouldn't be very good representation. I'd do the same thing. The real point is that Ryan did not support the stimuless bill in the first place. The taxation of any people for a program full of pork and wastefull spending. He was right in opposing it. I would have also. To try and spin the fact that he asked for stimuless money for his state after opposing a bill taxing the american people ( including those he represents ) to fund it shows your complete lack of intelligence.</Msg><Username>yankeeddandy</Username><Timestamp>1350390381230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350390678273-13</Id><Topic><Title>FACT RYAN ASKED JOE BIDEN FOR 2009 STIMULAS MONEY !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1350327195385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 14:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That makes you walhieeee. Sorry, I was imitating the right wing tourettes like reactionaries.. I love how all these right wingers justify their hypocrisy. They have no principles. And try as they might to suppress millions of votes on Nov 7th they'll be right back where we are today.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350390678273</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350391037817-14</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Clinton should consider this.</Title><Username>asu_eht_evol_i</Username><Timestamp>1350356675336</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 23:04:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You filthy right wingers worship Condi Rice. The Condi Rice who was National Security Adviser on 9-11. Where were your cries for heads then? You're a bunch of filthy hypocrites who are politicizing a tragedy and no ones minds will be changed by it.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350391037817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350391140646-15</Id><Title>ROFL - I doubled my portfolio Trading XOM!</Title><Msg>Listen to this: Exxon Mobil Corpo is highly likly to move rapidly. Its 50 day Moving Average is +1.07%, and is trading at a cap of 422.4B, and its average daily volume is trading at 12370400. Wall Street is continuously watching Exxon Mobil Corpo . Dont get left behind when the tide comes up. Check this out.... Copy &amp; Paste this to your browser -- mcaf.ee/wnu9x</Msg><Username>hebertconstance729</Username><Timestamp>1350391140646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350391197297-16</Id><Title>9-11 Was THE Largest Security Failure in US History</Title><Msg>You filthy right wingers worship Condi Rice. The Condi Rice who was National Security Adviser on 9-11. Where were your cries for heads then? You're filthy hypocrites who's cries fall on the ears of Fox"News" watchers and no one else. And what did you filthy rats do with the 9-11 Security FAILURE? You started an unjustifiable War and put it on the National Debt tab... Right Wingers are the scourge of the nation.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350391197297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350393578681-17</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Clinton should consider this.</Title><Username>asu_eht_evol_i</Username><Timestamp>1350356675336</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 23:04:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? You left-wingers didn't politicize 9-11????? What do you think the film farenheit 9-11 was??? From another of your big ( in girt as well ) leftist hero, Michael Moore???? You leftists are such hypocrites, it makes the rest of the population laugh at your childish nonsense.</Msg><Username>yankeeddandy</Username><Timestamp>1350393578681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 09:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350393957479-18</Id><Topic><Title>9-11 Was THE Largest Security Failure in US History</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350391197297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it was the creation of the entire Department of Homeland Security. You know, those folks who now screen airport passengers with high-tech equipment to keep air travel safe. Maybe you wouldn't know if you're too poor to afford an airline ticket with your welfare check. Lefty communist #$%$ like you are the scourge of the planet. May you rot in your own failure.</Msg><Username>yankeeddandy</Username><Timestamp>1350393957479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 09:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350395406239-19</Id><Topic><Title>ROFL - I doubled my portfolio Trading XOM!</Title><Username>hebertconstance729</Username><Timestamp>1350391140646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:39:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it`s information that the public hasn`t seen yet.Major volume and break-out, today.</Msg><Username>ffrancis34</Username><Timestamp>1350395406239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 09:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350397166154-20</Id><Topic><Title>9-11 Was THE Largest Security Failure in US History</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350391197297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The planners of 9-11 were allowed by the Clinton administration to build strength during his Presidency and plan the 9-11 attacks. I realize you are a clueless loonie but 9-11 was primarily the fault of the Clinton administration.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350397166154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 10:19:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350403947466-21</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does XOM get tax breaks?</Title><Username>jpaulgettytoo</Username><Timestamp>1350367156834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 01:59:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is called: The cost of doing business and, all businesses have the same tax break. BTW, all politicians say it's fine. That is the tax code. Educate yourself!</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1350403947466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 12:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350404588614-22</Id><Topic><Title>9-11 Was THE Largest Security Failure in US History</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350391197297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Double Indemnity insurance policy put in place in late August , 2001 by World Trade Center leaseholder Larry Silverstein was just good luck. Silverstein also escaped the largest asbestos removal project in the history of the world. World Trade Center #7, the 54 floor skyscraper with the small fire in the basement, collapsed in its footprint at the speed of gravity at 5:15 pm that afternoon replicating every controlled demolition ever shown on television. And the globalists will soon rape American taxpayers with another two trillion dollar excursion into Iran regardless of which of the Goldman Sachs' shills is puppets are elected President.</Msg><Username>potterkimberly44</Username><Timestamp>1350404588614</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 12:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350407252462-23</Id><Topic><Title>9-11 Was THE Largest Security Failure in US History</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350391197297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Party of Person Responsibility steps up... Yet again.. Thanks for proving what we already know yankeedoodledummy.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350407252462</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 13:07:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350407421067-24</Id><Topic><Title>9-11 Was THE Largest Security Failure in US History</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350391197297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More of the Party of Personal Responsibility blaming everyone else.. Keep lying to yourself you #$%$. You'll have your male dominated, third world, endless war state someday. And then it will end, for everyone.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350407421067</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 13:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350407632745-25</Id><Topic><Title>So is the State of Florida</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350332334355</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:18:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We just hired and I am now working with this lilly white, ex vet, tattooed covered male who just left Florida and he says that the mind set in that Rat hole state of Charletons creates racists and #$%$.. I am glad my new friend in work is an intelligent man. I don't have much tolerance for right wing stupidity.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350407632745</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 13:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350408674887-26</Id><Title>American Cars and Trucks are Burning More Biofuels</Title><Msg>American Cars and Trucks are Burning More Biofuels by Chris Clarke on October 15, 2012 4:30 PM Biodiesel service station in Fort Worth, Texas | Photo: Chris Dunphy/Flickr/Creative Commons License Cars and trucks in the U.S. are running on gasoline with a higher proportion of ethanol these days, but limitations in older vehicles are likely to keep that percentage from growing much further, according to a report released today by the Energy Information Administration (EIA). The report, Biofuels Issues and Trends, also notes that biodiesel use in the U.S. went up dramatically in 2011, more than tripling its contribution to the total diesel consumed in the U.S. in that one-year period. In 2011, the percentage of ethanol additive as a total amount of gasoline consumed in the U.S. climbed to 9.6%, up from 9.3% in 2010 and 8.0% in 2009. That means that gasoline across the U.S. is very close to the maximum percentage of ethanol approved for use in all cars and light trucks: the "E10" blend, named after its 10% ethanol content. Ethanol fuel, chemically identical to the alcohol found in alcoholic drinks, is generally distilled from fermented agricultural products. In the U.S., that's generally corn. More than 10% ethanol in gasoline poses a risk of corrosion of parts in older vehicles, and it also requires upgrading tanks, nozzles and hoses at gasoline stations. E10 can be dispensed by existing gasoline stations without upgrades. Still, a gasoline blend with more ethanol -- E15 -- has been approved for most newer cars, and it's technically feasible to raise that percentage much higher. Some gas stations already have "blending tanks" that can provide vehicles with ethanol blends ranging from 10% to 85% ethanol. According to the EIA report, biodiesel -- a fuel made from plant and animal fats -- has grown dramatically in the last decade. Biodiesel production in 2011 was more than 100 times 2001's level. Still, biodiesel isn't nearly as close to pushing its "blend cap" as ethanol. Diesel fuel blends containing up to 5% biodiesel are approved for all diesel engines in the U.S., but the overall percentage in U.S. fuels -- even with the dramatic increase over the last decade -- is less than half that. As ethanol and biodiesel are generally made from potentially edible crops, the industry has taken some criticism for adding to demand for those crops, raising food prices. A possible solution would be to extract biofuels from agricultural waste such as straw and corn stalks, but according to the report, not much has happened to advance so-called "cellulosic ethanol." Of four U.S. facilities built recently to produce cellulosic ethanol, three produced no fuel in 2011, and the fourth only produced a fraction of its capacity. kcet</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350408674887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 13:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350411186764-27</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Company has not achieved the desired sales levels</Msg><Username>pattonjohnny51</Username><Timestamp>1350411186764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:13:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350411214751-28</Id><Title>#$%$ WAS THAT NOSEDIVE BUY!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>...........</Msg><Username>oasis_for_hope</Username><Timestamp>1350411214751</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350411263889-29</Id><Title>Why Did Republicans Vote To Cut State Dept Security?</Title><Msg>The Party of Personal Responsibility strikes again! Darrell Issa (R-CA) voted to cut funding to two State Department accounts, one of which dealt with security. This plays into the notion that the Republicans think Americans have a short attention span and will freak out over the mere mention of the word “terrorism.”</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350411263889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:14:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350411996057-30</Id><Title>We have a 100 target on this,</Title><Msg>would buy</Msg><Username>greenlight_cap</Username><Timestamp>1350411996057</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350412334591-31</Id><Topic><Title>XOM is too superior to skip right now. Examine why!</Title><Username>jonathoncollins47</Username><Timestamp>1349959331474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 08:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coooooolllll</Msg><Username>diazdavid823</Username><Timestamp>1350412334591</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350412801632-32</Id><Title>Electric car battery maker A123 Systems files for bankruptcy</Title><Msg>Another Obamao boondoggle Oct. 16 (Bloomberg) -- A123 Systems Inc., the electric car battery maker that received a $249 million federal grant, filed for bankruptcy protection and said it would sell its assets to Johnson Controls Inc. The filing may fuel a debate over government financing of alternative-energy and transportation businesses. Federal grants and loans to companies including A123, Fisker Automotive Inc. and Tesla Motors Inc. have drawn scrutiny from congressional Republicans following the September 2011 bankruptcy filing of solar-panel maker Solyndra LLC two years after it received a $535 million loan guarantee from the U.S. Energy Department. “This action is expected to allow the company to provide for an orderly sale of the automotive business assets and all other assets and business units,” A123 said in a press release. Johnson Controls plans to acquire A123’s automotive business assets in a deal valued at $125 million and will provide financing of $72.5 million to support A123’s continued operations, according to the release. A deal to sell a majority stake to a Chinese company fell through, A123 said. The company listed assets of $459.8 million and debt of $376 million as of Aug. 31 in Chapter 11 documents filed today in U.S. Bankruptcy Court in Wilmington, Delaware. The Waltham, Massachusetts-based company said yesterday it expected to fail to make an interest payment due yesterday on $143.8 million of notes expiring in 2016.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350412801632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350413343010-33</Id><Topic><Title>Electric car battery maker A123 Systems files for bankruptcy</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350412801632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And another How Energy passed out tax-loss credits that mean taxpayers will pay twice for failure. Perhaps you thought the Solyndra scandal amounted to a $535 million government loan that will never be repaid. No such luck. In the latest twist, Solyndra's investors could be rewarded for their failure, thanks to a tax benefit the Administration handed out in a bid to evade political accountability. The Internal Revenue Service exposed this double Solyndra debacle last week in the U.S. bankruptcy court for the district of Delaware, which is unwinding the defunct solar-panel maker. The IRS formally objected to Solyndra's Chapter 11 reorganization plan, claiming its "principal purpose is tax avoidance." *** Having sold off its manufacturing plant, fired nearly 1,000 workers and proven the non-viability of its business model, Solyndra's only real assets are what the IRS calls "tax attributes." These are between $875 million and $975 million in net operating losses that can reduce future taxable income, which the IRS values as high as $350 million. Before it went toes up, Solyndra also accumulated $12 million in solar tax credits that can reduce tax liabilities dollar for dollar. Tax-loss carry-forwards are routine but worthless if a company can't turn profits to pay taxes on. So Solyndra's owners are asking the court to liquidate the rest of the business and contribute a net $6.7 million to pay off creditors for pennies on the dollar. A holding corporation will then emerge from Chapter 11 that won't make products or employ workers, but it will get the Solyndra tax offsets. The dummy company is owned by Argonaut Ventures I LLC, Solyndra's largest shareholder and the primary investment arm of the George Kaiser Family Foundation. Mr. Kaiser is a Tulsa oil billionaire who bundled campaign checks for Mr. Obama in 2008. The other owner is Madrone Partners LP, a California venture outfit. Solyndra's Energy Department loan closed in September 2009, and a year later it was back asking for more as it bled cash. To stave off bankruptcy, the company asked Energy to release the loan's remaining $95 million immediately, instead of in monthly drawdowns, and to restructure the terms (it had already technically defaulted). The emails that follow are from the negotiations that began in December 2010 and are either exhibits in the IRS objection or come from the 300,000 pages of documents the House Energy and Commerce Committee uncovered in its investigation. Argonaut and Madrone were prepared to commit a new $25 million but needed the government either to take a haircut or subordinate taxpayer repayment rights to new senior debt. Solyndra's private financing rounds were failing because new investors were coming in behind the government's $535 million. "The DOE really thinks politically before it thinks economically," Steve Mitchell, an Argonaut managing director, wrote to Mr. Kaiser on December 7, 2010. The Department of Energy gnomes demanded $75 million and refused to invite the political blowback that signing away taxpayer claims to private financiers would invite, but Mr. Mitchell wouldn't go above $25 million. So he wrote that he "politely moved the conversation toward how we should use the time to start discussing the bankruptcy process . . . To me it was clear that the DOE folks were somewhat caught off guard that we weren't going to bail out the company." Argonaut and Madrone could walk away in part because they had so little skin in the game. Solyndra had 73% debt to 27% equity, not the 65%-35% split that the Treasury Department wanted before Energy boxed it out of a 2009 due-diligence review in the push to get stimulus dollars out the door. Realizing that Argonaut-Madrone would rather liquidate than throw good money after bad, Energy eventually gave in. Meanwhile, Mr. Kaiser's mind was on the net operating losses (NOLs). He mused to Mr. Mitchell that "I would go a long way to preserve the NOLs," and he suggested that the final decision to ante up to $75 million could be "subject to our better understanding of whether the NOLs can conceivably be preserved in a semi-liquidation (that is, somehow maintaining the line of business and avoiding change of control)." In February 2011, Energy signed off on a deal that would subordinate its repayment interests to a new $75 million loan to Solyndra from Argonaut and Madrone. The two owners would open this tranche of senior debt to other investors for equity warrants. But under the Energy term sheet, those warrants would then bounce back to the Argonaut-Madrone holding company if Solyndra became defunct. That gave Argonaut-Madrone 99.9% control of the net operating losses. Solyndra went bust in September 2011, but Mr. Kaiser referred in August emails to "the consolation prize NOL" and wrote that "we could get the same benefit out of a new entity in there without absorbing the costs of resuscitating this one." In other words, the holding company will merge with another profitable Argonaut business that can use the tax breaks. The irony is that the law that created the loan program specifically bars the Energy Department from taking a junior debt position. So Energy simply produced a novel legal analysis claiming that this prohibition applies only when a loan originates, not when it is modified. One staffer at the White House budget office wrote at the time that "I think they have stretched this definition beyond its limits" and noted in particular that the government "is better off liquidating the assets today than restructuring under DOE's proposal." Fly-speckers at the Treasury agreed. *** Under the bankruptcy plan, taxpayers will recoup $27 million at most on Mr. Obama's $535 million "investment." The IRS and Energy Department are now asking the courts to reject the deal, because bankruptcy is designed to give a business a second chance, not goose a tax return. But this is little more than an ex post facto double-cross. Energy created the tax avoidance problem in the first place by gifting Argonaut and Madrone the net operating losses to delay the Solyndra crack-up that was fast becoming inevitable. That left taxpayers worse off than if they simply let Solyndra fail. This raises a question or two for the President who once called Solyndra a "testament to American ingenuity and dynamism" and who keeps accusing Mitt Romney of supporting tax breaks for outsourcing and corporate jets, which he doesn't. Here one of Mr. Obama's own billionaire pals is trying to sidestep a federal tax bill amounting to hundreds of millions of dollars as a result of an epic crony capitalist fiasco. The larger problem is Mr. Obama's economic model that seeks to picks winners and losers and misallocates capital. That's bad enough. But does he have to stick it to taxpayers twice for the same failed investment?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350413343010</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350414447036-34</Id><Topic><Title>XOM is too superior to skip right now. Examine why!</Title><Username>jonathoncollins47</Username><Timestamp>1349959331474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 08:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>keep it up</Msg><Username>diazdavid823</Username><Timestamp>1350414447036</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 15:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350416991785-35</Id><Topic><Title>FACT RYAN ASKED JOE BIDEN FOR 2009 STIMULAS MONEY !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1350327195385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 14:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now we learn that Ryan's family visit to the St. Vincent de Paul soup kitchen last week was a totally staged event that did nothing to benefit the charity. Personal charitable contributions or volunteerism are no substitute for the far greater sums that Gov. Romney and Rep. Ryan would steal from the poor and give to the rich through cuts to taxes and spending. If Rep. Ryan had actually spent a few minutes cleaning pots and pans at a soup kitchen, it would be no compensation for his proposal to starve families by cutting funding for food stamps.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1350416991785</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 15:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350417383528-36</Id><Topic><Title>9-11 Was THE Largest Security Failure in US History</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350391197297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ALL AL-QUAEDA attacks were planned during the Clinton adminstration including the FIRST WTC attack committed by none other than Ramsey Yussef the nephew of KHALID SHIEKH MOHAMMED. MOGADISHU "BLACK HAWK DOWN" - KHOBAR TOWERS - USS COLE - AFRICA EMBASSY ATTACKS....and Clinton did virtually nothing.OF COURSE AL-QUAEDA was going to attack the US.Clinton openly invited it by doing nothing.And he could have gotten Bin Laden ion the late 90's.He didn't have the 'nads to get it done.THAT would have prevented 9/11.Without AQ's support KSM could not have pulled it off.It would have failed,just like his Manila plot to blow up six passenger jets simultaneously.That plot failed and lead to the capture of Yussef,now serving time with the "Blind Sheik".</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350417383528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 15:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350417667157-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does XOM get tax breaks?</Title><Username>jpaulgettytoo</Username><Timestamp>1350367156834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 01:59:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If that were true, you (as mentally handicapped) would certainly be voting for Romney.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350417667157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 16:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350417778317-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Republicans Vote To Cut State Dept Security?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350411263889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:14:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not relevant to the Libya incident.State pulled out security personnel and denied requests for additional security not because of a lack of funding - but because they wanted a "lower profile".They were being repeatedly warned the situation was deteriorating and repeatedly refused - for policy reasons - the additional security. They didn't even respond after the embassy was BOMBED by IED before the 9/11 attack.THEN they LIED about the nature of an attack that was being transmitted in REAL TIME to state and the CIA..</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350417778317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 16:02:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350419345115-39</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Republicans Vote To Cut State Dept Security?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350411263889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:14:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the best you can do? some Republicans voted for some general budget decreases so the President who, by the way, RUNS the state dept through his Sec. of State, had no choice but to leave the missions most in danger with the least protection, right? And when the ambassador and others were murdered in Libya he had no choice, since some Republicans had voted to cut some moneys from State, except to lie over and over and over in the most outrageous fa likelyshion to the American people. You know, on 9/11/2001 by mid-afternoon Pres Bush was on TV speaking to the American people telling them that al quaeda was the likely culprit. Oddly enough, I don't think he made it to the tonight show or the view for months afterwards. Weird.</Msg><Username>fringnatical</Username><Timestamp>1350419345115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 16:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350421765353-40</Id><Topic><Title>Invest just invents "facts"</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350348121126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:42:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lie commie POS maxi.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350421765353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350421771966-41</Id><Title>MIKEY (LPH) IS IN PLAY THEY PAID CASH</Title><Msg>for the new facility and have no debt. They either go private or hit $6 next Q.. Thanks for the tip Mikey</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1350421771966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350421806738-42</Id><Topic><Title>Invest just invents "facts"</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350348121126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:42:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Up your dopey #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350421806738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350422051586-43</Id><Topic><Title>So is the State of Florida</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350332334355</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:18:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Commie POS maxipad is a bum and suck off society leach.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350422051586</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:14:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350422097707-44</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Republicans Vote To Cut State Dept Security?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350411263889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:14:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahlleee lies like the commie dumbocraps.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350422097707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350423962246-45</Id><Topic><Title>So is the State of Florida</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350332334355</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:18:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no idea why low IQ Maxwizard is asking for "facts" and loonie tune Wahleeee / Mrs Uerte is blaming it on Bush since anyone can Google to find out that it is "fact" that the State of Florida is recently implementing these racist measures - primarily to help the numerous low IQs, like Maxwizard, residing in Florida. More from the originally referenced article below (I wish i could link to it but the new Yahoo format won't allow it): "As an example, the percentage of white students scoring at or above grade level (as measured by whether they scored a 3 or higher on the reading FCAT) was 69 percent in 2011-2012, according to the state. For black students, it was 38 percent, and for Hispanics, it was 53 percent. In addition, State Board of Education Chairwoman Kathleen Shanahan said that setting goals for different subgroups was needed to comply with terms of a waiver that Florida and 32 other states have from some provisions of the federal No Child Left Behind Act. These waivers were used to make the states independent from some federal regulations. “We have set a very high goal for all students to reach in Florida,” Shanahan said. But Palm Beach County School Board vice-chairwoman Debra Robinson isn’t buying the rationale. “I’m somewhere between complete and utter disgust and anger and disappointment with humanity,” Robinson told the Post. She said she has been receiving complaints from upset black and Hispanic parents since the state board took its action this week."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350423962246</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350429219429-46</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Republicans Vote To Cut State Dept Security?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350411263889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:14:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush also didn't go to Las Vegas immediately thereafter.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350429219429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350429715014-47</Id><Title>DOE delays decision on natural-gas export license</Title><Msg>DOE delays decision on natural-gas export license By Zack Colman - 10/16/12 05:20 PM ET The Obama administration punted a decision on whether to prevent a liquefied natural gas (LNG) export license, saying it needs more time to review a complaint that an environmental assessment for the plan did not go far enough. The Department of Energy (DOE) said it needs to review a complaint regarding a conditional permit granted to Cheniere Energy. That permit would let the firm export LNG to countries without free-trade agreements from its Sabine Pass terminal in Louisiana. So far, it is the only project out of 15 to receive DOE approval to export LNG to such countries. The Sierra Club had asked DOE for a stay in the approval of the Sabine Pass permit, arguing the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission (FERC) used too lax an environmental assessment in evaluating the export proposal. The Oct. 5 ruling, which DOE released recently, says DOE needs more time Sierra Club’s complaint to decide whether it should grant a rehearing, a DOE official told The Hill on Tuesday. The official noted DOE has not issued a stay on the permit. Andrew Ware, a spokesman with Cheniere, said the company does not expect the Sierra Club complaint to impact the process. Still, the delay will likely do little to calm Republicans and some Democrats who say the administration is not serious about exporting LNG and that its regulations hinder the process. The Sierra Club said the FERC’s assessment did not answer questions about natural-gas production’s effects on air emissions, water quality and geology. Many Democrats share that view. They believe exporting LNG would ramp up use of unconventional drilling methods, commenting that too little is known about their environmental and health impacts. Some also are concerned that exporting LNG would raise natural-gas prices, denting consumers’ and manufacturers’ finances. But many lawmakers, mostly Republican, say the exports will help create jobs and increase revenues while also stabilizing natural-gas prices. They have urged the administration to expedite LNG export licenses, with some suggesting the White House is slow-walking the permits as a concession to environmentalists. DOE grants LNG export licenses more readily to countries with which the United States already has a free-trade agreement. Of 19 applications, DOE has approved 14 LNG export permits to free-trade-agreement nations. The administration has said analyzing fragmented global natural-gas markets is complex, and has cautioned against expanding LNG exports too quickly before the impacts are known. The Sierra Club did not immediately respond to requests for comment. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350429715014</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350431313967-48</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Republicans Vote To Cut State Dept Security?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350411263889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:14:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so the embassy attack in Libya is the same as 9/11--that is what you are saying?? how far have you shoved your head?? if you want war for embassy attacks I wonder what you think of Reagan??--where was his response as president when marine barracks were bombed--he did NOTHING--where is your outrage you have no principles in your life--only politics raised by whitetrash to be whitetrash (made stupid/stayed stupid) but until you or any or your ilk want to step up and serve in the military and EVERY 1 of your ilk wants taxes to pay for a war instead of a credit card--go lick grover norquist' crack you disgusting coward</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1350431313967</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 19:48:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350434087981-49</Id><Topic><Title>The 'real" Romney is revealed in 1 hour</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350432419846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 20:06:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the "real" rmoney is a chameleon--changes to fit--his "handler" said it months ago--just a etch a sketch --make it what you need at that moment. a joke unto himself as his "handlers" have morphed him into a shell of a person--hollow with no principles or convictions on any issue. healthcare --bin laden--abortion--bailouts--etc --etc. His current "stated" positions have ZERO correlation with his record and even less correlation (is that possible??) to his previous positions he will find support from the trailer dwellers--the sarah palin set--etc. you find brilliance in rick perry you will find conviction in mitt. you find morality in newt you will find honesty in mitt. if you find sesame street is a burden you will love letting wallstreet free. if you believe that the banking system is over regulated wait until the guy that banks "offshore" gets in charge</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1350434087981</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 20:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350439766135-50</Id><Title>Obama 8-Ball - Corner Pocket</Title><Msg>EZ shot.Might as well just prepare to rack 'em up for President Romney. These debate are really just style contests.Obama should have won these easily.Instead he got killed.They've revealed him to be an empty suit and out of gas.Romney's gonna win this election handily.Pretty amazing,considering we're in a bull market.Beating a sitting Prez during a bull market is rare.But thanks to his phenominal ineptitude Obama's managed to get it done!</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350439766135</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 22:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350440303060-51</Id><Topic><Title>The 'real" Romney is revealed in 1 hour</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350432419846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 20:06:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! Obama sounds horrendous.It's a town hall debate and he's desperately trying to turn it into a punch fest.HEY 'BAMA! THAT WAS THE LAST DEBATE! LOL! THIS debate is about keeping cool.And Romney is playing it just right,looking way more Presidential. 'bama is done.This election is over.Romney wins it going away....5 pts minimum on the national vote.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350440303060</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 22:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350440402121-52</Id><Topic><Title>ROFL - I doubled my portfolio Trading XOM!</Title><Username>hebertconstance729</Username><Timestamp>1350391140646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 08:39:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is there a split in the offing?? Getting a little price for us "middle class" investors--- !</Msg><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1350440402121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 22:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350440672609-53</Id><Title>Senator Obama</Title><Msg>THIS guy has been PRESIDENT for FOUR YEARS????? How could that even be possible? He acts like a Senator running for election the FIRST TIME.No stature,no charisma,no gravitas.There's CONGRESSMAN who have more charisma than this guy.Empty suit = empty chair behind the oval office desk. President Romney.....it's a done deal.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350440672609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 22:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350440908727-54</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Republicans Vote To Cut State Dept Security?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350411263889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:14:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So will Obama and Hillary be held responsible and made to pay for his poor judgement? I hope so! An attack on any one of our embassies is an act of war. Obama just lied again on this topic during the debate.</Msg><Username>bobbobareno</Username><Timestamp>1350440908727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 22:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350445309350-55</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>kevininthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350398845139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 10:47:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, I just downloaded it and I might end up using this every day now...</Msg><Username>frozencustardking</Username><Timestamp>1350445309350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350445537752-56</Id><Title>Joe-Bama!</Title><Msg>He slapped Thurston Howell III right back to where he belongs which is no where near the White House.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350445537752</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350445947670-57</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Republicans Vote To Cut State Dept Security?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350411263889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:14:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Bush wasted no time in pivoting the tragedy of his terrible national security record into another two trillion in debt and thousands dead. See Iraq. Shove your Benghazi whining where it belongs you filthy rat.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350445947670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>