<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-23"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343041644000-1</Id><Title>RE: XOM...</Title><Msg>Looking for a correction back down to 80-81 area.Maybe cover by Friday..right before XOM reports.</Msg><Username>italiansilk09</Username><Timestamp>1343041644000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 07:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343046035000-2</Id><Title>China’s CNOOC to Buy Canada’s Nexen for $15.1 Billion</Title><Msg>http://www.cnbc.com/id/48282309</Msg><Username>Low_Mac</Username><Timestamp>1343046035000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 08:20:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343060429000-3</Id><Topic><Title>California's future</Title><Username>infernalequinoxx</Username><Timestamp>1343008005000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 21:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will make lovely wine and peach country when the people leave. The industry is already streaming out, fleeing high power costs and emissions regulations. Real estate is losing value from the loss of industry and other business. Windmills can be sited among the orchards and vineyards. I would imagine within a couple of decades you could go to once vibrant cities and set up your own barony of sorts with a large "castle" furnished with all the modern trimmings, and have any number of serfs (former American middle class) to work the fields...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1343060429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 12:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343076059000-4</Id><Title>Celanese up on ethanol pact; takes aim at U.S. for new tech</Title><Msg>Celanese up on ethanol pact; takes aim at U.S. for new tech July 19, 2012, 4:24 PM Shares of Celanese Corp. CE+0.20%rose 5% Thursday after the materials company announced a new pact with Indonesia to use its TCX technology to produce ethanol from coal. Using a closed process that keeps emissions lower than other coal technologies, the TCX technology produces ethanol at a price of about $1.50 to $2 a gallon. Once the ethanol is produced, it burns more cleanly than petroleum products and helps reduce emissions from cars and trucks. Mark Oberle, senior vice president of corporate affairs for Celanese, said the company’s TCX process could produce ethanol from multiple sources including natural gas, depending on whatever’s most economical in a given market. “It’s a breakthrough technology that allows us to produce ethanol cost-effectively using a variety of feedstocks,” he said. Currently, the U.S. Renewable Fuel Standard precludes any hydrocarbon as a raw material, or feedstock, to make ethanol, but Celanese would like that to change, Oberle said. For now, the king of American renewable fuels remains corn-based ethanol, which is blended in gasoline at a rate of up to 15%. For the time being at least, Celanese has plenty on its plate with its new ethanol deal in Indonesia. U.S. regulators may not go along with classifying coal as a renewable fuel, but if the TCX process proves its worth overseas, policy makers could warm up to it. http://blogs.marketwatch.com/thetell/2012/07/19/celanese-up-on-ethanol-pact-takes-aim-at-u-s-for-new-tech/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343076059000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 16:40:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343076465000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Celanese up on ethanol pact; takes aim at U.S. for new tech</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343076059000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 16:40:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>July 19, 2012 Celanese Announces Joint Statement of Cooperation with Pertamina to Advance the Development of Fuel Ethanol Projects in Indonesia JAKARTA, Indonesia &amp; DALLAS--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- Celanese Corporation (NYSE:CE), a global technology and specialty materials company, today announced that it has entered into a Joint Statement of Cooperation to advance the development of fuel ethanol projects with Pertamina, the state-owned energy company of Indonesia. In line with its long-term strategy to develop new and renewable energy capabilities, Pertamina will collaborate exclusively with Celanese to jointly develop synthetic fuel ethanol projects in the Republic of Indonesia utilizing Celanese's proprietary TCX® ethanol process technology. "Celanese's TCX® Technology can help Indonesia meet its growing demand for affordable, locally-sourced, high quality and safe liquid transportation fuel. High-octane fuel ethanol produced using TCX®Technology would help improve air quality through the reduction of particulate matter as well as nitrogen oxide and sulfur oxide emissions," said Steven Sterin, chief financial officer and president of Celanese's Advanced Fuel Technologies business. "These projects support many of the Indonesian government's long-term objectives for the use of its abundant local resources, specifically lower-rank coal, to drive economic development, reduce imported energy requirements and to improve environmental and air quality standards. We are delighted to work with Pertamina to further develop this opportunity within Indonesia and look forward to working closely with them to bring many benefits to the country." Karen Agustiawan, President Director &amp; CEO, PT Pertamina (Persero), said: "A major priority for Pertamina is supporting the Government of Indonesia in securing and managing our energy resources to meet rising demand among both businesses and consumers so we can continue to drive our economic growth to benefit all sections of the society. To meet this goal, we are pleased to be actively working with companies like Celanese on the development and application of new forms of energy, such as synthetic fuel ethanol." Indonesia's current demand for transportation fuel in 2012 is expected to reach approximately 25 million tons and increase six percent annually through at least 2020. A 10 percent blend of high-octane fuel ethanol by 2020 would potentially require up to four world-scale TCX®Technology production units which could reduce Pertamina's gasoline import requirements by over 30 million barrels annually. In addition, high-octane fuel ethanol, which improves tailpipe emissions, may also assist Pertamina in meeting Indonesia's goals of improving the country's gasoline and air quality standards. Under the Joint Statement of Cooperation, Celanese and Pertamina will work together to define potential supply arrangements, production locations and distribution strategies. Following this work, along with final investment decisions made by each companies' management, and receiving all necessary approvals, production could begin in approximately 30 months. About Celanese Celanese Corporation is a global technology leader in the production of specialty materials and chemical products which are used in most major industries and http://amda-10q93v.client.shareholder.com/releasedetail.cfm?ReleaseID=693275</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343076465000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 16:47:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343078293000-6</Id><Title>HOW a REPUBLICAN in DEEP THOUGHT LOOKS</Title><Msg>http://slatest.slate.com/posts/2012/07/23/james_holmes_hearing_aurora_batman_shooting_supsect_due_in_court.html</Msg><Username>epsteinsusan</Username><Timestamp>1343078293000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 17:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343080764000-7</Id><Topic><Title>The economic risks going forward</Title><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1342275373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-14 10:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rethinking education: http://www.schooltube.com/video/2cb4889891b0c637f8f8/RSA-Animate-Changing-Education-Paradigms http://www.schooltube.com/</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1343080764000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 17:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343084787000-8</Id><Title>Canadian province turns away from gas, embraces oil development</Title><Msg>Canadian province turns away from gas, embraces oil development Alaska Dispatch | Jul 21, 2012 According to the Calgary Herald, Canada’s Northwest Territories is turning to oil and away from natural gas as the resource of its future after promising shale developments in the central Mackenzie region. David Ramsey, minister of industry and transportation for the province, said the region’s Canol Shale Formation could be as expansive as the prolific Bakken light oil field that stretches across Montana, North Dakota, Saskatchewan and Manitoba. Producers have invested $628 million in working commitments on 15 parcels in the central Mackenzie region since 2011. “It goes to show there is a resource there, it’s going to be proven up and if all goes to plan, it will transform the economy in NWT overnight,” Ramsey said at a Saskatoon conference on resource development. Initial estimates peg the Canol play at 2 to 3 billion barrels of recoverable crude in a region that has seen drilling activity for almost a century but has yet to reap many economic benefits. Remote and challenging terrain is among the hurdles producers face in getting petroleum to market. Companies such as Imperial Oil, Shell Canada and MGM Energy, ConocoPhillips and Husky Energy are seeking to eventually produce crude. If they succeed, it will mark a new direction for the territory, which saw its decades-long dream of natural-gas development dashed recently because of growing shale gas production in the United States and poor prices. The territorial government learned of the size and potential of the Canol formation in early 2011 after seismic work, the minister said. Strong oil prices open new development opportunities. The biggest challenge may be getting oil to market from this isolated, Arctic region. There are no all-weather roads; equipment is trucked in on ice highways during the winter and by barge or air during the summer. An existing oil pipeline built in the mid-1980s has limited capacity and probably will need to be expanded. “It is very remote so it will not be a cheap play, but all over North America companies are chasing after new oil opportunities,” said Dave Russum, director of geoscience with AJM Deloitte. Until recently, producers have drilled through the shale oil to reach the conventional pool of oil below. But now producers can target the shale directly. http://www.alaskadispatch.com/article/canadian-province-turns-away-gas-embraces-oil-development</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343084787000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 19:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343089308000-9</Id><Topic><Title>The economic risks going forward</Title><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1342275373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-14 10:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Broadly speaking, commodity scarcity and rising competition for commodities is "by far the biggest issue the world faces in the coming decade," according to Moyo. "Looking ahead, the forecast is for many more conflicts and much more significant pressure on commodity prices, all borne out of commodity scarcity." http://finance.yahoo.com/blogs/daily-ticker/china-race-resources-dambisa-moyo-sees-commodity-conflicts-120025018.html</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1343089308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 20:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343101879000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation is showing historic technical movement</Title><Username>ruthannbalton</Username><Timestamp>1343069957000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 14:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MAN...you can FORGET any technicals now!</Msg><Username>horseseven_7</Username><Timestamp>1343101879000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 23:51:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>