<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351486970538-1</Id><Title>Yes it is getting colder. Is this the climate change your talking about. Go dumb green jobs.</Title><Msg>And what about all the fuel efficient cars like chevy volt and the Prius. Where in the heck do you dispose the toxic batteries. How much energy does it take to etract the toxic materials like nickel cadmium in batteries. First of all Boys and girls it takes energy to make energy and sometimes it takes more energy to create this type of energy. you have to extract the materials and then you have to process the materials with energy and toxic processes and more pollutants. So is this the really the best way to create environmentally safe vehicles with the whole idea of toxic materials with less effiecnt energy? Some people are like robot that follow the media without a clue to understanding what it takes to extract green energy. Green energy is some of the worst types of environmentally hazzards the the earth. Same goes for those mercury ridden light bulbs. What about the toxic materials to create the solar cells in Solar panels. Do your homework! And I know the people who promote global warming cannot answer back these questions because these are true facts that are in your face.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1351486970538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 01:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351487364937-2</Id><Title>Obama supports are hoping he wins the election so they can collect welfare checks</Title><Msg>To post thier message all day long. Since they want to be the lowest common denominators in society.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1351487364937</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 01:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351502224310-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama supports are hoping he wins the election so they can collect welfare checks</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1351487364937</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 01:09:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What they don't realize is nobumba will bankrupt america and there will be no $.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351502224310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 05:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351502318451-4</Id><Topic><Title>5 to 1 Obama wins offer still stands</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1351212202113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:43:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What can you bet 2 cents. When your boy loses you're leaving at the end of my boot.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351502318451</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 05:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351502414377-5</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncrap Voter Fraud in Ohio</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351424350687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 07:39:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No maxidopey. That all that you can do is cheat you sewer rat.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351502414377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 05:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351502533634-6</Id><Topic><Title>So Far Ohio Not Taking Romney Bait and Switch</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351343138664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wahlee your soul is possessed by the devil and nobumba.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351502533634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 05:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351502622927-7</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons predicting Obama win, but use Barrons as a contrarian indicator</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1351400538044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 01:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hill going two jail.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351502622927</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 05:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351507436062-8</Id><Title>Global Warming Low IQ Sheeple</Title><Msg>will blame every weather event on man made global warming. If you are not a low IQ sheeple, you have noticed that, when man made global warming was proven a hoax, they quickly started calling it "climate change". We all learned from almost the day we were born that the climate changes continually so "climate change" means nothing other than that. Man made global warming was, is, and always will be "snake oil" sold by Al "Sore Loserman" Gore and believed in by low IQ sheeple. Hurricane Sandy and the cold front are normal weather events and there meeting along the NE coast is an abnormal weather event caused by probability and not caused by man made global warming. Maybe Obama caused this (kind of like the loonie tune libs said Bush caused Hurricane Katrina) - its his "October Surprise" LOL! "The hurricane is on path to meet a winter storm and a cold front, plus high tides from a full moon, and experts said the rare hybrid storm that results could cause havoc through 800 miles from the East Coast to the Great Lakes. Forecasters said the combination could bring close to a foot of rain in places, a potentially lethal storm surge of 4 to 11 feet across much of the region, and punishing winds that could cause widespread power outages that last for days. The storm could also dump up to 2 feet of snow in Kentucky, North Carolina and West Virginia."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351507436062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 06:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351508264161-9</Id><Title>OBAMA A COWART !!!! WE NEED A REAL AMERICAN PRESIDENT LIKE OBAMA</Title><Msg>..................</Msg><Username>savingamerica737</Username><Timestamp>1351508264161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 06:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351510939452-10</Id><Title>Left-over Meatloaf</Title><Msg>Perfect selection by Romney's campaign.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1351510939452</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 07:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351517940944-11</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming Low IQ Sheeple</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351507436062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 06:43:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..vs. Rmoney. Biggest laugh line at the Rethug Convention now exploding in Mitt's face!</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1351517940944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351518047574-12</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oceans rising, over the long term and short term. Biggest laugh line at R Convention now exploding in Mittster's face!</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1351518047574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351518361437-13</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ONLY thing you represent, wahleee boy, is brain death - and you do that at least very well.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351518361437</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351522949958-14</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not denying just giving reasons for and how to stop it. What do you give -- just names not idea's.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1351522949958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 11:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351531941158-15</Id><Topic><Title>our idiot president obama is a weather man now ! how about let the weather folks do there jobs and you do yours by protecting us from bad guys</Title><Username>jokerjoker835</Username><Timestamp>1351529900415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 12:58:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROFLMAO... Only egomaniac fools like him have egos larger in size than Sandy!</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1351531941158</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351532917931-16</Id><Title>Can He Be Re-Elected and Impeached at the Same Time?</Title><Msg>No wonder he and his staff are avoiding this issue! "Is it treason when you put your own reelection above the good of your country and the lives of its citizens? If so, Barack Obama committed treason in leaving the four Americans to die in Benghazi. Our Constitution defines it this way: “Treason against the United States, shall consist only in levying War against them, or in adhering to their Enemies, giving them Aid and Comfort.” Aid and comfort to the enemy — what is that? When you ascribe an action to the protest of a video when it is actuality a planned terror attack by Ansar al-Shariah, an established offshoot of al-Qaeda (if that’s not your “enemy,” then who) — and you knew that all along, you watched it live without doing anything, and then you told those who wanted to help to “stand down”? Meanwhile, our government may have been conspiring to arm another offshoot of al-Qaeda in Syria. How much more treasonous can you get? Benedict Arnold was a piker. Indeed, the discussion of Benghazi has just begun. And don’t be surprised if the conversation escalates from impeachment to treason very quickly. In fact, if Obama wins reelection you can bet on it. The cries of treason will be unstoppable. Not even if the mainstream media will be able to deny them."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351532917931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351534001653-17</Id><Topic><Title>Can He Be Re-Elected and Impeached at the Same Time?</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351532917931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(if that’s not your “enemy,” then who)?? gee the "W" told the whole world the enemy was saddam hussein people like you bought his lies --why you don't want him impeached ??</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1351534001653</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:06:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351538242335-18</Id><Topic><Title>Can He Be Re-Elected and Impeached at the Same Time?</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351532917931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Barack Obama committed treason in leaving the four Americans to die in Benghazi." Only very dumb people think that.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1351538242335</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351538267859-19</Id><Title>OT: I don't get this</Title><Msg>saw in the paper that even though the NYSE is closed, stocks were being traded electronically. I see no evidence of any stock trading on yahoo finance and it says markets will remain closed on Tuesday. Are stocks being traded electronically today and tomorrow? Paul</Msg><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1351538267859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351542836420-20</Id><Topic><Title>Can He Be Re-Elected and Impeached at the Same Time?</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351532917931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And maxidopey is leaving via the ocean.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351542836420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351542949372-21</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA A COWART !!!! WE NEED A REAL AMERICAN PRESIDENT LIKE OBAMA</Title><Username>savingamerica737</Username><Timestamp>1351508264161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 06:57:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He sucks and you suck.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351542949372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351547384861-22</Id><Topic><Title>OT: I don't get this</Title><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1351538267859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:17:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, they decided to close it all.</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1351547384861</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351550278389-23</Id><Topic><Title>So Far Ohio Not Taking Romney Bait and Switch</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351343138664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More comedy! Obviously,you don''t even know what a "bait and switch" is.That's what you get for living like a backwoods shut in.You REALLY ought to get out more often.REALITY would AMAZE you. LOL!!!</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1351550278389</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351550663415-24</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That proves you really DO live alone in the backwoods somewhere.Amazing.You'd better stay there!!! Otherwise a simple walk down the street would be TERRIFYING!!! You'd be SURROUNDED by Republicans - though I'm sure you can "recognize" one when you see one...right??? They actually look different...correct??? Like any other minority. Which would make you...A RACIST!!! ROTFLOL!!!!</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1351550663415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351554368245-25</Id><Topic><Title>Can He Be Re-Elected and Impeached at the Same Time?</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351532917931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time to impeach the POS Hussein. "You know who doesn’t like getting thrown under the bus? The CIA. You know what the CIA does when you try to throw it under the bus? They get even — quickly, quietly, and with fatal consequences. That seems the most logical explanation for the torrent of information pouring out this week (unless Hillary Rodham Clinton — also thrown under the bus by President Obama — is scrapping any chance of ever running for president again and is simply setting the whole administration on fire, along with her legacy as secretary of state). The main lesson from Watergate (after the no-brainer that you should never hire a guy named “Tricky Dick”) was this: The Cover-Up Is Worse Than The Crime. For some reason, Professor Obama seems not to know this crucial lesson. Or he’s just arrogant enough to say, “Well, that doesn’t apply to someone as brilliant as moi.” Make no mistake, though: There is a massive cover-up under way in the White House. Nothing else can explain the endless contradictions over the attack that left the U.S. ambassador to Libya and three other Americans dead. The White House has already had to rewrite the entire narrative once, holding a late night conference call with reporters just before a House hearing two weeks ago in which State Department officials told a whole new tale: There was no “spontaneous” protest over some anti-Islam video posted on YouTube. Instead, there were dozens of heavily armed terrorists who poured over a 9-foot-high fence covered with barbed wire to attack America on 9/11. Last week, Mr. Obama told another bald-faced lie when he declared at the presidential debate that he had termed the attack “terrorist” in a Rose Garden address the next day. He did no such thing; in fact, the White House and State Department took nearly two weeks to acknowledge it was a terrorist attack (all the while pushing the spontaneous protest and video canards)."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351554368245</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351558006735-26</Id><Title>For maxwizard: I suggest you read this:</Title><Msg>The "Unlawful Internet Gambling Enforcement Act of 2006."</Msg><Username>iggybiggies</Username><Timestamp>1351558006735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 20:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351560504726-27</Id><Title>Peak Natural Gas Consumption in America...</Title><Msg>Peak Natural Gas Consumption in America... ... is approaching very quickly. December 2013 through January 2014. Sixty-two days. Thereafter, clean coal and inexpensive renewable energy [solar, wind, geothermal, biofuels including second and third generation cellulosic ethanol and biodiesel] will steal an endlessly increasing marketshare from natural gas. My opinion</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351560504726</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351561740691-28</Id><Title>NYSE has 3 ft of water on the exchange FLOOR ! No MKT this week !</Title><Msg>wow.......</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1351561740691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>