<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345957725000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" multi-billion dollar corporate financier interests would risk their collective fate" They're individuals, and yes, they pour millions in.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345957725000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 01:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345957769000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Want more taxes?</Title><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1345930987000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 17:43:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're filth raul.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345957769000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345984415000-3</Id><Topic><Title>War on Women</Title><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345904625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 10:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I can't sleep I play some selected Hitler speeches and goose step around the house for ten or fifteen minutes and then relaxed, I sleep the sleep of the untroubled. I don't know what Hitler is talking about but he sure can talk! (Goose stepping is `great` exercise for the Abs!)</Msg><Username>maxchatrman</Username><Timestamp>1345984415000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:33:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345987405000-4</Id><Topic><Title>HOW AN IMBECILE SOUNDS!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345811208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 08:26:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually it's the older than 50 left wing nut/Communist old hippies that are the main problem. I think when Romney and the Republicans take back the Presidency, Senate, and House they should rewrite the Obama health care law to first determine lifestyle choices (work and living off the government welfare programs history, drug convictions, STD history, sexual preference, etc.) of each individual versus incurred medical costs and void or severly limit continued taxpayer funded medical and other care to the individuals who have made poor lifestyle choices and who are the "takers" who have been living off the taxpayer dollars paid by the "givers". That would be true justice. Just let the old useless "takers" die off and give incentive to the your current "takers" to become more productive and be "givers".</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1345987405000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 09:23:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345991783000-5</Id><Title>HE'S GOTTA BE KIDDING!</Title><Msg>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/08/24/ryan-on-abortion-exceptions-rape-is-just-another-method-of-conception/</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345991783000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:36:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345992346000-6</Id><Title>xom union boss makes over $2 million under the table</Title><Msg>222222222222</Msg><Username>nynynynynyny692</Username><Timestamp>1345992346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:45:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345993862000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Getting Killed</Title><Username>paul_alana22</Username><Timestamp>1345983435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already a member since 2006,</Msg><Username>dedra_avis12</Username><Timestamp>1345993862000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:11:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345995567000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Energy policies Bush: Pro drilling in the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, California, and all everywhere else there is cheap oil. Pro clean coal. Pro natural gas. Pro hydrogen economy and nano-tech and Federal research to develop it. Pro invasion of OPEC countries (like Iraq) to secure more oil supplies. Obama: Supposedly pro oil drilling but only in the most expensive areas with small fields and high cost oil. Anti- coal. Anti- cheap natural gas. Seems more interested in the Federal aspect of forced investment than the economics of cheap energy. In favor of military campaigns in countries with no oil (Afghanistan) and against maintaining American control over with large amounts of oil (Iraq). Against invading other countries with large oil fields (Libya) and allowing other countries (or local terrorist groups) to control the resources. Romney: His energy policy will be much like Bush. On most important single issue there is no resemblance between the three. Perhaps on peripheral issues of little relevance there is common ground...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345995567000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345996673000-9</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY HIT A HOME RUN TODAY</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345772318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 21:38:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When romney once ran the olympics, it was terribly in debt, when the olympics were over he had established a workable plan for the future games and left the treasury in the black with amble funds. romney is a problem solver and will create jobs and get this country running correctly again.....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345996673000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:57:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345996724000-10</Id><Title>War On Energy</Title><Msg>The Democrats have been on a campaign against it ever since the Kyoto Treaty was signed in 1997. They elected Gore as their nominee in 2000 because of his radical environmental agenda. Gore lost but the Democrats of his ilk in Congress kept up the fight. They managed to block Bush's energy policy, soon after he was elected, contributing to the oil price spike and the housing and financial crash that was a direct result of it. The election of Obama has escalated the conflict to new heights. Not only has Obama obstructed oil drilling in every cheap high yielding place he can manage, he has also blocked pipeline transportation to import cheap Canadian tar sands oil. Obama's EPA has launched endless regulatory assaults on the utilities and power plants. Their latest unconstitutional assault was shot down in the courts, but if Obama wins another term this promises to be only a temporary set back for his radical agenda. An Obama victory will cement America's fate. It's growth trajectory, which was built on cheap energy for the past 400 years, will come to an end.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345996724000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345996896000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Arab Socialism</Title><Username>weald_of_kent</Username><Timestamp>1345911469000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no he is just another idoit from plaistine and want to kiss muslins back side.</Msg><Username>dirtpoordog</Username><Timestamp>1345996896000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345997110000-12</Id><Topic><Title>War on Women</Title><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345904625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 10:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama is a disgrace to the UNITED STATES OF AMERICA.</Msg><Username>dirtpoordog</Username><Timestamp>1345997110000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:05:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345997355000-13</Id><Topic><Title>War on Women</Title><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345904625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 10:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True by any measurement possible!</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345997355000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345997512000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where did you read that?</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345997512000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:11:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345997692000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nailed!</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345997692000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345998340000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo deletes most messages with substantive words and links. You can find all the important difference on Google by using their search engine to find the facts on the Bush energy policy, and Romney's energy policy. Obama's energy policy is much more scattered and diffuse. Google up thing like "energy prices must necessarily skyrocket, van Jones, and EPA lawsuit {c02, air quality], Kyoto, green agenda.. You will not find yahoo to be a very useful source.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345998340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346003195000-17</Id><Title>60 votes in Senate</Title><Msg>The Senate is what will matter going forward + the White House. It will require 60 votes in the Senate to defeat the Democrat's environmental agenda and open up Alaska, the outer continental shelf, and all other Federal lands to oil drilling. Licensing of coal plants, and new heavy oil refineries, and repeal of the EPA's air quality regulations, will require 60 votes as well. The economy will not recover until American energy supplies are opened up fully to development. It is insufficient to control the White House as Bush proved. As for the phony economy built on debt, low interest rates, and inflated stock prices - that will deflate and push unemployment even higher when it does.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346003195000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 13:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346003400000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Go Long Bottom!</Title><Username>beighleyogn1979</Username><Timestamp>1345996095000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:48:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move.</Msg><Username>messingscd17878</Username><Timestamp>1346003400000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 13:50:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346003584000-19</Id><Topic><Title>War on Women</Title><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345904625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 10:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When I can't sleep I play some selected H____r speeches and goose step around the house for ten or fifteen minutes and then relaxed, I sleep the sleep of the untroubled. I don't know what H____r is talking about but he sure can talk! (Goose stepping is `great` exercise for the Abs!)" You make a good little environmental N--i wahleee boy. Perhaps you can apply for an job at the EPA if Obama wins.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346003584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 13:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346006796000-20</Id><Title>WOULD YOU AGREE ....</Title><Msg>http://www.isidewith.com/</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346006796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346007151000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>infowars.com There was 69 cent gas at one point under Clinton when the economy was better. Bush was all lip service and little on results in changing America's dependance on Israel's islamic neighbors for oil. The neocon lie that US taxpayers would be recompensed after the invasion of Iraq is unmentioned on the propagaters for Middle East genocide at MSNBC, CNN, and FOX News. I can hear Bibi's tools shrieking racism the day a US President puts America's interests first and invades the world's leading narco terrorist state, Mexico.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346007151000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346010363000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Go Long Bottom!</Title><Username>beighleyogn1979</Username><Timestamp>1345996095000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:48:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great return</Msg><Username>ritaccojtx82007</Username><Timestamp>1346010363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:46:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346010568000-23</Id><Title>SPEAKING of MITT ROMNEY!</Title><Msg>http://www.alternet.org/print/hot-news-views/why-mitt-romney-gets-squeamish-about-mormon-tithing</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346010568000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346011819000-24</Id><Topic><Title>HOW AN IMBECILE SOUNDS!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345811208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 08:26:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spoke to Her just today, she's a pro-choicer alright, believes in free choice for all Her subjects. By the way She's seending some stormy rath down on the G O P gathering in Fla. in an attempt to put a little fear of "the Almighty" in them for their misleading ways.</Msg><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1346011819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346012738000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>During the 1990s the economy of Eastern Europe and Russia collapsed due to the unraveling of the Communist economic system, which reduced oil demand in the former Warsaw Pact countries by nearly 3 million barrels per day. The United States and European economic profited handsomely from the collapsing oil prices caused by the gusher oil from those areas on the world market. Clinton had nothing to do with that; indeed his party actively undermined the Reagan arms buildup that helped to usher it in. Bush never had a chance to implement his energy policy because of Democrat obstruction in the Senate. The President cannot make law and getting laws passed without 60 votes in the Senate is effectively impossible. By the 2000s the former Warsaw Pact countries' economy was on the mend, and China's economy was surging ahead on the back of a major road building campaign. Oil demand rocketed up and thanks to Democrat obstruction of oil drilling in America the demand could not be met except after a 1000% increase in oil prices. That price increase caused the financial crisis. The ultimate solution to this fundamental supply/demand imbalance in the oil market will be the invasion of more OPEC countries to open up the supply sources they are manipulating to keep prices up. The United States has the power to do this if it chooses. It may well require nuclear weapons, to demonstrate the resolve of the United States to put an end to oil cartels and dictators obstructing market forces...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346012738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:25:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346013971000-26</Id><Title>All-out-war</Title><Msg>Syria we important for ushering in the conflict. They absolutely have weapons of mass destruction, there own, and quite likely Saddam Hussein's weapons as well... You can be certain that if weapons of mass destruction are used against American forces, by either the terrorist regime in Syria, or one of Iran's terrorist proxy groups which infest the area, the U.S. military will respond in kind. The U.S. military has battlefield, tactical, and strategic level nuclear weapons, and a very elaborate delivery system.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346014006000-27</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*Syria will be important for ushering in the conflict.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346014006000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346015639000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since when has a President had a majority in the House and sixty votes in the Senate. Are you suggesting it is hopeless for an energy policy change under Romney since he will never have sixty GOP Senators. In the late 1990's the number of vehicles on the road in Warsaw Pact nations had tripled from the pre Soviet collapse days. Poland had the fastest growing economy in Europe during the late 1990s. I do not remember Clinton having 60 votes in the Senate and a House majority. Bush=Obama=Romney=GoldmanSachs</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346015639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346016268000-29</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Said like a true American...war monger</Msg><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1346016268000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346017086000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Defended Stimulus When Bush Wanted It</Title><Username>bankhouseone</Username><Timestamp>1345533469000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 03:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DEFENDED STIMULUS RIGHT WINGERS !!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1346017086000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:38:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346018103000-31</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN &amp; AKIN ARE MORE ALIKED !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1345800176000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 05:22:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RYAN supported "the Unborn Victims of Violence Act" that sounds like Rape to me. That means TELL A WOMEN TO CARRY FULL TERM well thats RIGHT WINGERS BIG GOV'T telling u what to do. !!! However, don't worry according to Akin womens body can shut down when this happens this is the REPUBLICAN PARTY for u !!!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1346018103000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346018719000-32</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beware conservatives bearing "absolute" ownership of WMD.</Msg><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1346018719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346018847000-33</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN &amp; AKIN ARE MORE ALIKED !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1345800176000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 05:22:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conservatives feed on their own hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1346018847000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346019668000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Warsaw Pact in 1990, ex-East Germany, consisted of the Soviet Union, Hungary, Romania, Poland, Czechoslovakia, and Bulgaria. Its combined oil demand was 9,716,000 barrels per day. By 1999 its combined oil demand was down to 4,478,000 barrels per day, a drop of 5,238,000 barrels per day. The economic recovery of Clinton's first term was marked by the first 3 million barrel drop in former Warsaw Pact oil demand, and the second term extended it. http://www.eia.gov/cfapps/ipdbproject/iedindex3.cfm?tid=5&amp;pid=5&amp;aid=2&amp;cid=regions&amp;syid=1990&amp;eyid=2009&amp;unit=TBPD As for 60 votes. It takes only 40 to do nothing, which is what Clinton's energy policy consisted of. He could get by with that because of the collapse of the Soviet Union's economy and the torrent of cheap oil issuing from it. It takes 60 votes to do something, hence Bush's difficulties in increasing oil supplies.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346019668000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346019926000-35</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Said like a true American...war monger" I guess that would make you an anti-American peace-nik. The war promises to be quite and violent. Perhaps you should cover your eyes, or stick your head in the sand... The choice of Obama or Romney is irrelevant to it. It is coming.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346019926000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:25:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346020171000-36</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Beware conservatives bearing "absolute" ownership of WMD." One of the various definitions of insanity is to confront an insane person with a choice involving rational options or a question, and then get an answer or choice which is unrelated and irrational. You fit the definition of insane, wahleee boy. Keep it up.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346020171000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346021550000-37</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How would you analyze the issue and forcast the solution to outright genocide? If you don't care, just say so but, STFU with your naive view of reality. Those of us that pray for peace do not include the egomaniacal example of perennial tyrannical bullies that typify much of the Middle East. Your definition of "war monger" is misplaced along with your ability to understand reality.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1346021550000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:52:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346022849000-38</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're filth raul.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346022849000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346022971000-39</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Slam dunk" was the "absolute" used I believe.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346022971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346023898000-40</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There is no surer way of keeping possession than by devastation..." - Niccolo Machiavelli</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346023898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346024925000-41</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tory was not speaking from his guise of `War Monger`, if he really is one, he was speaking as a realist, he noted, correctly, that the situation is dark and getting darker, this is a retelling of reality, he leaves reality and enters faith and conjecture when he predicts the outcome of the events he foretells of, if the alternate media is correct in it's assessment, the coming struggle is pivotal in the determination of winners and losers, since many have power yet no one has ultimate power the one who is losing will strike the fatal blow for surely from the losers view; It is better that we all die rather than a victor standing over us, this is what the USA would do and that is what I would want them to do, I have no desire to be someones slave. Since the stakes are so high, around the World everyone is watching, Quite likely events will quickly be captured by the black Hole of chaos, to predict what things will look like after that journey is as foolish as describing the geography of Heaven, what ever it is when we get there, if we get there, it won't be what we thought it would be.</Msg><Username>maxchatrman</Username><Timestamp>1346024925000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346024945000-42</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""There is no surer way of keeping possession than by devastation..." In times of societal collapse, which Republicans still see as an option, despite centuries of societal stability (post 1506) within a system of legal recourse. For example, the possession weapons by ordinary members of society is usually the sign of a collapse in society, not a right to bear arms. Such extremes are just part of the course for the right (mongers), justified by ancient archetypes.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346024945000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346025430000-43</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Those of us that pray for peace do not include the egomaniacal example of perennial tyrannical bullies that typify much of the Middle East." "The first way to lose your state is to neglect the art of war; the first way to win a state is to be skilled in the art of war." - Niccolo Machiavelli Wars are expensive and dangerous solutions to problems as Machiavelli teaches. Ignoring enemies and giving them time to plot does not diminish their threat; on the contrary, it increases the threat with each passing day. A Prince should be mindful of the threats his enemies present, and take forceful action against them. Obama has ignored the threats and allowed them to festered to monstrous proportions. The solution will be even more monstrous, but quite necessary none-the-less. Bush's policies were not conducted according to sound Machiavellian policy either. The main difficulty was he did not understand you cannot win the hearts and minds of your enemy. Also did not want to hear what it would take to achieve his aims. Warmonger by chicken hawks is not good policy. It takes a firm hand at the wheel of the Ship of State to avoid devastating wars. We do not have a firm hand now, and haven't had one for quite some time...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346025430000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346026025000-44</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The first way to lose your state is to neglect the art of war; the first way to win a state is to be skilled in the art of war." Is it really 600 years? I thought it was only 60 years, where right-wingers are stuck in the past.... the 'white picket fence' stupidity.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346026025000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346026604000-45</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"In times of societal collapse, which Republicans still see as an option, despite centuries of societal stability (post 1506) within a system of legal recourse." You either do not know the history since 1506 or you are deliberately misrepresenting it to make another irrelevant conclusion. Try opening an excel spreadsheet and saving it as "war." Next list all the wars from 1506 to 2012 and which states were involved, and their expense. You should be able to see quite clearly a pattern of increasing military activity. This may be surprising to you, but it was no mystery to people like Machiavelli, but the states that were most skillful at war developed strong societies, superior legal structures, and ended up better off than their weaker more passive neighbors. Developing a state is important, too. There is a difference between a powerful state and a powerful monarchy. Skill in war is acquired by experience, not by theory or books. One more quote from Machiavelli: "The main foundations of every state, new states as well as ancient or composite ones, are good laws and good arms; and because you cannot have good laws without good arms, and where there are good arms, good laws inevitably follow, I shall not discuss the laws but the arms." You are a poor philosopher LC, and certainly no match for the like of Machiavelli. His statement above predicts perfectly the development of the superior legal, economic, and military state of Great Britain, France, and the United States, Germany, and many others. The hapless Oriental states just couldn't keep up... Believe whatever you want about the modern world, but keep in mind your attitude is not supported by history; indeed it is flat out contradicted by it. Your attitude is one of denial mixed with ignorance - a pathetic combination.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346026604000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:16:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346026681000-46</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How would you analyze the issue and forecast the solution to outright genocide?" quote of Rewindsteve Are you in search of a Happy Ending to this tale Stevie? Solutions, that lead to Happy Endings are getting very rare, I'll keep looking, if I find something it will be expensive, the cheap endings are all gone, but maybe, if you pay enough, something can be worked out!</Msg><Username>maxchatrman</Username><Timestamp>1346026681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:18:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346027011000-47</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The best way to get a Happy Ending is to get a real TV Preacher and send him all the cash you can, even if there is no Happy Ending for the World, you won't care, you'll be gone in the Rapture! This is the true win-win!</Msg><Username>donny_d_drivle</Username><Timestamp>1346027011000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:23:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346027209000-48</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are obviously not a scholar of Machiavelli, who was in charge of Florence’s defense until 1506. You also have no idea about relevancy.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346027209000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346027616000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are right for what it is worth Rockhard, Tory's blathering obfustication is just an attempt to cloud the issue, the very idea that a controversial man like Barry, could come from obscurity and attain the position he holds would be a stretch in a Disney movie, yet the people need myths to inspire them, and so there he sits, our inspiration.</Msg><Username>donny_d_drivle</Username><Timestamp>1346027616000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346028254000-50</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A truly imbecilic response. You have not addressed the fundamental lie you presented of "stable" peaceful societies developing into your modern world either, or one would suppose preferentially advancing. Address that lie first. Florence is irrelevant to it, as it 1506. You can pick any date arbitrarily the past 1000 years and your theory of law and society will be wrong. States and princes who fail at the art of war go by the wayside, and those that never even try fail by default... When you arrive at a more rational understanding of the past perhaps you can discuss Machiavelli's wisdom, and its relevance to the future. Any and all further messages that are off topic, and do not address the fundamental issues will be summarily ignored. Save yourself the trouble of writing them...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346028254000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346028923000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For Inspiration no one could beat President Reagan, we had all seen him in the war movies, flying planes, killing enemy, rescuing friends, and all round good guy, it seemed, yet he did have a dark side, I saw him once as a Doctor who cut off a man's legs in a fit of jealousy over a romantic interest, and so, while I did like Reagan i Couldn't shake the feeling that I was privy to a dark secret from his past and so, my approval was more measured than many peoples. (I guess it's called maturity? I am mature? right?)</Msg><Username>carl_cessman</Username><Timestamp>1346028923000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346029283000-52</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw., the relevancy is to conduct war, not how it is conducted, you war monger. If inevitable (last resort), so be it. BUT..... Last resort, originating as "Just War", I believe, has been modernized many times with the Convention Hague 1907 etc., but no better has the description on its use been said by Jackson; "We must make clear to the Germans that the wrong for which their fallen leaders are on trial is not that they lost the war, but that they started it. And we must not allow ourselves to be drawn into a trial of the causes of the war, for our position is that no grievances or policies will justify resort to aggressive war. It is utterly renounced and condemned as an instrument of policy." Republican have show, even up to this decade, that they hold these words in contempt.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346029283000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346029879000-53</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To conduct war or not conduct it is relevant to the health of the state, laws, institutions, and their advancement. The conduct of war speaks to the efficacy of war as a tool of policy. Both are well explained by Machiavelli. Both points can easily be backed up by endless historical examples. Bush's failure to accomplish anything useful in Iraq could be expected, as could Obama's failure in Afghanistan. It should be noted too that America failed to get results in Vietnam until Nixon launched Operation Linebacker II. The attitude of his enemy instantly improved, just as could be expected. The Hague Convention is off topic. That speaks again to your theory of peace and harmony which you have yet to support with any evidence.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346029879000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:11:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346030647000-54</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"To conduct war or not conduct it is relevant to..."....nothing Thanks for confirming that the right hold Jackson's words in contempt. "...your theory of peace and harmony which you have yet to support with any evidence." No such theory was posed. You have great trouble with comprehension.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346030647000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346030923000-55</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tory doesn't have to comprehend, he only has to believe, belief is what creates reality, in the mind of a believer, nothing is more powerfull than the power od belief it's self!</Msg><Username>donny_d_drivle</Username><Timestamp>1346030923000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346030932000-56</Id><Title>Economic Growth Is Unsustainable</Title><Msg>"The present global economy is caught in a catch-22 of its own making. Solutions exist, but the blindness that created the problem also stops the solutions from being seen." http://www.eveoftheapoc.com.au/Downloads/DebtVsGrowth.html</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1346030932000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346031559000-57</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was being generous in describing your ranting and raving about stable laws, and societies etc as a theory. You are quite correct it is just a rant. You had the chance to support it and did not. If you expect to find any support for your beliefs, or develop your ranting and raving into a theory of war &amp; peace you had best not look to Jackson or the leaders of the Party of Jackson. America was built on war. Jackson fought many wars. He marched the Cherokee nation off to the west defying a Supreme Court order. It is unlikely he read The Prince, but he certainly acted as a good one. Other Democrat Presidents like Polk went looking for wars too - that is how the Mexican -American War happened. Wilson (D) invaded Mexico. FDR led the nation in an enormous war. Truman nuked two Japanese cities knowing full well the Japanese were ready to surrender. Johnson escalated Vietnam massively and personally okayed targets. Barack Obama is turning into a "war monger" (as you would define it) too. A war is coming. Enjoy. You know nothing of the past, present or future. You are just rant and rave mindlessly. You have earned a place in the land of "ignore."</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346031559000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:39:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346031792000-58</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As for the peacenik fool "Jackson" you mention in regards to the Germans. I could care less about that kind of nonsense. Such people have no idea how wars are won. Look to the founder of your party for a tutorial. That is a much more useful Jackson for you ...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346031792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346031963000-59</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It amuses me that you conduct the acts you criticize. "Stable laws" now? Where did the "theory of peace and harmony" go? Since right-wingers feed on their own hypocrisy, you must be fat.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346031963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:46:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346032047000-60</Id><Title>Oil going for the highs, Iran and QE3 2B announced Friday</Title><Msg>With those combinations look to break the highs.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1346032047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346032097000-61</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"..you mention in regards to the Germans" Wrong. You have a real problem with comprehension.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346032097000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:48:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346032402000-62</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>", but no better has the description on its use been said by Jackson; "We must make clear to the Germans" I do believe if you could be put on a witness stand in a court of law you could be found to be legally insane. You cannot even remember the topic of your own ranting and raving from one minute to the next. You devolve into more and more logically irrelevant items and territory each passing message. I've tired of keeping tracking of it. Do try to keep out a court too... We wouldn't want want you to end up as a committed lunatic.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346032402000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346032733000-63</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You are right for what it is worth Rockhard" "Tory's blathering obfustication (sic)" "the very idea that a controversial man like Barry, could come from obscurity and attain the position" A truly bizarre collection of ranting and raving. It does not address the underlying energy policy. It ignores the facts under discussion. "Barry's" obscure background has even less relevance to the issue - if anything it flatly contradicts the idea of commonality between the men. Total rubbish... Boring. Ignore.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346032733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346033054000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was a reply to Rockhard's original post, nothing to do with energy policy. Rockhard commented on the unreality of our daily reality, he "Gets it" you don't, can't?</Msg><Username>donny_d_drivle</Username><Timestamp>1346033054000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 22:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346033158000-65</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here you demonstrate your extreme inability to comprehend, which diverts your ability to argue points towards zero (by vector?). Those of Jackson's words that were mentioned, were in regards to the point that the criteria to conduct war not be on policy. You have a huge problem with comprehension. "irrelevant to it, as it 1506" Your unfocussed guess that the date was irrelevant was followed by clarification as to his involvement in war policy up to 1506, which was followed by your cowardly recognition to the contrary.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346033158000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 22:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346033250000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346033250000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 22:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346033385000-67</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rockhard's theory is that Israel is behind them all. That theory has nothing to do with "unreality" but rather "reality" as he sees it; that is, a reality he does not like. Because of this "reality," so the theory goes, the American political process is a sham. If you do not believe this interpretation just ask the man in question. I have no doubt he will agree.. The theory is wrong as any careful inspection of the policies of the men in question will show. Energy policy speaks directly to the Middle East, and is most useful for debunking the theory. You do not understand the Middle East, nor energy policy broadly, or obviously even what the discussion is about. Boring...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346033385000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 22:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346033452000-68</Id><Topic><Title>HOW AN IMBECILE SOUNDS!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345811208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 08:26:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like Issac is heading toward Democratic New Orleans and skipping Tampa. Did God make a mistake or is he more angry at the Democrats? I'm so pleased you talk to Him regularly. I hope it eases your feelings of worthlessness.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346033452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 22:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346035320000-69</Id><Topic><Title>Go Long Bottom!</Title><Username>beighleyogn1979</Username><Timestamp>1345996095000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:48:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it. Good job man!</Msg><Username>beermannqtfm67731</Username><Timestamp>1346035320000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 22:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346035945000-70</Id><Topic><Title>Oil going for the highs, Iran and QE3 2B announced Friday</Title><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1346032047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:47:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good day, between issac and the venezeula explosion, i was looking for oil to break 100 on monday. glta,</Msg><Username>leereece42</Username><Timestamp>1346035945000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 22:52:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>