<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347876370408-1</Id><Topic><Title>What is Ryan's IQ?</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347838668158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is Obama's IQ and why won't he make his college transcripts available to voters? I suspect Ryan's IQ and grades are significantly higher than Obama's and Ryan achieved his grades without affirmative action help. Obama is the affirmative action poster boy; a failure by all measures except in his nice speaking voice, which God gave him. Wahleee you are truly an idiot, proved every time you post with one of your stupid aliases.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1347876370408</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 06:06:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347883532731-2</Id><Topic><Title>What is Ryan's IQ?</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347838668158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryans IQ 100 times higher then nobumba the commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347883532731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347888437789-3</Id><Topic><Title>What is Ryan's IQ?</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347838668158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cs &amp; Ds don't cut it.</Msg><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347888437789</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347888573311-4</Id><Title>Petition opposing Northern Gateway pipeline clears 10,000 signatures</Title><Msg>Petition opposing Northern Gateway pipeline clears 10,000 signatures Jenny Uechi Posted: Sep 16th, 2012 The Avaaz petition "No Enbridge Tankers/Pipeline in BC Great Bear Rainforest", having surpassed its original goal of 10,000 signatures, is now aiming for 20,000 names to pass against the Northern Gateway pipeline to the federal and provincial government. •Online petitions call for stop to Enbridge Northern Gateway pipeline The petition, started by Kelowna resident James MacGregor, has picked up an increasing number of signatures as more people have become aware of the issue. "BC's entire Great Bear Rainforest, its wildlife and the livelihoods of coastal First Nations are all at great risk if Enbridge's Northern Gateway pipeline is approved," he said. MacGregor plans to deliver the signed petition on October 1 to Prime Minister Stephen Harper. The federal Conservative government has set a deadline of Dec. 31, 2013 for the Joint Review Panel to complete their report on Northern Gateway. Due to growing opposition in BC, Stephen Harper has tempered his support for the Northern Gateway pipeline in recent weeks. Despite saying in early August that Northern Gateway was of "vital interest" to British Columbia and Canada, he has since stated that "science, not politics" will determine the pipeline's fate. In the past few months, opposition to the pipeline has spread spread so wide across through so many channels that critics have started to say that Northern Gateway looks to be a a non-starter. "I know I'm not the only one out there speaking up about the pipeline, but I felt like I couldn't sit back and do nothing," MacGregor commented. Having seen the natural landscapes of northern BC as well as the Yukon and Alaska over recent years, he said he developed an appreciation for the region. If the Northern Gateway pipeline is built, advocates say, it will endanger the protected waters and wildlife of the Great Bear Rainforest, which is one of the largest coastal temperate rainforest in North America. "Some resource projects carry with it an acceptable risk," he said. "Northern Gateway is not one of them -- not with Enbridge's track record of over 800 spills since 1999." vancouverobserver</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347888573311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347889099480-5</Id><Title>Canadian pipeline could drive up traffic in difficult Alaska waterway</Title><Msg>Canadian pipeline could drive up traffic in difficult Alaska waterway Alaska Dispatch | Sep 16, 2012 The cover story of the Anchorage Press this week covers the long history of cargo ships wrecking, running aground or otherwise causing the state of Alaska a load of grief while traveling the Great Circle Route, a marine thoroughfare which rubs up against the Aleutian Chain. Now a Canadian company's proposal for a new oil pipeline may dramatically add to the number of vessels traveling the Circle Route, increasing the risk of spills and mishaps in Alaska waters. The Great Circle Route is the quickest way to ship anything from the West Coast of North America to Asia, but it is notoriously difficult -- especially in Alaska waters around the Aleutian Islands. There are incidents involving ships traving the route that people may remember, such as in 2004 when the vessel Selendang Ayu, transporting 132 million pounds of soybeans, ran aground on Unalaska Island and spilled 338,000 gallons of fuel. But there are others not so well-known. For example, the Cougar Ace, a vessel that tipped over in 2006. Ultimately, the Ace was not a huge environmental burden, but the ship did end up losing its entire shipment of Mazda automobiles. Rescue tugs and other forms of marine assistance are usually impossible to find along Great Circle Route, , leaving vessels traveling the area fairly vulnerable and the state of Alaska liable for any environmental impacts. The proposed Northern Gateway Pipeline project would begin in Alberta, Canada, and run 730 miles north to the port of Kitimat in British Columbia. From there, an estimated 220 supertankers would travel the Circle Route each year. Vessels passing through will not be loaded with cute things like soybeans or Mazdas. They'll be hauling the real goods -- natural gas condensate, oil and diluted bitumen. If an accident did occur, it would be major. However the Enbridge Northern Gateway Pipeline is not a done deal, and it's essentially Canada's version of Pebble Mine. It still must hold up to a panel of experts, a round of public testimony and, finally, an environmental assessment. Only then can the project proceed. Read much more at the Anchorage Press, here. alaskadispatch</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347889099480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347890470649-6</Id><Topic><Title>What is Ryan's IQ?</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347838668158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Ryan bot is street smart not intelligent.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1347890470649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347898570961-7</Id><Topic><Title>What is Ryan's IQ?</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347838668158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another example of rmoneys' decision skills--who else was the "brain at bain" becaise this isn't it what a disaster the gop has become from Ike to Ford to even Reagan that now yields palin bush and ryan as leaders mittens is the bob dole sacrificial lamb and rightfully so--listen to trump/beholden to rush bimbo and advised by senor and gramm?? recipe for disaster yeppers stick the fork in</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1347898570961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347899978169-8</Id><Title>Thanks Obamao</Title><Msg>US Jobless Rate Really at 16%, Not 8.1%: Expert (CNBC) The U.S. unemployment rate of 8.1 percent is probably double that number when you include a host of measures of the jobless rate that are not included in the official data, one professional tells CNBC. The state of the U.S. labor market is in focus because the Federal Reserve said last week that until there are significant improvements in the sector, the central bank would continue to buy mortgage and other assets in order to revive economic growth. But the problem, says CEO of Richmond Asset Management in Hong Kong, Graham Bibby, is that the level of unemployment in the U.S. is probably worse than the Fed thinks it is, with the jobless rate probably closer to 16 percent when you look at other measures not used to compile the official number. "For example, if you have been unemployed for 12 months, given some other criteria, and you haven't been to the unemployment exchange, you haven't been to interviews, you haven't been looking at job adverts etc., you drop off the official unemployment numbers because you are not viewed as actively looking for employment. But technically, you are not employed," Bibby said on CNBC Asia's "Squawk Box". "Then there are statistics at the short-end such as how long you have to be unemployed before you are considered unemployed, and if you get a part-time job when you were looking for a full-time job, you also drop off the statistics. So the stats are quite a lot higher then they look," he added. The U.S. unemployment rate fell to 8.1 percent in August from 8.3 percent. Still, the jobless rate has remained above 8 percent since early 2009 and has remained stubbornly high - even with earlier monetary stimulus from the Fed and interest rates close to zero.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347899978169</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347903147516-9</Id><Title>Chevron making all time high up .70, why is this down?</Title><Msg>Should push 93</Msg><Username>riskreversal777</Username><Timestamp>1347903147516</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347907542364-10</Id><Title>OIL technical selloff ??? or some hedge fund under estimated the market ? Little favors for brothers</Title><Msg>Just pure manipulation all over agin Retail got hurt again</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1347907542364</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347908194048-11</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks Obamao</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347899978169</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba is a commie muzzie.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347908194048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347911191048-12</Id><Title>Right Wingers Wrong Again.</Title><Msg>Cutting taxes for the wealthy does not generate faster economic growth, according to a new report. But those cuts may widen the income gap between the rich and the rest, according to a new report. A study from the Congressional Research Service -- the non-partisan research office for Congress -- shows that "there is little evidence over the past 65 years that tax cuts for the highest earners are associated with savings, investment or productivity growth." In fact, the study found that higher tax rates for the wealthy are statistically associated with higher levels of growth. The finding is likely to fuel to the already bitter political fight over taxing the rich, with President Obama and the Democrats calling for higher taxes on the wealthy to reduce the deficit and fund spending. Mitt Romney and the GOP advocate lower marginal tax rates for top earners, saying they fuel investment and job creation.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347911191048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347913126799-13</Id><Title>Romney's Right to Criticize Obama on Muslim Protests</Title><Msg>Is it just me, or is it starting to feel like 1979 all over again? The rising gas prices, the mobs storming American embassies in the Middle East, the killing of an American ambassador, and an administration whose first response to this week's crisis in Libya was not to condemn the attackers, but to blame Americans who "abuse" their right of free speech. By Friday, the administration had made clear it was not in fact siding with the mobs, but the damage was done. Here's a look at the administration's first response as documented by the New York Times. A U.S. official "close to the issue" is now telling Foreign Policy that the embassy's original statement was put out against White House orders, but the White House has not commented. The official who put out the statement has not been disciplined. The statement came from the American embassy in Cairo on Tuesday morning, before Ambassador Christopher Stevens had been murdered: The Embassy of the United States in Cairo condemns the continuing efforts by misguided individuals to hurt the religious feelings of Muslims – as we condemn efforts to offend believers of all religions. Today, the 11th anniversary of the September 11, 2001, terrorist attacks on the United States, Americans are honoring our patriots and those who serve our nation as the fitting response to the enemies of democracy. Respect for religious beliefs is a cornerstone of American democracy. We firmly reject the actions by those who abuse the universal right of free speech to hurt the religious beliefs of others. The "condemnation" issued in the first sentence was not a condemnation of the violence, but a condemnation of an anti-Muslim film made by a private citizen in the United States who was "abusing" his right to free speech. No wonder the statement was controversial: The tone of it is defensive, weak, and embarrassed. It did not call for an end to the mayhem. It blamed America—and Americans who hurt others' feelings—first. It reminds me of this passage from lifelong Democrat Jeane Kirkpatrick's 1984 speech at the Republican National Convention in which she recalled a similar time, when terrorists attacked the Marine Corps barracks in Lebanon: When our Marines, sent to Lebanon on a multinational peacekeeping mission with the consent of the United States Congress, were murdered in their sleep, the "blame America first crowd" didn't blame the terrorists who murdered the Marines, they blamed the United States. But then, they always blame America first. And as the White House scrambled this week after snubbing Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu, who wanted to meet about the lack of a credible U.S. response to Iran's nuclear buildup, I'm also reminded of when Kirkpatrick criticized Democrats for being indifferent to the "new vulnerabilities" of our allies and the development of new weapons by our enemies: The Carter administration's motives were good, but their policies were inadequate, uninformed and mistaken. They made things worse, not better ... The United States grew weaker ... Mitt Romney was right to criticize the administration's original response to the attacks on our embassies. And the White House knew he was right—based on its own continuing disavowal of the same statement. This controversy was the last thing the White House needed after the Netanyahu fiasco. While the administration is right to condemn the obscure video that produced all this violence, it should also make it clear the U.S. government had nothing to do with the video—this one or any others like it. Like it or not, the freedom of speech that allowed this film to be produced in the first place is a right of individuals who live in democracies. In addition to American strategic interests, securing those basic human rights for many oppressed Muslims in Afghanistan and Iraq was why the United States went to war there. In the age of YouTube, there are sure to be other incidents like this; the administration's policy should be first, to condemn violence of any kind and second, to stand up strongly for free speech and other basic human rights in the Muslim world. As Kirkpatrick would put it, Obama's motives may be good, but his policies are inadequate, uninformed and mistaken.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347913126799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347914727256-14</Id><Title>Linn Co-op is Iowa’s First Retailer to Offer E15 - discounted 15 cents per gallon during the open house</Title><Msg>Linn Co-op is Iowa’s First Retailer to Offer E15 Posted by Cindy Zimmerman – September 17th, 2012 History was made today when the first gallon of E15 was sold in Iowa. Linn Co-op Oil Company in Marion is the state’s first retailer to give customers with 2001 or newer vehicles the choice of filling up with 15% ethanol blended fuel. “We are honored to be Iowa’s first retailer to offer E15 to our customers who have been asking for it,” said Jim Becthold, Service Manager for Linn Co-op Oil Company. “We anticipate that E15 could account for up to 50 percent of our total fuel sales.” Bechtold wanted to offer the fuel when it first received final approval from EPA in June, but was unable to do so until now because of EPA’s summer volatility standards that prevented him from being able to get the proper blendstock to use. As part of the introduction of E15, Linn Co-op will hold an open house this Friday, September 21, from 8 a.m. to 5 p.m. with lunch served from 11 a.m. to 1 p.m. E15 will be discounted 15 cents per gallon during the open house. To introduce E15 to Marion residents, the Iowa Renewable Fuels Association (IRFA), Iowa Corn Growers and the Iowa Power Fund Community Grant Program are sponsoring a media campaign that includes radio and print ads, billboards and direct mail. The campaign will run throughout September. IRFA Managing Director Lucy Norton says this type of campaign is available to any Iowa retailer who wants to offer E15 for 2001 and newer vehicle owners, noted Norton. Retailers preparing to offer E15 in the future are urged to contact the IRFA for promotional assistance. domesticfuel</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347914727256</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347916674076-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's Right to Criticize Obama on Muslim Protests</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347913126799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:18:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"when terrorists attacked the Marine Corps barracks in Lebanon"--that was under Reagan not a convenient fact for your propaganda but fact is fact the other FACT you left out--there was NEVER any retaliation for the Marine barracks bombings--just some tough talk by gipper and daddy bush--but talk is all NEVER let facts get in the way of opinion--go sarah go</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1347916674076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347922470650-16</Id><Title>Gateway pipeline hearings resume: First Nations get chance to question Enbridge</Title><Msg>Gateway pipeline hearings resume: First Nations get chance to question Enbridge Monday, 17 September 2012 16:14 Bob Weber, The Canadian Press The Douglas Channel, the proposed shipping route for oil tanker ships in the Enbridge Northern Gateway Project, is pictured in an aerial view just south of Kitimat, B.C., on January 10, 2012. THE CANADIAN PRESS/Darryl Dyck EDMONTON - Lawyers for an aboriginal group fighting the proposed Northern Gateway pipeline have raised more questions about who could end up with ownership stakes. Hana Boye, who represents the Haisla band which claims much of the pipeline's route as its traditional territory, queried Enbridge (TSX:ENB) officials on who put up money for 10 $10-million option agreements that could guarantee their holders space in the pipeline and a share of its ownership. "If we don't know who these investors are, we're not able to determine if they're financially viable, if they're market-force driven or if it's in the interest of Canadians," she said. Lawyers for environmental groups had already raised questions at hearings earlier this month about the possibility of Chinese interests buying control of the project. On Monday, Enbridge vice-president John Fisher said most of the purchasers have been identified. Those who aren't are covered by a confidentiality agreement, he said. Under further questioning, Fisher conceded that the Chinese state-owned oil company Sinopec owns one of the $10-million units. Boye then asked if the purchasers of the other units would be able to sell them and whether Enbridge would have any influence on who would be able to buy them. "It would be a private transaction between those two parties," Fisher said. "It could happen." Boye pointed out that Chinese energy firms are buying Canadian companies who have purchased option units. The China National Offshore Oil Corp. has purchased a share of MEG Energy, which is an option owner. As well, Chinese interests are also trying to buy Nexen (TSX:NXY), which owns another one of the 10 options. The testimony came as hearings on Enbridge's controversial pipeline resumed in Edmonton. It was the first chance for First Nations representatives to cross-examine company officials about the proposed $6-billion line. Haida and Haisla officials have made statements voicing concerns about the project at earlier hearing sessions. The pipeline would carry bitumen from Alberta's oilsands to the B.C. coast where it would be loaded onto tankers headed for Asia. People living along the route and on the B.C. coast fear the impact of possible spills, but supporters of the pipeline argue it's needed to expand Canada's export options. The latest round of hearings in Edmonton are to last all week. lethbridgeherald</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347922470650</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347924575929-17</Id><Title>EU Commission to cap food-based biofuels</Title><Msg>EU Commission to cap food-based biofuels U.S. biofuel policy also criticized Sep 17, 2012 7:05 PM - 0 comments By: Barbara Lewis and Michele Kambas Brussels/Nicosia | Reuters The European Commission announced a major shift in biofuel policy on Monday, saying it plans to limit crop-based biofuels to five per cent of transport fuel, after campaigners said existing rules take food out of people's mouths. Record-high global grain prices have intensified calls for changes in EU and U.S. biofuel policies, criticized for snatching away land that should be used for food. EU climate commissioner Connie Hedegaard and energy commissioner Guenther Oettinger confirmed in a joint statement on Monday they wanted to cap the use of crop-based fuel. "It is wrong to believe that we are pushing food-based biofuels," the commissioners said. "In our upcoming proposal for new legislation, we do exactly the contrary: we limit them to the current consumption level, that is five per cent up to 2020." Reuters reported last week the European Commission would seek to impose a limit on the use of crop-based biofuels of five per cent as part of a target to raise the share of renewable fuel in the transport mix to 10 per cent by 2020. The draft proposals, which are expected to be published in October, will need the approval of EU governments and lawmakers to become law. "The Commission's message for post-2020 is that our clear preference is biofuels produced from non-food feedstocks, like waste or agricultural residues such as straw," Monday's statement from the commissioners said. "These new types of biofuels are not in competition with food, nor do they require additional land. We are pushing biofuels that help us cutting substantial CO2-emissions, do not compete with food and are sustainable and green at the same time." Tough target With the 10 per cent target looking very difficult, energy ministers meeting informally on Monday in Cyprus, holder of the EU presidency, debated how biofuels could be developed sustainably. Speaking on the sidelines of the meeting, Oettinger said increasing the use of biofuels depended on developing a new generation of sources. These second-generation biofuels are much more costly than those made from crops such as rapeseed and wheat. "I think we agree that a higher figure for that mixture of biofuel beyond five per cent can only be achieved from a second generation source, not from crops but agricultural waste and leftovers instead of from food crops," he told reporters. Campaign group Oxfam urged ministers to support the proposed EU limit and to ignore warnings from biofuel producers that the plans would hurt Europe's economy and result in job losses. "European governments and the European Commission must not cave in to pressure from the biofuels industry," said Natalia Alonso, head of Oxfam's EU office. "We cannot continue to burn food in our petrol tanks while poor families go hungry." The EU's biofuel goal to source 10 per cent of road transport from renewable sources by the end of the decade is part of an overall aim to increase use of renewable sources and limit carbon emissions. It also has a goal to draw 20 per cent of the total energy mix from green energy. Oettinger said the bloc was on track for the 20 per cent goal by 2020, but subsidies were an issue and he urged a more harmonized EU approach. "A major disadvantage has been that in some member states, often budgetary consolidation has led to abrupt changes," he said. "This is the opposite of protecting people's confidence so they can safely plan, and it frightens off investors." Too much subsidy was as bad as sudden changes, and subsidies will have to dwindle as technology becomes more competitive, he said. "What we have seen is that there has been too much support actually in some cases, more has been done to encourage than necessary, leading to free-rider effects," Oettinger said. grainews</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347924575929</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 19:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347926625711-18</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's Right to Criticize Obama on Muslim Protests</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347913126799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:18:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney will say anything to get elected. He is for the white rich, period. He has only contempt for non white, non rich. Listen to his speeches to various groups. He'll say whatever it takes. His father was born in Mexico, so his father is Mexican.</Msg><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347926625711</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 20:03:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347929589236-19</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's Right to Criticize Obama on Muslim Protests</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347913126799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:18:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ u commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347929589236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 20:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347929691944-20</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wingers Wrong Again.</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347911191048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wahlee take your meds and go to bed, I mean your cardboard box .The one next to commie maxi dopey.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347929691944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 20:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347933965199-21</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wingers Wrong Again.</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347911191048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's true,higher rates for highest earners has little impact on growth. It also has little impact on the debt.And above all,it does nothing to address the problem of growth.Obama has no serious plan to grow the economy or prevent a default.If we default the poor will get fall to the street and the middle class will become poor.Obama is,above all,the greatest threat to the poor and working class in US history - because of the risk of default. Meanwhile Obama's Jimmy Carter impersonation has the country on the glide path to war.He has neither the guts no good sense to stand up for american values,like - Free Speech.The arab and muslim world is rfie with hateful media programming and he is silent.He's met the enemy and he believes the enemy is us.Like Doonesbury.So his "policy" is KEEP APOLOGIZING. If we re-elect this failure we deserve the disaster that will follow.Apparantly that is what it will take before the american people finally become more focused on the issues than they are on Ryan Seacrest and Kim Kardashian.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1347933965199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347934751835-22</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wingers Wrong Again.</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347911191048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there are a LOT of people that should apologize for the disaster that is Iraq of course to you the dead do not matter--of course to you the war debt does not matter (you paid for it with a tax cut remember)--so no skin in the game/no problem trailertrash you would think that at some point in your life some principle would outweigh your foxview politics--but your ignorance is just reflective of your upbringing</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1347934751835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347935746718-23</Id><Title>Mitt's Gonna Need All Those Shadow Donors</Title><Msg>Because he just told the 99% that he doesn't represent them.. Quick Mitt call overseas have them direct payments to Karl Rove so he can cover up the source.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347935746718</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:35:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347935748982-24</Id><Title>Mitt's Gonna Need All Those Shadow Donors</Title><Msg>Because he just told the 99% that he doesn't represent them.. Quick Mitt call overseas have them direct payments to Karl Rove so he can cover up the source.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347935748982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347936066721-25</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wingers Wrong Again.</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347911191048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right wingers depend on zero substance smear tactics funded by billionaires looking for billion $ tax cuts to keep #$%$ like Kyle in the stupid. People know Mitt's a loser, a puppet and a fraud. But are they smart enough to not take the rotten bait thrown by the likes of Rove and the "US Chamber of Commerce"(See outsourcers). We'll see in Nov but right now you'd have to say Romney is a losing cause.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347936066721</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347936066785-26</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wingers Wrong Again.</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347911191048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right wingers depend on zero substance smear tactics funded by billionaires looking for billion $ tax cuts to keep #$%$ like Kyle in the stupid. People know Mitt's a loser, a puppet and a fraud. But are they smart enough to not take the rotten bait thrown by the likes of Rove and the "US Chamber of Commerce"(See outsourcers). We'll see in Nov but right now you'd have to say Romney is a losing cause.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347936066785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347936247984-27</Id><Title>Right Wingers Wrong Again and Again!</Title><Msg>While the USA sweated through one of its warmest summers on record, so, too, did the rest of the globe, federal scientists from the National Climatic Data Center announced Monday. The average summer temperature over global land and ocean surfaces tied with 2005 as the third-highest on record at 61.25 degrees F, or 1.15 degree F above the 20th century average of 60.1 degrees F. Only the summers of 1998 and 2010 were warmer. Records go back to 1880. Climatologists define summer in the Northern Hemisphere as the months of June, July and August. The climate center is a branch of the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA). "Considering global land surfaces only, June - Aug. 2012 was record warm, at 1.85 degrees above average," the center's online report stated. The most unusual warmth occurred across parts of the Northern Hemisphere, including most of the United States and Canada, southern and eastern Europe, Kazakhstan and eastern Siberia. Droughts in the USA, eastern Russia and India all contributed to the high heat, says Jessica Blunden, climate scientist with the data center. If you have drought, the atmosphere doesn't have the moisture available to lessen the heat, she says. Also, Blunden says the change from La Nina, a cooling of Pacific Ocean water, to El Nino, a warming of that water, was another main factor in driving the global heat. The unusual warmth also caused Arctic sea ice to shrink to its lowest level on record, the National Snow and Ice Data Center reported. August itself was the fourth-warmest August on record worldwide. It marked the 330th consecutive above-average month. The last cooler-than-average month globally was February 1985, the climate center reports. Federal scientists last week announced that the USA experienced its third-warmest summer on record, trailing only 1936 and 2011.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347936247984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347937291801-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's Right to Criticize Obama on Muslim Protests</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347913126799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:18:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More lies from another lemming. Boring.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347937291801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347937453533-29</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's Gonna Need All Those Shadow Donors</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347935746718</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:35:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did he say they were clinging to their guns and bibles?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347937453533</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347937697017-30</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wingers Wrong Again.</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347911191048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think if you repeat yourself enough even you might believe the cr#p you post?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347937697017</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:08:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347937815101-31</Id><Topic><Title>Right Wingers Wrong Again and Again!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1347936247984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:44:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But they are good little lemmings who try never to think for themselves. It's apparently too difficult.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347937815101</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347940627375-32</Id><Title>Arizona Wins America’s Next Top Algae Biofuel Research Facility… For Now</Title><Msg>Arizona Wins America’s Next Top Algae Biofuel Research Facility… For Now September 17, 2012 By Tina Casey 2 Comments Arizona has just won a $15 million Department of Energy grant to establish the first ever national algae biofuel testbed in the US, which gives it at least temporary bragging rights to the #1 position as it jockeys with other states to establish the kind of algae-friendly cred that will attract new business into its borders. It’s going to have some stiff competition, though. Texas A&amp;M University’s algae biofuel research program also recently got a huge infusion of federal cash, and a network of regional research centers is growing in Hawaii, California, Ohio and Georgia. A National Push for Algae Biofuel Research To be fair, the competition is far more friendly than not. Under the new grant, Arizona and states with existing algae research centers will collaborate with each other and with federal laboratories as well as with private sector partners. The Arizona testbed will be called ATP3 (for Algae Testbed Public-Private Partnership), and will be housed at the Arizona Center for Algae Technology and Innovation at the Polytechnic campus of Arizona State University. Just as the name says, it will be supported by a laundry list of public and private partners, including the National Renewable Energy Laboratory, Sandia National Laboratories, Cellana LLC, Touchstone Research Laboratory, SRS Energy, Cal Poly San Luis Obispo, Georgia Institute of Technology, University of Texas at Austin, and Commercial Algae Management. Also weaving into the algae biofuel picture are the US Navy’s algae biofuel initiative, which has been forging ahead despite opposition from Republican leadership in Congress, NASA algae biofuel research, and the US aviation industry’s biofuel initiatives. What’s It All About, Algae Biofuel? If all this activity seems a little Manhattan Project–esque, there’s a good reason for the urgency. With only three percent of the world’s oil reserves, the US could drill its way to China and back without reducing its dependence on foreign supplies. Even aside from global warming issues, domestic fuel diversity is critical for long-term security. As the recent drought shows, food-based biofuel crops such as corn aren’t going to cut it over the long run, so attention is turning to non-food sources. Algae looks like a winner because it is rich in oil; it can be grown under controlled conditions; it can thrive in different regions of the US; and it won’t necessarily take up any space that could be used to grow food. Move Over Cacti, Here Comes Algae The new testbed in Arizona is designed to provide private industry with shared access to a national database for analyzing algae growth and algae biofuel production methods, which will help quicken the pace of research from the lab to fully scaled-up commercial algae farms and biofuel refineries. Notwithstanding members of Congress who have railed against federal support for algae biofuel, it seems that algae has the potential to become big business, and on that account, it is winning support from legislators at the state level. Algae could provide a particularly significant economic boost for states like Arizona, which could see its agriculture and energy production sectors grow in one fell swoop. In Arizona, ASU writer Amelia Huggins notes that state lawmakers recently approved two bills designed to create a friendly opening for private industry. One classifies algae as agriculture, and the other permits algae farming on state trust lands. Huggins also notes that algae research in the state has “benefitted from the strong support of Arizona Gov. Janice Brewer.” Clean Technica</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347940627375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>