<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349237291281-1</Id><Title>Hunt for Obama’s Middle East Policy Comes Up Empty</Title><Msg>There’s an old saying that liberals will support armed intervention in a foreign conflict only so long as nothing resembling a self-interest is at stake. If the cause is purely humanitarian -- if the refinement of American morality is the only possible domestic benefit -- liberals just might be persuaded to support the use of military force to help a starved, invaded or otherwise oppressed people. Which brings me to the baffling subject of Syria. Like many observers of the Obama administration, I’ve been confused by its unwillingness to take even the relatively modest steps required to bring about a decisive end to the regime of Bashar al-Assad. More than 30,000 people have been killed since the beginning of the uprising against him, according to the Syrian Observatory for Human Rights, and untold numbers have been wounded, tortured or raped. The Syrians who are rebelling are in dire need of the sort of support that the U.S. can best provide. The U.S. has the capability to efficiently neutralize Syria’s air defenses and impose a no-fly zone to ground Assad’s attack helicopters. And as Michael Doran and Max Boot pointed out in a recent New York Times opinion article, only the U.S. can lead a multinational effort to establish safe corridors between the Turkish border and the besieged city of Aleppo. If Aleppo was under the stable and permanent control of Syria’s rebels, it would spell the end of Assad’s regime and its appalling brutality. Elusive Explanation So what explains President Barack Obama’s hesitancy? Perhaps the caricature of liberals is true: In Libya, where Obama deployed the Air Force against the regime of Muammar Qaddafi -- whose crimes were terrible, but not as terrible as Assad’s -- there were only marginal national-security interests at stake. In Syria, the national-security interests are profound. It doesn’t seem plausible that Obama is hesitating because the U.S. self-interest is so nakedly apparent. Yet a better explanation for his passivity is elusive. Could Obama simply be avoiding a messy foreign entanglement during his bid for re-election? If this were true, it would make him guilty of criminal negligence. Is he the sort of man who would deny innocent and endangered people help simply because greater engagement could complicate his re-election chances? I truly doubt it. Here’s another possible explanation: Perhaps Obama isn’t quite the brilliant foreign-policy strategist his campaign tells us he is. Of course, he has had his successes. I’m not sure you’re aware of this, but Osama bin Laden is dead (killed, apparently, by Obama, who used only a salad fork and a No. 2 pencil). And, despite Republican assertions to the contrary, he has done far more to stymie Iran’s nuclear ambitions than his predecessor, George W. Bush, ever did. Yet Obama’s record in the Middle East suggests that missed opportunities are becoming a White House specialty. Syria is the most obvious example. Assad is a prime supporter of terrorism (as opposed to Qaddafi, who had retired from terrorism sponsorship by the time his people rose up against him), and his regime represents Iran’s only meaningful Arab ally. The overriding concern of the Obama administration in the Middle East is the defanging of Iran. Nothing would isolate Iran -- and its Lebanese proxy, Hezbollah -- more than the removal of the Assad regime and its replacement by a government drawn from Syria’s Sunni majority. Ensuring that Muslim extremists don’t dominate the next Syrian government is another compelling reason to increase U.S. involvement. ‘Weak,’ ‘Feckless’ Yet all we have from Obama is passivity, which is a recurring theme in the administration’s approach to the Middle East. So is “aggressive hedging,” a term used by the Brookings Institution’s Shadi Hamid to describe Obama’s strange reluctance to clearly choose sides in the uprisings of the Arab Spring. “There’s a widespread perception in the region that Obama is a weak, somewhat feckless president,” Hamid, who runs the Brookings Doha Center, told me. “Bush may have been hated, but he was also feared, and what we’ve learned in the Middle East is that fear, sometimes at least, can be a good thing. Obama’s aggressive hedging has alienated both sides of the Arab divide. Autocrats, particularly in the Gulf, think Obama naively supports Arab revolutionaries, while Arab protesters and revolutionaries seem to think the opposite.” Leaders across the Middle East don’t take Obama’s threats seriously. Neither Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu nor the Arab leaders of the Gulf countries believe he’ll act militarily against Iran’s nuclear program in his second term. Obama’s handling of Middle East peace negotiations couldn’t be characterized as passive; they could, however, be described as thoughtless. Obama publicly demanded that Netanyahu freeze settlement growth on the West Bank. When Netanyahu only partially and temporarily complied, Obama, in reaction, did nothing. Obama was wrong to draw a line in the sand over settlements, which are a derivative issue (if the Israelis and Palestinians settle their borders, the settlement issue will also be solved). But because he made it an issue without a thought to follow-up, he managed to freeze the peace process. From the Arab perspective, Obama didn’t carry through on a stated policy. This didn’t help his reputation. “Netanyahu and other Israeli leaders have run roughshod over Obama, embarrassing and undercutting him,” Hamid said. “They simply don’t believe that Obama will do anything about it.”</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349237291281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 00:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349237396107-2</Id><Topic><Title>Hunt for Obama’s Middle East Policy Comes Up Empty</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349237291281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 00:08:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Note: “Bush may have been hated, but he was also feared, and what we’ve learned in the Middle East is that fear, sometimes at least, can be a good thing. Obama’s aggressive hedging has alienated both sides of the Arab divide. Autocrats, particularly in the Gulf, think Obama naively supports Arab revolutionaries, while Arab protesters and revolutionaries seem to think the opposite.”</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349237396107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 00:09:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349238250166-3</Id><Title>Obamao lies again - as always</Title><Msg>U.S. had early indications Libya attack tied to organized militants (Reuters) - Within hours of last month's attacks on U.S. diplomatic facilities in Benghazi, Libya, President Barack Obama's administration received about a dozen intelligence reports suggesting militants connected to al Qaeda were involved, three government sources said. Despite these reports, in public statements and private meetings, top U.S. officials spent nearly two weeks highlighting intelligence suggesting that the attacks were spontaneous protests against an anti-Muslim film, while playing down the involvement of organized militant groups. It was not until last Friday that Director of National Intelligence James Clapper's office issued an unusual public statement, which described how the picture that intelligence agencies presented to U.S. policymakers had "evolved" into an acknowledgement that the attacks were "deliberate and organized" and "carried out by extremists." The existence of the early reports appears to raise fresh questions about the Obama administration's public messaging about the attack as it seeks to fend off Republican charges that the White House failed to prevent a terrorist strike that left a U.S. ambassador and three others dead. "What we're seeing now is the picture starting to develop that it wasn't a problem with the intelligence that was given, it's what they did with the intelligence that they were given," Representative Mike Rogers, chairman of the House of Representatives Intelligence Committee, said in an interview on Tuesday. "This picture is still a little fuzzy but it is starting to come into focus and it appears that there were, very early on, some indications that there was jihadist participation in the event," he said. The Obama administration has strongly defended its public accounts of what happened in Benghazi, and said its understanding has evolved as additional information came in. "At every step of the way, the administration has based its public statements on the best assessments that were provided by the intelligence community. As the intelligence community learned more information, they updated Congress and the American people on it," said White House spokesman Jay Carney. Some officials said U.S. spy agencies tried to avoid drawing premature conclusions about how the violence began and who organized it. "Unless you have very good reports that strongly suggest who was behind the attack for sure, it is prudent to be careful, because placing emphasis publicly, even tentatively, on any one group or groups too soon can lead everyone down the wrong path," said one official, who spoke on condition of anonymity. Republicans have sought to make the shifting stories told by administration officials about the attack, and inadequate security precautions at the U.S. diplomatic site in Libya, a major issue in the presidential campaign leading up to the November 6 election. Two House Republicans said they would hold Congress' first hearing on the matter on October 10. CIA TALKING POINTS The stream of intelligence flowing into Washington within hours of the Benghazi attacks contained data from communications intercepts and U.S. informants, which were then fashioned into polished initial assessments for policymakers. Officials familiar with them said they contained evidence that members of a militant faction, Ansar al-Sharia, as well as al Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb, or AQIM, were involved in the assaults. The report did not allege the attacks were a reaction to the anti-Muslim film, but acknowledged it was possible that the attackers sought to use an outbreak of violence in Cairo over the film, which insulted the Prophet Mohammad, as a pretext for attacks. One official said initial reporting suggested militants had begun planning attacks on U.S. targets in Benghazi before September 11, but may well have decided to use the protests as a pretext for moving forward that day. Reuters reported on September 12, citing U.S. government officials, that the attacks may have been planned and organized in advance, and that members of Ansar al-Sharia and AQIM may have been involved. Yet on September 15, administration officials, relying upon what they said was other information from intelligence agencies, circulated to members of Congress a set of talking points prepared by the CIA that purported to summarize what U.S. intelligence knew. The talking points said: "The currently available information suggests that the demonstrations in Benghazi were spontaneously inspired by the protests at the U.S. embassy in Cairo and evolved into a direct assault against the U.S. diplomatic post in Benghazi and subsequently its annex." The document then noted that "There are indications that extremists participated in the violent demonstrations." It contained no further elaboration. The talking points reflected information that White House officials and Congress were given in closed-door intelligence briefings in the days immediately after the attacks. In one such session, CIA director David Petraeus used lines which paralleled the talking points. "It seems increasingly clear that the briefings provided to Congress and the public about the Benghazi attack were at best incomplete and at worst misleading," Senator Saxby Chambliss, the Republican vice chair of the Senate Intelligence Committee, told Reuters. "Within hours of the attack, intelligence assessments highlighted the role of al Qaeda-affiliated terrorists, but the administration focused instead on a video that appears to have had little, if anything, to do with the violence in Benghazi," Chambliss said. Susan Rice, the U.S. ambassador to the United Nations, also appeared to use information contained in the talking points on Sunday September 16 when she made five appearances on TV talk shows. On CBS' "Face the Nation," Rice said the Benghazi attacks were triggered by a "hateful video," which prompted a "spontaneous protest" that "spun from there into something more violent." Regarding militants, she said only that it was "clear that there were extremist elements that joined in and escalated the violence." Congressman Peter King, a New York Republican, has urged Rice to resign over the issue, a call the State Department has rejected. A ROLE FOR ANTI-MUSLIM FILM? The Daily Beast website reported last week that in the hours after the attack, U.S. intelligence agencies monitored communications between members of Ansar al-Sharia and AQIM. Ansar al-Sharia operatives "bragged" about their attack on the U.S. diplomatic mission and acted as if they were "subordinate" to AQIM, it quoted a U.S. official as saying. It now appears questionable that the anti-Muslim film, which sparked a violent protest against the U.S. Embassy in Cairo earlier on September 11, played a significant role in the Benghazi attack. Some U.S. officials have not foreclosed that possibility. But Rogers, the House Intelligence Committee chairman, said he had never seen intelligence reporting to support such an assertion. "I haven't seen anything that shows that the intelligence community said on the day of, or the immediate day following, that this was a spontaneous event," he said.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349238250166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 00:24:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349241110128-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obamao lies again - as always</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349238250166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 00:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumbocrap party has been the biggest joke of the world. All should be impeached and jailed for treason.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1349241110128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 01:11:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349241171871-5</Id><Topic><Title>Hunt for Obama’s Middle East Policy Comes Up Empty</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349237291281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 00:08:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba and dumbo party suck $hit.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1349241171871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 01:12:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349263423417-6</Id><Title>DID YOU SEE HANNITY TAPE ON OBAMA !!! OBAMA HATES WHITE FOLKS ! HE EVENCHANGE HIS DILECT TO SOUND NORE BLACK!! HE CALL</Title><Msg>The illegal immigrats - mexican rats .....obama only care for the black folks !11 guys you better think about that +++++++++++++++obama a muslim</Msg><Username>savingamerica219</Username><Timestamp>1349263423417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272979407-7</Id><Title>Mitt armed with Quiver full of Zingers!!</Title><Msg>Watch this #$%$-bag shoot himself on to his foot tonight.</Msg><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349272979407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274958239-8</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt armed with Quiver full of Zingers!!</Title><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349272979407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:02:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney does not need zingers. He needs a lie detector. Anyone who does not understand that is void of the ability to reason and, should not enjoy the right of voting.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1349274958239</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:35:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349276110652-9</Id><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending September 28, 2012</Title><Msg>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending September 28, 2012 U.S. crude oil refinery inputs averaged 14.8 million barrels per day during the week ending September 28, 222 thousand barrels per day above the previous week’s average. Refineries operated at 88.2 percent of their operable capacity last week. Gasoline production increased last week, averaging 9.1 million barrels per day. Distillate fuel production decreased last week, averaging 4.6 million barrels per day. U.S. crude oil imports averaged 8.1 million barrels per day last week, up by 511 thousand barrels per day from the previous week. Over the last four weeks, crude oil imports have averaged 8.5 million barrels per day, 295 thousand barrels per day below the same four-week period last year. Total motor gasoline imports (including both finished gasoline and gasoline blending components) last week averaged 573 thousand barrels per day. Distillate fuel imports averaged 58 thousand barrels per day last week. U.S. commercial crude oil inventories (excluding those in the Strategic Petroleum Reserve) decreased by 0.5 million barrels from the previous week. At 364.7 million barrels, U.S. crude oil inventories are above the upper limit of the average range for this time of year. Total motor gasoline inventories increased by 0.1 million barrels last week and are in the lower half of the average range. Finished gasoline inventories increased while blending components inventories decreased last week. Distillate fuel inventories decreased by 3.7 million barrels last week and are near the lower limit of the average range for this time of year. Propane/propylene inventories increased by 1.3 million barrels last week and are above the upper limit of the average range. Total commercial petroleum inventories decreased by 2.4 million barrels last week. Total products supplied over the last four-week period have averaged 18.3 million barrels per day, down by 3.3 percent compared to the similar period last year. Over the last four weeks, motor gasoline product supplied has averaged about 8.7 million barrels per day, down by 2.5 percent from the same period last year. Distillate fuel product supplied has averaged about 3.7 million barrels per day over the last four weeks, down by 4.5 percent from the same period last year. Jet fuel product supplied is 1.7 percent higher over the last four weeks compared to the same four-week period last year. Data Overview (Combined Table 1 and Table 9) eia --------------------------------------- BLOOMBERG DOLLAR INDEX SPOT bloomberg --------------------------------------- Energy Futures Prices Below you may find all the futures prices &amp; quotes for: Crude Oil, Heating Oil, Gasoline RBOB, Natural Gas, ICE Brent Crude Oil, Ethanol (E) and more. Real Time Streaming Futures Quotes (CFDs) forexpros ---------------------------------------- e85 prices e85prices ---------------------------------------- gas buddy gasbuddy ---------------------------------------- * Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production ethanolrfa * Usually updated late Thursday afternoon. URLs provided for you at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349276110652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349276366789-10</Id><Topic><Title>New XOM Investors Must See</Title><Username>powersschultz893</Username><Timestamp>1349270450791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:20:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think this is a great resource for any one looking for good reliable information. Don't listen to the bashers, get your own information and make your own educated decisions.</Msg><Username>vargasboris55</Username><Timestamp>1349276366789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349285663276-11</Id><Title>America met 83% of its energy needs in the first six months of the year!</Title><Msg>The boom in oil and natural gas production helped the U.S. cut its reliance on imported fuel. America met 83 percent of its energy needs in the first six months of the year, department data show. If the trend goes on through 2012, it will be the highest level of self-sufficiency since 1991.</Msg><Username>think5pm</Username><Timestamp>1349285663276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349286757562-12</Id><Title>Study finds a LCFS in Minn. would create nearly 32,500 jobs</Title><Msg>Study finds a LCFS in Minn. would create nearly 32,500 jobs By Erin Voegele | October 02, 2012 A study recently published by the Political Economy Research Institute at the University of Massachusetts, Amherst explores some of the economic impacts of establishing a low carbon fuel standard (LCFS) in Minnesota. The study, titled “The Employment Impacts of a Low-Carbon Fuel Standard for Minnesota,” found that enacting a LCFS in Minnesota could create nearly 32,500 jobs when analyzed through 2025. The study evaluates three possible scenarios. The first assumes no change to the distribution of transportation fuel consumption. The second assumes that the fuel mix will change in response to the federal renewable fuel standard (RFS). The third assumes a more aggressive change in the fuel mix in response to the establishment of a statewide LCFS. According to the report, the research team has estimated the employment that would result from building the capacity to produce each of these fuel mixes as well as the ongoing employment from actual production activities. In all scenarios, employment increased in response to increased consumption of transportation fuels. However, the report states that employment increases the least under the first scenario, and the most under the LCFS scenario. Under the baseline scenario, one new corn ethanol plant would need to be installed within the state, along with 33 new ethanol blender pumps. A total of 1,300 new job-years would be created through direct, indirect and induced means. A job-year is one full-time position for one year. According to the report, the RFS scenario would lead to the development of six cellulosic ethanol plants in Minnesota, while 30 percent of current ethanol plants would be retrofit to utilize biomass to produce process heat. The scenario would also lead to the installation of 2,726 ethanol blender pumps, with at least one installed at every Minnesota refueling station. The RFS scenario would lead to the creation of nearly 13,000 direct, indirect and induced job-years. These job years would come from ethanol production and distribution, biodiesel production and distribution and the development of charging stations for electric vehicles. The LCFS scenario would lead to the development of six new corn ethanol plants and 10 cellulosic ethanol plants. All current ethanol plants would also be retrofit to generate process heat from biomass feedstock. The scenario would also lead to the development of 2,726 ethanol blender pumps, with approximately 32,500 direct, indirect and induced job-years created. These jobs years would also come from ethanol production and distribution, biodiesel production and distribution and the development of charging stations for electric vehicles. A full copy of the report can be downloaded from the PERI website. ethanolproducer --------------------------------------------------------------------------------- ... 19 pages ... THE EMPLOYMENT IMPACTS OF A LOW-CARBON FUEL STANDARD FOR MINNESOTA Heidi Garrett-Peltier Political Economy Research Institute University of Massachusetts, Amherst September 2012 umass URL at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349286757562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349287438689-13</Id><Title>Oil went down before debate starts</Title><Msg>LOL!!!!LOL!!!</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1349287438689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349287811224-14</Id><Title>Presidential debate could shed light on energy issues</Title><Msg>Presidential debate could shed light on energy issues By ANDREW RESTUCCIA and DARREN GOODE | 10/3/12 4:27 AM EDT Wednesday’s presidential debate offers one of the final chances to pin down the candidates on the energy issues that have loomed so large in this campaign — from gasoline prices and green jobs to the Keystone XL pipeline and Solyndra. On some of the biggest issues, President Barack Obama and Mitt Romney have been content to evade the specifics. Obama, for example, has never offered a detailed response to more than 18 months of Republican attacks about how his administration handled the failed $535 million Solyndra loan guarantee — aside from his defense that all decisions were based on the “merits.” And Romney has left plenty of wiggle room in his shifting stances through the years on what, if anything, the government should do about global warming or incentives for renewable energy. Debate moderator Jim Lehrer could also explore the wide gulfs between the nominees’ competing energy visions — Obama’s emphasis on green jobs and his call for repealing oil industry tax breaks versus Romney’s promises to dramatically expand oil drilling and repeal Environmental Protection Agency regulations. In some areas, the candidates’ rhetoric has been quite similar, including their discussions of energy independence and an all-of-the-above energy policy — even though they disagree on what exactly those words mean. And although Romney has pledged to approve Keystone on Day One of his presidency, plenty of observers expect that the pipeline would win approval in a second Obama term, as well. So what should Lehrer ask Wednesday night? POLITICO compiled this list of suggestions with the help of environmentalists, industry representatives, independent experts, campaign surrogates and congressional staff from both parties. The debate’s setting in Colorado could offer an ideal backdrop: It’s a politically purple bellwether state that has been a hotbed for green energy as well as oil and gas. 1. Climate change Questions for Romney: How do you explain the seemingly dramatic shifts in your position on climate change since you were governor of Massachusetts? As governor, you worked to reduce greenhouse gas emissions and opposed a coal-fired power plant because it “kills people.” And you initially supported a regional cap-and-trade program although you ultimately declined to sign on to the program. Today, you oppose cap and trade and have criticized Obama’s efforts to reduce greenhouse gas emissions from coal-fired power plants. What specifically would you do to address climate change? Questions for Obama: Your administration has proposed a climate change regulation for new power plants that opponents say will contribute to the death of the coal industry. How do you defend the regulations? And will your administration propose additional measures to address climate change in a second term, including rules to limit greenhouse gas emissions from existing power plants? Lastly, if it were politically feasible, would you again pursue cap-and-trade legislation? Question for both: The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration says July was the hottest month in the contiguous United States since record-keeping began in 1895. Do you see this and other extreme weather as the result of climate change? 2. Renewable energy Questions for Romney: Your campaign has said you oppose the extension of the production tax credit for wind energy, which expires at the end of the year. But you have never discussed wanting to kill the tax credit in interviews or on the campaign trail. Why not? Backers say ending the tax credit would cost thousands of jobs, many in key battleground states, such as Iowa and Colorado. Are they wrong? Questions for Obama: Can you explain what exactly went wrong with Solyndra, and would your administration approve that $535 million loan guarantee if you could do it over again? Why did your energy secretary override objections from staffers at the Treasury Department and Office of Management and Budget to prop up the company despite its financial problems? Also, why is your administration falling short — so far — on your promise to create 5 million green jobs over 10 years? 3. Regulations Questions for Romney: As president, how would you balance economic concerns with those affecting public health? Are there any existing or pending EPA regulations that you believe should move forward unabated? Which ones should go back to the drawing board or never be implemented? Questions for Obama: When do the environment and public health come first in enacting regulations, and when should worries about jobs prevail? Which proposed regulations from your first term did you think would have gone too far? What regulations would be priorities in your second term? 4. Oil drilling and Keystone Questions for Romney: You want to vastly expand oil and gas drilling, but what public lands or waters, if any, would you keep off limits? How would you ensure that offshore oil and gas drilling is done safely? Would you keep in place the offshore drilling safety and environmental standards the Department of the Interior has implemented since the Deepwater Horizon disaster as well as the Obama administration’s reorganization of the scandal-ridden Minerals Management Service? Questions for Obama: TransCanada has submitted a new Keystone route for consideration, and you have already approved the southern route connecting Oklahoma to Texas. Aren’t you essentially signaling that you would approve Keystone’s northern portion early on in your second term? Given the length of time it has taken to make final decisions on both Keystone and Shell Oil’s Arctic drilling plans, isn’t it simply taking too long for these kinds of projects to win approval? How would your administration improve oil and natural gas production specifically on federal lands? 5. Hydraulic fracturing and the natural gas boom Question for Romney: Should the federal government serve any role in ensuring hydraulic fracturing is done safely, especially in environmentally sensitive areas, such as those in Colorado? Question for Obama: Will you expand federal regulation of fracking? 6. All of the above Questions for both: You express support for increased domestic oil and gas production as well as recognizing large benefits from energy efficiency and renewable energy. How specifically would you compel a divided Congress to act? Both of you have talked about an all-of-the-above energy strategy, but the president has proposed regulations that critics say would kill the coal industry, and Romney has stated positions undercutting green power. How do you reconcile these inconsistencies to develop a long-term energy policy? With major tax reform looming as an issue in the next Congress, what energy tax policies will you pursue to keep energy-related job growth going in the next four years? politico</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349287811224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349288706974-15</Id><Title>Interior Department seeks climate change advisers - help steer its scientific work on the effects of climate change on natural resources</Title><Msg>Interior Department seeks climate change advisers By Ben Geman - 10/03/12 10:11 AM ET The Interior Department is creating a panel of outside experts to help steer its scientific work on the effects of climate change on natural resources. The department, in a notice to be published Thursday, will seek nominations for the new, roughly 25-member “Advisory Committee on Climate Change and Natural Resource Science.” The experts will advise the U.S. Geological Survey’s National Climate Change and Wildlife Science Center (NCCWSC) and the Interior's network of regional Climate Science Centers. The notice, to be published in Thursday’s Federal Register, states that the committee will include members from federal, state and local governments, scientific and conservation groups, academics, Native American tribes, landowners, and businesses. The group’s mission is to provide input on the “contents of a national strategy identifying key science priorities to advance management of natural resources in the face of climate change.” It will also provide advice on ensuring scientific integrity and quality of the NCCWSC’s work. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349288706974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349289281458-16</Id><Title>How's this for an RFS overhaul idea?</Title><Msg>How's this for an RFS overhaul idea? The American Petroleum Institute wants to overhaul the RFS, but under one hypothetical scenario, it should be careful what it wishes for By Ron Kotrba | October 03, 2012 Late last week, I was on an American Petroleum Institute media call organized to discuss biodiesel RIN integrity issues and the renewable fuel standard. A short introduction was given by API’s Bob Greco before the floor was opened up for questions. In his introduction, Greco, as expected, said the RFS program is becoming “increasingly unrealistic and unworkable.” He spoke of ethanol blend walls, and how the RFS is “forcing” more biofuel into the market than vehicles can handle; nonexistent cellulosic volumes; and the increased biodiesel mandate for 2013. “The agency has upped the biodiesel volume requirements above what the statute requires, which will hike refiner costs by hundreds of millions of dollars and could impact consumers,” Greco told reporters from some of the largest media outlets in the country, including the New York Times. “The RFS program needs an overhaul. That will take congressional action to accomplish. While legislation has been introduced to address the RIN problem, so refiners can begin purchasing RIN credits in 2013 knowing they are valid, EPA could make that unnecessary if it simply got to work and fixed the problem itself.” Logic tells me that as biodiesel volumes increase, oil volumes decrease. That is the whole point of the RFS—to reduce fossil fuel consumption for the noble causes of preserving the environment, increasing national security and promoting domestic job creation—right? The 2013 biodiesel mandate increase of 280 million gallons (from 1 billion gallons to 1.28 billion gallons), while hugely important for the biodiesel industry, is a drop in the bucket compared to the 200 billion gallons a year of gasoline and diesel that oil companies refine. That equates to just over a tenth of one percent (0.14 percent). If a biodiesel RIN is, say, $1, and it takes 1.5 RINs to equal a gallon of biodiesel, then the oil companies are buying credits for $1.50 to replace a gallon of diesel fuel they would otherwise have sold you for $4 a gallon. This is how ruthlessly competitive the oil companies are. They will not tolerate it when just a tenth of a percent of their market is replaced by a product that boosts incomes for domestic farmers, manufacturers, grease collectors and businessmen. The petroleum lobby continuously goes on and on about how unjust and unfair and penalizing RFS is to oil refiners. They say it needs an overhaul. Well how about this? Let’s overhaul the RFS to get rid of RINs altogether and force the refiners to purchase wet biodiesel gallons—if they want an overhaul, then maybe that’s how it should be done. If they want to incessantly complain about the cost of purchasing biodiesel RINs and the financial liability they now hold for buying invalid RINs, and use their immensely powerful influence to convince government that it is on the wrong track by wanting cleaner air, increased national security and more jobs at home, then instead of overhauling the program in a way they find desirable, maybe it should be reprogrammed to force obligated parties to buy physical product. I wonder how many millions of dollars the oil lobby spends on trying to eliminate the RFS from existence. On the call, I had the chance to ask Greco a question. “Under any new rules, whether done legislatively or administratively, who does API think should be held liable if an affirmative defense is given and the petroleum companies, the obligated parties, are not required to replace any invalid RINs—would that be any third-party verifiers or the faulty RIN generator itself, and if so, what if the faulty RIN generator, for instance, in jail or out of business? Who should be held monetarily liable, if not the oil companies?” Greco responded, saying, “We think ultimately the provider of the RINs ought to be held liable for providing faulty RINs. They are the fraudulent actor in that situation and ought to be held accountable for that. We don’t feel that the oil companies should be penalized twice for purchasing a RIN and then being required to purchase yet another one to make it whole.” I did not feel that Greco answered the question I asked, so I followed up more directly. “If the RIN generator is out of business, does API believe that the third-party verifier should hold liability?” After hesitation, Greco said, “That’s a possible approach. We need to better understand the way EPA is looking at this. Clearly there are more parties involved in the RIN transaction than the biodiesel producer and the refiner. These RINs are being stripped off and can be traded multiple times so there are multiple parties involved in this. But our bottom line is that the refiner purchases a RIN in good faith and follows the process that EPA has signed off on, then that party should not be held liable—we should be provided an affirmative defense against holding that invalid RIN.” While the petroleum industry is fiercely cutthroat, the biodiesel RIN assurance market is also very competitive. While the outcome is still largely unclear, someone has to be held accountable if the fraudulent actor is out of business or in prison. If not, then the intention of the RFS is missed and we end up back where we started years ago: solely at the mercy of Big Oil without any long-term plan to be otherwise. In a recent article published by Biodiesel Magazine, EcoEngineers raised the possibility of RIN insurance. But if you are in the third-party verification market—and there are many out there—are you prepared to be liable for bad RINs that oil companies purchase? biodieselmagazine</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349289281458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349289636101-17</Id><Topic><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending September 28, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349276110652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:55:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This Week In Petroleum October 3, 2012 Next Release: October 11, 2012 U.S. Oil Production Continues to Grow U.S. oil production, including crude oil and lease condensate, has grown steadily since 2008, a change from the two decades of declines before 2008. This growth has been driven mainly by increased production from various tight (very low permeability) formations. (Permeability measures how well liquids and gases can flow through open spaces in rocks.) Horizontal drilling combined with hydraulic fracturing have allowed exploration and production (E&amp;P) companies to access commercial volumes of oil from rock formations that are less permeable than those found in conventional formations. The U.S. Energy Information Administration (EIA) expects that development of tight formations will lead to continuing significant increases in U.S. oil production in the coming years. Three key basins with tight formations have been the largest contributors to U.S. oil production growth: the Permian Basin in West Texas and southeastern New Mexico; the Western Gulf Basin in southern Texas, which includes the Eagle Ford shale; and the Williston Basin, which extends over parts of North Dakota, South Dakota, and Montana and which includes the Bakken formation (Figure 1). Since January 2009, North Dakota's crude oil production has more than tripled from an average of less than 190,000 barrels per day (bbl/d) to nearly 675,000 bbl/d in July 2012, based on North Dakota Department of Mineral Resources statistics (Figure 2). This growth makes North Dakota the second largest oil producing state, behind Texas and ahead of both Alaska and California. The Bakken tight oil formation has accounted for nearly all of the new production in North Dakota. EIA forecasts total Williston Basin production, including North Dakota and Montana, will approach 1.1 million bbl/d by January 2014. Texas oil production has increased about 770,000 bbl/d since January 2009, and in June 2012 averaged 1.9 million bbl/d. Texas has seen the largest volumetric increase of any state. The Permian Basin, which was already producing significant quantities of conventional oil, has experienced increases in oil production from both conventional and shale plays. EIA forecasts Western Gulf Basin production to rise to almost 930,000 bbl/d and Permian Basin production to reach 1.55 million bbl/d by January 2014. The shift of the U.S. drilling rig fleet away from dry natural gas to oil and wet natural gas suggests that the production of oil and other liquids will continue to climb. E&amp;P companies are making significant capital investments in horizontal drilling rigs and deploying them to tight oil plays. Many existing rigs with horizontal-drilling capabilities are being redeployed from plays rich in dry natural gas to those that can produce crude oil and other liquids that have a significantly greater value under current market conditions. The total number of rigs drilling for oil increased 76 percent from an average of 801 in February 2011 to an average of 1,409 in September 2012, based on detailed weekly active rig count data provided by Baker Hughes Incorporated. The number of rigs drilling horizontal wells has grown even more rapidly, increasing from 362 to 823, over the same period. September 2012 data show that a weekly average of 58 percent of the entire U.S. onshore rig fleet was drilling horizontal wells, compared to 45 percent in February 2011. Because horizontal drilling is often associated with tight formations, it is apparent that an increasing number of producers are targeting tight geology. The geographical distribution of the rig fleet also suggests that E&amp;P companies are directing more resources to drilling for tight oil. In February 2011, North Dakota and Texas already were leading all other states in average number of rigs targeting oil, averaging 150 and 390 per week, respectively. The average weekly oil rig count increased to 182 in North Dakota and 692 in Texas in September 2012. These two states, which produce the majority of the oil from the three key basins containing tight formations with liquids, account for more than half the net increase in rigs over this time period. Based on this information, a large proportion of new and existing drilling rigs are expected to be allocated towards liquids in North Dakota and Texas, and many of these rigs likely will be drilling horizontal wells. Gasoline and diesel fuel prices decrease for a second consecutive week The U.S. average retail price of regular gasoline decreased two cents last week to $3.80 per gallon, 37 cents per gallon higher than last year at this time. Prices decreased in all regions of the Nation except the West Coast, where the price was up two cents to $4.08 per gallon. The Rocky Mountain price decreased less than a penny to remain at $3.77 per gallon. The largest decrease came in the Gulf Coast, where the price is $3.56 per gallon, down five cents from last week. The East Coast and Midwest prices both decreased three cents to $3.80 per gallon and $3.78 per gallon, respectively. The national average diesel fuel price decreased less than a penny to $4.08 per gallon, 33 cents per gallon higher than last year at this time. Prices decreased in all regions of the Nation except the Gulf Coast, where the price is up less than a penny to remain at $4.00 per gallon. The Rocky Mountain and West Coast prices were both down two cents to $4.21 and $4.30 per gallon, respectively. The East Coast price is $4.08 per gallon, a penny less than last week. The Midwest price decreased less than a penny to $4.01 per gallon. Propane stocks show another strong build Last week, total U.S. inventories of propane received a large build of 1.3 million barrels to end at 75.6 million barrels, 18.1 million barrels (32 percent) higher than the same week last year. The bulk of the build occurred in the Gulf Coast region, which added 0.9 million barrels. Elsewhere, Midwest regional stocks grew by 0.4 million barrels and Rocky Mountain/West Coast stocks added 0.2 million barrels. East Coast regional inventories fell by 0.1 million barrels. Propylene non-fuel-use inventories represented 6.0 percent of total propane inventories. Heating Oil and Propane Prices The weekly heating oil and propane price section containing data for October 1 will not be published on October 3 due to system difficulties. The data for October 1 will be released along with the data for October 8 on October 11, 2012. eia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349289636101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349291247239-18</Id><Title>83% of what we need for oil is now drilled in the USA!!! Who cares about Iran?!!!</Title><Msg>New reports says we are closing in on 100% of what we need in the USA!!!! BYE BYE ARABS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>think5pm</Username><Timestamp>1349291247239</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349299831584-19</Id><Title>When back to $100, like it was 5 years ago?</Title><Msg>stock split would be nice!</Msg><Username>metalmeister79</Username><Timestamp>1349299831584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:30:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349300550769-20</Id><Title>If Obama wins the debate....</Title><Msg>....conservatives will syas he lost the debate.</Msg><Username>luke_oflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1349300550769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349300650383-21</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama wins the debate....</Title><Username>luke_oflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1349300550769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:42:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a bunch of crooked liars are the Republicans</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1349300650383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349303834674-22</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama wins the debate....</Title><Username>luke_oflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1349300550769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:42:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lies will not win the debate. Your thoughts are hypothetical, delusional and, typical of the media that you, no doubt, are a slave to. Try watching with an open mind and, consider your future, if the thought has ever occurred to you. Your vote is important. Cast it with your brain. Look beyond the spoon-fed mandacity that will eventually destroy you and yours..............And, mine.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1349303834674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349306528476-23</Id><Title>Exxon plant in Northern Texas is on fire.</Title><Msg>Smoke everywhere.</Msg><Username>futurenetsoft</Username><Timestamp>1349306528476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349306975992-24</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon plant in Northern Texas is on fire.</Title><Username>futurenetsoft</Username><Timestamp>1349306528476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the exxon plant is int the Texas City -- Beaumont Tx location ...via Fox News... T</Msg><Username>emmachatman</Username><Timestamp>1349306975992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349307714975-25</Id><Title>Enbridge says B.C. premier declined offer to meet over benefits of pipeline</Title><Msg>Enbridge says B.C. premier declined offer to meet over benefits of pipeline Dene Moore, Today, Canadian Press VANCOUVER - While the British Columbia government remains locked in a dispute with neighbouring Alberta over revenues from the proposed Northern Gateway pipeline, the province has declined offers from Enbridge (TSX:ENB) to discuss benefits. Al Monaco, chief executive officer of the Calgary-based company, said Wednesday that the $6-billion pipeline is a strategic development for all of Canada. B.C. is "quite legitimately" insisting on criteria such as First Nations involvement and environment safety before it will approve the project, he said, but so far has not requested a meeting with Enbridge about concerns over the revenues and potential benefits of the pipeline. In fact, Monaco said the province has turned down the company's offers for discussions. "My understanding it that it's not their desire to meet with us at this point in time, but we remain open to sitting down with the premier, as we would other members of the government or, frankly, whomever we need to," Monaco told reporters in a conference call following an investor conference. There are many benefits to B.C. from the project, Monaco said: it would be the largest energy project in B.C. history and would generate hundreds of millions of dollars in spinoffs, taxes and jobs. "As to whether or not there are any additional benefits beyond that, that's something that the governments I know are, hopefully, discussing now or in the future. We would certainly be glad to be sitting at the table in that discussion but at this point we haven't seen that opportunity," Monaco said. Premier Christy Clark has outlined five criteria that must be met before B.C. will allow construction of the pipeline to deliver diluted bitumen from the Alberta oil sands to a tanker port proposed for Kitimat, B.C., to transport crude to Asian markets. The project faces opposition due mostly to the risk of a spill on land or from the tankers off the B.C. coast, and Clark has said the project must include world-leading response plans for a marine or land oil spill. It must also address aboriginal and treaty rights and include First Nations participation. Monaco said he believes Enbridge can deliver on those demands. But Clark said B.C. also must get a greater share of the fiscal and economic benefits from the pipeline than is currently on the table, to reflect the greater risk to the environment for the westernmost province. Alberta says sharing royalties from the project is a non-starter, and Clark has responded by suggesting B.C. could withhold hydro and regulatory approvals to press the issue. Clark was not immediately available to comment, but her spokesman, Mike Morton, said it would be inappropriate for the premier to meet with Enbridge officials until the review on the proposed pipeline is complete. Morton said this discussion has to take place between B.C., Alberta and the federal government. Clark reiterated in a speech to the University of Calgary's School of Public Policy on Tuesday that B.C. could make things difficult for the project. "British Columbia has the power to grant or withhold 60 permits," she said. "British Columbia's power would be required to power up the pipeline from B.C. Hydro, a Crown corporation. There's a whole number of things the British Columbia government could do and certainly if this project was forced through without meeting the five conditions, it wouldn't be just the British Columbia government that would be in court. It would be every First Nation across the line." The project is currently undergoing a joint environment assessment review. That panel has until the end of 2013 to complete its report and recommendations. Monaco told an investor conference earlier that the controversial project benefits the entire country. "The bottom line on Gateway I think is this: It is a highly strategic project to Canada and there is general agreement that accessing the Asian market is in our interest," he said. "As a resource driven economy, there's no question that Canada needs access to tidewater and the project is going to generate billions in terms of spinoffs, thousands of jobs and benefits to communities." It could help boost the price Canadian oil producers see because without access to Asian markets, Canadian producers will face a further discounting in oil prices compared with international benchmarks caused by a supply glut at a key storage hub in Cushing, Okla. The glut has caused oil priced at Cushing — the WTI benchmark — to trade at a discount to other international benchmarks. "I don't think that is a tenable situation in the longer term," he said. In addition to the Enbridge project, Kinder Morgan has proposed its own $4.1-billion Trans Mountain project that would expand an existing pipeline from Alberta to the Vancouver area. thetyee</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349307714975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349310130650-26</Id><Topic><Title>New XOM Investors Must See</Title><Username>powersschultz893</Username><Timestamp>1349270450791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:20:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was really looking for some great news. Now I found it.</Msg><Username>espinoza.flynn43</Username><Timestamp>1349310130650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349311309108-27</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama wins the debate....</Title><Username>luke_oflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1349300550769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:42:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lies will twist the perception of who won the debate........idiot. Fox will tell you who won. Liberals will be making up their own mind.</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1349311309108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349319465203-28</Id><Title>Exxon stock drops hard tomorrow - Texas fire, oil plunge and higher taxes coming</Title><Msg>Exxon Fighting Fire at Baytown Refinery Understand its a massive fire. Could we drop to $87 a share or lower tomorrow??</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1349319465203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321099220-29</Id><Title>You can't beat Obama...</Title><Msg>He has 100% of the black and Hispanic vote. That's more than 50%. Romney won the debate, but it's just a waste of time. I think Obama was #$%$ off at Lehrer's incompetence.</Msg><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1349321099220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321458975-30</Id><Title>Can you believe Mitt actually admitted that he and the Republicans in Congress tried to block economic recovery !</Title><Msg>#$%$ ? !!!!!</Msg><Username>besttoyou1</Username><Timestamp>1349321458975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321598276-31</Id><Title>ROMNEY "whoops" NOBAMA !! NOBAMA KNOWS NOTHING !!!!!</Title><Msg>....get the fool out of the WHITEHOUSE now !!!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1349321598276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349321725919-32</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama wins the debate....</Title><Username>luke_oflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1349300550769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:42:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Obama lost badly. Even Bill Marr says he did a lousy job along with a lot of the networks - none associated with Fox News. Eat your heart out wahleee boy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349321725919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349321947481-33</Id><Topic><Title>Can you believe Mitt actually admitted that he and the Republicans in Congress tried to block economic recovery !</Title><Username>besttoyou1</Username><Timestamp>1349321458975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:30:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another boring lie. You're desperate wahleee boy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349321947481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:39:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349322591526-34</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon plant in Northern Texas is on fire.</Title><Username>futurenetsoft</Username><Timestamp>1349306528476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fire is out. No injuries.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349322591526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>