<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-13"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347510964413-1</Id><Title>Biofuels supporters buoyed after meetings with lawmakers</Title><Msg>Biofuels supporters buoyed after meetings with lawmakers By Zack Colman - 09/12/12 04:07 PM ET Biofuels supporters who swarmed Capitol Hill offices this week feel confident they have sufficient congressional commitment to preserve a fuel rule critical to the industry. The meetings come after biofuels groups hired a lobby firm to deflect attacks from some lawmakers and livestock and poultry groups against the portion of that rule that buoys corn ethanol production. Tom Buis, the CEO of biofuels industry group Growth Energy, said the “170-some appointments” biofuels proponents held Monday through Wednesday assured him of bipartisan and administration commitment to the renewable fuel standard (RFS). “I think they all came away really, really pleased with the visits,” Buis said of biofuels proponents. “I think people on Capitol Hill understand that this is the only really significant energy policy Congress has had in 40 years.” Buis hinted Wednesday there could be another wave of publicity from biofuels groups in favor of the RFS. That standard, which requires refiners to blend 36 billion gallons of biofuels into traditional transportation fuel by 2022, is credited with jump-starting the biofuels industry. Greenwire reported last week that Growth Energy, the Renewable Fuels Association (RFA) and DuPont all hired lobby firm Glover Park Group to spearhead a blitz backing the corn ethanol portion of the RFS. The story cited industry sources that said Glover Park Group would ask Democratic lawmakers for support. Glover Park Group did not return requests for comment from The Hill. Regarding Growth Energy’s plans, Buis said Wednesday that the group will make a “public announcement when we’re ready.” He denied the developing strategy had a partisan flavor. “Our message is not toward Democrats or Republicans or independents — it’s toward everyone,” Buis said at a Wednesday press conference in response to a question from The Hill. “We’re nonpartisan, we have tremendous support on the Democratic and on the Republican side. ... We don’t want to make it a partisan message.” RFA confirmed Wednesday with The Hill that it had retained Glover Park Group. It disputed reports that it would focus on outreach to Democrats, saying the RFA would work with both parties. Glover Park Group is no stranger to biofuels. The Grocery Manufacturers Association hired the firm to wage a 2008 campaign against corn ethanol, according to federal lobby disclosure records. The corn ethanol portion of the RFS has attracted criticism from lawmakers and the livestock and poultry industries in the wake of this summer's devastating drought. They contend that this year’s blending requirement of 13.2 billion gallons of corn ethanol, combined with drought conditions, has pushed corn prices to record highs. As a result, several governors have asked EPA to temporarily waive the corn ethanol requirement this year. Biofuels groups say that logic is faulty, arguing the drought — not the RFS — has raised prices. They said refiners had already ratcheted down corn ethanol production in response to high prices, and that a chunk of corn harvested for corn ethanol is reused in feed for livestock and poultry. Maintaining the corn ethanol portion of the RFS is crucial to bringing “advanced” biofuels to commercial scale, biofuels industry representatives said Wednesday. Those biofuels will comprise 21 of the total 36 billion gallons the RFS requires for blending by 2022, but they are just now starting to come online. Waiving the corn portion would create instability for advanced biofuels investors, industry representatives said. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347510964413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347523935355-2</Id><Title>Barack Hussein Carter</Title><Msg>Well,you can't sat were weren't warned.Lots of folks said Obama would be another "Carter" and the resemblence is now striking.Like Carter,Obama is lost for ideas on the economy and his mealy-mouthed apologetic foreign policy is actually antagonizing the whackos in the mid-east.They're even attacking embassies ala Carter. If the voters re-elect this failure then the country will deserve what it gets.Apparantly some are going to require an ugly wake up call before they concentrate their minds enough to realize what's going on.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1347523935355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 04:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347530871954-3</Id><Title>nobumba commie</Title><Msg>Watch the movie nobama 2016 and you will know why.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1347530871954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 06:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347531759006-4</Id><Title>U.S. Embassy in Yemen Stormed as Gunfire Heard in Vicinity</Title><Msg>Protesters attempted to storm the U.S. embassy in Sana’a, Yemen two days after four people were killed during an attack on an American diplomatic mission in Libya. Yousef Al-Ahjan, a protester, said he and others managed to breach the first security perimeter. Some of the assailants set two embassy vehicles on fire. Smoke could be seen rising from the vicinity of the embassy compound and gunfire could be heard. Police have cordoned off the area near the embassy preventing all access. Mohammed Ali, a protester who was walking away from the compound area after security forces fired into the air, said he and others were protesting an anti-Islamic video posted on YouTube. The video, which seeks to ridicule Islam’s Prophet Muhammad, also sparked demonstrations in Egypt and Tunisia. Ali also said they want the U.S. ambassador to Yemen expelled. ================================================= The new tighter security in the middle east?</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1347531759006</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 06:22:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347538591528-5</Id><Title>THANK GOD FOR MITT ROMNEY STANDING UP FOR AMERICA WHILE OUR JACK #$%$ PRESIDENT IS</Title><Msg>APOLOGIZINGS</Msg><Username>americafirst120</Username><Timestamp>1347538591528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347541354768-6</Id><Topic><Title>THANK GOD FOR MITT ROMNEY STANDING UP FOR AMERICA WHILE OUR JACK #$%$ PRESIDENT IS</Title><Username>americafirst120</Username><Timestamp>1347538591528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How bout the press heard in open scheming how to trick Romney. These commie c--k suckers should be fired.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347541354768</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:02:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347543704002-7</Id><Title>Joule commissions 1st renewable fuels plant</Title><Msg>Joule commissions 1st renewable fuels plant Boston Business Journal by Kyle Alspach, VC Editor Date: Wednesday, September 12, 2012, 10:21am EDT Enlarge Image Courtesy Joule has commissioned its first fuel production demonstration plant, in Hobbs, N.M., shown here in a rendering. Bedford-based Joule Unlimited has commissioned its first demonstration plant, in New Mexico, where the company aims to prove the commercial readiness of its method for producing low-cost renewable fuels without biomass. The company said its first "SunSprings" demonstration plant, located in Hobbs, N.M., and will start out producing ethanol. The firm has also developed technology for creating renewable diesel fuel, though Joule said it will commercialize ethanol before seeking to bring its diesel fuel to market. Both types of fuel are produced from specially engineered photosynthetic bacteria, waste carbon dioxide, sunlight and water. The production method involves erecting solar converter systems across unused land. Joule says the technology has the potential to decentralize the fuel industry, allowing fuel to be produced wherever the necessary elements are available. The commissioning of the plant is funded by Joule's $70 million third round of funding, announced in January. Joule was founded in 2007 by Flagship Ventures, and has raised at $110 million in funding to date from Flagship and unnamed investors. Joule said it has also formed a subsidiary, Joule Fuels, to "oversee plant deployment and partnerships – from site selection and project development to plant construction and operations – with the immediate goal of commissioning multiple plants worldwide." The full release: Signaling another major step towards commercialization, Joule today announced the commissioning of its first SunSprings™ demonstration plant in Hobbs, New Mexico, where the company will prove its scalable platform for solar fuel production – the first of its kind – using a fraction of the land and capital investment required for algae-derived or agricultural biofuels. Joule aims to show that its uniquely modular system can achieve replicable results whether installed across one or thousands of acres – opening the door to near-term deployment by eliminating scale-up costs and risks that have hamstrung biofuels for years. Unlike sugar-based biofuel producers, Joule directly and continuously converts solar energy into liquid fuels, without costly raw materials, pretreatment or downstream processing. In contrast with algae-based approaches, Joule uses optimized microorganisms that act as living catalysts to produce fuel, rather than first producing biomass and later extracting lipids or sugars for subsequent multi-step conversion into fuel. The SunSprings plant is designed to demonstrate the complete Joule process with its advantages in cost, scale and efficiency, all at the multi-acre scale that directly translates to full scale through modular replication. “This project is the culmination of advances not only in our core technology, but in building a commercial-ready system and engineering a scalable process that are now pilot-tested and prepared for deployment,” said William J. Sims, President and CEO of Joule. “For the first time, we are bringing the tremendous benefits of modular and linear scale to renewable fuel production, which has been notoriously hampered by batch processes, ponds and fermentation tanks that simply cannot scale without more land, more money and unpredictable results. In contrast, we’ve built a low-cost solution that emulates large-scale results and commercial-scale economics without the need for hundreds of acres or hundreds of millions of dollars. With just one module, we will show what’s possible with 100 modules or more – a low-risk, high-return equation with near-term commercial impact.” “A short four years after we began lab operations, we are pleased to reach this important milestone in the company’s development,” said Noubar Afeyan, Founder and Chairman of Joule. “Based on several breakthrough innovations, Joule has produced a platform to sustainably produce liquid fuels at costs competitive with all existing alternatives. Now we are eager to show the promise of commercial production,” he added. SunSprings plant operations will begin with production of Joule Sunflow™-E to compete in the ethanol market, valued at approximately $64 billion. Because Sunflow-E is derived from sunlight and industrial waste CO2, Joule can uniquely meet market demand with no depletion of natural resources or impact on global food supply and pricing. Joule has already achieved productivity rates of 15,000 and 8,000 gallons/acre/year in the lab and outdoor production, respectively, well above the maximum productivities that biomass-dependent processes can achieve. Following demonstration, Joule will be equipped to deploy its modular platform across multiple sites around the world, targeting initial productivities of 10,000 gallons/acre/year. This includes an opportunity to build a commercial facility in Hobbs, where the company has access to 1,200 additional acres and the inputs that drive its process. As the technology continues to advance, Joule ultimately targets productivity of up to 25,000 gallons of Sunflow-E per acre annually, at costs as low as $1.28/gallon without subsidies. To support its progress towards commercialization, the company also announced today the launch of Joule Fuels, a global subsidiary formed to capitalize on the $1+ trillion fuels market with exclusive access to Joule’s revolutionary technology, IP and know-how. This hand-picked team of experts will oversee plant deployment and partnerships – from site selection and project development to plant construction and operations – with the immediate goal of commissioning multiple plants worldwide. “Joule’s production platform is well suited to many regions around the world, where improving local energy security and environmental performance are critical goals,” said Peter Erich, President of Joule Fuels. “We are actively seeking sites and partners to deploy Joule Fuels plants in these regions, enabling localized production of high-volume, cost-competitive fuels in a sustainable process. This includes unique opportunities for off-take partners and input providers, including industrial CO2 emitters who can meet sustainability goals by directly converting their emissions into clean, renewable fuels.” Joule Fuels will initially commercialize Sunflow-E, with Sunflow-D for the global diesel market to follow. Unlike biodiesel, a low-concentration blendstock, Sunflow-D is comprised of diesel-range paraffinic alkanes and can therefore be blended with conventional diesel in concentrations of 50% or greater, displacing more oil. Moreover, Sunflow-D is inherently sulfur-free and has a very high cetane value. Sunflow-D is now in development with an ultimate productivity target of 15,000 gallons/acre/year at costs as low as $50/barrel without subsidies. bizjournals</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347543704002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347543819952-8</Id><Topic><Title>THANK GOD FOR MITT ROMNEY STANDING UP FOR AMERICA WHILE OUR JACK #$%$ PRESIDENT IS</Title><Username>americafirst120</Username><Timestamp>1347538591528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here you clowns go again . supporting another chicken hawk . Who dodged the draft went to France instead and speaks fluent French . Give me a break . Your hatred along with inability process anything outside the FOX Network . Makes you low information voters who should be poll taxed to prevent our great nation from slipping backwards .</Msg><Username>mk_yb</Username><Timestamp>1347543819952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347543951183-9</Id><Title>A Response To the Low Info Voters On This Board</Title><Msg>Here you clowns go again . supporting another chicken hawk . Who dodged the draft went to France instead and speaks fluent French . Give me a break . Your hatred along with inability process anything outside the FOX Network . Makes you low information voters who should be poll taxed to prevent our great nation from slipping backwards .</Msg><Username>mk_yb</Username><Timestamp>1347543951183</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347546658386-10</Id><Title>The WTI oil over $100/bbl and much higher soon</Title><Msg>QE to infinity and Middle east war.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1347546658386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347548068619-11</Id><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report September 13, 2012</Title><Msg>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report September 13, 2012 for the Week Ending September 7, 2012 Notes and Definitions Beginning with the report period for the week ending March 16, 2012, EIA is including salt dome and nonsalt-dome subtotals for the Producing Region in the Summary section. The sum of the components may not equal the total for the Producing Region, because of independent rounding. Summary Working gas in storage was 3,429 Bcf as of Friday, September 7, 2012, according to EIA estimates. This represents a net increase of 27 Bcf from the previous week. Stocks were 342 Bcf higher than last year at this time and 284 Bcf above the 5-year average of 3,145 Bcf. In the East Region, stocks were 80 Bcf above the 5-year average following net injections of 38 Bcf. Stocks in the Producing Region were 147 Bcf above the 5-year average of 957 Bcf after a net withdrawal of 13 Bcf. Stocks in the West Region were 57 Bcf above the 5-year average after a net addition of 2 Bcf. At 3,429 Bcf, total working gas is above the 5-year historical range. Working gas stocks in the Producing Region, for the week ending September 7, 2012, totaled 1,104 Bcf, with 207 Bcf in salt cavern facilities and 897 Bcf in nonsalt cavern facilities. Working gas stocks decreased 14 Bcf in the salt cavern facilities and remained at the previous week's level in the nonsalt cavern facilities since August 31. An historical series of the salt and nonsalt subtotals of the Producing Region is available for download at eia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347548068619</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:54:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347556533062-12</Id><Topic><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending September 7, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347460711253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:38:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production 9/7/2012 ETHANOL Production declines, Stocks rise slightly, Demand surges as a % of gasoline demand. ethanolrfa org</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347556533062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:15:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347556598139-13</Id><Title>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production</Title><Msg>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production 9/7/2012 ETHANOL Production declines, Stocks rise slightly, Demand surges as a % of gasoline demand. ethanolrfa</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347556598139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347556685322-14</Id><Title>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol &amp; Livestock Feed Production 9/7/2012</Title><Msg>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol &amp; Livestock Feed Production 9/7/2012 9/7/2012 ETHANOL Production declines, Stocks rise slightly, Demand surges as a % of gasoline demand.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347556685322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:18:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347560079044-15</Id><Title>LPH reports tonight</Title><Msg>I'm long LPH, should be increasing production by double soon. This is my stock pick of the year, trading at less then half book value and P/E of 2.</Msg><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1347560079044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:14:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347560640291-16</Id><Title>$Hey Washington$</Title><Msg>No no more f--kin $ for egypt and libya.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1347560640291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347560687781-17</Id><Topic><Title>A Response To the Low Info Voters On This Board</Title><Username>mk_yb</Username><Timestamp>1347543951183</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GFY commie POS.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1347560687781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347561791351-18</Id><Topic><Title>THANK GOD FOR MITT ROMNEY STANDING UP FOR AMERICA WHILE OUR JACK #$%$ PRESIDENT IS</Title><Username>americafirst120</Username><Timestamp>1347538591528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you I assume believe everything you hear on MSDNC. Idiot!</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347561791351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347562003734-19</Id><Topic><Title>A Response To the Low Info Voters On This Board</Title><Username>mk_yb</Username><Timestamp>1347543951183</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical lib - doesn't believe in free speech and probably not in God either.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347562003734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347562839120-20</Id><Title>so when is split?</Title><Msg>and I really don't care what anyone says about how it doesn't make a difference as to how many pieces there are in a pizza. I like stock splits. they give the share holder (at least this shareholder) a feeling of confidence in the company. Paul</Msg><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1347562839120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347563405812-21</Id><Title>New high on XOM and COST</Title><Msg>smart money $$$$$$</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1347563405812</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347564304753-22</Id><Title>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending September 12, 2012</Title><Msg>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending September 12, 2012 Release Date: September 13, 2012 In the News: Pennsylvania’s natural gas production has risen steadily in 2012 despite a significant reduction in the number of new natural gas wells being drilled by operators.The August 23 Natural Gas Weekly Update examined the slowing pace of natural gas drilling in Pennsylvania, noting that the number of new natural gas wells started per day in 2012 has declined sharply in recent months. The state’s natural gas production, however, continues to increase despite the reduction in new well starts. According to BENTEK Energy LLC (Bentek), Pennsylvania’s natural gas production has increased every month in 2012, rising from an average of about 4.4 billion cubic feet (Bcf) per day in January to approximately 5.9 Bcf per day in August. As with production increases in recent years, the rising 2012 volumes are associated predominantly with horizontal drilling programs in sections of the Marcellus and other shale formations. The state’s increasing natural gas production in 2012 is largely a function of a robust inventory of producing wells, particularly the relatively highly-productive horizontal wells drilled and completed during the past three to four years. The drainage area of wells – and therefore their productive potential – increases significantly by switching drilling orientation from vertical to horizontal, and expands even further with longer horizontal laterals. Underscoring the likelihood of continued natural gas production increases in Pennsylvania is the state’s large backlog of already drilled but not yet producing natural gas wells, as well as the impending completion of pipeline projects necessary to market the natural gas. Overview: (For the Week Ending Wednesday, September 12, 2012)•Natural gas prices increased for the report week (Wednesday to Wednesday) at many of the country’s trading locations, with an exception at Transco Zone 6-NY, which registered a decrease of 3 cents. The Henry Hub price closed at $2.96 per million British thermal units (MMBtu), up 9 cents for the week. •The natural gas futures market trended steadily higher over the week. At the New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), the October 2012 natural gas contract gained nearly 27 cents per MMBtu to close at $3.063 per MMBtu yesterday. •Working natural gas in storage rose last week to 3,429 billion cubic feet (Bcf) as of Friday, September 7, according to the U.S. Energy Information Administration’s (EIA) Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report (WNGSR). An implied storage build of 27 Bcf for the week positioned storage volumes 342 Bcf above year-ago levels. •The natural gas rotary rig count, as reported by Baker Hughes Incorporated on September 7, declined by 21 to 452 active units. Meanwhile, oil-directed rigs declined by 10 to 1,409 units. more summary data Prices: Natural gas prices increased over the report week at most spot market locations. For example, at the Sumas, Henry Hub, SoCal, Chicago, and Algonquin Citigate trading points, spot prices increased between 9 cents and 16 cents for the week. The largest price increase occurred at the Algonquin Citygate trading point (serving Boston), which increased by 16 cents (4.5 percent) from $3.55 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.71 per MMBtu yesterday. The NYMEX October 2012 futures contract rose by 9.6 percent from $2.795 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.063 per MMBtu yesterday. The 12-Month Strip (average of October 2012 to September 2013 contracts) increased by 6.7 percent over the same period, from $3.290 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.510 per MMBtu yesterday. Total consumption for the report week registered an overall decrease, driven by a significant decrease in the power sector. According to estimates from Bentek, domestic natural gas consumption declined by 5.0 percent from last week, driven by decreases of 14.6 percent in the power sector due to cooler weather. Consumption in the industrial and residential/ commercial sectors increased by 1.6 percent and 17.6 percent, respectively. Total supply for the week increased by 2.3 percent, driven by an increase in domestic production. According to Bentek estimates, domestic weekly dry gas production was 3.1 percent higher than the previous week and 2.2 percent above the same time last year. Imports from Canada decreased by 6.4 percent to 5.3 Bcf. Liquefied natural gas (LNG) sendout dropped sharply, down 11.1 percent from last week to 0.2 Bcf; sendout volumes remain well below (47.8 percent) year-ago levels. more price data Storage Working natural gas in storage increased to 3,429 Bcf as of Friday, September 7, according to EIA’s WNGSR. This represents an implied net injection of 27 Bcf from the previous week. This week’s injection was 45 Bcf below the 5-year (2007-2011) average injection of 72 Bcf, and 53 Bcf below last year’s injection of 80 Bcf. Inventories are currently 342 Bcf (11.1 percent) greater than last year at this time and 284 Bcf (9.0 percent) greater than the 5-year average. Two of the three storage regions posted increases this week. Inventories in the East and West regions increased by 38 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 51 Bcf) and 2 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 6 Bcf), respectively. The Producing region posted a decrease of 13 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 14 Bcf). In the Producing Region, working natural gas inventories decreased 14 Bcf (6.3 percent) in salt cavern facilities and remained at the previous week’s level in nonsalt cavern facilities. Temperatures during the storage report week were 5.1 degrees warmer than the 30-year normal temperature and 4.0 degrees warmer than the same period last year. Temperatures in the lower 48 States averaged 76.1 degrees, compared to 72.1 last year and the 30-year normal of 71.0 degrees. During the week all regions were warmer than normal, particularly the East North Central and West North Central Census divisions in the Midwest, which, respectively, averaged 7.7 and 7.1 degrees warmer than the 30-year normal. eia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347564304753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564394487-23</Id><Topic><Title>so when is split?</Title><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1347562839120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Believe me, a split means more dividend after they annually raise it.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1347564394487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564729769-24</Id><Topic><Title>so when is split?</Title><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1347562839120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If he does so he believes wrong because you are completely wrong. The rate of increase in the dividend is completely independent of a slit or the lack of one. There might a a temp "confidence" factor to a split. That is subject to debate. But your 'faster growing dividend" theory is 100% bunk.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1347564729769</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:32:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347564889899-25</Id><Topic><Title>THANK GOD FOR MITT ROMNEY STANDING UP FOR AMERICA WHILE OUR JACK #$%$ PRESIDENT IS</Title><Username>americafirst120</Username><Timestamp>1347538591528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor baby. No defense of your President huh? Maybe because we're cruising for the fiscal cliff and his mealy-mouthed Jimmy Carter foreign policy has made us no friends. Pavlov rang the bell and you drooled" time to hate a Republican!" Woof,woof! Pathetic. THIS DEM WILL VOTE ROMNEY</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1347564889899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:34:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347565994575-26</Id><Title>MIKEY HAVE YOU SEEN "LPH" NEWS LONGWEI PETROLIUM</Title><Msg>Its good news on 3rd facility im bettin on. bought more</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1347565994575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347566072513-27</Id><Title>Ben!!!</Title><Msg>XOM's Best. Friend. Ever!</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1347566072513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:54:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347566118995-28</Id><Title>$500 oil coming !</Title><Msg>Yippee, I'm gonna be rich!</Msg><Username>mcfool_chuckles</Username><Timestamp>1347566118995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:55:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347566440934-29</Id><Topic><Title>$500 oil coming !</Title><Username>mcfool_chuckles</Username><Timestamp>1347566118995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:55:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I mean I love it, I mean I love the thought of $20/gallon gasoline bankrupting our refineries! How many people can afford $20/gallon gasoline?</Msg><Username>mcfool_chuckles</Username><Timestamp>1347566440934</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:00:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347568019150-30</Id><Title>Republicans always want war</Title><Msg>But avoids serving in the military during war. They go on missions or stay in college. The Republicans always seek deferments. During war, the risk should be spread among all citizens.</Msg><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347568019150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347570415907-31</Id><Topic><Title>Ben!!!</Title><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1347566072513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES HE IS! $500 OIL COMING! HI HA HAH HI, I'm gonna be rich I tell ya!</Msg><Username>mcfool_chuckles</Username><Timestamp>1347570415907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347573744796-32</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans always want war</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347568019150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't know Bill Clinton was a Republican. Silly me.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347573744796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:02:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347575090302-33</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans always want war</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347568019150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Hussein served in the military just like Mr. Hillary Clinton did. LOL! These stupid loonie libs with mental disorders are a complete waste of space, time, and energy.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1347575090302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:24:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>