<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352364120413-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wins, I lose.</Title><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1352301386448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:16:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I haven't cost you anything. If you don't understand that buying individual stocks is risky, no matter who's in the White House, then you shouldn't be buying individual stocks at all.</Msg><Username>cdanajackson</Username><Timestamp>1352364120413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 03:42:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352367410004-2</Id><Title>Paul Ryan -- R I P</Title><Msg>soon to become a sarah palin--just a punchline and "expert" for fox news phony religious views phony conservative values just a phony goodbye eddie munster--go on a apology tour with "w" bush</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1352367410004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 04:36:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352373785710-3</Id><Title>Exxon Mobil Stock Forecast: Two Case Studies</Title><Msg>Two Case Studies on Exxon Mobil published in a good article on: ** I Know First system ** site. Good Trading!</Msg><Username>rightdon26</Username><Timestamp>1352373785710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 06:23:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352381385898-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Mandate - Repeal Reaganomics</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352302392379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:33:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It sounds like you never want to be in the high income bracket . Just remember that tax is not just for single people .</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1352381385898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 08:29:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352383874925-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Mandate - Repeal Reaganomics</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352302392379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:33:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It sounds like you never want to be in the high income bracket" No it is better to have a strong and stable monetary system and economy, and that will not occur as long as the government is running these deficits. A rate of return X minus a high tax is better than no rate of return minus a low tax. The basis of the banking system is debt and the assurance that it will be paid back. There is no assurance that it will be with Reaganomics and W'nomics in play. That is why investment is so low except by speculators in commodities, and other parasitic activities.</Msg><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352383874925</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 09:11:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352384246735-6</Id><Topic><Title>MEMO TO PARASITES---hosts leaving USA ---FAST !!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1352339883533</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 20:58:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No- the uber-earners in a place like Los Angeles or San Francisco, or New York City cannot make those incomes any other place. The economy is not based on tangibles like manufacturing, although that too is expanding now. No - it is based on services, and services require resources and opportunities- many of which are provided by a powerful government and legal system. Hong Kong's service opportunities are well captured by its top dogs... The powerful horses can pull harder - and they will too. Yes they will, just as they pulled harder on the reigns to keep up with a 50% tax rate during most of Reagan's term, a 70% rate before Reagan....You are just lazy. Leave if you want. Nobody cares.</Msg><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352384246735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 09:17:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352386809293-7</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Stock Forecast: Two Case Studies</Title><Username>rightdon26</Username><Timestamp>1352373785710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 06:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A fall in the short-term bond yields of Exxon Mobil (XOM) and Johnson &amp; Johnson (JNJ) to below those of comparable Treasurys - a rare phenomenon caused by soaring demand as investors seek safety and a bit of return - is prompting some investors to predict that top-rated companies could soon be able to issue debt at cheaper rates than the government. "It's only a matter of time," says Carret's Jason Graybill.</Msg><Username>tomsongarry</Username><Timestamp>1352386809293</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 10:00:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352389354617-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Mandate - Repeal Reaganomics</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352302392379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:33:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reaganomics in all ways are bad. People who make more should pay more but people who make less should pay a little. Everyone should pay something for our system to work (Jamestown - no work no eat ).</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1352389354617</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 10:42:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352389506994-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Mandate - Repeal Reaganomics</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352302392379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:33:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like you have no plans to be a high income earner. you know better than we do what you're capable of, so you clearly are not capable of high-earning.... best path for you is welfare. it's there for you now, and getting better by the minute! enjoy!</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1352389506994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 10:45:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352391297415-10</Id><Title>Green Engery vs Fosil Fuels.</Title><Msg>I know what Obama next four years will be all about, his first four years got him Obamacare.</Msg><Username>smkpit</Username><Timestamp>1352391297415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:14:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352392061940-11</Id><Topic><Title>Green Engery vs Fosil Fuels.</Title><Username>smkpit</Username><Timestamp>1352391297415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:14:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trying to force green energy on us before it's ready have been proven ineffective and costly. Obamacare will be met with the same results.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1352392061940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:27:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352392099770-12</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan -- R I P</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1352367410004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 04:36:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dung beetle returns to its favorite outhouse, The Republican outhouse of Congress.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1352392099770</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:28:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352392224015-13</Id><Topic><Title>Quiet in here ain't it ????????</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1352335093801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 19:38:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just think, if we did not spend 500+million on Afghanistan and Paskistan every person in the USA could go to college FREE. Why are we there?</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1352392224015</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:30:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352392498982-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Mandate - Repeal Reaganomics</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352302392379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:33:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As you kill the free markets, you will kill your handout.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1352392498982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:34:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352393874554-15</Id><Topic><Title>Green Engery vs Fosil Fuels.</Title><Username>smkpit</Username><Timestamp>1352391297415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:14:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The physicists working out of the universities brought us the science for the A-Bomb and nuclear power. They brought us the chemistry and physics for the pharmaceutical industry, explosives, fertilizers, and agro-chemistry, and modern medicine. The government is responsible for that. The government can and will address the problem of fossil fuels... You will not like the result, that is for sure, but don't delude yourself into thinking it cannot move the needle in the first instance. The history does not support your view and it will be costly for you when you are proven wrong.</Msg><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352393874554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:57:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352394180942-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Mandate - Repeal Reaganomics</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352302392379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:33:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no handout to lose. I will be investing strongly when the Bush tax cuts are history, and Obama has demonstrated his power to ram a tax increase and defense cut down the throats of the GOP leadership in Congress. That will be end of Reaganomics and the chaos it is has wrought in the economy - it's a sad note that the best investment since he was elected was the longest term bond you could find... No doubt there will be considerable panic on Wall Street when the taxes come, but the power of government to fix the problem of runaway deficits will have been demonstrated and it will be time to become bullish. Watch and learn.</Msg><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352394180942</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 12:03:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352395046350-17</Id><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report November 8, 2012</Title><Msg>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report November 8, 2012 Released: November 8, 2012 at 10:30 a.m. (eastern time) for the Week Ending November 2, 2012. Notes and Definitions Summary Working gas in storage was 3,929 Bcf as of Friday, November 2, 2012, according to EIA estimates. This represents a net increase of 21 Bcf from the previous week. Stocks were 109 Bcf higher than last year at this time and 244 Bcf above the 5-year average of 3,685 Bcf. In the East Region, stocks were 38 Bcf above the 5-year average following net injections of 5 Bcf. Stocks in the Producing Region were 153 Bcf above the 5-year average of 1,132 Bcf after a net injection of 8 Bcf. Stocks in the West Region were 53 Bcf above the 5-year average after a net addition of 8 Bcf. At 3,929 Bcf, total working gas is above the 5-year historical range. Working gas stocks in the Producing Region, for the week ending November 2, 2012, totaled 1,285 Bcf, with 307 Bcf in salt cavern facilities and 977 Bcf in nonsalt cavern facilities. Working gas stocks increased 7 Bcf in the salt cavern facilities and decreased 1 Bcf in the nonsalt cavern facilities since October 26. An historical series of the salt and nonsalt subtotals of the Producing Region is available for download at: eia ---------------------------- Weekly Coal Production Data for week ended: November 03, 2012 | Release Date: November 08, 2012 | Next Release: November 15, 2012 For the week ended November 03, 2012: •U.S. coal production totaled approximately 19.4 million short tons (mmst) •This production estimate is 1.1 percent lower than last week's estimate and 10.8 percent lower than the production estimate in the comparable week in 2011 •Coal production east of the Mississippi River totaled 7.9 mmst •Coal production west of the Mississippi River totaled 11.5 mmst •U.S. year-to-date coal production totaled 861.2 mmst, 6.2 percent lower than the comparable year-to-date coal production in 2011 •As of the week ending September 15, 2012, all of 2011 production has been revised to match the Mine Safety and Health Administration (MSHA) final 2011 production and second quarter 2012 production has been revised to match MSHA production. These changes are present in the Revisions/Archives section, and are also reflected in the "Current Weekly Estimates" and "Current Monthly Estimates" tables in the year-to-date and 52 weeks ended totals. These changes are not reflected in the two Original Estimates tables. eia Weekly U.S. Coal Production eia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352395046350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 12:17:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352396992584-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Mandate - Repeal Reaganomics</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352302392379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:33:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will both be "watching". It will be you that does the "learning".</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1352396992584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 12:49:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352397622204-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Mandate - Repeal Reaganomics</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352302392379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:33:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure you will be watching, but if you had any sense you would have sold already before your horse lost, as all the polls said he would. The stock market is certain to be much lower once the taxes are factored into the prices. In fact, I fully expect a full blown crisis like last summer only this time worse. Obama is not going to budge from his position. The GOP may well be suicidal and try to test his resolve. There could well be a default on the national debt... So get ready for some fun times. We will see if you have the will power to hold through the chaos after losing so much on the ride down. You will know when i buy of course...</Msg><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352397622204</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:00:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352397713479-20</Id><Topic><Title>Green Engery vs Fosil Fuels.</Title><Username>smkpit</Username><Timestamp>1352391297415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:14:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As has already been shown, it will be costly for all of us. As far as history goes, history has already shown (over and over) that socialism/big government does not work and NEVER has. Further, the ideas that come from the academic community would be worthless without programatic application of free markets.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1352397713479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:01:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352399044627-21</Id><Title>Debt Limit War Coming - Fiscal Cliff is only minor</Title><Msg>"Treasury continues to expect the debt limit to be reached near the end of 2012. However, Treasury has the authority to take certain extraordinary measures to give Congress more time to act to ensure we are able to meet the legal obligations of the United States of America. We continue to expect that these extraordinary measures would provide sufficient “headroom” under the debt limit to allow the government to continue to meet its obligations until early in 2013." -Assistant Treasury Secretary Matthew Rutherford, October 31, 2012 Obama has the GOP cornered now. If they refuse to raise the top tax brackets back to the Clinton levels, and indeed well beyond them to address the deficit all he need do is nothing to win. The government will run out of money, and the GOP will take the blame for it. You can expect the "war" to be brief. The national media will be on Obama's side and the financial markets will blame the GOP for the crash... Then Obama will get what he wants...</Msg><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352399044627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:24:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352399994612-22</Id><Title>GREEDINNEESS MADE ME LOOK STUPPIDDD1!!</Title><Msg>IDDDIOT!!! HOW ABOUT U?</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1352399994612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:39:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352400185540-23</Id><Title>Energy lobbyist: Keystone an ‘early test’ of Obama's pro-oil stance</Title><Msg>Energy lobbyist: Keystone an ‘early test’ of Obama's pro-oil stance By Ben Geman - 11/08/12 12:29 PM ET The head of the oil industry’s biggest trade group put fresh political pressure on President Obama Thursday to approve the Keystone XL oil sands pipeline. Jack Gerard, CEO of the American Petroleum Institute, said the decision will be a bellwether of Obama’s campaign-season backing for oil-and-gas development. “It will be one of the early tests, early questions of ... whether his actions will match is words,” Gerard told reporters. “We are hopeful, but that will be one of the early tests for the president.” The fate of TransCanada’s proposed pipeline, which would bring oil from Alberta’s tar sands projects to Gulf Coast refineries, is shaping up as a major post-election battle. [color=#00CC00][b]Environmentalists have scheduled a Nov. 18 demonstration at the White House against the project.[/b][/color] A Mitt Romney victory would have been a big win for pipeline advocates, as he had repeatedly pledged to approve the cross-border project on “day one” if elected. But pipeline advocates are expressing confidence that the White House — which plans a decision on a cross-border permit in the first quarter of 2013 — will also go their way. Canadian Prime Minister Stephen Harper said Thursday that he’s optimistic that the Obama administration will give Keystone a green light, according to Reuters. Lobbying giant Patton Boggs, in a post-election analysis circulated Wednesday, similarly predicted that the State Department, which handles the pipeline application review, will endorse the project. “With TransCanada having developed a new route through Nebraska that is likely to receive broad support in the state, we expect the State Department to complete its ongoing review of the application and to make the necessary national interest determination in favor of the project in the first quarter of 2013,” the analysis states. Environmentalists strongly oppose Keystone because of greenhouse gas emissions from extracting and burning oil sands, forest damage from the massive projects and fear of spills along the pipeline route. Business groups and a number of unions strongly back the project, calling it a way to boost U.S. energy security and create jobs. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352400185540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:43:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352400216623-24</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Limit War Coming - Fiscal Cliff is only minor</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352399044627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was a supporter of the gop--then came the "W" and the same gop congress that Clinton had--instead of continuing the balanced budgets the w ran up 7 trillion in DEBT. ALL with NOTHING to show for it. from credit card wars to free drugs to tax breaks for wealthy to sponsoring lance armstrong just waste followed by fraud. that WAS NOT--IS NOT--WILL NOT ever find support among informed voters or citizens. but if you watch fox and believe you are informed after Tues election--you are so stupid you do not even realize you are stupid. there are plenty here that have run away now in shame--like 4skin, yank, rewind, rhodebob, the steves etc; then you still have the inferno and invest part of the too stupid to be ashamed crowd. but they said several times they were LEAVING USA if Obama won AGAIN--so as soon as they can figure out how to get the family doublewide out of the country--goodbye</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1352400216623</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:43:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352400941807-25</Id><Title>In the wake of the GOP’s disappointing election, Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio) on Wednesday signaled a willingness to accept higher tax revenues as part of a deficit cutting deal.</Title><Msg>In the wake of the GOP’s disappointing election, Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio) on Wednesday signaled a willingness to accept higher tax revenues as part of a deficit cutting deal.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352400941807</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:55:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352401587429-26</Id><Title>Take Action Now to Protect Us from Pollution</Title><Msg>Take Action Now to Protect Us from Pollution By Danielle Baussan and Daniel J. Weiss | November 8, 2012 In the wake of Tuesday’s historic presidential victory, a newly reelected President Barack Obama can continue his efforts to protect our nation’s public health from the ravages of pollution. Voters rejected Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney’s high-profile campaign proposals to rely on antiquated, dirty, coal-fired power plants and overturn other new public health safeguards. The president’s new mandate provides his administration with the backing to complete unfinished Environmental Protection Agency safeguards before his inauguration on January 20, 2013, to a second term of office. A number of vital proposed health safeguards from power plant, vehicle, and industrial pollution still linger in administrative limbo. It is unclear why these rules were held up, but now that the president will remain in the White House, this unfinished business must be completed. These actions would clear the regulatory slate, enabling the administration to address two big problems in its second term: ■Reducing carbon pollution from existing power plants and other industrial sources ■Strengthening the ozone smog health standard to provide more protection for children, seniors, and other vulnerable people Make no mistake: The tragic fatalities and billions of dollars of damages from Hurricane Sandy are yet another warning about the imperative to further reduce climate change pollution. Building on the standards to reduce carbon pollution from motor vehicles adopted during his first term can be a major legacy of President Obama’s second term. IMAGE Here’s a list of five major and essential Environmental Protection Agency rules to protect public health that the administration should finalize immediately as a prelude to President Obama’s climate-change and pollution-reduction agenda in his second term. Reduce carbon pollution from new power plants In March 2012 the Environmental Protection Agency released a draft rule limiting carbon pollution from new power plants. This standard was promulgated in response to the 2007 Supreme Court ruling requiring the agency to regulate carbon dioxide emissions under the Clean Air Act if it found that carbon dioxide emissions endangered public health and the environment. The agency published such a finding in 2009, noting that carbon-pollution-associated climate change will increase the frequency of unusually higher temperatures and heat waves. Increased temperatures can increase the risk for formation of ground level ozone or smog. Breathing ozone may lead to shortness of breath and chest pain; increased risk of asthma attacks; increased susceptibility to respiratory infections; need for medical treatment and for hospitalization for people with lung diseases, such as asthma or chronic obstructive pulmonary disease; and premature death. Children and senior citizens are most vulnerable to harm from smog. The Environmental Protection Agency held several listening sessions while drafting the proposal, held two public hearings on the proposed rule, and extended the comment period to 73 days. Almost 3 million comments were sent to the agency in favor of reducing carbon pollution from both new and existing power plants—a record for an Environmental Protection Agency rule proposal. The agency is now in the midst of finalizing its rule. The Obama administration must act quickly to create a new generation of cleaner power plants so that it can begin to develop a carbon pollution reduction regime for existing power plants. Reduce hazardous pollution from industrial boilers The Clean Air Act requires the Environmental Protection Agency to issue rules limiting the hazardous air pollutant emissions (which include mercury, carcinogens, and particulates) from large industrial, commercial, or institutional boilers. The rule, known within the agency and around Capitol Hill as the MACT Boiler Rule, was first published in 2003, but it has been delayed for almost a decade. The D.C. Circuit Court vacated (voided) the 2004 rule in 2007 because it excluded many types of industrial boilers from pollution controls. The Environmental Protection Agency then issued a revised final rule by a court-imposed deadline of March 2011, but delayed that rule for another, “reconsidered” version that was released in December 2011. That reconsidered rule would apply to less than 1 percent of boilers while reducing enough pollution to avoid up to 8,100 premature deaths, 5,100 heart attacks, and 52,000 cases of aggravated asthma every year. The Environmental Protection Agency estimates that Americans would receive $12 to $30 in health benefits for every dollar spent to reduce these pollutants. After administrative and legal delays, the Environmental Protection Agency should issue the final rule by the end of 2012. Finalizing this rule by January could end years of delayed protection from toxic mercury and improve public health. Reduce smog pollution from cars, light trucks, and gasoline The Environmental Protection Agency’s “Tier 2” Vehicle and Gasoline Sulfur Program was finalized in February 2000. The program reduced about 90 percent of sulfur from gasoline and created tailpipe emissions standards for model year vehicles from 2004 to 2009. More than a decade later, a “Tier 3” standard is being developed that relies on improved technology to reduce the impact of motor vehicles on air quality and public health by establishing new standards for vehicles and gasoline. These standards wouldn’t just affect motor vehicles in the future; gasoline standards would improve public health immediately. Sulfur additives in gasoline can make cars less efficient, which increases vehicle emissions. Those emissions include volatile organic compounds and nitrogen oxide that form smog and harm humans. The National Association of Clean Air Agencies estimates that anticipated reductions of sulfur in gasoline would be the equivalent of removing 33 million light cars and trucks off the road. Another study found that a Tier 3 rule could reduce nitrogen oxide emissions by 25 percent in the Northeast United States alone. Nitrogen oxide contributes to ozone smog and acid rain, and impairs public health. It’s estimated that the avoided harms to public health in the Northeastern part of the United States in 2018 would have an economic value of up to $1.2 billion (in 2006 dollars). It could cost less than one penny per gallon of gasoline and approximately $150 per new vehicle while simultaneously reducing smog ingredients. This reduction can avoid more than 400 premature deaths and 52,000 lost workdays each year. The Environmental Protection Agency is expected to propose lowering the sulfur standard from 30 parts per million to 10 parts per million, similar to standards in many European countries, in Japan, and in California. The Tier 3 rule has not yet been proposed, but many affected industries, including a consortium of global automakers, have pressed the agency to move forward with its rulemaking. Modernize protection from soot In June 2012 the Environmental Protection Agency proposed to strengthen the nation’s air quality health standards for fine particulate matter. Commonly referred to as soot, this pollutant is a mix of small particles like nitrates, sulfates, or dust that are 2.5 micrometers in diameter or smaller, which comes from vehicles, power plants, and other industrial sources. When inhaled, these particles can lodge in the lungs, causing serious health effects. This new rule would improve public health and visibility by swiftly limiting short-term soot exposure. Long-term exposure to soot can cause premature death and is linked to heart attacks and strokes. Some studies suggest that long-term soot exposure may be linked to cancer and to harmful developmental and reproductive effects in children, such as infant mortality and low birth weight. The soot standard has a long history. The Environmental Protection Agency began its first review process of air quality standards for fine particle soot in 1997. The D.C. Court of Appeals and the U.S. Supreme Court reviewed the rule for five years. Pursuant to a 2003 modified consent decree, the agency published its proposed revisions to the PM 2.5 National Ambient Air Quality Standard on January 17, 2006. The agency issued its final rule on October 17, 2006. In 2009 the D.C. Circuit Court ruled that the Environmental Protection Agency had to reconsider its fine-particle soot standard because it improperly issued weak, less-protective standards. The agency proposed revisions on June 29, 2012, and agreed to finalize the air quality standards by December 14, 2012, as part of a settlement to a lawsuit. The Obama administration should publish its final rule on December 14 and put an end to the delay of this new respiratory health safeguard. Improve clean air quality standards for cement manufacturing In 2010 the Environmental Protection Agency issued a proposed rule to further limit soot, mercury, and other hazardous pollutants from existing and new cement kilns. Cement manufacturing is one of the largest industrial sources of mercury pollution in our nation. The Environmental Protection Agency estimates that the rule would eliminate 92 percent of the mercury and fine-particulate soot emissions from cement kilns. The rule was challenged in the D.C. Circuit Court of Appeals, which found that the agency’s cement standards were fine but that storage standards for clinker needed to be reconsidered. When clinker (the mix of raw materials used to make cement) is fired in a kiln, it causes the emission of particulates and hazardous chemicals, including mercury. It can continue to emit some hazardous chemicals when stored in piles. In June 2012 the Environmental Protection Agency proposed changes to the Portland cement rule; it held a public hearing in August. On September 9 the agency submitted its final rule, which will take effect today. The Obama administration must be prepared to defend this standard against legal challenges so it will protect people from breathing in mercury from cement manufacturing. Moving now against climate change Now that President Obama has been reelected, let’s hope he focuses his energy on protecting us from mercury, soot, and toxic air pollutants. He can make a down payment on that effort in his second term of office by taking action on these five essential Environmental Protection Agency rules in 2012. Danielle Baussan is Associate Director of Government Affairs at the Center for American Progress. Daniel J. Weiss is a Senior Fellow and Director of Climate Strategy at the Center. americanprogress</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352401587429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 14:06:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352401650435-27</Id><Title>WLL is being bought by STO</Title><Msg>today</Msg><Username>zilanewswatch</Username><Timestamp>1352401650435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 14:07:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352402547585-28</Id><Title>Is there news from IRAN ??</Title><Msg>??????????????????</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1352402547585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 14:22:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352402733598-29</Id><Topic><Title>Is there news from IRAN ??</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1352402547585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 14:22:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check out Foxnews</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1352402733598</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 14:25:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352404557940-30</Id><Topic><Title>Is there news from IRAN ??</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1352402547585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 14:22:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dick cheney said they are dancing in the street and we are liberators oh sorry--wrong country and wrong propaganda</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1352404557940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 14:55:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352405871035-31</Id><Topic><Title>In the wake of the GOP’s disappointing election, Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio) on Wednesday signaled a willingness to accept higher tax revenues as part of a deficit cutting deal.</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352400941807</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:55:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>john boner is a liar and a fraud--just wants to change his tune after TUES and seeing how HIS pandering to the teabags was disaster--he has 2 years to flip and flop and MISlead the fox news whitetrash--saying 1 thing and doing another. then he too will become another footnote and relegated to sarah palin status as an "expert" on fox news. the sooner the "still brainwaves" portion of the gop repudiates ALL things boner all things ryan all things jewzbag "cantor" and elects real leadership (not talking/doing) with fiscal principles (not 7 trillion in debt because "w" says so) the sooner they will get REAL AMERICANS to look and respect their opinion--CUT ALL SPENDING with #1 being bloated military--increase upper level taxes--BALANCE the budget--deny food stamps/welfare for illegals--QUIT saying NO to EVERYTHING the prez says just because of his party--begin process to remove Alito from SCOTUS--show honest educated leadership not trump and limbo talking points--STEP UP GOP</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1352405871035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:17:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352406472793-32</Id><Topic><Title>Is there news from IRAN ??</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1352402547585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 14:22:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>little dick too busy working w/ turdblossom on Benghazi related impeachment proceedings...</Msg><Username>mackerelsnappinhannity</Username><Timestamp>1352406472793</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:27:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352407307381-33</Id><Topic><Title>Is there news from IRAN ??</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1352402547585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 14:22:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did IRAN just surrender? Because XOM's pps is plunging.</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1352407307381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:41:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352412405350-34</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Limit War Coming - Fiscal Cliff is only minor</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352399044627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP has become a party of many eccentrics. I quite agree.</Msg><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352412405350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 17:06:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352412658851-35</Id><Topic><Title>Is there news from IRAN ??</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1352402547585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 14:22:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should know by now that Obama is not going to attack them. According to some news reports he's feeling them out about peace talks to start next month... The oil market is already totally glutted with the NE in a state of devastation. When the Iran sanctions get lifted it will flood the market with even more oil, too.</Msg><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352412658851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 17:10:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352417703607-36</Id><Title>Perfect Storm for an oil crash</Title><Msg>There's the Hurricane devastating the Northeast, wiping out vast swathes of the service economy of the area. That will take quite some time to recover and in the meantime income and demand will be sharply reduced. Southern Europe is already in very deep recession and Germany is slipping into one now, eroding China's exports to those places. The USA's trade deficit outside oil is almost gone now, and indeed is gone with places like Europe. The dying up dollars to Europe, in turn, dries up their demand for oil, and also their demand for Chinese products many of which they pay for with dollars earned trading with the USA. China itself is slowing dramatically as its internal housing and construction market is in steep decline, and its banks are massively leveraged lending on construction projects and to local governments. Taxes will skyrocket next year in the USA which will reduce US consumption, particularly imports from China and Europe worsening the situation in those places. The stage is set for a synchronous global depression. The stock market could easily decline 50% by this time next year... As for oil $40/bbl is an optimistic price target, especially considering that Obama now has full power to pursue dovish Iran policy... Save what you can...</Msg><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352417703607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 18:35:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352421765418-37</Id><Topic><Title>In the wake of the GOP’s disappointing election, Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio) on Wednesday signaled a willingness to accept higher tax revenues as part of a deficit cutting deal.</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352400941807</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:55:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I assume 'higher tax revenues' includes tax subsidies and concessions to all fossil fuel industries. Suddenly renewable energy will appear to be inexpensive.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352421765418</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 19:42:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352424427856-38</Id><Title>Big Oils turn UNIONS !</Title><Msg>Now that the unions and liberals have spoken, it's time for big oil to speak. I want to see $175/barrel oil and gasoline at $7.50/gal. STICK IT TO EM !</Msg><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1352424427856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:27:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352426026334-39</Id><Title>Close Your Business - It Will Correct The Obama Mistake</Title><Msg>The re-election of Barak Obama was a (50% of Americans) mistake. Sadly now, 100% of us will have to pay for it. The good thing though....Republicans (people with budgets and plans) can weather it far better than the Lib, Unions, and US Treasury can. If I owned a business and had enough wealth already, I'd simply close the business down and lay-off everyone. If in four years, IF a Republican president is elected, I'd re-open the business and smile. IF NOT, oh well. If every business did this, the money well would quickly go dry up for the spend-happy Democrats and their entitlement constituency establishment would, well, have to find a job in a no-jobs environment. Oh no, what a mean-spirited idea....make some poor unaccustomed-to-it-soul have to seek WORK!</Msg><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1352426026334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:53:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352427377362-40</Id><Topic><Title>Close Your Business - It Will Correct The Obama Mistake</Title><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1352426026334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Close up ASAP. Your shuttered shop will lower land values, wages, and reduce the cost of those items in the manufacturing process for other business. That will allow big business to relocate back to the USA to take advantage of the lower costs and reduce the trillions of dollars of imports that flood into the USA yearly from cheaper areas overseas. If your idea of a small business is an llc speculating in real estate by all means shut down - do the economy a favor. If you are real professional educated in the law or medicine you should find no problem passing whatever tax is placed onto you, to others... Big business will need your service, and anybody get a real value from your service will need it. As for the rest - they are not so very essential. If a strip club happens to go out of business because of taxes and it can't figure out how to pass them on, so be it...</Msg><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352427377362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:16:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352428054309-41</Id><Topic><Title>Close Your Business - It Will Correct The Obama Mistake</Title><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1352426026334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This was the meme on Right Wing Radio Today and the parrot has arrived on the board. Go ahead and shut your business down so I my liberal brothers and sisters can gain market share. We'll gladly fill the void you hysterical fools will leave and we'll do better by our customers.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1352428054309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:27:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352428376398-42</Id><Topic><Title>Close Your Business - It Will Correct The Obama Mistake</Title><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1352426026334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way listening to all these hysterical fools on right wing radio is really funny and quite entertaining. The "patriotic" Americans of the right are all more than willing to scuttle the ship as they continue with their treasonous little psychotic temper tantrum.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1352428376398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:32:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352428579214-43</Id><Topic><Title>Big Oils turn UNIONS !</Title><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1352424427856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:27:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go for it and all the US military protection they get gratis(that's free to a #$%$ like you) will be removed and the profit you aspire to will simply be offset with higher security costs and lower profits.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1352428579214</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:36:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352428886589-44</Id><Topic><Title>Quiet in here ain't it ????????</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1352335093801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 19:38:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical brain washed right wing mentality. Let me set you straight you fool. The plurality voted for their own best interests. The other 57 million fools voted for the interests of a few billionaires.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1352428886589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:41:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352429325381-45</Id><Topic><Title>Energy lobbyist: Keystone an ‘early test’ of Obama's pro-oil stance</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352400185540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:43:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course he'll cave. He's the "cave" man. I always said that the most widely held secret in this nation today is that Obama is a Moderate Republican. These hysterical right wing Beck fans are merely racist fascists who want death and destruction to sweep the country in the name of "purity" and the psychotic sky #$%$ they have been led to believe in.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1352429325381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:48:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352430369900-46</Id><Title>This stock is so weeeeeak....</Title><Msg>This is headed to 65 accompanied by a lowering of US debt rating.</Msg><Username>anniannc</Username><Timestamp>1352430369900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 22:06:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352430443236-47</Id><Title>U.S. envoy tempers Tory optimism on Keystone XL as Obama win stokes hope</Title><Msg>U.S. envoy tempers Tory optimism on Keystone XL as Obama win stokes hope Mike Blanchfield, The Canadian Press Nov 07, 2012 17:17:00 PM OTTAWA - The Harper government shouldn't be getting its hopes up that Barack Obama's re-election will mean speedy approval of the controversial Keystone XL pipeline, says the U.S. ambassador to Canada. U.S. envoy David Jacobson's assessment provides a sobering counterpoint to the optimism expressed by the government Wednesday that the Keystone XL pipeline can proceed now that the American campaign is over. "I'm not going to pre-empt the president's decision," Jacobson told The Canadian Press in an interview this week on the eve of Obama's victory over Republican challenger Mitt Romney. "We don't even have a route yet from the state of Nebraska, and until we have that, nothing can happen," he said. "This thing has got to move in an orderly fashion. But I think we need to keep Keystone in the proper context of what is the largest energy relationship between two countries in the world ... It is not a huge part of that relationship." Romney repeatedly pledged to immediately approve "the pipeline from Canada" throughout the presidential campaign. Obama delayed approval of the project until next year — after Tuesday's presidential election — after environmental groups put enormous pressure on his government. The TransCanada pipeline, which would carry bitumen from the Alberta oilsands to U.S. refineries in the Gulf of Mexico, has faced pressure from environmental regulators in Nebraska. The Obama administration denied Keystone's bid in January because of concerns about the proposed pipeline route over the Ogallala aquifer, a major fresh water source. TransCanada has since unveiled a new pipeline route around the area. Natural Resources Minister Joe Oliver said Wednesday he is confident the newly re-elected Obama administration would see the economic benefits of the pipeline. "We believe that the XL pipeline will ultimately be approved by the U.S. administration because it's in America's national interest. It responds to national security concerns and it will create jobs and economic activity in the United States," Oliver said. "It's good for both countries." Prime Minister Stephen Harper was not pleased with Obama's decision to delay Keystone's approval, but has said he understands the realities of U.S. presidential politics. Obama is no longer in the middle of an election so the project can proceed on its merits, Oliver said. TransCanada said Wednesday that it still believes the project will be approved. "The facts that support the approval of Keystone XL remain the same — and the need for this pipeline grows even stronger the longer its approval is delayed," the company said in a statement. Alberta Premier Alison Redford said she, too, is looking forward to working with Obama and promoting the province's resources as critical for the U.S. to achieve energy independence and economic security in North America. Obama didn't specifically mention the Keystone project in his victory speech early Wednesday. But he pledged to work with both parties towards "freeing ourselves from foreign oil." Obama's re-election is also sparking hope that the issue of climate change — a topic that was largely missing from action during the long presidential campaign — will gain new momentum in his second term. That has emboldened the very U.S. opponents of the Keystone project whose activism pushed the project to the back burner for further review. The National Resources Defense Council, the New York-based advocacy group that has opposed the pipeline, called Oliver's comments "wishful thinking." "Approval of the Keystone XL tar sands pipeline is certainly not a given, especially when a second term for President Barack Obama is going to mean a strong commitment to fighting climate change pollution and promoting clean energy choices," the council's Canada program director Danielle Droitsch said in a blog post Wednesday. "More than ever, Canada's current approach to energy development — which strongly favours a massive build up of tar sands production — is at odds with America's path." In the interview, Jacobson said "Canada and the United States have exactly the same goals with respect to greenhouse gas emissions." He said both countries have pledged a 17 per cent reduction in emissions by 2020 and 80 per cent by 2050. But he said the aftermath of hurricane Sandy means "you don't have to be a genius to know that something is going on here." NDP Leader Tom Mulcair expressed hope Wednesday that Obama's re-election would lead to progress on a joint Canada-U.S. cap and trade system to help bring down greenhouse gas levels. "I think that the beginning of this second term really does open up a whole new era," said Mulcair. "People who understand the importance of coming to grips with climate change understand that a cap-and-trade system is the only serious way of guaranteeing the result of a reduction of greenhouse gas." The Harper government has said it's only interested in a cap-and-trade system if the U.S. moves in that direction. news1130</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352430443236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 22:07:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352435606140-48</Id><Topic><Title>Quiet in here ain't it ????????</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1352335093801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 19:38:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bran dead accusing others of being brain washed? What a laugh. The plurality voted for more free stuff to be taken from those who actually produce. It's too bad what is going to be happening in this country but I'm sure you can always blame it on Bush.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352435606140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 23:33:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352435701156-49</Id><Topic><Title>Quiet in here ain't it ????????</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1352335093801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 19:38:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that what happened to you in 2010? You are a sad case jerk who will likely pay the price for your vote a lot sooner than you think.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352435701156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 23:35:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352435901892-50</Id><Topic><Title>Close Your Business - It Will Correct The Obama Mistake</Title><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1352426026334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:53:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The strip clubs are mostly owned by Dems. They will thrive in the recession to come, likely with subsidies from Obama's stash if necessary.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352435901892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 23:38:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352435981867-51</Id><Topic><Title>In the wake of the GOP’s disappointing election, Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio) on Wednesday signaled a willingness to accept higher tax revenues as part of a deficit cutting deal.</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352400941807</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:55:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Demonstrating the racism of the brain dead - thanks wahleee boy for again showing your true colors.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352435981867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 23:39:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352436175875-52</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Limit War Coming - Fiscal Cliff is only minor</Title><Username>whiggeryrules</Username><Timestamp>1352399044627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 13:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another series of lies wahleee boy. But anything to stay on the dole, I guess.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352436175875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 23:42:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>