<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-26"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356504797061-1</Id><Title>Texas Man Takes Last Stand Against Keystone XL Pipeline</Title><Msg>Texas Man Takes Last Stand Against Keystone XL Pipeline December 25, 2012 by: Elizabeth Shogren, NPR The Keystone pipeline is supposed to carry tar sands oil from Canada to Texas — a route that runs right through David Daniel's land. To try to save his woods from bulldozers, Daniel built tree houses 80 feet in the air and protesters climbed up into them. An east Texas landowner was so determined to block the Keystone XL pipeline from coming through his forest that he took to his trees and built an elaborate network of treehouses eight stories above the ground. "It popped into my head a long time ago, actually," says 45-year-old David Daniel. "If I had to climb my butt on top of a tree and sit there, I would. It started with that." It turned out to be Daniel's last stand in a long battle against the Keystone XL, a pipeline project that would bring oil from Canada all the way to refineries in the Texas Gulf Coast. And he lost. But Daniel's extreme efforts highlight the agony that individuals around the country are facing as new pipelines are built so a larger portion of oil can come from Canada and into the U.S. "It feels very invasive, but the reality is that it happens all around the United States. It's not limited to just Texas," says Amy Jaffe, an energy expert from the University of California, Davis. "The bottom line is, it's public good because we use so much oil in this country that we cannot afford in our current lifestyle to turn down infrastructure. We're all participating in that by getting in our car." An Airborne Fortress When I visited Daniel this summer at his 20-acre spread outside the town of Winnesboro, he said he was learning that the tar sands oil the pipeline will carry is a "whole new monster." He worried not only about losing the big old trees he loves, but also about what would happen to his family if a pipeline burst, and the thick, dirty crude flowed out. He said he had lots of questions that the pipeline company wouldn't answer. He was also keeping a secret from me: the leafy canopies of his tall oaks were hiding treehouses and platforms that he was building to stymie construction crews when they showed up on his property. We walked right under them the first time I visited. When I returned this month, I saw a network of seven treehouses and platforms that were connected with cables and ropes. They stretched across 500 feet. Think of it as an airborne fortress. Daniel didn't have any money to fight in the courts. But he did have skills very few people have. He used to work for the circus and often rigged the high-wire that he'd ride a motorcycle across and the 50-foot-high platform he'd jump from after lighting himself on fire. Daniel is now a carpenter. Even so, building structures so high in trees took months. He says it was an intense time for him, because of all the unknowns, and it shows. He looks older and more haggard than he did a few months earlier. His red beard is shaggier. Fighting The Law Around September, the pipeline company spied the treehouses from a helicopter. "Actually we learned from the air. We have an aerial patrol that flies the right of way, looking for any changes, and low and behold, one day there were blue tarps and wires up in the trees," says David Dodson, a spokesman for TransCanada, the company that is building the pipeline. When TransCanada's crew arrived to start construction, Daniel was there to block them. TransCanada immediately sued Daniel for preventing its work, and app1DOTkuhfDOTorg/articles/npr1356465917-Texas-Man-Takes-Last-Stand-Against-Keystone-XL-Pipeline.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356504797061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 01:53:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356509503591-2</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Purification</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356465511169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-25 14:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What does not work is liberal policies such cutting taxes to fight recessions"? A typo?</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1356509503591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 03:11:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356524349355-3</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Purification</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356465511169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-25 14:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What does not work is liberal policies such cutting taxes to fight recessions"? A typo? That is most certainly not a typo. That policy is a right out of the playbook of economic liberalism... It is more deficit, "stimulus," Keynesian garbage... The idea is to unleash "animal" spirits, i.e. speculation, by cutting taxes and financing the resulting deficit with debt, which it most certainly does, and the policy is exactly the wrong policy for sustainable growth. Somehow the idea of a British socialist ended up in the mainstream of "conservative" and "liberal" American political dogma. The policy still does not work, no matter how many time it is tried or how many fools try it.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356524349355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 07:19:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356524566867-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Purification</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356465511169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-25 14:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keynesian liberals believe animal spirits, i.e. speculation are good for an economy. So one of their policy prescriptions is to run a deficit to finance a tax cut. The speculation is the problem not the solution. The problem just gets bigger and bigger the more tax cuts and "stimulus" programs they throw at it - until the whole thing collapses and their "animal spirits" are flushed...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356524566867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 07:22:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356525940266-5</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Purification</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356465511169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-25 14:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A true orthodox Keynesian liberal makes an academically cute but ultimately irrelevant distinction between the good animal spirits and bad ones. The bad ones they believe are the bad part of speculation which they define narrowly as short term risk takers, and the good ones - more longer term ones- are naturally the ones they hope to encourage. The economy does not work as they would like. One reason the latest implosion was so severe in 2008 was the riot of long term "risk taking" from fannie/freddie/bush tax cuts - the good animal spirits...There's plenty more of that now as all the central banks have their shoulder to the wheel to get lots more animal spirits going. They are just charlatans, but dangerous ones because they are listened to...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356525940266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 07:45:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356533385112-6</Id><Title>A Thought On Subsidies</Title><Msg>A Thought On Subsidies (Reader Comment) December 26, 2012 Zachary Shahan Anti-wind and anti-solar folks (yes, there are a few out there — mostly tied to the fossil fuel industry) love to bring up renewable energy subsidies. However, there are so many reasons why they really shouldn’t be eager to do so. For example, fossil fuel and nuclear subsidies dwarf renewable energy subsidies. IMAGES.. Subsidies in first 15 years of subsidies for various energy sources. Additionally, many indirect subsidies never even get counted in most subsidy analyses — such as the tremendous extent to which we subsidize oil through our military and</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356533385112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 09:49:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356533493656-7</Id><Title>fossil fuel &amp; nuclear subsidies dwarf renewable energy subsidies</Title><Msg>fossil fuel &amp; nuclear subsidies dwarf renewable energy subsidies HEADLINE IMAGES</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356533493656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 09:51:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356538752666-8</Id><Title>Options Players Wage on Exxon Mobil Corporation (XOM)</Title><Msg>NEW YORK (AVAFIN) -- Exxon Mobil Corporation witnessed a record number of call and put contracts during the busy trading session. There were 0.5 call contracts traded for each put contract yielding a 1.82 put/call ratio where 89,242 put and 49,025 call contracts exchanged hands. A significant increase in the trading volume of a stock's option often is a precursor of movement by the underlying stock. In such instances, put/call Ratio can be used as an investor sentiment indicator, where a high ratio implies that the overall investor sentiment is bearish and a low put/call ratio implies that the sentiment is bullish. Exxon is an integrated oil and gas company that explores for, produces, and refines oil around the world. In 2010, it produced 2.4 million barrels of oil and 12.1 billion cubic feet of natural gas a day. At year-end 2010, reserves stood at 17.2 billion boe, 47% of which are oil. The company is the world's largest refiner, with 36 refineries, and it is one of the world's largest manufacturers of commodity and specialty chemicals. Shares of Exxon Mobil Corporation declined $1.66 (1.87%) to $87.23 in today's trading session. The price of XOM ranged between $87.01 - $88.60. Volume is 31M in relation to the three month average volume of 12M shares. XOM is trading below the 50 day moving average and higher than the 200 day moving average. The stock's 52 week low is $77.13 and 52 week high is $93.67. Performance indicators show that the stock has lost -1.24% within the last quarter.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1356538752666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 11:19:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356540070971-9</Id><Topic><Title>fossil fuel &amp; nuclear subsidies dwarf renewable energy subsidies</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356533493656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 09:51:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One has to ask the question why? Could it have something to do with reliablilty? One has to be in favor of renewable energy, but what happens on a calm, cloudy, day? Government has a number or responsibilities both to the environment and people who need essential reliable energy.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1356540070971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 11:41:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356540596280-10</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is making a good point. Of course the god haters, athiests, and communists would not agree. Further one should demand that the full profile and potential warning signs of this attack should be made available such that future attacks might be prevented. No more of this dont ask dont tell. Further when teachers, scout leaders and coaches are applying for jobs there should be no dont ask dont tell policy. Think it is high time that the government and media stop covering up for special interest lifestyle groups to protect their feelings and work on make prevention a priority. One might expect there are many cases of profiles being edited and that makes identification of potential problems and prevention all that much more difficult. jmho</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1356540596280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 11:49:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356541404839-11</Id><Topic><Title>fossil fuel &amp; nuclear subsidies dwarf renewable energy subsidies</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356533493656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 09:51:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The highway system is a huge subsidy. Other subsidies are important as well, such as the government putting its thumb on the mortgage rate to push it down and encourage building of single family homes. Single family homes strung out along highways generate far more gasoline &amp; diesel demand than the free market solution of apartment buildings. If you reduce the cost of single family homes relative to apartments, you get more single family homes, and more oil demand. The government should yank all its subsidies to mortgages and direct the money to productive investments in science. The reliability issues you speak for alternative energy sources will quickly disappear as the technology improves. At this point that would entail passing a law ordering the Federal Reserve to sell every mortgage security it owns, book the losses, and abolish the mortgage interest deduction to raise revenue to cover the losses the government has accrued buying mortgages. If the US government keeps doing what it is now eventually its own credit rating will collapse and then it will have to abandon all the subsidies anyway...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356541404839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 12:03:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356541804332-12</Id><Topic><Title>Options Players Wage on Exxon Mobil Corporation (XOM)</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1356538752666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 11:19:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure waste. The government should tax it at 90% and encourage those gamblers to find something else better to do with their time...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356541804332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 12:10:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356542956458-13</Id><Title>Chuck Hagel.</Title><Msg>Would be an inspired pick, and it looks as though Obama wants him for the job. He's also a Republican, but obviously not a Richard Nixon or George W Bush Republican. The Israeli lobby despises him, which is a good indication that he is a horse of a different color.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356542956458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 12:29:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356546801436-14</Id><Title>European-Arab meeting of interests</Title><Msg>Middle East oil has been vital to Europe since the 1950s. European technology has been important to the Arabs as well, and they invest heavily in Europe today. European banks house Arab wealth, and wealthy Arabs are common on the streets of Frankfurt, Munich, Bonn, Berlin, London, Birmingham, Paris... The Arabs are quite bright too, and their elite has no problem filling top rank positions in the sciences at major universities across Europe. The Arabs developed much of the world's chemical knowledge while European government and society withered in barbarity during the Dark Ages. If they are treated like animals as happens in some place in the Middle East through misguided polices they don't do well, but can change. Things are hopeful on the American front as well now that the warmongering administration of George W Bush is gone. Obama is doing his best to hold back the warmongers in his midst, and is making good progress.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356546801436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 13:33:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356550008644-15</Id><Title>Oil lobby seeks to work with Obama</Title><Msg>Oil lobby seeks to work with Obama Financial Times-46 minutes ago After four years of combat between the American Petroleum Institute and the White House, Jack Gerard, the lead representative of 500 oil and ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356550008644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 14:26:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356550412469-16</Id><Title>Report finds US energy production growing, consumption down</Title><Msg>Report finds US energy production growing, consumption down By Zack Colman - 12/26/12 12:53 PM ET A new report shows U.S. energy consumption dropping, even as the industry experiences a boost in production. U.S. energy consumption declined 3 percent between January and September compared with that period last year, according to data the U.S. Energy Information Administration (EIA) released Wednesday. During the period evaluated, energy use from transportation and industry dropped 1.2 and 1.5 percent, respectively. Residential and commercial energy use declined 5.2 percent. Energy production, however, rose 2 percent through the same time frame. Fossil fuel development increased 3.14 percent, while renewable energy production fell 2.8 percent. The statistics underscore two energy-related debates sure to get attention in the next Congress — energy efficiency and fossil-fuel drilling on federal lands. Green groups are hoping some of President Obama’s executive actions will curtail energy consumption further. Meanwhile, the oil-and-gas industry and its congressional allies aim to push Obama to open more federal lands to fossil fuel drilling, boosting domestic energy production. New shale oil-and-gas plays buoyed much of the energy sector’s growth through the past year. Led by hydraulic fracturing, or fracking, most of that increase has come from private and state lands. The oil-and-gas industry wants Obama to open more federal lands to drilling, saying it could bring additional revenues to the Treasury. While the White House has praised states' monitoring of fracking — which injects a high-pressure mixture of water, sand and chemicals into tight rock formations to tap hydrocarbons — it has been cautious on expanding its use. Green groups say the process might contaminate drinking water and that it releases heat-trapping methane gas. Industry has said the method is safe. The Interior Department is set to release regulations for fracking on federal lands next year. Industry and GOP have resisted those rules, warning they might impose a “one-size-fits-all” approach to areas with different geological concerns and considerations. On the energy demand side, green groups are fixing to get comprehensive energy efficiency legislation through the next Congress. Lawmakers recently passed upgrades for efficiency on some appliances, and have expressed a willingness to work on more sweeping legislation. Organizations ranging from environmental to national security groups want to focus more on enhancing energy efficiency in buildings. Buildings account for 36 percent of the nation’s total energy consumption, according to the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA). If Congress proves to be a roadblock, green groups contend Obama will continue using administrative authority to achieve energy efficiency goals. They point to recently finalized vehicle fuel efficiency standards — which proponents say will help lower transportation-related energy consumption even further — and a directive to improve energy efficiency at manufacturing facilities. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/274569-eia-us-energy-consumption-down-production-up</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356550412469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 14:33:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356555780396-17</Id><Title>Retailer Federal Bailout Coming</Title><Msg>Reason? Fiscal Cliff uncertainty. I can see it now. $100 B for the Macy's and Nordstrom's of the world.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1356555780396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:03:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356558881417-18</Id><Topic><Title>Retailer Federal Bailout Coming</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1356555780396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:03:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the Federal Reserve could announce a $1 trillion credit card debt purchase program. Like all their other bailouts and manipulations it would consist of taking $1 trillion in bank reserves from Federal Reserve System member banks, buying the credit card debt with the $1 trillion, and giving the banks IOUs worth $1 trillion. The banks would come up with the $1 trillion by selling securities or allowing their very short term ones to mature to dollars without being reinvested. As in all its other manipulations, the Fed would want to push the price of the debt it is buying sky-high to get the interest rate down. When the consumers default on the debt, as is typical with credit card debt, and the Fed loses money they can then ask Congress to bail them out - after all Congress owns them and is on the hook for the IOUs the Fed has issued to perform its manipulations. Congress could tell Treasury to print the money to fund the bailout, and then watch its credit ranting implode as international investors sold bonds. The Fed itself cannot recapitalize itself without an Act of Congress...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356558881417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 16:54:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356560032397-19</Id><Topic><Title>Report finds US energy production growing, consumption down</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356550412469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 14:33:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"U.S. energy consumption declined 3 percent between January and September compared with that period last year." Energy consumption is one of the most reliable indicators of economic activity there is. There has never been a case in US history when energy consumption dropped for so long as, and so fast, without there being a horrendous recession.... Theoretically energy consumption could drop because of efficiency but that is not why it is dropping...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356560032397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 17:13:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356561409248-20</Id><Topic><Title>Barney Frank To Take Senator Kerry's Seat!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356144530095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:48:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GFY greedful. I am not what you label me but you are a fascist. I don't play shades of gray very well and that is why I tell truth regardless of what party the lying thugs affiliate with. And don't forget who made you...</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356561409248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 17:36:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356561713491-21</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Manylumen you're insinuating that what happened in that school has to do with God stiking back because of people's gender and or sxual preference? You're a freak. And there are no "God haters" just people who are seeking freedom from religious zealots like you and the jihadi's that are trying to take over everyone else's freedom and replace it with your theocratic rules. GFY! You freak.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356561713491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 17:41:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356561945590-22</Id><Topic><Title>Barney Frank To Take Senator Kerry's Seat!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356144530095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:48:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>black liberation ideology is communist, which is no doubt where you picked up your lingo. It is communist lingo, wahleee boy, whether or not your ignorance keeps you in the dark on it. I do keep this id to torment you -and is working out well. I shall keep it I think. lol</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356561945590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 17:45:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356564414971-23</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh ye of no faith or knowledge! Heal thy self and seek the redemption that you are missing. I can help you if you want help.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1356564414971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 18:26:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356564711542-24</Id><Title>$16.4 trillion in climbing...</Title><Msg>Such a record...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356564711542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 18:31:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356564729016-25</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coming from a filthy hypocrite like you who elects politicians who want the poor to have less food and healthcare your advise rings hollow. You are the last person a peaceful god will redeem. But in your hypocritical salvation you can be the biggest MF r you want to be then so long as you pretend to be a "man of god" you'll be forgiven. A righteous god takes a hypocrite like you and casts you into he!! with Andy Breitbart.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356564729016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 18:32:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356565223172-26</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They deserve to be cast into He!!; so that divine Justice never stands in the Way, it makes no Objection against God’s using his Power at any Moment to destroy them. Yea, on the contrary, Justice calls aloud for an infinite Punishment of their Sins. Divine Justice says of the Tree that brings forth such Grapes of Sodom, Cut it down, why cumbreth it the Ground, Luk. 13. 7. Have you been reading Jonathan Edwards, wahleee boy? lol</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356565223172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 18:40:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356569334584-27</Id><Title>Dark Cloud</Title><Msg>on Blackheath Common a large oak was spotted being ripped from the soil by the wind. on Constitution Avenue a Grand Caravan was spotted its windows blackened... on a bleak day in January the omens heralded the sunset of a great land, its heritage rejected and cast into the tempest...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356569334584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 19:48:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356571522912-28</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahlee is a true communist rebel rouser. He will be deported from america for treason.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1356571522912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 20:25:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356571584722-29</Id><Topic><Title>$16.4 trillion in climbing...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356564711542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 18:31:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch what happens to the dumb poor #$%$ that voted dumbocrap.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1356571584722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 20:26:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356575514119-30</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huckabee is correct. We never had this kind of violence until God was forced out of the public schools. Kids went to school with hunting rifles in their trucks and there were no problems like we see today. Put your liberal pointed head in the sand and keep acting like #$%$ thinking govt is going to solve all your ills. Govt is the problem or you progressives would have solved all of this with your war on poverty,food stamp program, free housing,abortion on demand. Obama's kids have 11 armed guards protecting them at their PRIVATE school. Why can't kids have at least one at their public schools? You liberals deserve to die if you aren't willing to arm and defend youselves. Our children can't defend themselves. Those killed deserved better. Blaming the NRA or legal gun owners is a cop out as usual for you festering maggots. I can't stomach liberals because you are so caught up in your marxist idealogy that you have lost all common sense and reasoning abilities.</Msg><Username>eagle1776321</Username><Timestamp>1356575514119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 21:31:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356580600427-31</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Children were murdered by an assault weapon. The firefighters a few days ago were murdered by an assault rifle. Common denominator=Assault Rifle. As for Huckabee, Huckabee is a bloated snaked oil salesman.. And Your comments reveal how big of a #$%$ you are.. So how exactly was God "out of schools" ? Did they give him a bus? Did he get a cab ride? Last I checked the Pledge of Allegiance that kids read EVERY DAY states, " One Nation UNDER GOD" so #$%$ you #$%$.. In your world of hysterical right wing lies you throw in with the screwballs that claim these kids were abandoned by God and left to be slaughtered. Well if your God would do that then F him! And if you think that then F you! You miserable creep, climb back into your rathole and eat your bullets</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356580600427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 22:56:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356581113091-32</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh and on other thing eagledroppings. is that weasel who sits on NRA's board of Directors Grover Norquist gonna allow us to raise taxes to put "Armed Police" in every school? Someone has to pay. You hypocritical right wing losers talk out of both sides of your mouths. And your beloved NRA are nothing more than Corporate Lobbyists for Gun Manufacturers, They care about $$ not the Constitution you right wingers use as toilet paper. And take all your nonsense about people being communists and shove it. You call people who fought in WWII communists because they belonged to a Union. You baggers are trash. You have no respect for anyone or anything including life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness. You push your corporate sponsored theocratic garbage down everyones throat and could care less about liberty.. You're theocrats and fascists who are no different than the Taliban nor the 1930's Germans you aspire to be.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356581113091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 23:05:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356582257838-33</Id><Title>an inspirational song for all subjects of tyrants</Title><Msg>God save our gracious Queen! Long live our noble Queen! God save the Queen! Send her victorious, Happy and glorious, Long to reign over us: God save The Queen! O Lord our God arise, Scatter her enemies, And make them fall: Confound their politics, Frustrate their knavish tricks, On Thee our hopes we fix: God save us all. Thy choicest gifts in store, On her be pleased to pour; Long may she reign: May she defend our laws, And ever give us cause To sing with heart and voice God save the Queen!</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356582257838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 23:24:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356582652171-34</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet another demonstration of brain death by the poster boy for same.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1356582652171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 23:30:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356582899470-35</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One can understand the separation of church and state argument, still religion is a force for good. Bottom line is religious people dont do things like we saw in that new town school. One does not have to be a freak to see that religion is founded on creative forces not destructive forces.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1356582899470</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 23:34:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356584168419-36</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The important questions include: are there some common denominators in such tragic events and are there some signs or indications that could be used for prevention? crimes like those have nothing to do with the creative force of God, but rather that it has been driven out. Society would be wise to keep anything that the bible says is an abomination to god out and away from the classroom.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1356584168419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 23:56:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>