<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343110550000-1</Id><Title>Bush doubled welfare spending in just four years</Title><Msg>In Bush's first term, he doubled Federal social spending with a GOP House and Senate majorities. No Democrat in history has ever managed to achieve this.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1343110550000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 02:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343118787000-2</Id><Title>Hows that Outsourcing Candidate Mitt doing??</Title><Msg>India and China workers built that wealth. Yes slave labor works. How many AMERICAN JOBS were SHIPPED to India and China Mitt???</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1343118787000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 04:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343126820000-3</Id><Title>CNOOC’s Failed Unocal Bid Paved Way for Nexen Deal</Title><Msg>http://www.cnbc.com/id/48296409</Msg><Username>Low_Mac</Username><Timestamp>1343126820000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 06:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343135979000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Don't Bother Right Wingers It's Too Complex</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1343097625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 22:40:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walhiee, I believe deep down that you are striving to become like me: An anti-green, pro gun, Tea partying, Big Oiling individual, and are really insensitive to the plight of the left. You just throw this stuff out there to satisfy your copied coworkers to maintain employment in an extremely liberal environment.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1343135979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343140260000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Don't Bother Right Wingers It's Too Complex</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1343097625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 22:40:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/e52c592a-d4ad-11e1-bb88-00144feabdc0.html#axzz21Y9MLjXB</Msg><Username>epstein_susan</Username><Timestamp>1343140260000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343140977000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Don't Bother Right Wingers It's Too Complex</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1343097625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 22:40:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey cmontx, are you really Sherlock Holmes revealing the true Walhiee. I think you got it right! Well in Nov. we'll get rid of the biggest problem Obama and in time we'll have to deal with getting Romney straightened out and get our USA back on the right track. I continue with XOM's DRIP and am happy without losing any sleep. I see a nice $$$ profit in 5 yrs, + div's. What more could you ask.</Msg><Username>floridahank</Username><Timestamp>1343140977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:42:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343141511000-7</Id><Title>I would wait till earnings, should be good.</Title><Msg>They do well with 80 range oil</Msg><Username>riskreversal777</Username><Timestamp>1343141511000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343142032000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Don't Bother Right Wingers It's Too Complex</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1343097625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 22:40:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an intellectual Wahleee, you use your brains and abilities trying to make the World a better place for all, I've known that for a long time and that is why, for what it's worth, I've always supported you. We are all trapped on the space ship together, so at the end, we, or our descendants, will all share the same fate. Infernal will immediately accuse you of writing this, you and I both know you didn't, so let him bluster on. Good Morning Mr. Infernal, all the best to you Sir, he said, Cap in hand, as he sidled out the door taking care to stay out of range of Infernal's walking stick!</Msg><Username>carl_cessman</Username><Timestamp>1343142032000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:00:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343145001000-9</Id><Title>Middle East vs. Europe = Oil vs. Financials</Title><Msg>Syria vs. Greece Iran vs. Spain What will happen if Syria and Iran did something stupid and at the same time Greece and Spain did something stupid ? Which way would the oil trade and the market ?</Msg><Username>tom.jone15</Username><Timestamp>1343145001000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343145186000-10</Id><Title>Friday we were 86+, and oil was lower, BUY</Title><Msg>RIGHT NOW</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1343145186000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343145734000-11</Id><Title>QE1 QE2 The Fed 0%</Title><Msg>Ask yourself what the Fed has done for you: 1. Do the zero percent interest rates allow you to earn anything on your savings after a lifetime of hard work? 2. Have you do well in the stock market since the institution of QE1 QE2 and zero per cent rates? 3. Do you think your net worth and income are higher or lower because of QE1 QE2 and 0% rates? 4. How much has QE1, QE2, and 0% rates brought down unemployment? 5. How have these policies affected market volatility? 6. Who benefits from these policies: savers, investors, and workers or the federal government, banks, and Wall Street? 7. Is it right for savers to be forced to lend their money to banks corporations or the government for free or to be forced into overpriced stocks? 8. In summary what has Mr. Bernanke and the fed done for you??</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1343145734000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343145767000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Middle East vs. Europe = Oil vs. Financials</Title><Username>tom.jone15</Username><Timestamp>1343145001000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Goldman Sachs vs. Greece and Spain. Likud vs Iran and the World</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1343145767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343146041000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Friday we were 86+, and oil was lower, BUY</Title><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1343145186000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:53:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not that simple. Stock has been hitting a brick wall at 86-87 for the last 4+ years. More importantly earnings come out Thursday. I will leave it to you to look up how XOM has done on the days its earnings come out and the days shortly after. A hint: it hasn't been pretty for the last several years.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1343146041000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343147793000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Friday we were 86+, and oil was lower, BUY</Title><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1343145186000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:53:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Busted 84 again. Dismal. No matter how bad the market does this thing is worse. Five years of this. Need new management but won't happen. The XTO deal should have been enough to get the CEO fired in and of itself.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1343147793000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343150211000-15</Id><Title>KIOR...KIOR...KIOR.....biofuel..squeeze</Title><Msg>just spreading the outlook...................</Msg><Username>stock_advance_picker</Username><Timestamp>1343150211000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343155230000-16</Id><Title>your all too negative here, I'll see u when they meet EPS, last time 88</Title><Msg>after release.</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1343155230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343160874000-17</Id><Title>B.C. and Alberta premiers spar over pipeline revenue</Title><Msg>B.C. and Alberta premiers spar over pipeline revenue CBC News Posted: Jul 24, 2012 7:30 AM PT Last Updated: Jul 24, 2012 9:05 AM PT The premiers of B.C. and Alberta are squaring off over how to divide the revenues from Enbridge's proposed Northern Gateway pipeline — if the project ever goes ahead. B.C. Premier Christy Clark told CBC Radio on Tuesday morning that the province will only approve the project if it gets its fair share of the revenue from the proposed crude oil pipeline, in order to compensate the province for taking on the majority of the environmental risk. "Alberta's interests in this are pretty obvious. Alberta gets the large bulk of the benefits, takes very little of the risk. B.C. takes most of the risk and we get very few of the benefits. So I think it's pretty obvious that we have some talking to do here," said Clark. But Premier Alison Redford said in a statement on Monday that B.C. is pitting one province against another, rather than doing what is best for Canada as a whole. "Leadership is not about dividing Canadians and pitting one province against another. Leadership is about working together. That’s when our country benefits, that’s when Canada leads," said Redford. The two premiers are expected to meet in Halifax this week, but Alberta's strong reaction to B.C.'s proposal on Monday could lead to some tension in the room when the premiers begin their talks on Thursday. Redford was hoping to use this week's meeting of the Council of the Federation in Halifax to garner widespread support for her proposed national energy strategy. She talked up the idea with other western premiers at their meeting in late May, but Clark did not attend that gathering. Enbridge spokesman Todd Nogier called the debate over revenue an "opportunity," but said the existing deal would already give B.C. tangible benefits. "The tax revenue that would flow to the B.C. government would be $1.2 billion over the course of 30 years. There will be about 560 to 600 full-time jobs, good-paying full-time permanent positions," said Nogier Under the current terms, B.C. Environment Minister Terry Lake said Monday that British Columbia would get only eight per cent of the pipeline revenue while assuming 100 per cent of the marine risk for the port terminal and tanker traffic on the West Coast, and 58 per cent of the land-based risk for the pipeline. 'We need the market access' The Alberta premier also said the additional safety measures proposed by Enbridge last week should quell any concerns about the environmental risk. "The fact that pipelines are still by far the safest means by which to transport oil, significantly mitigate the environmental risk and weaken the B.C. government’s argument for compensation based on potential risk." Alberta Energy Minister Ken Hughes has also defended the Northern Gateway project, saying the pipeline review he ordered on Friday should take care of any safety concerns around the proposal. Alberta Intergovernmental Affairs Minister Cal Dallas also dismissed the idea of paying for B.C.'s approval. "We don't have any history of sharing in uranium in Saskatchewan or the vast mining resources that exist in Ontario and Quebec, and certainly with respect to forestry products and the like that move from west to east from British Columbia." http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/british-columbia/story/2012/07/24/bc-alberta-gateway-pipeline.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343160874000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343160910000-18</Id><Topic><Title>B.C. and Alberta premiers spar over pipeline revenue</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343160874000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:14:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dallas says Alberta was hoping to have full co-operation from B.C. in winning public support for the pipeline. "Obviously we're going to pursue every available option that we have. We need the market access. We need to move product to market." 5 criteria laid out by B.C. Premier Clark has yet to say if B.C. will give its approval to the controversial pipeline. "It hasn't even finished its environmental review. The company changed their proposal last week and I imagine it will change again before we get to the end of the process," Clark told CBC Radio. "So we don't have all the information yet, no one has all the information yet, no one has all the information and I don't think anyone could sensibly say well gee we know enough about it to be able to say yes or no at this stage," she said. B.C. has also yet to put a price tag on its approval of the project, but financial compensation is just one of the five criteria laid out by B.C. on Monday for its approval of the pipeline. "I can't put a number on that today, but I can say it doesn't matter what the number is if we can't make sure we do this in a way that protects the environment," said Lake. The other criteria include a successful completion of the federal review, upgrading the marine and land oil spill response capabilities at the federal and provincial levels, and addressing the legal requirements regarding First Nations' aboriginal and treaty rights. First Nations' and environmental concerns The new criteria are just the latest challenges for Enbridge's proposed $5.5-billion pipeline to link Alberta's oilsands with a West Coast tanker port, which is already facing stiff opposition from First Nations, environmentalists and B.C.'s opposition New Democrats. Forest Ethics spokeswoman Tzeporah Berman was one of several environmentalists to point out the unrefined crude oil the pipeline would carry would be particularly difficult to clean up in the event of a spill. "Bitumen is very hard to clean up. It sinks. So they say they're going to put world-class standards in place, but the fact is the risk is unacceptable," said Berman on Monday. B.C. Union of Indian Chiefs Grand Chief Stewart Phillip said he only got a call about the new criteria minutes before they were announced on Monday. "It was a very frantic phone call, two minutes trying to articulate the assurance for our aboriginal title and rights interest," said Phillip. Just last week, Enbridge announced plans to spend up to $500 million to improve Northern Gateway's safety features. But First Nations quickly dismissed the plan, saying they have no trust in Enbridge given the company's poor record when it comes to handling spills.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343160910000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343161024000-19</Id><Title>Nexen bid part of China’s plan to become resources powerhouse</Title><Msg>Nexen bid part of China’s plan to become resources powerhouse PAV JORDAN The Globe and Mail Published Monday, Jul. 23 2012, 10:32 PM EDT Last updated Tuesday, Jul. 24 2012, 9:17 AM EDT China is taking a historic step toward its ambition to become a global resources powerhouse with a $15.1-billion (U.S.) bid to buy Calgary-based oil producer Nexen Inc. The bid by state-backed CNOOC Ltd. is the largest by a Chinese firm for a foreign company, and confirms that Canada has become a proving ground for China’s rise in the global economic order as it deploys some of its trillions of dollars in foreign reserves to secure strategic resource properties around the world. More Related to this Story • China’s CNOOC to buy Nexen for $15.1-billion • Analysis CNOOC’s Nexen bid: A new test for Harper • Streetwise CNOOC offers goodies to pass foreign investment review The deal builds on a string of previous acquisitions by Chinese firms in Canada’s oil sands. It would be the second-largest deal ever in Canada’s energy sector and, if approved, the sixth-largest takeover ever in Canada. Though it may test the Harper government’s stance on foreign ownership, two years after it blocked a $39-billion (Canadian) takeover offer for Potash Corp. of Saskatchewan Inc., there are strong indications that the deal will be approved. For one, CNOOC, China’s third-largest oil company, has cultivated relationships with top players in Ottawa in recent years. In March, CNOOC executive Fang Zhi met with deputy ministers from Natural Resources Canada, International Trade and Industry Canada to discuss its acquisition ambitions in Canada, in general terms. The Prime Minister’s Office was advised of the deal on Sunday. And because most of Nexen’s oil output comes from outside Canada, most analysts expect CNOOC’s offer to eventually win the blessing of Prime Minister Stephen Harper, who has actively courted Chinese investment in Canada during visits to China. In a friendly takeover deal announced Monday morning, CNOOC (originally known as China National Offshore Oil Corp.) offered $27.50 (U.S.) in cash for each share of Nexen – valuing the company at more than 60 per cent above its closing price on Friday. Nexen and CNOOC were already partners in a heavy oil development at Long Lake, southeast of Fort McMurray, that has so far fallen short of its investors’ hopes. “We are in Canada to invest,” CNOOC chief executive Li Fanrong told reporters in a conference call. “We intend to be a local company as much as a global one.” In a statement, Industry Minister Christian Paradis said CNOOC has indicated it will soon file for approval from Investment Canada, and a decision depends on whether the deal would provide a “net benefit” to Canada. Among the factors to be considered are the effect on employment and economic activity, the level of participation by Canadians in the business, and the impact of productivity and technological development. The Nexen deal was announced almost simultaneously with a $1.5-billion deal by China’s top refiner, Sinopec Corp., to acquire a 49-per-cent stake in the North Sea operations of Talisman, one of Canada’s top oil and gas exploration companies. http://www.theglobeandmail.com/report-on-business/nexen-bid-part-of-chinas-plan-to-become-resources-powerhouse/article4436971/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343161024000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343161066000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Nexen bid part of China’s plan to become resources powerhouse</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343161024000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“The slogan of the Chinese government for their major companies is to go global,” said Richard Herd, the chief China economist for the Organization of Economic Cooperation and Development. “They are hoping they can earn better returns in resources in direct investment abroad than they can in investing in U.S. treasuries.” China has been largely responsible for a global commodities boom that started over a decade ago when it went to international markets to acquire materials needed for massive industrialization of its economy, including oil and gas, copper, metallurgical coal and iron ore. At the same time the giant Asian economy began encouraging its large resource companies to become producers instead of just buyers of strategic materials. Until about a year ago, prices for those commodities enjoyed record highs, before they began to fall on mounting economic turbulence in Europe, a still-struggling U.S. economy and slowing growth in China. “They are trying to secure access to resources on a long-term basis,” said Michael Amm, a China specialist at Torys law firm who thinks China is still in the early stages of its commodities buying spree. “We’re certainly in the middle of the beginning.” The deals also reflects a world where growing political risks in regions like Africa may push Chinese firms to balance their portfolios with investments in more stable jurisdictions. “I think this is the tip of the iceberg in deals in the oil patch,” said Keith Spence, president of Toronto-based Global Mining Capital, a boutique financial advisory firm that advises Chinese firms buying Canadian resources. “I think you are going to see a lot more deals in the next while. Right now we have three or four assignments specifically looking for Chinese oil and gas deals.” .............................................................................................. The following are China’s most notable energy deals in Canada:</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343161066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343173155000-21</Id><Topic><Title>your all too negative here, I'll see u when they meet EPS, last time 88</Title><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1343155230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it when people claim 'XOM missed by ...' In reality, XOM doesn't make any claims on earnings and do not provide future guidance. So XOM basically can not miss. They issue the earnings perfectly everytime. They get it exactly correct. The ones who miss are the analyst reading their crystal balls and tea leaves. Then when they get it wrong they shout XOM missed. To them I say BS, you just ain't gotta clue, your wild @ss guess was wrong so it was you who missed.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1343173155000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343173420000-22</Id><Topic><Title>QE1 QE2 The Fed 0%</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1343145734000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:02:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interest rates would be very low even without the Federal Reserve. Free Trade is enormously deflationary as it floods the market with cheap products, and increases unemployment which keeps wages down and purchasing power low. The high unemployment also causes loan defaults and discouraging lending... The choice is not between earnings nothing in cash and something in stocks. Rather the choice is earning nothing in cash and losing money in stocks as they fall with deflation...Europe's debt situation is becoming critical which will make the deflationary winds howl louder.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1343173420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343177917000-23</Id><Topic><Title>QE1 QE2 The Fed 0%</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1343145734000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:02:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting post but how is there deflation when my health insurance premium just went up another 31%, my dentist raised his fees 15%, my prescriptions ( no unusual medications) are up 15% this year, gasoline has been $3.60 to $4 all year, food has been skyrocketing for years (I gave up meat because it's so expensive and my bills at the supermarket are still going up insanely, natural gas may be down but my utilities never stop going up. The more necessary something is to live the more it's been going up. I haven't even mentioned tuition. NOTHING I need is going down in price EVERYTHING is going up, a lot. There may be things that are going down (maybe iPads cell phones computing power etc) but they are all things many people don't use and unfortunately I can't eat this things, put them in my gas tank, or use them to treat my blood pressure. ,EV</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1343177917000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 20:58:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343178546000-24</Id><Topic><Title>QE1 QE2 The Fed 0%</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1343145734000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:02:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The general price level will be bounded by the amount of credit in the economy, which is a function of the money supply, and more importantly the willingness to leverage given quantities of money by credit extension. The supply of credit will not rise with this much unemployment and floods of cheap foreign products running industry out of business. Some prices can rise in a deflationary environment by collecting more of the economy's credit and purchasing power, leaving less for other areas. If healthcare prices or gasoline prices rises that will lower other prices, namely stocks. The government taxing people to pay for higher and higher healthcare expenditure will lower corporate profits and stock prices as well...Whether they borrow or tax the result will be the same.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1343178546000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 21:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343181399000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Brace Yourself For Another XOM Surprise.. SELL NOW?</Title><Username>johnskelly271</Username><Timestamp>1343135747000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:15:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like a fresh air your post runs into my heart through the window of my PC.Thanks for being so articulate.</Msg><Username>carrollraymundo473</Username><Timestamp>1343181399000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 21:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343184191000-26</Id><Title>KiOR Passes A Major Hurdle; Still Faces Several More</Title><Msg>KiOR Passes A Major Hurdle; Still Faces Several More July 24, 2012 | 4 commentsby: Tristan R. Brown | about: KIOR KiOR (KIOR) investors were overjoyed to learn today that the EPA has granted the company Part 79 registration for its cellulosic gasoline product, judging by the fact that the share price is up more than 13% at the time of writing. This is a significant milestone as it makes KiOR the first U.S. company to receive EPA permission to sell cellulosic gasoline domestically. (Cellulosic gasoline is different from cellulosic ethanol in that, as the name suggests, it is chemically identical to petroleum-based gasoline and avoids many of the fuel equipment and infrastructure limitations encountered by ethanol.) Part 79 registration is required by all fuel and fuel additive producers before they can sell their product within the U.S. In a nutshell, it is a seal of approval from the EPA with regard to the product's impacts on public health. Today's news removes some uncertainty from the cellulosic biofuels industry, as there has been no guarantee until now that cellulosic gasoline is capable of satisfying the requirements of Part 79. It is very important news for KiOR simply because the company would not be able to sell its main product in the U.S. without the EPA's permission, which it now has. That said, this simply means that the EPA will allow KiOR to compete with petroleum refiners; whether the market will allow it to compete successfully is another matter entirely. KiOR still faces two major hurdles on the road to long-term economic feasibility, both of which it will need to overcome. The first is the establishment of a binding cellulosic biofuel mandate under the RFS2, without which cellulosic biofuel producers such as KiOR cannot expect to compete economically with petroleum refiners in the near term. It is not guaranteed that this will occur in 2012, as there is a good chance that the EPA will either bow to "Big Oil" pressure and voluntarily waive the mandate as it has in the past, or be forced to do so by either the courts or Congress. The second hurdle is the achievement of high gasoline yields from biomass feedstock, without which KiOR will not be able to generate the low gasoline production costs needed to compete with petroleum refiners in the long term. I shall remain skeptical that these yields are possible until I either see them generated via catalytic pyrolysis on a commercial-scale basis or reported in the peer-reviewed literature, as the yield data that I have seen is much lower than will be needed. Today KiOR cleared an important regulatory hurdle. It still faces equally daunting policy and scientific hurdles that must be surmounted before the company can achieve economic feasibility, however. Investors in the company can let out a sigh of relief, but further celebration isn't warranted by today's news. Disclosure: I am long KIOR. http://seekingalpha.com/article/743621-kior-passes-a-major-hurdle-still-faces-several-more KiOR Passes A Major Hurdle; Still Faces Several More Seeking Alpha - ‎8 hours ago</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343184191000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 22:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>