<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347337754267-1</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Novemeber yet? So we can put 0bama on unemployment</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1347289939431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:12:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have never had 100% employment but there were a LOT more people employed when Bush left office than there are now. Thanks Obamao. "snicker"</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347337754267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347338156029-2</Id><Title>Larry Flynt supports Obamao</Title><Msg>Of course - he knows that Democrats boo God and favor porn.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347338156029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:35:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347352634835-3</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Flynt supports Obamao</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347338156029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:35:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep dirty rotten commie dumbocraps. One thing no one has figured in and that is the hand of God. Watch out he is PO.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347352634835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 04:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347370401665-4</Id><Title>Linn Co-op to get boost with E15 sales</Title><Msg>Linn Co-op to get boost with E15 sales The Linn Co-op Oil Co. in Marion will get a big helping of promotional support next week as it becomes one of the first Iowa fuel retailers to offer E15 for mainstream vehicles. The Iowa Renewable Fuels Association announced Monday that it’s launched an advertising campaign to promote E15. The campaign is co-sponsored by the Iowa Corn Growers. Billboards announcing the availability of E15 at Linn Co-op and a Sept. 21 open house have been erected at 1250 Blairs Ferry Road and 895 Seventh Ave., Marion. The billboards will be changed to a branding message on Sept. 24, and will be up until Oct. 7. The slogan for the campaign will be “The roads of Iowa will never be the same.” Campaign messages will emphasize the cost savings and performance benefits of E15, according to association officials. The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency approved rules allowing retailers to sell the 15 percent ethanol fuel blend for 2001 vehicles in June, and Linn Co-op was among the first five retailers to receive an EPA approval letter to sell the fuel. Linn Co-op Oil Co. was ready to begin selling E15 in July, but it was not available at local petroleum terminals, and it was was too costly to transport E15 from terminals that had it. The co-op will offer an E15 pump at its 325 35th St., Marion, facility. Jim Becthold, service manager for the co-op, said he expects E15 to retail for about 5 cents less per gallon than E10, the 10 percent ethanol blend. Becthold said it’s anybody’s guess how many motorists will switch over from E10 to E15. “It could be anywhere from 20 percent to 80 percent, I have no idea,” Becthold said. “I’d like to see 50 percent.” Becthold said the Sept. 21 open house will feature a 15 cent-per-gallon discount on E15, and free hot dogs with chips from 11 a.m. to 1 p.m. “We’re excited that we’re only a week away from having E15 available for all 2001 and newer vehicles,” said Lucy Norton, the association’s managing director. “It has been a very long time coming and we’re enthusiastic about Linn Co-op’s first-in-the-state status.” Becthold said he expects a few other cooperatives in Iowa to begin selling E15 at about the same time. Many cooperatives have a high percentage of members who are stakeholders in the success of ethanol, through corn-growing or investment in ethanol plants. Becthold said the leadership by co-ops mirrors the situation when ethanol was first introduced in the 1970s. Co-ops also have been among the early adopters of blender pumps, which allow motorists to adjust the percentage of ethanol they want in fueling their flex fuel vehicles. While the blender pumps can be set to provide E15 to flex fuel vehicles, most of the flex fuel vehicle owners preferred higher ethanol blends if they were at a blender pump. Representatives of Iowa’s largest gasoline retailers, Casey’s General Store and... ------------------------------------------ New Billboard Touts E15 to Iowa Motorists Posted by John Davis – September 10th, 2012 A new billbord courtesy of the Iowa Renewable Fuels Association introduces E15 to motorists in in Marion, Iowa. This IRFA news release says the new billboard will go up at Linn Co-op Oil Company, the first EPA-approved retailer in Iowa to sell E15 for 2001 and newer vehicles, SUVs, and light-duty trucks. “We’re excited that we’re only a week away from having E15 available for all 2001 and newer vehicles,” said Lucy Norton, IRFA Managing Director. “It has been a very long time coming and we’re enthusiastic about Linn Co-op’s first-in-the-state status.” ‘The Roads of Iowa will Never be the Same’ is the theme for the campaign that will be extended throughout September to include other media and direct mail. The billboards are a way to introduce E15 to Marion residents by touting the cost-savings and performance benefits of the latest fuel to receive EPA approval. This campaign is being co-sponsored by Iowa Corn Growers. IRFA points out that the Hawkeye State (or maybe more accurately after this weekend’s game, the “Cyclone State”) is a leader in renewable fuels production with 41 ethanol refineries capable of producing nearly 3.7 billion gallons annually and one new facility under construction and another 3 biodiesel facilities able to produce 320 million gallons annually. domesticfuel</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347370401665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347371457562-5</Id><Topic><Title>Linn Co-op to get boost with E15 sales</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347370401665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production 8/31/2012 ETHANOL Production rises, Stocks climb but Demand as a % of gasoline demand falls.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347371457562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347372756240-6</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Novemeber yet? So we can put 0bama on unemployment</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1347289939431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:12:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whichever candidate wins, rest assured that the next presidency will also be a failure.The best thing about an Obama victory would be the defeat of the Republican hate machine and its shameless manipulation of the minds of the ignorant.</Msg><Username>co1trane</Username><Timestamp>1347372756240</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347376865080-7</Id><Title>Lagging again</Title><Msg>Once again lagging all the averages and other oil stocks by huge margin today. Remains 7 to 8 points below where it was 4 years ago. Stock once was 20 points above CVX now 25 points lower. Shows the importance of the quality of management. XTO deal ranks as possibly the stupidest, most wealth destroying acquisition ever by a major corporation and share owners paying dearly for it in terms of stock performance.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1347376865080</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347378278702-8</Id><Topic><Title>What will be the price of unleaded gasoline in four years?</Title><Username>water_skipper</Username><Timestamp>1347209366094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:49:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The price of gasoline in the US is determined by the international price of oil. It is a wonderful example of the Republicans manipulation of the minds of the ignorant that they have successfully blamed Obama because the price of gasoline is higher today than it was 4 years ago. What was the international price of oil 4 years ago, and what is it today?</Msg><Username>co1trane</Username><Timestamp>1347378278702</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347382731236-9</Id><Topic><Title>What will be the price of unleaded gasoline in four years?</Title><Username>water_skipper</Username><Timestamp>1347209366094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:49:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The price of unleaded gasoline will depend on the international price of oil. There is nothing much that the president of the US can do to affect the international price of oil.</Msg><Username>co1trane</Username><Timestamp>1347382731236</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:58:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347386809382-10</Id><Title>Moodys Warns - Obama Sleeps</Title><Msg>Another step closer to the fiscal cliff.And if we go over those who will suffer will be the poor and middle class.The poor will fall to the street the middle class will become poor.Seriously. Meanwhile the President whistles a happy tune and has no serious plan to prevent this catastrophe.Obama is,above all,the greatest threat to the poor and middle class in this country's history.There's no countdown to the crises.It will come with little imminent warning,in the middle of the night,signaled as always by rumblings in global markets.What will follow is a global crash signaling ugly times ahead. THEN you'll see Dems and Repubs working together,getting something done finally.It will be done in a state of emergency called AUSTERITY.Every social program the poor and unemployed rely on will be slashed,slashed some more and then slashed again.Once austerity is imposed there's no way out other than massive immediate cuts. Idealogically,Obama is nowhere.A "liberal" with no plans to avoid this potential horror show for the poor.He rejects the successful ideas from around the globe,even those of liberal left govts. Instead he magically transforms those ideas when they cross the US border and calls them "right wing",evidence be damned. This guy is a peril to the entire populace yet the media remains on cruise control and along with 'em - the public.This should be no contest.There's no alternative but to choose the alternative to Obama - and hope for the best.In fact Romney couldn't be more well suited for the task at hand. He certainly understands business.He rescued the 2002 Olympics from a total disaster [300 million in the red] and made it a success,politically and financially.As Gov. he got along well with Dems who controlled the state legislature.And he left office a popular Republican in a state dominated by liberal politics.It's a no brainer.We're on the verge of a crises and this guy fixes stuff.And he's proven he can work across the aisle. It's time to move on...........</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1347386809382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347388923282-11</Id><Title>Congressional report warns drones could track faces, never leave sky</Title><Msg>Congressional report warns drones could track faces, never leave sky By Brendan Sasso - 09/11/12 10:30 AM ET The use of drones in American skies raises new questions about the value of privacy and the extent of government surveillance, according to a report released last week by the Congressional Research Service. It is not clear how courts will apply constitutional privacy protections to drones, but the report notes that Congress could enact laws to restrict the ability of police to use the technology. Domestic drones are now uncommon, but the Federal Aviation Administration has predicted that within 20 years, 30,000 commercial and government drones could be flying in U.S. skies. Drones are cheaper to build and fly than manned aircraft, making them more useful to the government for aerial surveillance. Some drones are the size of traditional jets but others — called "nano drones" — can be as small as an insect. Drones could also be equipped with other surveillance technologies to identify people or license plates. "In the near future, law enforcement organizations might seek to outfit drones with facial recognition or soft biometric recognition, which can recognize and track individuals based on attributes such as height, age, gender and skin color," the researchers write. A drone from Lockheed Martin called the "Stalker" can be recharged from the ground using a laser. The report predicts that in the future, drones could theoretically stay in the sky forever. Analyzing past court cases, the researchers conclude that police would likely have to obtain a search warrant to use nano drones or heat sensing imaging to spy on people within their homes. But the report writes that it is unclear how courts will treat drone surveillance of a person's backyard, swimming pool, deck or porch. The Supreme Court has held that police do not need warrants to fly helicopters or airplanes over people's homes and gather evidence. The justices concluded that the areas were in public view and the people should have had limited expectations of privacy. The courts could treat drones similarly to other aircraft or they may decide that they raise more serious privacy concerns. Drones can stay in the air longer than manned aircraft and can hover in one place, the researchers note. "This capability may sway a court’s determination of whether certain types of warrant-less drone surveillance are compatible with the Fourth Amendment," the researchers write. Lawmakers have introduced several bills this session to limit how police can use drones to gather information. Rep. Austin Scott (R-Ga.) and...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347388923282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:42:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347389820597-12</Id><Title>EPA official: GOP bill would 'cripple' global climate efforts</Title><Msg>EPA official: GOP bill would 'cripple' global climate efforts By Zack Colman - 09/11/12 01:32 PM ET An Environmental Protection Agency official said during a Tuesday hearing that a House Republican-sponsored bill would “cripple” the agency’s ability to reduce greenhouse gas emissions. The House Energy and Commerce subcommittee on Energy and Power hearing discussed a bill (H.R. 4255) that would eliminate EPA’s ability to offer financial assistance for international greenhouse gas reduction activities. Subcommittee Chairman Ed Whitfield (R-Ky.), the bill's sponsor, called it a “non-controversial bill.” He packaged the bill as a way to cut the federal deficit, though EPA has spent just $140 million on such foreign grants since 2001 – most of which were authorized under former President George W. Bush. Republicans said deficit cutting has to start somewhere, acknowledging that the total tab for EPA's foreign grants program is minor. But Whitfield said the programs -- such as a $400,000 program to study urban air quality in Indonesia and $141,000 to test swine manure -- were frivolous when domestic infrastructure and economy need money. "We can’t maintain our roads, bridges and domestic programs, but yet we have money to give China to study swine manure," Whitfield said. "Something doesn’t smell right in this situation." Craig Hooks, EPA assistant administrator in the Office of Administration and Resource Management, disagreed. “The EPA believes that HR 4255 will cripple the agency’s ability through grants to address harmful air pollutants that affect both the global and domestic environment,” Hooks said in written testimony. “Air pollution from overseas sources represents a growing problem for public health globally and here in the United States.” The bill in question at the Tuesday hearing underscored the divide between Democrats and Republicans on the nation’s role in international climate change agreements. Democrats backed a global climate deal in their platform during the Democratic National Convention last week. President Obama has also championed his efforts to strike international climate agreements. GOP presidential candidate Mitt Romney stated in a recent questionnaire that U.S. efforts to regulate greenhouse gas emissions would have little effect without coordinated international action. However, Romney did not call for increased U.S. leadership in that department. Instead, he said the U.S. should end "unilateral" actions to limit greenhouse gases because they would be ineffective and hurt the economy. Rep. Henry Waxman (D-Calif.), the top Democrat on the House Energy and Commerce Committee, said such stances present a “cynical Catch 22” in GOP policy on climate change. “When EPA proposes to crack down on U.S. emissions of greenhouse gasses, Republicans on the Committee say that unilateral climate change harms U.S. competitiveness. They say they want an international solution,” Waxman said in written testimony. “But when EPA makes grants to build global support for reducing emissions of methane or black carbon, which contribute to climate change, the same members attack EPA for spending U.S. funds abroad,”...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347389820597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347390277623-13</Id><Title>Very weird, it's lower than the open, when Dow was up 20</Title><Msg>hmmmmmmmmm</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1347390277623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:04:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347390304489-14</Id><Title>I think it can get above 90</Title><Msg>then fall</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1347390304489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:05:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347391942157-15</Id><Title>89.80 close</Title><Msg>I Wanna short it thr</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1347391942157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347392626036-16</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Novemeber yet? So we can put 0bama on unemployment</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1347289939431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:12:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction, when Bush left office the nation was losing minus 700,000 jobs a month fact... Since Obama took office the nation has only been gaining plus 150,000 (on average) jobs a month give or take a few thousand. The GOP is not interested in job creation other then in the Far East, to create higher corporate profits on cheap labor costs...That is not going to change with a Romney/Ryan administration, since they have always been in the pockets of the lobbyists of corporate America. Romney can't even identify with a middle class America's needs, I.E. the end of Medicare in favor of a voucher system, give me a break! Once repealed Medicare will never be reinstated,,and yea Granny and Gran pa's coverage will be next.And for what? So the 1% can keep more of their millions tax free, as they trickle down on the economy.I may not be happy with" Obama Care", but it is at least amendable, and plus150k jobs monthly, is better then minus 700K jobs monthly, and the return of the Bush days.</Msg><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1347392626036</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347394470473-17</Id><Topic><Title>Is it Novemeber yet? So we can put 0bama on unemployment</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1347289939431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:12:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More mindless propaganda. You're a good little lemming.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347394470473</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347395434661-18</Id><Topic><Title>Moodys Warns - Obama Sleeps</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1347386809382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't Moody's the same people who falsely puffed up the credit ratings of all those bad derivatives? It would seem their opinions are more suspicious than reliable.</Msg><Username>westsbest0304</Username><Timestamp>1347395434661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347402453098-19</Id><Topic><Title>Moodys Warns - Obama Sleeps</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1347386809382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's called the "Fiscal Cliff" for a reason.Moody's didn't create it.They just rate solvency.If their timing is spot on or way off doesn't matter.And since there is no other countdown to catastrophe it's the best we've got.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1347402453098</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347403229237-20</Id><Title>Stopping Line 9: Communities mobilize for Ontario's tar sands battle</Title><Msg>Stopping Line 9: Communities mobilize for Ontario's tar sands battle By Dave Vasey | September 11, 2012 The Northern Gateway pipeline might be dead in the water for now, but Enbridge's Line 9 could be pumping tar sands through Ontario soon (more here and here). Tar sands are already being refined at an estimated rate of 225,000 barrels/day in Sarnia, Ontario's chemical valley, termed the most polluted place on earth by the National Geographic Society. For local First Nations, Enbridge continues a pattern of ignoring, marginalizing, and tokenizing community concerns. In the history of 'Canada' this is nothing new and neither is the action communities are taking to protect their lands. Originally termed the 'Trail Breaker' project, the Line 9 reversal was scrapped after substantive community resistance in the municipality of Dunham, Quebec and in the U.S. northeast. Using Orwellian language, Enbridge tabled the project due to a "lack of commercial support." No proper consultation with First Nations In September 2011, Trail Breaker was revived as 'Line 9 Reversal Phase 1' and community outreach events began, characterized by rhetorical presentations to town councils. To date, First Nation communities have not been properly consulted and community meetings by Enbridge have not been held on reservations. Enbridge claims Line 9 has 'no significant impact to Aboriginal communities' in its internal assessment, though Line 9 run is literally across the street from Amjiwnaang First Nation and runs directly through the Haldimand Tract. Indeed, the Haudenosaunee Development Institute, Aamijiwnaang First Nation and Onieda Nation all submitted concerns to Enbridge and the National Energy Board (NEB) about the project. On July 27, 2012 the NEB approved Phase 1 of the Line 9 reversal almost two years to the date after the infamous Enbridge Kalamazoo spill of 20,000 barrels of tar sands dilbit in Michigan. Forebodingly, Enbridge spilled 1000 barrels in Wisconsin the same day as Line 9's approval. Between 1999 and 2010 Enbridge had 804 spills that dumped 161,000 barrels of oil onto lands and into water. Residents of Kalamazoo have documented how Enbridge has failed to clean up the 2010 spill, leaving the ecosystem devastated and communities concerned about their health. Tellingly, in July 2012 Enbridge walked out of a 'community outreach' event in London, Ontario when Haudenosaunee land defenders and allies demanded Enbridge acknowledge community concerns about Line 9 (see video's here and here). Environmental racism In tar sands politics, there has been a callous disregard for local concerns and blatant environmental racism demonstrated by governments and corporations. Additionally, tar sands dilbit has proven destructive to aging pipeline infrastructure and refineries. In May 2011, 28,000 barrels of tar sands crude spilt near Little Buffalo in the Lubicon Cree's traditional territory. Clean up efforts have been questionable as community members have identified areas in the region still massively contaminated by oil. Indeed, during the past two decades of oil and gas development in Alberta, $6 billion has been pirated from Lubicon lands, though community households have no running water. Canada has been condemned three times by the United Nations for its treatment of the Lubicon Cree people. An incident earlier this summer in Berkley, California further proved dilbit is incompatible with aging infrastructure. On August 6, 2012, a Chevron refinery processing dilbit blew up and local workers and community residents paid the price with hospital bills and housing value collapses. For years, the community had documented increased accident rates at the Chevron facility, located in a predominantly poor and black neighborhood. The parallels with Aamijiwnaang First Nation in Sarnia are apparent (more here and here). At ground zero Alberta, communities continue to be poisoned but also to resist further tar sands encroachment. Elders and community activists throughout Alberta have reported extreme ecological change and cancer epidemics (see videos here and here). Alberta Health has confirmed cancer increases of 30 per cent in Fort Chipewyan, though to date Harper will not fund a health study or respect First Nations sovereignty by acknowledging the shocking change tar sands has brought to traditional lands. Tar sands activism building momentum Instead, Harper has effectively cut off all funding for health and environmental studies in an effort to silence voices on the front lines of tar sands development. However, the Athabasca Chipewyan First Nation has taken Shell to court to demand the company fulfill its obligations to the community around health and education. Additionally, the Beaver Lake Cree have 'won' the right for their case to be heard against the government of Alberta, which cites over 20,000 separate Treaty violations as well as a decline of 74 per cent for caribou populations. When members of the Athabasca Tribal Council similarly expressed concerns about wildlife impact from tar sands, the Alberta government responded with a barbaric and unnecessary wolf-culling program. Community leaders and activists have told these stories to international media, and momentum on tar sands activism has been substantive. Texans are blockading the Keystone XL and the Northern Gateway is being blocked through the political will of over 110 First Nations and a collective memory of land theft and homeland destruction. In August 2012, the Third Annual Tar Sands Healing Walk was held and youth from both Six Nations and Aamijiwnaang First Nation were there to share stories with communities from Alberta and B.C., as well as witness tar sands destruction first hand. In Ontario, communities are mobilizing around Line 9 through a network of communities including the April 28th Coalition and Indigenous Environmental Network, amongst others. At the local level, Line 9 represents an important struggle for Indigenous and non-Indigenous action. Enbridge has largely ignored the fact that Line 9 crosses the Haldimand Tract and that changing the contents from light crude to tar sands crude is extremely dangerous. According to the 1701 Treaty, most of Line 9 passes through Six Nations lands. Six Nations has taken important stands to protect their lands both historically and in the recent past. Six Nations' struggle in Caledonia, at Dump Site 41 and in Dundalk has built an important network of allies throughout southern Ontario and effectively stopped each project in its tracks. In Aamijiwnaang First Nation, a lawsuit put froth by EcoJustice and community members targets the Ontario government's approval of a Suncor tar sands smoke stack which has been knowingly operating at above acceptable human health limits. Aamijiwnaang has 63 chemical refineries within 50 km of the community. Community-monitoring has reported that 40 per cent of the population required inhalers to breath and 39 per cent of women had experienced miscarriages. It is one of the most blatant cases of environmental racism in North America. In global geopolitics, Line 9 represents access to European and U.S. northeast markets as well as an ideological displacement of 'foreign' oil in southern Ontario/Quebec. Despite rhetoric about 'ethical oil' from the far right government, the tar sands are a war-time project. Canada is still occupying Afghanistan and profiteering from oil market destabilization; Bush and Blair were both just declared war criminals by Nobel Peace winning intellectual Desmond Tutu. Indeed, Canada has long participated in oil pirating and the U.S. war machine and Conservative/Liberal elites have negotiated the terms. Pratt's 1976 The Tar Sands: Syncrude and the politics of oil documents far right narratives of the need for war in the Middle East, 'free trade,' and U.S. tar sands markets (read: military bases) as necessary ingredients for 'economically viable' tar sands production. Pratt also documents the impact on local First Nations and highlights community calls for environmental monitoring. It was not until 2011 that monitoring stations in Alberta began testing for tar sands toxins and Harper cut their funding this year. Those in finance, politics and oil profiteering should take notice -- the math is out on tar sands and it's apparent: both government and industry will sacrifice communities in the name of 'economics' and 'capitalism.' Aamijiwnaang, Six Nations, Fort Chipewyan, Lubicon, and other Indigenous communities are trapped in an apartheid system that is literally killing their communities with pollution and poverty. However, in the age of austerity, global revolt, and increased consciousness of the impact of capitalism on oppressed people, the same old dog and pony show is not gonna fly this time around. Ontario's tar sands battle is here and ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347403229237</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347407243523-21</Id><Title>OVERNIGHT ENERGY: Senate goes nuclear</Title><Msg>OVERNIGHT ENERGY: Senate goes nuclear By Ben Geman and Zack Colman - 09/11/12 06:02 PM ET State of Play: Wednesday will bring heavy Senate focus on battles over nuclear power plant safety and waste. Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) Chairwoman Allison Macfarlane will make her first appearance before the Senate since winning confirmation to the post in late June. She will testify at the Environment and Public Works Committee hearing about the NRC’s steps to boost safety in light of the March 2011 disaster at Japan’s Fukushima Daiichi power plant. Battles over the scope and pace of the NRC's post-Fukushima safety reforms for U.S. plants have unfolded since the accident. Macfarlane will appear alongside the NRC’s four other commissioners. Senate lawmakers will also plunge into a topic that has vexed Congress and policymakers for decades: what to do with nuclear waste piling up at the nation's power plants. The Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee will gather Wednesday to discuss a bill aimed at breaking the logjam. The bill would implement recommendations from a January report by the Blue Ribbon Commission on America’s Nuclear Future. President Obama, who has dropped long-delayed plans for the Yucca Mountain waste dump, formed the commission to evaluate the nation’s handling of nuclear waste. The commission recommended developing interim storage sites to hold the waste accumulating at nuclear power reactors; restarting efforts to build one or more permanent disposal sites; and establishing a new independent federal body to assume oversight duties from the Energy Department. Committee Chairman Jeff Bingaman (D-N.M.), who is retiring this session, has acknowledged his bill will not pass this year. He could not agree on language with Sens. Dianne Feinstein (D-Calif.), Lamar Alexander (R-Tenn.) and ranking member Lisa Murkowski (R-Alaska). But Bingaman has cast the bill as a step toward ending the nation’s impasse over nuclear waste...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347407243523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347413676266-22</Id><Topic><Title>Moodys Warns - Obama Sleeps</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1347386809382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Moody's didn't create it' You're wrong. They played an integral role in allowing the fiscal collapse of 2008 by incorrectly or worse yet colluded regarding "rating solvency". Moody's is a self important entity that adds nothing to the betterment of our financial well being. And I'd go even further and say they're a criminal enterprise considering their recent collusion in knowingly incorrectly " rating solvency". So for me dismissing them as hot air is where the best I could say for them.</Msg><Username>westsbest0304</Username><Timestamp>1347413676266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 21:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>