<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351835892733-1</Id><Topic><Title>Wind Farm Operating Costs Fall 38% in Four Years, BNEF Says</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351799585895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:53:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Construction cost of a power plant can be dimensioned as dollars per megawatt, but operating cost in dollars per megawatt is essentially meaningless. Electricity is bought and sold in units of energy (e.g., megawatt-hrs). Operating and maintenance costs occur over a period of time as does the production of electrical energy. Typically, when an article on alternative energy fails to mentioning the cost per unit energy generated or provides meaningless information, it is because the alternative energy being discussed is not competitive with conventional energy sources.</Msg><Username>cntplshtrd</Username><Timestamp>1351835892733</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 01:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351869519675-2</Id><Topic><Title>Blame Obama ...........LOL</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1351811777000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:16:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If obama happens to be re-elected, who will he blame for the past four years......kind of scary isn't it.....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351869519675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:18:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351869906539-3</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your comparison is horse manure.. You know the stuff between your ears that stinks like the pollution you consumed to get you where you are. WAHLIEEEEEEEEE.......THE NEXT TIME YOU WANT TO SAY SOMETHING RAISE YOUR HAND THEN PUT IT OVER YOUR MOUTH.....STUPIDITY SHOULDN'T BE ALLOWED TO BREED....BE SURE YOU HAVE PLENTY OF CONDOMS....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351869906539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 11:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351872344373-4</Id><Title>Hitt the SELL button and run like hell</Title><Msg>This b*tch is set to be dumped big time !!!!</Msg><Username>jbuishot</Username><Timestamp>1351872344373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351878073113-5</Id><Topic><Title>Hitt the SELL button and run like hell</Title><Username>jbuishot</Username><Timestamp>1351872344373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 12:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean you or your wife ??</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1351878073113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 13:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351879527134-6</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>Big miserable dog getting ready to break 90 again. Stock remains below May of 2008 price. Rotten production every quarter. Worst acquisition in history of business (XTO). Ineptness of management would be laughable if it were not so costly to shareholders.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1351879527134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351879718849-7</Id><Title>Remember, DIVIDEND x-date is Wednesday</Title><Msg>so.... don't go too short. haha</Msg><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1351879718849</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:08:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351883527978-8</Id><Title>WHO SAVED THE MIDDLE CLASS AUTO JOBS ? O B A M A 2012 !!! PERIOD !!!</Title><Msg>STOP THESE SOB AT THE GATE !!!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1351883527978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351886289091-9</Id><Topic><Title>WHO SAVED THE MIDDLE CLASS AUTO JOBS ? O B A M A 2012 !!! PERIOD !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1351883527978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:12:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With everyone else who pay taxes.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1351886289091</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 15:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351899372677-10</Id><Title>World's Largest Offshore Wind Farm Fires Up - expected to add a 240MW power generating capacity to the 630MW already delivered by said 175 turbines</Title><Msg>World's Largest Offshore Wind Farm Fires Up October 30th, 2012, 14:20 GMT · By Laura Sinpetru Only yesterday, DONG Energy, E.ON and Masdar made it public news that the London Array (i.e. the world's largest offshore wind farm) successfully generated its first watts and fed them into the country's national grid. Apparently, this offshore wind farm is to comprise 175 Siemens 3.6MW turbines, of which 151 have thus far been installed. Should things go as planned, the remaining 24 should be set in place and connected to the grid within the following few months. Once all of these wind turbines are set in place, their combined power generating capacity will translate into as many as 470,000 households across the UK having their electricity demands met with the help of this green energy source. According to Business Green, the UK Country Manager for DONG Energy, Benj Sykes, made a case of how, “The London Array project will be the first of the next generation of larger offshore wind farms and we are pleased to have reached first power.” Furthermore, “Being able to efficiently develop large offshore wind farms and harvest the scale advantages in both construction and operation is an important element in our continuous efforts to bring down costs of energy of offshore wind.” This large-scale offshore wind farm is located in the Thames Estuary, and local officials hope that is will do more than just help improve on the country's ecological footprint. Thus, they believe that these wind turbines will also deliver significant financial benefits, both because the electricity they will soon start generating is to be rather cheap, and because proper management of this wind farm will help create various job opportunities. A second phase of this project, which is still waiting for approval, is expected to add a 240MW power generating capacity to the 630MW already delivered by said 175 turbines. “To have a world class wind farm maintained from Ramsgate is great for the local community and local business. We very much hope that the company will be able to realize its plans to develop Phase Two adding an additional 240MW,” stated Laura Sandys, MP Thanet South. softpedia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351899372677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 19:36:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351900087100-11</Id><Topic><Title>World's Largest Offshore Wind Farm Fires Up - expected to add a 240MW power generating capacity to the 630MW already delivered by said 175 turbines</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351899372677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 19:36:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>while the rest of the world spends $$ getting OFF the opec/terrorist pipeline and creating sustaining energy the USA spends $$ occupying Iraq because the "w" wanted to show daddy how it was done--we got it big "W"--YOU DA MAN and with your sound biz skills it didn't really cost anything--put on that credit card and cut taxes to make it balance--YOU DA MAN didn't you go to same biz school as Rmoney??--was he a cheerleader too??--HE DA MAN</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1351900087100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 19:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351900458652-12</Id><Title>How democrats govern</Title><Msg>Suspended Maryland Delegate Tiffany Alston has been permanently removed from office and cannot be reinstated, according to a state attorney general’s opinion issued Thursday. Mrs. Alston, Prince George’s Democrat, pleaded guilty last month to charges she used campaign funds to pay for her wedding and was also found guilty in June of using state funds to pay an employee at her law firm. Her attorneys have said she hoped to return to office, but Dan Friedman — who works for the attorney general’s office as counsel to the assembly — wrote in an opinion Thursday that she gave up the possibility of reinstatement when she agreed to the plea deal. Mrs. Alston’s attorneys have contended that completing court-ordered community service would downgrade her conviction to probation, which they said would allow her to return to office in time for next year’s General Assembly. Mr. Friedman disagreed but said she is eligible to run for office in 2014 because her misdemeanor conviction does not make her ineligible to vote. J. Wyndal Gordon, an attorney for Mrs. Alston, declined to comment Friday. Read more: P.G. delegate removed from office after guilty plea - Washington Times http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/nov/2/pg-delegate-removed-office-after-guilty-plea/?utm_source=RSS_Feed&amp;utm_medium=RSS#ixzz2B72p85xD Follow us: @washtimes on Twitter</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351900458652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 19:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351904014280-13</Id><Topic><Title>World's Largest Offshore Wind Farm Fires Up - expected to add a 240MW power generating capacity to the 630MW already delivered by said 175 turbines</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351899372677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 19:36:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>W went to Iraq for the same reason we're still in the middle east. Because the very second we stop trading oil for dollars your fat #$%$ way of life ceases to exists. The SWIFT agreement is what we are there to enforce.</Msg><Username>mike_templar</Username><Timestamp>1351904014280</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 20:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351908420298-14</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You'll need more that that to stop American freedom you filthy right wing rats. WAHLIEEE.....JUST KEEP POSTING YOUR FILTH. THERE IS NOTHING YOU CAN POST THAT HAS AN OUNCE OF TRUTH IN IT. SAVE US ALL FROM YOUR LIES.....TAKE A WALK, MAYBE INTO THE PASSING LANE ON YOUR FREEWAY.....WHAT EVER YOU DECIDE, JUST GO AWAY FOR GOOD...THANK YOU......DISMISSED....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351908420298</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351909071061-15</Id><Topic><Title>So Far Ohio Not Taking Romney Bait and Switch</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351343138664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt is merely a modern day version of Herbert Hoover. YOU JUST DON'T GET IT WAHILEEEE.....GO AWAY, YOU DON'T HAVE A CLUE ABOUT WHAT YOU WRITE....IF YOU WANT A MUSLIM TO LEAD YOU AND NOT AN AMERICAN, YOU ARE JUST PLAIN SICK.....ENOUGH OF YOU. DISMISSED.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351909071061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351909909639-16</Id><Title>NAACP executive gets 5 years for voter fraud</Title><Msg>Think she's a Republican? A Mississippi NAACP executive is in jail after being convicted of voter fraud for fraudulently casting absentee ballots, including for four dead people. Lessadolla Sowers, who is a member of the Tunica County NAACP Executive Committee, was convicted and sentenced in April for what a judge said were crimes that cut “against the fabric of our free society.” She was given a five-year sentence for each of the ten counts of voter fraud for which she was convicted, but the sentencing judge allowed her to serve the terms concurrently, according to the Tunica Times.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351909909639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351910077627-17</Id><Title>New O'Keefe video exposes Vermont voter fraud</Title><Msg>James O’Keefe’s Project Veritas has released a new video exposing just how easy it is to commit voter fraud in Vermont. The video, a sequel to O'Keefe's "Primary of the Living Dead" in New Hampshire, shows a Veritas agent entering various voting places around the state of Vermont, giving a different name each time. Each time, he is given a ballot without showing an ID, to his disbelief. O'Keefe's new video from Vermont could not be more timely, coming the day after the U.S. Department of Justice's civil rights division blocked a Texas photo ID requirement for voters -- to the applause of the American Civil Liberties Union, which claimed that the law was “discriminatory” against “Latinos, African-Americans, elderly citizens, and others.”</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351910077627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351910300486-18</Id><Topic><Title>How long before infernal and invest croak ???????????</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1351812178848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No response max? As always: big hat, no cattle. What a joke.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351910300486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351910352009-19</Id><Title>raise taxes on the oil companies</Title><Msg>every time they raise gas prices raise their taxes and soon they get the message. The CEOs pay of all companies should be regulated by the government. their high pay like the big oil CEOs people are make to pay by the high gas prices. How you think they get all their money?</Msg><Username>demsenate4obama</Username><Timestamp>1351910352009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351910526663-20</Id><Topic><Title>How democrats govern</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351900458652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 19:54:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>trumpedup charged by her republican opponents party that use same dirty tricks based on lies. we still remember Tricky Dick!!!!!</Msg><Username>demsenate4obama</Username><Timestamp>1351910526663</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351910772424-21</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncrap Voter Fraud in Ohio</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351424350687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 07:39:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where the news source you make it up? I going to kick a #$%$ if I see anyone vote rommey next week</Msg><Username>demsenate4obama</Username><Timestamp>1351910772424</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:46:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351910909353-22</Id><Topic><Title>How democrats govern</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351900458652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 19:54:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trumped up by the 3 Republicans left in Prince Georges County? You are a true idiot.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351910909353</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:48:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351911202228-23</Id><Topic><Title>raise taxes on the oil companies</Title><Username>demsenate4obama</Username><Timestamp>1351910352009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you enjoy broadcasting your extreme stupidity?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351911202228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 22:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>