<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-12"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355290770188-1</Id><Title>Kearl oilsands project very close to startup in northern Alberta</Title><Msg>Kearl oilsands project very close to startup in northern Alberta Calgary Herald-1 hour ago Imperial Oil's $10.9-billion Kearl oilsands project will produce 110,000 barrels per day in its first phase, with an eventual goal of 345,000 bpd. The project is ... Great PHOTO</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355290770188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 00:39:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355294247996-2</Id><Title>TransCanada will fight order to halt Keystone XL work</Title><Msg>TransCanada will fight order to halt Keystone XL work By Zain Shauk | December 11, 2012 | Updated: December 11, 2012 6:38pm Comments 2 A judge in Nacogdoches County has issued a temporary restraining order to halt work on the Keystone XL pipeline, according to court documents. Attorneys for Trans-Canada, which is building the pipeline, said they will fight the order at a hearing set for Thursday and do not expect it to thwart construction of the pipeline, which has drawn opposition from environmentalists and some landowners in its path. County Court-at-Law Judge Jack Sinz issued the order in response to a lawsuit filed by Michael Bishop, 64, who owns land in the county. Bishop could not be reached for comment. He alleged in his petition that TransCanada misrepresented the purpose of Keystone XL when it negotiated an agreement to run the line through his land. While the company said the pipeline would transport crude oil, Bishop alleged, the product planned for the pipeline is different because it is produced from Canadian oil sands. chronDOTcom/business/article/TransCanada-will-fight-order-to-halt-Keystone-XL-4109569DOTphp</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355294247996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 01:37:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355305227851-3</Id><Topic><Title>Union Thugs</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355272655427</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 19:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All these unions are is #$%$ rebel big mouths.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1355305227851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 04:40:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355305283347-4</Id><Topic><Title>Extinct lizard named after President Obamao</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1355263245755</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 17:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shut upppppp stupid</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1355305283347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 04:41:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355308370851-5</Id><Title>Don't forget about Gazprom</Title><Msg>http://seekingalpha.com/article/1059311-why-gazprom-is-a-steal</Msg><Username>marketsmasters</Username><Timestamp>1355308370851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 05:32:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355321695852-6</Id><Title>Propel Gets $21 Million to Build Renewable Fuel Stations</Title><Msg>Propel Gets $21 Million to Build Renewable Fuel Stations By Andrew Herndon on December 11, 2012 Propel Fuels Inc., a closely held retailer of ethanol and biodiesel blends, received $21 million in financing to expand its network of biofuel stations. Gentry Venture Partners and existing investors Nth Power LLC, Craton Equity Partners and @Ventures provided $11 million in equity capital as part of the company’s Series D financing round, Propel said in a statement on its website today. It also received $10 million in debt and didn’t identify the provider. Propel, based in Redwood City, California, operates 24 fuel stations in California and six in Washington. The funding will help it expand to about 75 locations within a year, Chief Executive Officer Matt Horton said in a phone interview. The U.S. Energy Department and the California Energy Commission have awarded Propel $22 million in grants to expand its network, and the private investments will provide some of the required matching funds, he said. businessweekDOTcom/news/2012-12-11/propel-gets-21-million-to-build-renewable-fuel-stations</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355321695852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:14:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355322617451-7</Id><Title>OPEC keeps output ceiling, the climate change-pasta nexus, and more</Title><Msg>OPEC keeps output ceiling, the climate change-pasta nexus, and more By Ben Geman - 12/12/12 08:37 AM ET The Wall Street Journal reports from OPEC's meeting in Vienna: OPEC decided Wednesday to maintain its oil production ceiling of 30 million barrels a day, though it was unclear whether the group would say anything to address the fact that it's currently producing well above that target, according to OPEC delegates. Despite the swift accord on the production ceiling at the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries meeting in Vienna, the group continued to wrangle over who would replace its outgoing secretary-general, Libyan national Abdalla Salem el-Badri, who is due to retire at the end of the year. Newsweek reports that “if humans want to keep eating pasta, we will have to take much more aggressive action against global warming.” Click here to find out why. The Associated Press reports on the fallout from Duke Energy’s merger with Progress Energy. National Public Radio looks at whether California will have a new oil-and-gas boom. The BBC reports that German prosecutors have raided Deutsche Bank offices “as part of an investigation into a tax evasion scheme involving the trading of carbon permits.” thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/272445-news-bites-opec-keeps-output-ceiling-the-climate-change-pasta-nexus-and-more</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355322617451</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:30:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355323546987-8</Id><Title>Tea Leaves Suggest Flag/Wedge Forming</Title><Msg>A 5 year chart shows a wedge forming where a rising trend line since June 2010 will meet resistance at ~$95 sometime in mid year 2013 (June, Q3). My expectation is a break out to the up side.</Msg><Username>kb31416</Username><Timestamp>1355323546987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 09:45:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355326873879-9</Id><Title>New Year's Investments</Title><Msg>Short Exxon Mobil @$89.15 Short Chevron @$108.30 Short Royal Dutch Shell-A @$68.60 Short ConocoPhillips @$58.35 Short BP @$41.54</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355326873879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:41:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355328356031-10</Id><Title>Commodity/Energy Price Bubble Analogs</Title><Msg>1795-1819 1871-1874 1914-1921 1973-1986 2000-2013? Each time energy prices and commodity prices shot up and each time they crashed right back to level they were at before they rose - in inflation adjusted terms. The economics are elementary. High energy prices are their own undoing. They increase the pace of technological innovation and investment, factors which increase the supply of energy sources and reduce the demand for energy.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355328356031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:05:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355328805761-11</Id><Title>Commodity Price Bubble Investing 101</Title><Msg>Rule 1: Short all commodity price bubbles, especially energy price bubbles. when past bubbles occurred from their beginning to the final crash. 1795-1819 1871-1874 1914-1921 1973-1986 2000-2013--- The economics are elementary. The bubble is its own undoing, as it increases the profit from investment and new technology. The higher level of investment keeps supply higher for years, and new technology reduces demand for years.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355328805761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:13:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355331370106-12</Id><Topic><Title>New Year's Investments</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355326873879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:41:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>some additional ones: Total SA @$50.65 Royal Dutch Shell-B shares @71.00 Schlumberger @73.00 20% of net worth short.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355331370106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:56:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355335941497-13</Id><Topic><Title>New Year's Investments</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355326873879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:41:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm actually making money. The euro is rising against the dollar and I've sold every dollar except the ones I collected shorting. I've consolidated all the short positions into XOM, however, at $90.20... Still 20%.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355335941497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:12:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355337350346-14</Id><Topic><Title>XOM could very well happen to be the company to watch this week.</Title><Username>andersonkenneth619</Username><Timestamp>1355317959375</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 08:12:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I checked it out,</Msg><Username>kirkraymond625</Username><Timestamp>1355337350346</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:35:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355337792721-15</Id><Topic><Title>Union Thugs</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355272655427</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 19:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unions elevate wages and make industry less competitive. The antidote is free immigration. If you flood the labor market with cheap labor it destroys the unions. Low wages are good for an economy; high wages are bad. The Democratic Party is nice enough to the Big Business' job for it, pursuing a lax immigration policy that lowers wages. Eventually wages will drop enough to make America competitive with China.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355337792721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:43:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355338259978-16</Id><Title>Slum wars</Title><Msg>Unlimited immigration out of Mexico and Latin America is the solution to America's inner city decay. They compete for the same turf as black drug gangs. Latin Americans do assimilate too and have a much better work ethic than the current inhabitants of the ghetto. Wages will fall as the Latino steamroller floods the inner cities.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355338259978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:50:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355339274558-17</Id><Title>Grassley says wind energy tax credit will be in final budget deal</Title><Msg>Grassley says wind energy tax credit will be in final budget deal December 11, 2012 By O. Kay Henderson Republican Senator Chuck Grassley predicts a few dozen tax credits, including the wind production tax credit, will easily win approval once the stalemate between the president and congress is broken. “I believe when we break the ice and there’s a framework put together…then that gives the other committees of congress an opportunity to operate,” Grassley says, “and I think that you’d find unemployment and the wind energy tax credit and 59 other tax incentives that are expiring at the end of this year just kind of thrown into that package.” Extended unemployment benefits are set to expire for about two million Americans before year’s end, as are the tax breaks Grassley mentioned. According to Grassley, December 18 rather than the 31 is the key deadline for taking action in congress — to meet paperwork deadlines in the House and Senate. Grassley says he and other Republicans are willing to “give” the president $800 billion in additional tax revenue — but that solves just seven percent of the deficit problem lawmakers are trying to address. “In other words, the other 93 percent is on the spending side,” Grassley says. Like other Americans, Grassley has been following the public statements of President Obama and House Speaker John Boehner, the top Republican in congress. “And the only good news that I can give you that there might be progress — with emphasis upon the word ‘might’ — is the fact that neither one of them have bene talking about what they’ve discussed or their differences on television,” Grassley says. “Sometimes it’s a good indicator.” The senator says congress won’t be able to tackle the long term problems in Social Security, Medicare and Medicaid. Plus, Grassley says the changes that must be considered wouldn’t be implemented within the “10 year window” of the budget agreement that’s being negotiated. Grassley made his comments this morning during a telephone conference call with Iowa radio reporters. radioiowaDOTcom/2012/12/11/grassley-says-wind-energy-tax-credit-will-be-in-final-budget-deal/?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed:+RadioIowaNews+(Radio+Iowa+News)&amp;utm_content=Google+Reader</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355339274558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:07:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355345915243-18</Id><Topic><Title>New Year's Investments</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355326873879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:41:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cha-Ching. Closed out everything to dollars. Consisted of loss of -0.60% on 20%, -0.120% in total, on the initial trade from pre-Fed to post-Fed. Then a gain of 0.72% (90.2 to 89.55) on 20%, +0.144% in total on post-Fed trade to close... Some small change on the oil companies. The big bonus was the favorable move in the euro against the dollar... another 0.20% gain...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355345915243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 15:58:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355348668871-19</Id><Title>Fed's policy</Title><Msg>borrow more money from the banks, thereby reducing bank lending, in order to boost credit to the government debt and mortgage market. The policy will reduce the velocity of circulation of money as the money banks lend circulates in the real economy, and the money in mortgage market and government debt market circulates from one account to another in places such as Liechtenstein, Zurich, Beverly Hills, the Hamptons, Chicago's North Side, or the Cayman Island, etc...Whether the balance is $156,555,555 or $157,225,444, or $558,555,666 or $559,254,666, day to day, is not going to impact the rate of spending or the circulation of that money at all. Such wealth is helped by lower rates but it does not circulate. In the meantime the money that is being sucked up out of the banks to bid the big accounts higher and higher cannot circulate at all. The policy is deflationary, although it can increase commodity prices for a while longer until they crash under the pressure of higher investment stimulated by cheap money. Unemployment? No noticeable impact, that is unless deflation speeds wages to a lower level and clears the market. The monetary policy has nothing do with that process though. As always, it is best to sit in short term bills as these bubbles build...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355348668871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:44:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355359199652-20</Id><Topic><Title>New Year's Investments</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355326873879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:41:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What will happen to your short when Israel nukes Iran and the price of oil doubles overnight? Just playing devils advocate - literally and figuratively :-)</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355359199652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 19:39:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355360438668-21</Id><Title>Lawmakers to push tax code change for renewable energy in 2013</Title><Msg>Lawmakers to push tax code change for renewable energy in 2013 WASHINGTON | Wed Dec 12, 2012 6:59pm EST (Reuters) - A group of U.S. lawmakers said on Wednesday that they plan to push ahead in the new year to change the tax code so renewable energy projects could qualify for beneficial tax structures commonly used by pipelines and other energy-related companies. Democratic and Republican sponsors of proposed legislation said they think momentum is growing for their idea to allow wind, solar, biofuel and other renewable projects to structure as "master limited partnerships" (MLPs). The structures allow companies to raise money in the stock market, while having income taxed only at the unit holder level, thus avoiding corporate income taxes. "Small tweaks to the tax code could attract billions of dollars in private sector investment to renewable energy deployment," the 29 lawmakers said in a letter to President Barack Obama, asking for the administration's support. Their proposals come as Congress looks for ways to boost government revenues and cut spending to deal with the U.S. debt, and ahead of an anticipated push for comprehensive tax reform in 2013. Some Democrats have said they want to get rid of tax breaks for oil and gas companies, while many Republicans have criticized temporary tax incentives for renewable energy. Democratic Senator Chris #$%$ of Delaware said all types of energy would gain if the MLP tax structure, widely used by fossil fuel companies, is extended to renewables. "It does not take anything away from oil or gas or pipelines, as some other proposals would do," said #$%$, who sponsored proposed legislation in the Senate with Republican Jerry Moran of Kansas. "Why not have a predictable, clear, long-term tax advantage financing vehicle for both, for a genuinely all-of-the-above energy strategy?" #$%$ told reporters. Senator Lisa Murkowski, the top Republican on the Senate Energy Committee, has signed on as a cosponsor. In the Republican-controlled House of Representatives, a companion bill is sponsored by Ted Poe, whose Texas district is home to refineries and pipelines, as well as Democrats Mike Thompson of California and Peter Welch of Vermont. "We need everything," Poe said, explaining why he supports a plan to boost renewable energy. reutersDOTcom/article/2012/12/12/us-usa-tax-energy-idUSBRE8BB1V320121212</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355360438668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 20:00:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355362173822-22</Id><Topic><Title>New Year's Investments</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355326873879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:41:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I covered the shorts already. The strategy of diversifying into the unknown of the Fed helped cushion the adverse price move early in the day, and when it was clear XOM was the speculator's favorite, concentrating against it made it made easy to clear out with a small gain by close. The euro move was gravy. If Israel nukes Iran Exxon Mobil would drop by about 50% in a week, assuming you could even trade it at all. The selling in stock indexes, mutual funds, and panicking pensions would totally overwhelm the small buffer of real buyers in the market and there would be no floor. Exxon Mobil would not make money on a nuclear war either. It does not have enough oil for its refineries and would face enormous losses on them. It still must pay its pensions whether of not its investments cover them too. It faces windfall profits taxes on almost all its international fields, and cannot make much more profit than it is getting now no matter what the oil price is. It would find its operations in Qatar either destroyed or nationalized by the government there, and its UAE operations would see a similar fate. It would face price controls and rationing in the USA and Europe... Oil would shoot up and then collapse when the banking runs and stock market crash overwhelmed the supply disruption and permanently lowered oil demand. sitting in cash appeals to me at the moment. I pick and choose my targets of opportunity.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355362173822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 20:29:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355370561455-23</Id><Topic><Title>Kearl oilsands project very close to startup in northern Alberta</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355290770188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 00:39:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'bout time that this project is promoted on this board... going to be a gigantic success... stock will reach an all time high... have a nice day...</Msg><Username>be.pick</Username><Timestamp>1355370561455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 22:49:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355371857020-24</Id><Title>Obama offers funds to launch U.S. offshore wind farms</Title><Msg>Obama offers funds to launch U.S. offshore wind farms Wendy Koch, USA TODAYShare 2 Comment How much potential does offshore wind hold? The U.S. government says it could quadruple the nation's electricity generation, and it's offering new funds to help get the first projects off the ground. (Photo: Peter Dejong AP) Story Highlights Deptartment of Energy award funds to seven offshore wind projects 8:12PM EST December 12. 2012 - To help launch the U.S. offshore wind industry, the Obama administration announced funding Wednesday for seven projects and environmental groups said they've agreed with developers on how to protect endangered North Atlantic right whales. The Department of Energy said the funding, up to $168 million over six years, will expedite the development of the nations' first offshore wind farms. None are operational yet, but nine have reached the advanced development phase and 24 more are in earlier stages. "The United States has tremendous untapped clean energy sources," Energy Secretary Steven Chu said in the announcement. He noted the department's projection that offshore wind offers more than 4,000 gigawatts of electricity potential -- four times the nation's current total generation. Last year, land-based wind power accounted for a third of new electrical capacity, and 70% of its equipment was made in the United States. More: USA TODAY energy news The funding comes amid turmoil in the U.S. wind industry. A lucrative federal tax credit that helped propel its recent boom faces expiration at the end of this month. A bipartisan group of lawmakers is pushing a one-year extension as part of an overall deal to avert the "fiscal cliff." Yet Congress and President Obama have yet to reach such a deal. To buoy offshore wind's chances for success, environmental groups announced Wednesday that they reached agreement with wind developers to protect North Atlantic right whales. The voluntary measures would reduce or avoid the noise of weather tower construction during peak migration periods. Such sound could disrupt whale communication, migration and feeding. "We share with these leading developers a common objective to get offshore wind up and running as quickly as possible as a key tool in the fight against climate change," Tricia Jedele of the Conservation Law Foundation Rhode Island said in a statement. The accord was reached between her group, the National Wildlife Federation, the Natural Resources Defense Council and three mid-Atlantic wind developers: Deepwater Wind; Energy Management Inc (owner of Cape Wind in Massachusetts) and NRD Bluewater Wind. The Obama administration, which aims to get 80% of the nation's electricity from clean energy sources by 2035, has taken several steps to develop technologies and expedite leasing for offshore wind projects. In February, Interior Secretary Ken Salazar said federal environmental reviews for designated "wind energy areas" off Delaware, Maryland, New Jersey and Virginia were complete, clearing the way for their developers to seek leases. Under the Department of Energy's new funding, which builds on $42 million in R&amp;D awards given last year, each project will receive up to $4 million to complete engineering, site evaluation and planning. The department will then select up to three of the projects, offering each up to $47 million, to abet their commercial operation by 2017. The seven projects are in six states: Baryonyx Corporation's project near Port Isabel, Texas; Fishermen's Atlantic City Windfarm in New Jersey; Lake Erie Development Corporation's wind turbines off the coast of Cleveland in Lake Erie; Principle Power's facility off Coos Bay, Ore.; Statoil North America's turbines in the Gulf of Maine off Boothbay Harbor; University of Maine's farm near Monhegan Island; Dominion Virginia Power's project off the coast of Virginia Beach. usatodayDOTcom/story/news/nation/2012/12/12/obama-offshore-wind-projects/1765029/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355371857020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 23:10:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>