<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342952788000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Libs fighting libs</Title><Username>infernalequinoxx</Username><Timestamp>1342914301000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 19:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>California has a serious energy problem caused by wild-eyed liberal policies. Industry was leaving the state, fleeing high power rates and air quality standards, even before the 2008 Housing Panic/Crisis, and even more is leaving now with the new Democrat Governor. It is not that capital is unavailable to grow the economy, or that it can't grow, it is just that it can't grow in lib bastions like California, which drags down the national average.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1342952788000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 06:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342962670000-2</Id><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Msg>There timing is simply the best! I shorted the market prior to it plummeting and made money, and went long when I received there daily video saying to buy at the bottom and again bigtime in the money on both calls! There daily video its free, and maybe it can help you like it has helped me. WWW.TOPRATEDANALYST.INFO</Msg><Username>nathcrne89</Username><Timestamp>1342962670000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963191000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Say Chesapeake’s Taxes Show Need to Update Old Law</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342877359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 09:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Govt studying to restructure subsidy: Awang Adek News 2012-07-22 17:38 BACHOK, July 22 (Bernama) -- The Finance Ministry is studying, with a view of restructuring all forms of subsidies, especially oil and gas, to ensure they meet the target groups and help to reduce the burden of the low income earners. Towards this end, Deputy Finance Minister Datuk Dr Awang Adek Hussin, said he welcome suggestions from any quarters to be included for tabling of Budget 2013. He told this to reporters after meeting residents of Kampung Perupuk here today. Awang Adek was responding to a suggestion by Umno Youth for the government to restructure the subsidies given to the people so that they could be channelled directly to the target groups. According to Umno Youth leader, Khairy Jamaludin, currently, the subsidies, like for oil and gas, were found to benefit the high income earners more. The matter had been raised by many quarters, but none had submitted a comprehensive delivery system that could meet the target, said Awang Adek, who is also Kelantan Umno deputy liaison chief. He said the government had placed the price of RON97 under managed float and maintained the subsidy for RON95, used mostly by the low income earners. http://www.mysinchew.com/node/75773</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342963191000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963404000-4</Id><Topic><Title>The economic risks going forward</Title><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1342275373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-14 10:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks there, "Willy." http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FdSORiSaRW8</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1342963404000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342963676000-5</Id><Title>Drought drives up price of ethanol</Title><Msg>Drought drives up price of ethanol 10% of a gallon of gasoline is additive made from corn By Rick Barrett of the Journal Sentinel July 21, 2012 (35) Comments The severe drought that has scorched much of the U.S. corn crop could be felt by consumers at the gasoline pump as well as the grocery store. That's because 10% of nearly every gallon of gasoline is ethanol, a fuel additive distilled from corn. As corn fields wither in the heat, the price of ethanol on the Chicago Board of Trade has risen nearly 25% this year to more than $2.70 per gallon - well above its average of about $2 a gallon over the last seven years. Rising ethanol costs could add about another nickel per gallon to the retail gasoline price, said Thomas Elam, an agricultural economist from Carmel, Ind. "With corn prices going up, the ethanol producers have to get more for their product," Elam said. "They have to recover their costs, just like everybody else." By law, gasoline in most states must contain 10% ethanol. Supporters say it reduces dependence on foreign oil, reduces air pollution and helps support the farm economy. Wisconsin ranks seventh among ethanol-producing states, where the fuel additive is an important source of income for grain farmers, some of whom also own shares in ethanol distilleries. But with the drought pushing up grain prices, some corn users - especially livestock farmers - say the nation's Renewable Fuels Standard that mandates ethanol use in gasoline should be reconsidered. Under the policy, billions of gallons of the fuel additive must be produced a year regardless of the effect it has on others - sometimes pitting livestock farmers against grain farmers, with the animal producers saying it has driven up feed prices. "There's a constant back-and-forth going on now between ethanol producers and livestock farmers," said Erin Roth, executive director of the Wisconsin Petroleum Council. "In a good year, it's not an issue because there's enough corn to go around," Roth said. "But this fight always surfaces when U.S. corn production gets whittled away by something. And now it's being more than whittled away; it's being chopped away because of the drought." There should be more flexibility in the number of ethanol gallons produced a year, especially when there's been a drought that's damaged the corn crop, added David Warner, a spokesman for the National Pork Producers Council. Elam says the Renewable Fuels Standard has increased corn, soybean and wheat prices to the detriment of food and fuel producers. He says it's resulted in higher prices at the grocery store as nearly every product on the shelves is touched by the price of grain. "The increases we have seen in commodity prices are strongly associated with the fuel mandate," he said. "At the same time, we haven't seen the promised benefits on oil imports or gasoline prices. This means that while Americans are forced to pay more for food, they're also not seeing lower prices at the pump. It's a lose-lose situation." Ethanol policy supporters say the fuel additive is saving U.S. motorists money, partly because it typically costs less per gallon than gasoline. http://www.jsonline.com/business/drought-drives-up-price-of-ethanol-h166ocf-163285106.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342963676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963689000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Drought drives up price of ethanol</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342963676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the problem with that claim, Elam says, is ethanol isn't as energy-efficient as gasoline. "It has to sell at a significant discount to gasoline to achieve equal fuel costs per mile," he said. The nation's corn growers say the Renewable Fuels Standard should be left alone, rather than taking a knee-jerk approach to changing it with every year's harvest. "Having a long-term approach to an energy policy continues to be important," said Josh Morby, executive director of the Wisconsin Bio Industry Alliance. "I think we need to stay the course, with a focus on cleaner-burning fuels and renewable energy. I am not trying to minimize the impact the drought is going to have on farmers or ethanol producers, but the fact remains we have worked with politicians to develop a long-term energy policy that includes ethanol as a key component." The price of gasoline at the pump is more affected by the cost of crude oil, the global economy, and lessened demand for motor fuel as U.S. consumers drive fewer miles and increasingly have more fuel-efficient cars. The price of gasoline could edge up some in the next few months as higher ethanol prices work their way into the market. But that will be "small potatoes" compared with what could happen to food prices next year because of the diminished corn crop, Elam said. In August and September, the Agriculture Department should have a better handle on how much of the nation's corn crop has been damaged. It could further fuel the debate about how much of the crop should be designated for ethanol. Already there's a lot of pressure on ethanol distilleries that have seen demand for their product decline even as the cost of corn, their main raw ingredient, has risen sharply. Some distilleries have shut down because of the soaring costs. This fall, a 15% blend of ethanol in gasoline is supposed to be available in the marketplace. But it might not come, experts say, because of the rising cost of corn. "The 15% blend is just going to die. Just like the 85% blend, called E85, has died," Elam said.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342963689000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963803000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Drought drives up price of ethanol</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342963676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Energy Futures Prices Below you may find all the futures prices &amp; quotes for: Crude Oil, Heating Oil, Gasoline RBOB, Natural Gas, ICE Brent Crude Oil, Ethanol (E) and more. Real Time Streaming Futures Quotes (CFDs) http://www.forexpros.com/commodities/energies</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342963803000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963949000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Drought drives up price of ethanol</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342963676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:27:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production http://ethanolrfa.org/pages/weekly-ethanol-feed-production</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342963949000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342967804000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Username>nathcrne89</Username><Timestamp>1342962670000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:11:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting</Msg><Username>jeni.savor98</Username><Timestamp>1342967804000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342968511000-10</Id><Title>Oh Great, Two Piplines Blown Up</Title><Msg>This weekend, a pipeline from Iraq to Turkey, in addition to one from Egypt to Israel and Jordan. http://www.zawya.com/story/Oil_pipeline_from_Iraq_blown_up_in_Turkey-ZAWYA20120721063435/</Msg><Username>ahrranbee</Username><Timestamp>1342968511000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:48:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342972007000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Whats Wrong Now?</Title><Username>ferrellvqo881</Username><Timestamp>1342966052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:07:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>gwenniexfm112</Username><Timestamp>1342972007000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342975939000-12</Id><Title>EPA to take a second look at coal rules</Title><Msg>EPA to take a second look at coal rules http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_P/threadview?m=te&amp;bn=2753&amp;tid=49498&amp;mid=49498&amp;tof=1&amp;frt=1#49498</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342975939000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:52:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342976692000-13</Id><Topic><Title>EPA to take a second look at coal rules</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342975939000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:52:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I smell election year politics at work here. If Obama gets re-elected, you can bet it'll be all stops opened with the war against energy.</Msg><Username>ahrranbee</Username><Timestamp>1342976692000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:04:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342981620000-14</Id><Topic><Title>The groups CEO told NBC 4 on Satruday</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1342930311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 00:11:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one bankrolls gun confiscation more than this group.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1342981620000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342981698000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Great, Two Piplines Blown Up</Title><Username>ahrranbee</Username><Timestamp>1342968511000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:48:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bernanke can print endless money to replace the pipelines and bill idiot America</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1342981698000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:28:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342984014000-16</Id><Title>Do a Jimmy James at Los Colinas....</Title><Msg>They will get the message. haha. Make sure Rex is in the the picture.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1342984014000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342987309000-17</Id><Topic><Title>stock market charts</Title><Username>lanniefwi498</Username><Timestamp>1342970221000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:17:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Am Impressed!!!</Msg><Username>aubfum677</Username><Timestamp>1342987309000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:01:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342992370000-18</Id><Title>meet U.S. EPA-mandated requirements 4 ethanol derived from cellulosic sources</Title><Msg>KBR to Provide Services for DuPont Iowa Cellulosic Ethanol Plant Posted on 09 July 2012 by Andy Eubank KBR recently announced it has been awarded a contract for engineering and procurement services for DuPont’s first cellulosic ethanol plant in Nevada, Iowa. KBR will provide front-end engineering, detailed engineering and procurement services to DuPont’s Industrial Biosciences Group for this first-of-a-kind plant to be constructed in the Midwest United States. The ethanol facility is designed to process 1,300 tons per day of corn stover and produce 27.5 million gallons of ethanol per year. The cellulosic ethanol product will be used as a blending component in gasoline by fuel manufacturers and will enable them to meet U.S. EPA-mandated requirements for ethanol derived from cellulosic sources. KBR is executing the project from its Wilmington, Del. Operations Center, a bio fuels center of excellence. Ground breaking is scheduled for the second half of 2012 with a 12-18 month construction period. “KBR and DuPont have a long-standing partnership and a history of successful project execution,” said David Zelinski, President, Downstream. “This award further affirms and solidifies KBR’s 20-plus year partnership with DuPont in the safe and efficient development and execution of capital projects, and reinforces KBR’s position as an EPC leader in bio fuels projects.” KBR is a global engineering, construction and services company supporting the energy, hydrocarbon, government services, minerals, civil infrastructure, power, industrial, and commercial markets. For more information, visit http://www.hoosieragtoday.com/index.php/2012/07/09/kbr-to-provide-services-for-dupont-iowa-cellulosic-ethanol-plant/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342992370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 17:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342992464000-19</Id><Topic><Title>meet U.S. EPA-mandated requirements 4 ethanol derived from cellulosic sources</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342992370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 17:26:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dutch firm investing in new biofuels An Emmetsburg plant will be Iowa's first to use noncorn feedstock for ethanol. 10:43 PM, Jul 21, 2012 EMMETSBURG, IA. — At a time when ethanol is under attack from livestock feeders, Big Oil and world hunger advocacy groups, an investment by a Dutch conglomerate into a cellulosic ethanol plant would seem to be a stretch. But to Feike Sijbesma, CEO of Royal DSM, a Dutch-based maker of food and feed additives, the American ethanol venture is so natural that its value is obvious. “There is a limited supply of oil, even with the new discoveries,” Sijbesma said on a visit to Emmetsburg in June. “We have a new technology that in five years will transform the industry.” Biofuel boosters need a win, and they hope the Poet/DSM venture will provide it. For the past two years, the U.S. government has had to acknowledge that its targets for noncorn biofuels haven’t been met. Cellulosic ethanol made from corn residue, primarily leaves and stalks, is probably Iowa’s best hope to keep its leadership in biofuels, which it has earned with its 41 corn ethanol plants now in operation. The Emmetsburg cellulosic plant has been delayed at least two years, in part because of foot-dragging by the federal government’s loan guarantee process. Finally Poet, which already garnered $20 million in Iowa state government funds, gave up on Washington and in January signed on DSM as a 50-50 venture partner. It hopes the $250 million plant will open in time for the 2013 harvest. The plant will be the first in Iowa to use feedstock other than corn. DuPont plans a similar facility at Nevada. Poet, which operates seven ethanol plants in Iowa, already is gathering the stover, as the residue is called, in huge bales piled near the existing corn-fed ethanol plant that it operates at Emmetsburg. The stover-fed plant will be built adjacent to the existing facility. “I know people have criticized cellulosic ethanol here in the U.S. for being too slow,” said Sijbesma. “But even a five-year delay is a small price to pay for a technology that will benefit our children and grandchildren.” Poet President Jeff Laut said the Sioux Falls, S.D.-based company will begin to expand the technology to its other plants as soon as it works out the kinks at Emmetsburg.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342992464000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 17:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342993308000-20</Id><Topic><Title>meet U.S. EPA-mandated requirements 4 ethanol derived from cellulosic sources</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342992370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 17:26:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At the Olympics, BP’s biofuel hopefuls go for a test drive By Kirsten Korosec | July 18, 2012, 10:28 AM PDT Athletes and officials riding in BMW’s special fleet of vehicles at the London 2012 Olympics might be the unwitting participants of an advanced biofuels trial. BP, the official oil and gas partner of London 2012, will test three advanced biofuels in about 100 of the 5,000-odd vehicles that make up BMW Olympic fleet. Two of those fuels — a cellulosic ethanol product and a biobutanol biofuel — could be commercially available by 2014, BusinessWeek reported. Commercialization is the critical step for any next-gen biofuels startup. The same rule applies for capital-rich oil majors like BP. Some oil companies stand to gain a great deal from the emergence of biofuels. Pike Research noted in a March report that Shell and BP were the top two oil companies with the best positioning to benefit from the growth of biofuels. A closer look BP is testing three advanced biofuels: cellulosic ethanol, biobutanol and a sugar-to-diesel product. The cellulosic ethanol is made from energy grasses and then blended with the company’s BP Ultimate unleaded fuel. BP has invested in biofuels research since at least 2006. It wasn’t until BP’s $98.3 million purchase Verenium’s cellulosic biofuels business in 2010, that the company took serious steps towards commercialization. BP is developing a 36-million gallon commercial-scale plant and 20,000-acre farm in Highlands County, Florida, where the energy grasses will be grown and turned into cellulosic ethanol. Construction has begun on the farm and work on the industrial facility is expected to begin this year and will take two years to complete, BP said. BP’s biobutanol is made by the advanced fermentation of plant sugars by a special microorganism. The biobutanol used to fuel part of BMW’s fleet was produced at a demonstration plant built by BP and DuPont in Hull, England. The sugar-to-diesel biofuel is at its earliest stage of development and likely won’t be ready for commercialization for some time. BP has worked for years to develop a sugar-to-diesel technology that can be scaled up beyond the lab. In 2009, BP announced a joint development agreement with Martek Biosciences Corporation to advance the development of a technology for the conversion of sugars into biodiesel. Back to the Olympics The official Olympic fleet provided by BMW has to meet some stringent emissions requirements. The vehicles it supplies have to come in below 120 grams of carbon dioxide per kilometer. That’s 13 percent lower than the average emissions of vehicles in the UK. In order to meet those requirements, BMW is supplying about 200 electric vehicles such as the MNI E and the BMW 1 Series ActiveE. Other vehicles include the BMW 320d Efficient Dynamics, which will be the main command car of the Olympic Torch Relay and the official vehicle for cycling events. BMW also is supplying about 400 bicycles and 25 motorcycles. Photo: BMW http://www.smartplanet.com/blog/intelligent-energy/at-the-olympics-bps-biofuel-hopefuls-go-for-a-test-drive/17620</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1342993308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 17:41:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342994573000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Great, Two Piplines Blown Up</Title><Username>ahrranbee</Username><Timestamp>1342968511000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:48:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the gas pipeline from Egypt to Israel had been shut down since April, due to a payment dispute, that Israel wasn't paying 'nough... the recent fire came from residual gas within... the pipeline had been attacked fifteen times since February 2011... thus recent fire will have zero effect on markets... the pipeline from Kirkuk to the sea terminal of Ceyhan (Yumurtalik) has also been attacked more times than one can shake a stick at, within Turkey's border... typically it takes from two to five days to get the oil flowing again... pipeline originally built in 1973 and is maintained by Turkey's Petroleum Pipeline corporation, for which has six pumping stations within Turkey to more easily get the flow going quickly... recent explosion fire was put out the same day and work began to repair... thus will have some effect, yet not much, given the history of attacks on the pipeline... have a nice day...</Msg><Username>be.pick</Username><Timestamp>1342994573000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 18:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342995600000-22</Id><Title>Average gas price prediction for 2013</Title><Msg>If Obama is re-elected - $4/gallon If Romney is elected - $6/gallon</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1342995600000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 18:20:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343005985000-23</Id><Title>Stock split</Title><Msg>I have been a long time holder of Xom and wondering if anyone has heard rumor of a stock split coming. The price of the stock is holding well above then price range where the last split occurred</Msg><Username>waynerosario</Username><Timestamp>1343005985000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 21:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343008005000-24</Id><Title>California's future</Title><Msg>http://www.washingtonpost.com/national/as-more-cities-tip-toward-insolvency-vallejo-offers-mixed-picture-of-life-after-bankruptcy/2012/07/22/gJQAOaeI2W_story.html</Msg><Username>infernalequinoxx</Username><Timestamp>1343008005000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 21:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343015265000-25</Id><Title>BACK right on time for the BIG short!!</Title><Msg>YEEEEEEEEEEEEEEHAWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWW !! after 2 weeks of H ............</Msg><Username>horseseven_7</Username><Timestamp>1343015265000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 23:47:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>