<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350446423319-1</Id><Title>Pittsburgh Can Now Buy 100% Renewables 10% Cheaper Than Standard Utility Rate</Title><Msg>Pittsburgh Can Now Buy 100% Renewables 10% Cheaper Than Standard Utility Rate October 16, 2012</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350446423319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:00:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350446953553-2</Id><Topic><Title>Joe-Bama!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350445537752</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You were obviously watching a different debate. Not only did Obamao lie throughout, the CBS (not Fox) snap poll said Romney won. CNN poll said Romney won on the economy by 58-40. Bye bye Barack.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350446953553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:09:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350447082983-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Republicans Vote To Cut State Dept Security?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350411263889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 14:14:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still brain dead and as always resorting to name calling, since you've got nothing else to offer.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350447082983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:11:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350447142107-4</Id><Title>University of Minnesota developing home-grown diesel alternative</Title><Msg>University of Minnesota developing home-grown diesel alternative Posted: 6:30 am Tue, October 16, 2012 By Todd Nelson Pulp-mill byproduct, biomass would be converted into fuel for new engines Minnesota pulp mills could meet 10 percent of the state’s diesel fuel needs with a clean-burning, renewable alternative that University of Minnesota researchers are developing. Researchers also are designing a fuel-injection system that would enable standard diesel engines to use the diesel fuel substitute. The work involving the substitute dimethyl ether, or DME, is at an early stage. Even so, the project led by David Kittelson, a mechanical engineering professor in the College of Science and Engineering, has received backing from a state grant and big-name industry partners, and has generated several patent applications on new DME-related fuel systems. Supporters include General Motors, which gave an unrestricted grant for DME research and testing a number of new diesel engines slated to go in passenger vehicles in 2014. And Sweden-based Volvo is providing consulting. Chemrec, a Swedish bio-refining company producing DME from a pilot plant at a pulp mill in northern Sweden, is supplying DME for engine testing. The U’s Initiative for Renewable Energy and the Environment (IREE), part of the Institute on the Environment (IonE), awarded a grant to support the research. While typically refined from fossil fuels, DME also can be produced by the gasification of a thick, dark liquid known as black liquor, a byproduct of the paper-making process. Over the course of a year, a small black-liquor gasifier at one of Minnesota’s paper mills could produce 7 million gallons of DME, enough to fuel about two-thirds of Metro Transit’s bus fleet, according to a grant proposal filed by Kittelson. If every pulp mill in Minnesota were producing DME, Kittelson’s proposal said, the output would meet 10 to 15 percent of the state’s diesel fuel requirements during a year. That share would rise, of course, if DME also were to be produced from Minnesota’s substantial cellulosic biomass resources such as prairie grass, forestry waste and corn stalks. Leading an evaluation of the economics of DME production at a Minnesota pulp mill is Steven Taff, associate professor and extension economist in the department of applied economics in the university’s College of Food, Agriculture and Natural Resource Science. The economic analysis is speculative because no gasifier has been built here, so there is no existing cost, price and other data to use, Taff said. “The fuel is very desirable for certain performance reasons and presumably if the market recognizes those performance characteristics, then they may be willing to pay enough money to generate enthusiasm by a paper mill to produce this material,” Taff said. Eric Larson, a research engineer for Princeton University’s Princeton Environmental Institute, said Chemrec’s success in producing DME to fuel a fleet of trucks has proved that the technology is ready. The next step is to get it into larger-scale systems and to find ways to use it effectively. “It’s got great promise in terms of the environment,” said Larson, who has studied the technical, commercial, environmental and energy impacts of bio-refining based on data from a reference pulp mill in the southeastern United States. “The challenges are the technical issues that the guys in Minnesota are working on.” One way to build a market for DME would be to blend it directly into propane at a mixture of up to 20 percent, which would work in gas grills or propane-fueled vehicles, Larson said. “I don’t know what vehicle markets they’re looking at, but the ones that look particularly attractive for trying to retool with DME would be heavy vehicles used in densely populated areas like transit buses and trucks that run around cities,” Larson said. “That’s where most of the pollution that people get exposed to is from. If you can retool the FedEx fleet to run on DME, you’re going to clean up the urban environment more than putting DME on cross-country 18-wheelers.” Kittelson likes DME’s potential as a diesel substitute because of its low greenhouse-gas emissions and high efficiency. It can be produced locally and consumed in areas where biomass is readily available. DME made from biomass feedstocks produces about 10 times the energy that goes into making it, according to Kittelson’s work. DME burns with no soot and produces little pollution of any kind, according to the IonE. That solves one of conventional diesel fuel’s challenges — emission of hazardous fine particles that must be captured with expensive filters. At the same time, however, DME faces a chicken-and-egg quandary other alternative fuels can encounter, Kittelson said. “The problem with DME is that unlike, for example, biodiesel, you can’t just mix it with diesel fuel and run,” he said. “You have to have a dedicated engine. And if you don’t have dedicated engines, there’s not a market for DME. So basically, you need engines for there to be a market but nobody will build engines unless there’s a supply of DME.” That’s why Kittelson is working to develop a DME fuel-injection system for diesel engines. The effort in part involves finding the right mix of additives to boost the viscosity and slipperiness of DME to provide sufficient lubrication for it to run in a diesel engine. DME has a watery consistency, unlike diesel fuel, which Kittelson said is a good lubricant. The idea is to see how the additives affect engine emissions, to determine the best tradeoff between additives and emissions. Ideally, Kittelson said, the fuel-injection system under development also would work with propane, which already is used to run vehicles. “We’re doing this because there is a glut of propane on the market,” Kittelson said. “It’s not a renewable fuel but is a very clean-burning fuel. It has so much in common with DME that we consider co-development of injection systems for DME and propane to be advantageous.” As of now, no Minnesota pulp mill is producing DME, although Kittelson said he has had conversations with paper companies and with others about smaller-scale systems that would produce DME from biomass such as tree farm waste. One alternative under consideration is to produce bio-methanol from black liquor or cellulose, Kittelson said. The production process is similar to that of DME, and bio-methanol could serve as a sort of bridge to support production until DME gains wider acceptance. There would be a ready market for bio-methanol, which could replace fossil methanol in biodiesel production. “That would provide a market for the initial (bio-methanol) product,” Kittelson said. “Then as the demand for DME increased we could switch to production of a larger fraction of DME.” Andre Boehman, a professor of mechanical engineering at the University of Michigan and an expert on DME and alternative fuels and engines, said Kittelson’s work is one of the few active DME research projects in the country today. “That’s why it’s very encouraging that Professor Kittelson has gotten this project in place and is once again getting DME-related research going in North America,” Boehman said. Boehman, who described Kittelson as a friend, colleague and mentor with whom he has worked on past alternative fuel research efforts, also serves as the senior vice president for research at the International DME Association, a global industry advocacy group based in Washington, D.C. Part of the promise of DME is that it can be produced from so many sustainable resources, Boehman said. The DME produced at the pulp and paper mill in Sweden is from 97 percent renewable resources, while biodiesel from soybeans and corn ethanol are 66 percent and 28 percent renewable, respectively. “It’s a fuel that gets you excited,” he said. “I jokingly refer to it as virus. I fell in love with this fuel and I am not going to let go until we see it in use in this country. It’s the same with so many in the DME community.” finance-commerce</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350447142107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 00:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350450621647-5</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney, show us your underwear</Title><Username>charitymindvoid</Username><Timestamp>1350228927392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 11:35:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://messages.yahoo.com/Government_%26_Politics/By_Country_or_Region/United_States/Politics/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=18066891%23americasbecomingafasciststate&amp;tid=2148311&amp;mid=2148311&amp;tof=34&amp;rt=2&amp;frt=2&amp;off=1</Msg><Username>charitymindvoid</Username><Timestamp>1350450621647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 01:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350450983436-6</Id><Title>Court hears arguments in California clean-fuels case</Title><Msg>Court hears arguments in California clean-fuels case Published: October 16, 2012 Updated 11 hours ago By JASON DEAREN — Associated Press SAN FRANCISCO — A federal appeals court hearing a case seeking to stop California's first-in-the-nation mandate requiring fuel producers to reduce greenhouse gas emissions is focusing on whether the law discriminates against out-of-state businesses. A three-justice panel of the 9th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals on Tuesday heard oral arguments about the constitutionality of California's low-carbon fuel standard, a piece of the state's landmark global warming law, AB 32. The justices' questions focused on the law's reliance on a "carbon intensity score," which measures pollution from a fuel's entire life cycle, not just when it is burned in a vehicle. Out-of-state refiners and ethanol companies say this discriminates against their products because transportation to California raises the score. The state says the law does not discriminate and will spur clean-fuels innovation. THIS IS A BREAKING NEWS UPDATE. Check back soon for further information. AP's earlier story is below.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350450983436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 01:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350454907905-7</Id><Topic><Title>MIKEY (LPH) IS IN PLAY THEY PAID CASH</Title><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1350421771966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>warrants expire soon then ?????</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1350454907905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 02:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350460166898-8</Id><Topic><Title>Joe-Bama!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350445537752</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 23:45:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet more hilarity from the one who called Obama a neo-republican.Oh yeah,you're all so enthusiatic about Obama! That's why it alllll about Romney. President Mitt Romney.Letterman and Conan gonna be eating crow by the bowl full,but they'll have fun with his name - after inauguration day.It's a shame George didn't live to see it happen.He was a great man.One of this country's great success stories and a civil rights champion throughout his political career.But somewhere on high he's watching,with pride..</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350460166898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 03:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350464796608-9</Id><Title>We COULD see a MINUS -800 point DROP ON THE DOW today ! woooohoooo!</Title><Msg>SHORTIES get ready !!!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1350464796608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 05:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350468111170-10</Id><Title>hofstra and candy suck</Title><Msg>What a disgrace they were . The school and moderator were hostile to Romney. She did'nt let Mitt talk or give him time, this was all one sided. But this did'nt surprise me, ny would vote for hitler if he ran on dumbo ticket.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350468111170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350468159149-11</Id><Topic><Title>The 'real" Romney is revealed in 1 hour</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350432419846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 20:06:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobumba lies all the way.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350468159149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 06:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350471619002-12</Id><Title>mitt romney will save america, obama was the same , he just told one lie after another ! watch the news next few days ,they hang obama on his lies !</Title><Msg>..................................want $6 gas vote obama</Msg><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471619002</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350471700405-13</Id><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Msg>MITT THE MAN TO SAVE AMERICA</Msg><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350475805198-14</Id><Title>Death Of A Salesman</Title><Msg>Is what you saw last night . Everything about Romney is phony including his religion .His is a gutter religion build on lies that is why the Sh$t just rolls of off his tongue .</Msg><Username>mk_yb</Username><Timestamp>1350475805198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350477874548-15</Id><Topic><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES, but oil companies love Obama for the excessive profits he allowed the banks and oil companies to steal from everyone.</Msg><Username>bobbobareno</Username><Timestamp>1350477874548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350478647976-16</Id><Topic><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney clearly won the debate last night because he told too many lies, but the media has already started to spin it as a in for Obama. dems graduated with honors from the Paul Joseph Goebbels, Reich Minister of Propaganda in Nazi Germany from 1933 to 1945, school of misinformation. I don't care how they spin it in the coming days: Obama lost the debate.</Msg><Username>bobbobareno</Username><Timestamp>1350478647976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350478981892-17</Id><Topic><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney clearly won the debate last night because Obama told too many lies, but the media has already started to spin it as a win for Obama. dems graduated with honors from the Paul Joseph Goebbels, Reich Minister of Propaganda in Nazi Germany from 1933 to 1945, school of misinformation. I don't care how dims spin in the coming days: Obama lost the debate. (You didn't really think I was going to let the erroneous post stand, did you?)</Msg><Username>bobbobareno</Username><Timestamp>1350478981892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350479366282-18</Id><Topic><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As for last nights debate. nobumba candy crowmeat and hofstra all SUCK. All were biased and Romney did not get a fair shake.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350479366282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350479404456-19</Id><Topic><Title>Death Of A Salesman</Title><Username>mk_yb</Username><Timestamp>1350475805198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 08:10:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you are a sick twisted communist.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350479404456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350479447442-20</Id><Topic><Title>mitt romney will save america, obama was the same , he just told one lie after another ! watch the news next few days ,they hang obama on his lies !</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471619002</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More like $8 gas but then american are stupid.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350479447442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:10:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350479551960-21</Id><Topic><Title>The 'real" Romney is revealed in 1 hour</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350432419846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 20:06:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Desspite the lies from nobumba and a biased moderator Romney still wins. America has a new pres.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350479551960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350480141250-22</Id><Title>Candy Crowley LOL!</Title><Msg>of the Communist News Network (CNN), one of the primary Democrat controlled nedia outlets, looks like and is a typical ugly liberal hack who does her best to help out "her boy" Barack. After she aided Barack on his messup of the Libya situation, she and John King of CNN admitted Romney was correct in his point, but the lib media and their mindless sheeple folowers like Wahleee will never admit it. "They weren’t the only ones. Even Politico’s Mike Allen called the Crowley point “arguable” and pointed to the transcript of Obama’s statement saying it “generally” referred to “acts of terror.” CNN’s John King called the Obama statement a “generic” comment about terror, not specifically calling the Libya attack a terrorist act. Afterward, CNN’s post-debate analysis team focused heavily on that point and Crowley herself admitted Romney had been right “in the main.”</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350480141250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350480455384-23</Id><Topic><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The spin this morning is Obama had a narrow win last night. What? What lies will be told next? After more than four years of continuous lies, and putting aside all the lies we heard from the Clintons during the Clinton Administration, the dims continue to spin, spin, spin, lie, lie, lie. It was not a win for Obama. Obama lied his way into office in the '08 elections. I think he is a pathological liar.</Msg><Username>bobbobareno</Username><Timestamp>1350480455384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350482466920-24</Id><Title>NEW 12 Month High Today</Title><Msg>We're heaading thru $100.00 as the market sees recovery economy pushing Oil much higher in the year head, and especially with winter demand and switchover to heating oil continues....great dividend , good price increase all translates to great over all return in up or down mkt. !!</Msg><Username>pkj100</Username><Timestamp>1350482466920</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350482810427-25</Id><Topic><Title>Candy Crowley LOL!</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350480141250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hofstra and crowmeat suck.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350482810427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350483072140-26</Id><Topic><Title>NEW 12 Month High Today</Title><Username>pkj100</Username><Timestamp>1350482466920</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:01:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why the nice bump up today? Does the market like the Celtic acquisition? XOM buying its shares again? Oil is only up about 1/2 percent. I do love it though whatever the reason.</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1350483072140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:11:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350483478609-27</Id><Title>Another new high</Title><Msg>Energy sector will be on fire going in to elections!</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1350483478609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350484448030-28</Id><Topic><Title>NEW 12 Month High Today</Title><Username>pkj100</Username><Timestamp>1350482466920</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:01:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure would be nice to see HEAVY volume with new high</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1350484448030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:34:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350484773196-29</Id><Topic><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how saving the financial system, reducing unemployment and generally getting the economy out of the mess Bush left has increased oil demand, thus increasing oil cost. Oh, and domestic oil production is up too.</Msg><Username>adhill1</Username><Timestamp>1350484773196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350486073742-30</Id><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending October 12, 2012</Title><Msg>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending October 12, 2012 U.S. crude oil refinery inputs averaged 14.8 million barrels per day during the week ending October 12, 70 thousand barrels per day above the previous week’s average. Refineries operated at 87.4 percent of their operable capacity last week. Gasoline production increased last week, averaging over 9.0 million barrels per day. Distillate fuel production increased last week, averaging nearly 4.5 million barrels per day. U.S. crude oil imports averaged over 8.3 million barrels per day last week, up by 126 thousand barrels per day from the previous week. Over the last four weeks, crude oil imports have averaged about 8.1 million barrels per day, 785 thousand barrels per day below the same four-week period last year. Total motor gasoline imports (including both finished gasoline and gasoline blending components) last week averaged 530 thousand barrels per day. Distillate fuel imports averaged 85 thousand barrels per day last week. U.S. commercial crude oil inventories (excluding those in the Strategic Petroleum Reserve) increased by 2.9 million barrels from the previous week. At 369.2 million barrels, U.S. crude oil inventories are above the upper limit of the average range for this time of year. Total motor gasoline inventories increased by 1.7 million barrels last week and are in the lower half of the average range. Of the increase in total motor gasoline inventories, almost all of it was due to an increase in blending components inventories. Distillate fuel inventories decreased by 2.2 million barrels last week and are below the lower limit of the average range for this time of year. Propane/propylene inventories decreased by 1.3 million barrels last week, but remained above the upper limit of the average range. Total commercial petroleum inventories decreased by 2.7 million barrels last week. Total products supplied over the last four-week period have averaged 18.8 million barrels per day, which is the same level compared to the similar period last year. Over the last four weeks, motor gasoline product supplied has averaged nearly 8.7 million barrels per day, down by 2.3 percent from the same period last year. Distillate fuel product supplied has averaged about 3.9 million barrels per day over the last four weeks, down by 4.2 percent from the same period last year. Jet fuel product supplied is 2.3 percent higher over the last four weeks compared to the same four-week period last year. eia Data Overview (Combined Table 1 and Table 9) eia --------------------------------------- BLOOMBERG DOLLAR INDEX SPOT bloomberg --------------------------------------- Energy Futures Prices Below you may find all the futures prices &amp; quotes for: Crude Oil, Heating Oil, Gasoline RBOB, Natural Gas, ICE Brent Crude Oil, Ethanol (E) and more. Real Time Streaming Futures Quotes (CFDs) forexpros -------------------------------------- e85prices --------------------------------------- gasbuddy --------------------------------------- biodiesel retail-locations --------------------------------------- Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production [Usually updated late Thursday] ethanolrfa URLs at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350486073742</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:01:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350486390032-31</Id><Title>2800% GAINS POSSIBLE with EFIR oil discovery,cheap buy at 0.0002,READ</Title><Msg>2800% GAINS POSSIBLE with EFIR oil discovery,cheap buy at 0.0002,READ EFIR about to start next drilling across from BP and Chevron wells, currently producing 500,000 barrels of oil per month. This stock is at the bottom; the only it can go is up. Bought 4 millions shares, cost= $800. Sell 4 million shares at 0.01 = 4 million x 0.01 = $ 40,000 profit. With 2800% gains, EFIR can turn around your losses and bring your trading account back positive.</Msg><Username>pennyupdates</Username><Timestamp>1350486390032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350486673258-32</Id><Topic><Title>XOM is too superior to skip right now. Examine why!</Title><Username>jonathoncollins47</Username><Timestamp>1349959331474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 08:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fantastiiccccooo</Msg><Username>watsonneill</Username><Timestamp>1350486673258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350487826866-33</Id><Topic><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>christ if only the economy could go back into paralysis so the cost of gas would come down. you almost wish romney would win so these mouth-breathers could get what they're asking for. but they're too stupid to notice it when it happens.</Msg><Username>misanthropope</Username><Timestamp>1350487826866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350489322615-34</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its party time today</Msg><Username>watsonneill</Username><Timestamp>1350489322615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350489432499-35</Id><Title>Exxon to Buy Alberta’s Celtic for $2.91 Billion</Title><Msg>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-10-17/exxon-canada-to-acquire-celtic-exploration-to-add-alberta-output.html</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1350489432499</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 11:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350490255752-36</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Chart Evaluation &amp; Sell Mention</Title><Username>luckyone581</Username><Timestamp>1350302108811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 07:55:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I shorted XOM today at 93.36 and have changed by stop loss to 93.79.</Msg><Username>luckyone581</Username><Timestamp>1350490255752</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:10:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350491729680-37</Id><Topic><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"if only the economy could go back into paralysis". PROBLEM IS THE ECONOMY NEVER LEFT A STATE OF PARALYSIS BECAUSE ENERGY PRICES WON'T RELEASE THEIR CHOKE HOLD. Their will never be an economic recovery unless energy prices fall.</Msg><Username>bobbobareno</Username><Timestamp>1350491729680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350491842872-38</Id><Title>Who is next after Celtic? WMB? thoughts</Title><Msg>Anyone speculating on next acquisition target? I would think with Natural gas prices up today, there could be a movement soon in WMB XOM is a great long!</Msg><Username>jeremysikessr</Username><Timestamp>1350491842872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350492336871-39</Id><Topic><Title>The 'real" Romney is revealed in 1 hour</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350432419846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 20:06:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even Dick Morris says it will be a land slide for Romney. Bye bye #$%$ commie maxi dopey.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350492336871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 12:45:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350495060389-40</Id><Title>This Week In Petroleum October 17, 2012</Title><Msg>This Week In Petroleum October 17, 2012 Next Release: October 24, 2012 An Update on West Coast Gasoline Markets On Monday, October 8, the average retail price of regular gasoline in California reached $4.66 per gallon, driving the West Coast average price to $4.41 per gallon, the highest weekly price since the summer of 2008. The sharp price increase came after a combination of refinery and logistical problems stressed a market that had been operating with persistently low inventories throughout much of 2012. The higher prices last week were limited geographically to California, and wholesale prices have already declined sharply following a waiver from the Governor of California that allowed an early switch to winter-grade fuel and as disrupted refinery operations returned to normal. As discussed in the August 22 edition of This Week In Petroleum, due to a lack of significant pipeline connections to other regions of the United States, and because of its distance from the actively traded physical product markets of the Atlantic Basin, supply disruptions on the West Coast often have a larger impact than disruptions in the eastern part of the country. Prior to the recent price increases, gasoline markets on the West Coast have been periodically tight during 2012. A series of refinery outages since February have led to persistently low gasoline inventories (Figure 1). Gasoline supply issues began with a fire at BP's Cherry Point, Washington, refinery, which caused a three-month shutdown. Market pressures intensified after BP's Carson City, California, refinery underwent planned maintenance in March. These outages, combined with other smaller market disruptions, contributed to sharp inventory draws through the spring. West Coast gasoline inventories fell to 24.1 million barrels by May 18, more than 5 million barrels (about 20 percent) below the five-year average level for that time of year, making it the lowest level in more than ten years and the second lowest level since the beginning of the data series in January 1990. Gasoline inventories rose from late May into June as refinery issues abated and as higher prices attracted incremental supplies from outside the region. Despite the increase, inventories remained below their seasonally typical five-year range for most of the summer. A crude unit fire at Chevron's refinery in Richmond, California, in early August put additional stress on supply, and press reports have indicated that the Richmond crude unit will be out of service through 2012. Tesoro's Golden Eagle, California refinery, undertook planned maintenance in September, further pressuring West Coast markets. By the end of September, gasoline inventories in the region were again below the seasonally typical five-year range. On October 1, ExxonMobil's Torrance refinery experienced a sudden and unexpected loss of power from the utility grid that resulted in a shutdown. With inventories already low, concerns about the adequacy of gasoline supplies drove wholesale prices higher on the West Coast during the first week of October (Figure 2). As of the market close on September 28, California specification reformulated blendstock for oxygenate blending (CARBOB) was trading at $3.37 per gallon in Los Angeles, and had averaged a 6-cent-per-gallon premium to RBOB in New York Harbor over the previous ten trading days. By October 4, CARBOB in Los Angeles had reached $4.39 per gallon, a $1.16 premium to New York Harbor RBOB. CARBOB has historically traded at a premium of 10-15 cents per gallon to New York RBOB. This premium is mostly due to the additional cost to produce CARBOB; it is also volatile and depends on other factors such as transportation costs and market conditions. Unlike other disruptions on the West Coast this year, which affected prices in Washington, Oregon, and California, the impact of last week's disruption was generally limited to California. News that the Torrance refinery had returned to normal operations on Friday, October 5, calmed wholesale prices. More importantly, on October 7, the California Air Resources Board allowed for an early switch from summer- to winter-grade gasoline. Typically, summer-grade gasoline must be supplied through the end of October. The waiver allowed more components that are produced at West Coast refineries to be blended into finished gasoline, immediately alleviating supply tightness. In addition, winter-grade gasoline that meets California specifications is more available globally than the summer-grade equivalent. Summer-grade California gasoline is only produced at a limited number of refineries outside of California, and those refineries are significantly distant, including facilities in Asia and Canada's East Coast. By October 16, wholesale CARBOB prices in Los Angeles had fallen to $2.92 per gallon, a one-cent-per-gallon discount to New York Harbor RBOB. Retail gasoline prices in California are beginning to follow wholesale prices downward. On October 15, the U.S. Energy Information Administration (EIA) reported the average price for regular retail gasoline was $4.62 per gallon, a four-cent-per-gallon decrease from the previous week. Prices for the West Coast as a whole were $4.39 per gallon. Through the end of 2012, EIA's October Short-Term Energy Outlook projects prices to continue to ease on the West Coast, falling from their current level to average $3.76 per gallon in December 2012. Gasoline price down while diesel fuel price increases The U.S. average retail price of regular gasoline decreased three cents last week to $3.82 per gallon, 34 cents per gallon higher than last year at this time. Prices decreased in all regions of the nation except the Gulf Coast, where the price was up less than a penny to $3.54 per gallon. The Midwest price decreased nine cents to $3.69 per gallon. The average gasoline price in the Rocky Mountain region is $3.73 per gallon, down a penny from last week. The West Coast price dropped two cents to $4.39 per gallon. Rounding out the regions, the East Coast price was down less than a penny to $3.79 per gallon. The national average diesel fuel price increased six cents to $4.15 per gallon, 35 cents per gallon higher than last year at this time. The largest increase came in the Midwest, where the price increased 11 cents to $4.15 per gallon, followed by an increase of seven cents in the Rocky Mountain average price to $4.27 per gallon. The East Coast and West Coast prices each increased three cents, to $4.13 per gallon and $4.35 per gallon, respectively. Rounding out the regions, the Gulf Coast price is $4.02 per gallon, an increase of two cents from last week. Propane stocks show first significant draw of the season U.S. stocks of propane experienced the largest draw in months during the week ending October 12, 2012, as the winter heating season commences. Total propane stocks were down 1.3 million barrels to end at 74.6 million barrels, 15.7 million barrels (27 percent) higher than a year ago. The Gulf Coast led the draw, declining by 0.9 million barrels, followed by the Midwest region which drew down 0.5 million barrels. East Coast regional inventories added 0.1 million barrels and the Rocky Mountain/West Coast stocks were up slightly. Propylene non-fuel-use inventories represented 5.7 percent of total propane inventories. Residential heating oil prices rise while residential propane prices see minor reduction Residential heating oil prices increased during the period ending October 15, 2012. The average residential heating oil price rose by 5 cents per gallon last week to reach $4.03 per gallon, an increase of 26 cents per gallon from the same time last year. Wholesale heating oil prices increased by almost 7 cents per gallon last week to reach a price shy of $3.35 per gallon, 21 cents per gallon more than last year at this time. The average residential propane price decreased last week, by less than a penny per gallon, to reach a price just under $2.37 per gallon. This is a drop of 43 cents per gallon compared to the same period last year. Wholesale propane prices increased by almost 2 cents per gallon to $0.99 per gallon for the week ending October 15, 2012. This was a decrease of nearly 57 cents per gallon when compared to the October 17, 2011 price. eia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350495060389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350496129107-41</Id><Title>White House energy aide hopes for ‘reset button’ with Congress</Title><Msg>White House energy aide hopes for ‘reset button’ with Congress By Ben Geman - 10/17/12 12:49 PM ET Heather Zichal, a top White House energy and climate change aide, expressed hope Wednesday that the Obama administration and Capitol Hill can boost collaboration on green energy after the elections. Zichal, speaking at a renewable energy conference, said she is “hopeful that we will be able to hit the reset button with Congress, and working together we can look at the needs of the renewable industry and take steps to make certain that clean energy continues to increase.” Zichal, addressing the RETECH 2012 conference, said that energy is “certainly going to remain a top priority for the Obama administration.” In the near term, the White House is pressing Congress to extend the soon-to-expire production tax credit for wind energy projects. More broadly, Zichal said the administration’s goals include long-term policy to avoid “boom and bust” cycles in green energy, and the right regulatory frameworks to ensure natural gas production proceeds safely and responsibly. She also said investments on transmission and infrastructure, and commitment to basic energy R&amp;D, are priorities. “After all, it was years of federal research dollars that helped develop the technology that is now allowing us to take advantage of our natural gas resources,” she noted. Natural gas production in the U.S. is currently at record highs. “All of those policies have been and continue to be priorities of the Obama administration. We have got a lot more work to do but I think it is fair to say we have come a long way,” said Zichal, who is deputy assistant to the president for energy and climate change. Zichal’s hope for a “reset” follows recent years that have been heavy on collisions between the Obama administration and GOP lawmakers over energy. Little legislation has advanced, but there have been battles over green energy loans and drilling policy that included GOP subpoenas for documents. White House green energy initiatives, including President Obama’s plan for a national “clean energy standard,” have sputtered. Democrats, meanwhile, have parried House GOP bills to thwart various environmental rules and require an expansion of oil-and-gas leasing that’s far more aggressive than Obama supports. But White House officials have touted first-term steps including the major boost in auto mileage standards and support for green energy projects in the 2009 stimulus package, which they call a major factor behind renewable generation growth. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350496129107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350496379734-42</Id><Title>Enviros argue European airline emissions trading is working</Title><Msg>Enviros argue European airline emissions trading is working By Keith Laing - 10/17/12 12:49 PM ET A European Union requirement that airlines trade credits for carbon emissions emitted by flights to and from countries on the continent is already working, an environmental group argued Wednesday. The New York-based Environmental Defense Fund (EDF) said the new rules, which have been vocally opposed by both lawmakers and the U.S. airline industry, have already reduced emissions and "sparked innovation" in other sectors, despite being in their first full year of implementation for airlines. “What we found very clearly is that after a three-year trial period and almost five years of full operation, the world’s first global warming cap-and-trade program is doing exactly what the EU designed it to do — cut dangerous emissions, spur the deployment of low-carbon innovation and do so at low cost,” EDF Attorney Alexa Hanafi said in statement about a report issued by the organization. Under the rules, airlines have to reduce their emissions from 2006 levels by 3 percent by 2013 and 5 percent by 2020. The enforcement mechanisms and fines for noncompliance are similar to cap-and-trade proposals environmentalists once tried to push in the United States. The EDF's Hanafi said the fears of opponents to the European emissions trading system, which are similar to objections that have been raised in the U.S., have not come to fruition. On both sides of the Atlantic Ocean, critics argued that the emission rules would place undue burdens on businesses and stifle economic activity. But Hanafi said, “[W]hile many people are acutely aware of the global recession, Europe’s struggling economy and today’s low market prices for EU emission allowances, we found that there is another reality that is less well-known: despite some initial challenges, the EU Emissions Trading System is successfully reducing the EU’s global warming pollution, and offers real lessons to other countries and states seeking to decouple economic growth from emissions growth.” The EDF Director of Strategic Climate Initiatives Derek Walker, who is based in California, added, "[L]essons from the EU’s Emissions Trading System have relevance all over the world and nowhere more so than in California, where regulators and policymakers have been working hard to proactively adapt to the challenges revealed by the EU’s early years of implementation. “The bottom line is that emissions trading has been an economic and environmental success in the EU and it will be in California too," Walker said. U.S. airlines have said they will not have to begin making payments for emissions on flights to countries within the EU until April 2013, but they have asked both President Obama and Congress to step in to prevent the rules from being applied to them. The House has passed a bill to block the EU emission trading rules from being applied to U.S.-based airlines, but a similar measure has thus far been stalled in the Senate. Transportation Secretary Ray LaHood has called the European emission rules "lousy," but he has said the Obama administration will defer to Congress for a formal ban. The EDF report can be read here. the hill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350496379734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350496602623-43</Id><Title>debt, war, unemployment, the post office even, handouts, poor earnings SELL</Title><Msg>GET OUT now.....</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1350496602623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350498049799-44</Id><Title>CNBC "pumpers" will be working DOUBLETIME now..bwhahahaha!</Title><Msg>ridiculous.....MKT should FALL 2-3000 points on the DOW !</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1350498049799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350499106674-45</Id><Topic><Title>The Right Way To Trade XOM</Title><Username>aguilardelgado966</Username><Timestamp>1350485987262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:59:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your life will never be the same again after investing  your amount on such shares ,can grunt u on these. hope for the best.</Msg><Username>v.roman61</Username><Timestamp>1350499106674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:38:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350499189955-46</Id><Topic><Title>Candy Crowley LOL!</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350480141250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats are so desperate they are lying through all orifices. LOL! "The most shocking exchange took place on the Benghazi attack that left the U.S. ambassador to Libya and three others dead. Mr. Romney: “You said in the Rose Garden the day after the attack, it was an act of terror? It was not a spontaneous demonstration, is that what you’re saying.” Mr. Obama made no defense. “Please proceed, governor.” “I want to make sure,” Mr. Romney said. “Get the transcript,” the president said. Then Ms. Crowley jumped in to do her own fact-check, on the spot. “It — it — it — he did in fact, sir. … He did call it an act of terror.” The truth is, he didn’t. The day after the attack, he said only this: “No acts of terror will ever shake the resolve of this great nation, alter that character or eclipse the light of the values that we stand for.” It took another two weeks before the White House would label the attack an act of terror."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350499189955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 14:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350502339757-47</Id><Title>The 5 Most Misleading Statements from the Second Presidential Debate</Title><Msg>Obama falsely claims he called Benghazi attacks “acts of terror” in Rose Garden speech The president’s claim that he did, contrary to Governor Romney’s critique, call the Benghazi attacks “acts of terror” in a September 12 Rose Garden speech got perhaps the most play of any questionable statement last night. In fact, that claim is false. In the speech in question, the president vaguely alluded to “acts of terror,” but he did not classify the Benghazi attacks as such. Given that the attacks took place on the anniversary of the most notorious terrorist attack in history, there was by no means a clear implication that the phrase referred to the then-ongoing assaults on American diplomatic facilities across North Africa. Even moderator Candy Crowley, who insisted during the debate that Obama “did in fact” label the Benghazi attacks terrorism in the Rose Garden, walked back that claim in a post-debate interview. She said Romney’s critique was “right, in the main,” but that he had “picked the wrong word.” CNN itself noted that the White House acknowledged Benghazi was a terrorist attack for the first time a full nine days after the attacks themselves, as Ezra Dulis of Breitbart News pointed out. Other reporters likewise declared Romney correct on that score after the debate, including Politico’s Mike Allen, the Washington Post’s Glenn Kessler, and the Washington Times’s Anneke Green. Obama again misleads on job creation numbers Obama often insists that 5 million jobs have been created on his watch, and Heritage has addressed that claim before. In order to arrive at this number, the president examines a time frame that is as friendly to his own record as possible. In short, he measures job growth not from the beginning of his term, but from the employment low-point about a year later. If measured from January 2009, when Obama took office, the country has actually added only about 316,000 jobs. Of course even that overstates the president’s record, since obviously the federal government is not responsible for every job created in the private sector (and the 5 million number actually refers only to private sector jobs – government jobs are down even within the timeframe Obama touts.) Data visualization expert Matthias Shapiro (also known by his Twitter handle @PoliticalMath) created a very informative video – a bit dated, but still highly applicable – to explain the president’s chicanery on this issue. Despite Obama’s claims, oil and gas production on federal land is way down In an exchange about domestic energy production, Obama claimed that American oil and gas companies are “actually drilling more on public lands than in the previous administration.” In fact, as Heritage has pointed out, fossil fuel production of federal land hit a nine-year low in 2011. ABC’s Jonathan Karl also noticed this disconnect. “Oil drilling permits on public land dropped by 37% in the first two years of the Obama administration, [and] 42% in terms of leases for natural gas,” Karl noted. Romney inflates the alleged effect of Chinese currency manipulation on U.S. job growth Governor Romney, who has frequently criticized China for “cheating” through alleged currency manipulation, falsely suggested that that currency manipulation has a significant effect on U.S. employment. As Heritage’s Derek Scissors noted in a recent report: [T]he exchange rate between the yuan and the dollar has no direct effect on American prosperity or American jobs. It never has. Seventeen years ago, China sharply devalued the yuan against the dollar. Yet American unemployment fell for years afterward. Since 2005, the PRC has been slowly raising the value of its currency, which is what protectionists say they want. And American unemployment has soared. Obama claims he saved the auto industry. In fact, he just saved the UAW The president is fond of inflating the impact of his auto industry bailout, and claimed again last night that his administration “saved an auto industry that was on the brink of collapse.” But government involvement in the General Motors and Chrysler bankruptcies amounted to a bailout not of the companies themselves, but of their largest union, the United Auto Workers, as Heritage’s James Sherk has noted. None of that [bailout] money kept factories running. Instead, it sustained the above-average compensation of members of an influential union, sparing them from most of the sacrifices typically made in bankruptcy—a bankruptcy they contributed to.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350502339757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350502713667-48</Id><Title>XOM purchase of Celtic Exploration:</Title><Msg>See the analysis below! Makes Lone Pine Resources (LPR) an attractive BUY! FST spun LPR off at around $8.50 and NOW LPR is $1.60! “Looking at Celtic Exploration.. their book value is $6.71.. trading at $25 after this news.. around $18 before. They were trading at about 3 times book value with negative EPS and 125% the revenue of LPR. LPR's book value is $4.46 and we are trading at about 1/3 of that. Where is the disconnect here? After LPR finalizes the sale of non-core acreage their debt will be almost identical to CLT. LPR has gapped down the last two quarters and should see a little bounce with their asset sales. LPR should be trading comfortably in the 2-3 range”</Msg><Username>semiequipmentgodoftheyear</Username><Timestamp>1350502713667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350503293277-49</Id><Topic><Title>XOM purchase of Celtic Exploration:</Title><Username>semiequipmentgodoftheyear</Username><Timestamp>1350502713667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are better voices for XOM then this</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1350503293277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350503847327-50</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>kevininthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350496258855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:50:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well this is not a mind blowing app, but it is useful and I like it - thanks for the tip.</Msg><Username>peelingoutsummer</Username><Timestamp>1350503847327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350505400315-51</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gains 4% on Intrade</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350504608578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's sad when one party derides the other for believing in the US Constitution and the principles of our founding fathers..</Msg><Username>huck_iie</Username><Timestamp>1350505400315</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350505729083-52</Id><Topic><Title>The Right Way To Trade XOM</Title><Username>aguilardelgado966</Username><Timestamp>1350485987262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:59:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can count on your money by investing in the stock market for better future returns.</Msg><Username>flynnacosta69</Username><Timestamp>1350505729083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350506860611-53</Id><Topic><Title>The 5 Most Misleading Statements from the Second Presidential Debate</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350502339757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:32:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maxwizard is one of the low IQs getting taxpayer funded help from Obama and the Democrat Party. His Sister is the infamous Obamaphone lady. LOL!</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350506860611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350507159746-54</Id><Title>Another Glen Beck Fan Off The Streets... Phew, Mormon Madness Must End!</Title><Msg>Federal officials have arrested a suspect that they say was plotting to attack the Federal Reserve's building in New York City, according to a report from NBC 4 News. People walk past the Federal Reserve building in New YorkLaw-enforcement officials said that the plot was a sting operation monitored by the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the New York Police Department and that the public was never at risk, according to the report. According to the report, the suspect drove a van he believed to be loaded with explosives from Long Island to Lower Manhattan. He then placed the van near the Federal Reserve and was then arrested by the FBI and NYPD. [More From CNBC: Iran Plotting to Spill Oil in Strait of Hormuz, Magazine Claims] "It is important to emphasize that the public was never at risk in this case, because two of the defendant's 'accomplices' were actually an FBI source and an FBI undercover agent," said Mary Galligan, the N.Y. Fed's acting assitant director. "The FBI continues to place the highest priority on preventing acts of terrorism." The suspect, whom sources said is from the Jamaica Queens section of New York City, is currently in custody in New York. Sources say he was acting alone</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350507159746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350507171222-55</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gains 4% on Intrade</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350504608578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maxwizard thinks the "constitution" has something to do with his digestive track and his "founding fathers" wilted away in Africa centuries ago. He won't admit it, but slavery of his ancestors did him a big favor because otherwise, if he was born, he would be dead by now or not doing so well in Africa. Call it racist if you want, but this is the truth.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350507171222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350507280051-56</Id><Topic><Title>Candy Crowley LOL!</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350480141250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 09:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He did, you lose.... Say hello to FOUR MORE YEARS!!!!</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350507280051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:54:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350507328766-57</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gains 4% on Intrade</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350504608578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know, those Republicans sure are sick aren't they?</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350507328766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350507420359-58</Id><Title>Wahleee Proven an Idiot Once More</Title><Msg>Kind of like every time Obama opens his mouth, every time Wahleee posts, he lies. "Federal authorities arrested a Bangladeshi national Wednesday morning for allegedly plotting to blow up a Federal Reserve building in New York City's lower Manhattan, mere blocks away from the site of the terrorist attack of Sept. 11, 2001. The 21-year-old suspect, Quazi Mohammad Rezwanul Ahsan Nafis, attempted to detonate what he thought was a 1,000-pound bomb in front of the Fed building on Liberty Street, but the device was a fake supplied to him by undercover FBI agents who had been tracking his activity, the FBI's Joint Terrorism Task Force said Wednesday afternoon. The supposed explosives posed no threat to the public, the FBI said. A criminal complaint accuses Nafis of having overseas connections to Al Qaeda and travelling to the U.S. in January to recruit individuals to form a terrorist cell "</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350507420359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350507485041-59</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gains 4% on Intrade</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350504608578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's absolutely INSANE. Yeah, according to your racist insanity slavery was exactly the way to get a leg up in America. You work for a beating and NEVER GET PAID. Yup, that'll build generational wealth.. No wonder why they aren't that concerned about inheritence taxes. Invester the molester You are a racist scab.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350507485041</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350507647061-60</Id><Topic><Title>Wahleee Proven an Idiot Once More</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350507420359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:57:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh you would have loved it if the Beck fan got away with it.. You could have used it to win in Nov. But alas you are destined to lose.....</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350507647061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350508208965-61</Id><Topic><Title>The Right Way To Trade XOM</Title><Username>aguilardelgado966</Username><Timestamp>1350485987262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 10:59:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the info..very useful. Volume not what I would like so we'll see what happens. Any thoughts? Thanks again!</Msg><Username>monroenicholson62</Username><Timestamp>1350508208965</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 17:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350511468285-62</Id><Topic><Title>XOM purchase of Celtic Exploration:</Title><Username>semiequipmentgodoftheyear</Username><Timestamp>1350502713667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jgiled, you may be correct. strange thou that LPR has a book value in the mid $4s</Msg><Username>semiequipmentgodoftheyear</Username><Timestamp>1350511468285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350511573119-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gains 4% on Intrade</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350504608578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you follow any stocks? Or do you come to the stock message boards only to rant and spew hatred for the Republicans of America? Get a grip, take a pill, get laid, do something because you're like a hemorrhoid.</Msg><Username>whistling_past_the_graveyard</Username><Timestamp>1350511573119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:06:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350515826992-64</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gains 4% on Intrade</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350504608578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah sure whatever you say. You lie like Obama. Anyone who has been laughing at your post for over 3 years like me knows you are a low IQ black (or maybe albino?) Obama supporter. Whatever the case, you and Wahleeee are the board idiots - or is it bored idiots? Either way, you have always been and always will be a loser; wasted life that God has kindly bestowed upon your sorry ---.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350515826992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:17:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350517187124-65</Id><Title>Report: Energy production threatens to strain nation’s water supply</Title><Msg>Report: Energy production threatens to strain nation’s water supply By Zack Colman - 10/17/12 01:55 PM ET The federal government must better monitor the nation's water supply as expanded domestic energy production threatens to further strain water resources, warns a Government Accountability Office (GAO) report released Tuesday. With an earlier Congressional Research Service study projecting the energy sector to account for 85 percent of the growth in domestic water consumption between 2005 and 2030, the GAO report says the federal government must improve oversight on the nexus between water and energy. The report calls for the Energy Department to institute an oversight program to evaluate water availability and use by energy producers. It notes the Energy Policy Act of 2005 required the department to implement a similar program, but has so far failed to do so. The report adds that climate change, population growth, increased competition for energy resources and demographic changes would “exacerbate the challenges associated with water and energy supply and demand, and shifts in any of these areas are expected to increase demand for both of these resources.” Higher energy consumption in general has required using more water for cooling power plants. A significant amount of the growth in water consumption also has come from the emergence of new energy production methods. For example, hydraulic fracturing used to tap hard-to-reach oil-and-gas deposits revolutionized the natural-gas drilling industry. Known as fracking, that process injects a high-pressure mixture of water, chemicals and sand into tight rock formations to unlock fossil fuel reserves. Biofuels production also has siphoned considerable amounts of local water for growing feedstocks, the report noted. A federal rule requires refiners to nearly triple current production levels by blending 36 billion gallons of biofuel into traditional transportation fuel by 2022. Those developments — and, in particular, the fracking boom — combined with the past summer’s drought have led to water shortages across the country. That forced water auction prices higher, with energy companies outbidding farmers who traditionally had little problem securing water through that avenue. On the other hand, many energy firms could not find enough water to continue fracking. Federal, state and local agencies need to better coordinate water and energy decisions to avoid those situations, the report says. Too often, that planning is “stove-piped” to different authorities with little coordination, it adds. The report calls for those agencies, as well as industry, to improve water supply data collection to better inform planning decisions. “[T]he lack of such data makes it challenging to fully #$%$ the impact that particular energy policy choices will have on water resources,” it says. thehill -------------------------------------- ENERGY-WATER NEXUS Coordinated Federal Approach Needed to Better Manage Energy and Water Tradeoffs 38 pages gao URL's available at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350517187124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350517531264-66</Id><Title>Obama campaign defends debate silence on climate change</Title><Msg>Obama campaign defends debate silence on climate change By Zack Colman - 10/17/12 06:00 PM ET The Obama campaign defended the president’s silence on climate change during Tuesday’s debate after environmentalists and activists criticized him for not directly addressing the issue. “Whether it’s on the stump or at the White House, President Obama has long focused on ways to develop clean energy as a core economic pillar. By advocating for the growth of renewable energy, as he did in Tuesday’s debate, President Obama has continually called for action that will address the sources of climate change,” Adam Fetcher, a spokesman for the campaign, told The Hill in an email Wednesday. Environmentalists have pushed both Obama and GOP presidential candidate Mitt Romney to address climate change in the debates, saying the summer's drought, record temperatures, wildfires and storms make it a salient issue. Many thought the president had that chance during an exchange on energy during Tuesday's debate at Hofstra University in New York state. Some environmentalists expressed disappointment that Obama touted his record on drilling and coal while failing to mention the effect expanded fossil fuel production would have on climate change. Others, however, said Obama’s record on climate change, as well as various stump speeches, show his commitment to tackling the issue. They cited air pollution rules and fuel efficiency standards rolled out during Obama’s term, along with the president’s consistent backing of clean energy. Fetcher said the differences between Obama and Romney on energy should indicate which candidate is more devoted to mitigating the effects of climate change. “While Mitt Romney questioned the science behind climate change and mocked it in his convention speech, President Obama will continue to make the case for cleaner American sources of energy that will create jobs and fight climate change,” Fetcher said. Romney has said humans contribute to climate change but has called for more studies to determine the level of that impact. He has said “unilateral” U.S. actions to curb climate change could undercut the nation’s economic competitiveness. [color=#33CC00][b]CNN’s Candy Crowley, who moderated Tuesday’s debate, said she ran out of time before she could ask a prepared question on climate change.[/b][/color] the hill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350517531264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:45:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350517861241-67</Id><Title>US environment agency fights back over mountaintop mining</Title><Msg>US environment agency fights back over mountaintop mining Courts set to decide on agency's power to protect wildlife and habitats. Natasha Gilbert 16 October 2012 The US Environmental Protection Agency is fighting tooth and nail to stop destructive mining practices that threaten the aquatic habitats and wildlife of the url at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350517861241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 19:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350519765704-68</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gains 4% on Intrade</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350504608578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rot in he!! you right wing POS!</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350519765704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:22:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350519952198-69</Id><Topic><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In June 2008, six months before W retired from his very "suckcessfull ?" presidency , gas was $4.00 a gallon. It went down for the next six months to about half that. But a lot of house prices also were cut in half. Now gas is high and houses are making a comeback. Romney would give us more stuff like W. But if that's what you want vote for the Mitten.</Msg><Username>ab_lmno_xyz</Username><Timestamp>1350519952198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350521265163-70</Id><Topic><Title>$ GAS WAS $1.84 THE DAY OBAMA TOOK OFFICE,TODAY ITS $3.85 !!!!!!!!!OBAMA HATES OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>savingamerica622</Username><Timestamp>1350471700405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 07:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gas was also 4.25 under bush what's your point, we all should hate oil companys</Msg><Username>tclucky0529</Username><Timestamp>1350521265163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 20:47:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350522077584-71</Id><Title>YEAP..the "Earnings Jockey's" are working overtime ! MOST came from layoffs!</Title><Msg>Take Goldman for instance..$2.45/sh Q3 2012.....in Q4 2010 $8.10.....MINUS 75% yet a "beat" was declared by the CNBC "pumpers" !...GET OUT of the MKT soon...........we're heading SOUTH !!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1350522077584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350526861861-72</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder if invest and infernal will disappear ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350525016176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I give a rat about those shriveled dog logs--they have no purpose in life but to stink (no offense to the dog)--the only concern is something like a shizzle pants mcconnell--in a position of responsibility and neglecting every duty he has sworn to uphold. the only thing him and his lil buddies are beholden to is grover norquist and his lil pledge to protect rich special interests even if they trample on all of America in the process. shame on EVERY disgusting person that holds any lil' "pledge" above their elected sworn duties</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1350526861861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350530193009-73</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder if invest and infernal will disappear ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350525016176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've been on this board for well over 12 years now and will be here long after you're gone. Won't want to miss you spewing your skewed hatred after the election. And watching you descend into insanity is always entertaining.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350530193009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350530228461-74</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder if invest and infernal will disappear ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350525016176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still brain dead wahleee boy. It's not a reversible condition.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350530228461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350530345127-75</Id><Topic><Title>Another Glen Beck Fan Off The Streets... Phew, Mormon Madness Must End!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350507159746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:52:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A great demonstration of brain death from the poster boy for same. Thank you.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350530345127</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:19:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350530805384-76</Id><Topic><Title>The 5 Most Misleading Statements from the Second Presidential Debate</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350502339757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:32:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OOOO - the big bully threatens again - and over a news article he doesn't like. Does it make you feel important max instead of emasculated? Or is that your regular lib tactic when you can't refute a point and have nothing of substance to contribute. Pathetic - you are really going downhill.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350530805384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350531316003-77</Id><Title>Fact Check: Top Ten Worst Lies of the Second Presidential Debate</Title><Msg>The Second Presidential Debate featured repeated claims by each candidate that the other was not telling the truth--as well as at least one claim of fact by the moderator that turned out to be false. There were even questionable claims by the audience itself. Here are the top ten worst lies told during the Second Debate: 10. "I told you I would cut taxes for middle-class families, and I did. I told you I’d cut taxes for small businesses, and I have." President Barack Obama has made this claim repeatedly during the campaign, but it is not true, as even the liberal Huffington Post acknowledges. The few tax cuts that Obama did enact--such as the temporary payroll tax holiday--were short-term, or conditional. Furthermore, as the Romney campaign has often pointed out, Obama has raised many taxes on the middle class, including the infamous Obamacare "penalty," and his taxes on "millionaires and billionaires" would hit small businesess. 9. "...[H]e was asked, is it fair for somebody like you, making $20 million a year, to pay a lower tax rate than a nurse or a bus driver....And he said, yes, I think that’s fair." Obama was referring to Romney's recent 60 Minutes interview. But the transcript reveals Obama was not telling the truth. Romney was not saying it was fair that higher income should be taxed at a lower rate. He was referring specifically to the principle that capital gains should be taxed lower than other income because it has been taxed once already--a principle, incidentally, that Obama agrees with in his own tax policy. 8. "He called the Arizona law a model for the nation." Obama tried to knock Romney's immigration policy while at the same time accusing him of flip-flopping on the issue. But as Romney pointed out, he was referring specifically to the e-Verify part of the law--the requirement of instant verification of workers' legal status. That provision is even favored by unions. Obama made it seem Romney praised the law as a whole--which he had not. He went on to say that he himself objected to the provision that allowed police to check suspected illegal immigrants' documentation--but that provision survived a challenge at the Supreme Court. 7. "I want to make sure our timekeepers are working here." For the third debate in a row, the Democratic candidate complained that he was not receiving as much time to speak as the Republican. And for the third debate in a row, the Obama/Biden ticket actually spoke for longer--much longer--than the Romney/Ryan ticket, a testament to the ability of the incumbents to pressure the moderators, and the susceptibility of the left-leaning moderators to such pressure. Obama received a full three minutes more time in last night's debate--and the percentage difference was even higher at one point in the proceedings. 6. "They rely on it for mammograms." Obama attacked Romney's proposal to cut off federal funding to Planned Parenthood by claiming that the organization provides mammograms to women to help prevent breast cancer. It's been a repeated claim made by the left for months. The problem is that it's just untrue--and even left-leaning mainstream media fact-checkers have acknowledged that. What is perhaps worse than Obama's misleading claim about mammograms is the unsupported implication that Romney wants to deny life-saving health care to women--a cheap shot to which Romney was given no chance to respond. 5. "You can ship jobs overseas and get tax breaks for it." We have heard the same lie for eight years from Obama. In 2004, he ran for U.S. Senate from Illinois on a promise to end such tax breaks. He did it again when he ran for President of the United States in 2008. And yet he has never done anything about it--because there are no such tax breaks. There is merely a deduction that companies can take for moving, even within the U.S.--and which helps offset the double taxation of U.S. businesses abroad, which would make American companies less competitive. Repealing it would ship jobs overseas, actually. 4. "And the production is up....What you’re saying is just not true." Obama contested a claim by Romney that production of oil and gas is down on federal lands. He even accused Romney of not telling the truth. But Romney was right--exactly right, down to the percentage decline. Furthermore, Obama's claim that he has been increasing oil and gas production on federal lands flies in the face of recent policy decisions, such as closing off a large part of the National Petroleum Reserve-Alaska to further development. Obama has tried to take credit for expansion on private lands, while opposing expansion wherever possible. 3. "In what new ways do you intend to rectify the inequalities in the workplace, specifically regarding females making only 72 percent of what their male counterparts earn?" The false premise from a member of the audience was especially egregious because her question had been selected in advance by the moderator. The supposed wage gap between men and women for the same work is largely a myth. As Diana Furchtgott-Roth pointed out: "Women make about 95 percent of what their male counterparts earn, if the male counterparts are in the same job with the same experience." 2. "He wanted to take them into bankruptcy without providing them any way to stay open." After Obama accused Romney of wanting American auto manufacturers to go bankrupt, Romney pointed out that Obama had, in fact, taken the auto companies through bankruptcy. Obama's retort was to accuse Romney of wanting to take the companies bankrupt in order to put them out of business--a blatant lie. Romney actually suggested in his famous 2008 op-ed: "In a managed bankruptcy, the federal government would propel newly competitive and viable automakers, rather than seal their fate with a bailout check." 1. "He did call it an act of terror." The worst untruth told by a moderator in presidential history. Candy Crowley's intervention in favor of Obama caused the president's cheering section to burst into applause, in violation of the rules, and there was little that Romney could say in response. But she was wrong--Obama's reference to "acts of terror" in his Sep. 12 statement was in a general, abstract sense, and came long after he had described the 9/11 attacks on U.S. diplomatic missions as demonstrations against an anti-Islamic video. Even Crowley seemed to realize what she had done: it wasn't long before she walked back her own comment.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350531316003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350531377830-78</Id><Topic><Title>Fact Check: Top Ten Worst Lies of the Second Presidential Debate</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350531316003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:35:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey max: did you tutor Obamao on how to lie with a straight face, or did he tutor you?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350531377830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350532237744-79</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gains 4% on Intrade</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350504608578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 16:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We're not the same - but you and wahleee boy are sure sounding like twins these dats. Doesn't that make you feel great!</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350532237744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 23:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>