<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-16"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347768586573-1</Id><Title>Christians will continue to be slaughtered in greater numbers as US/Israel continue to overthrow dictators</Title><Msg>The US surrounded Israel with numerous torture sanctioning dictatorships and now, after engineering the Arab spring, are sowing chaos and war. For 2000 years Iraq maintained a stable Christian community until the coalition forces liberated Iraq and 95% have slaughtered or dislocated. Bethlehem was 40% Christian 30 years ago but zionist forces have reduced their numbers to 5%. The white Christian holocaust is moving at full speed in the USA at the behest of the same open border neocon Trotskyites. Over 1000 military bases around the world paid for by American taxpayers while an invasion from the world's largest narco terrorist state, Mexico, is facilitated by both Republicans and Democrats.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1347768586573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 00:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347785946803-2</Id><Topic><Title>Christians will continue to be slaughtered in greater numbers as US/Israel continue to overthrow dictators</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1347768586573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 00:09:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let them try, big surprise over here.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347785946803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 04:59:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347787879053-3</Id><Topic><Title>maxipad</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347661767352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:29:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now I think he left the country before nobumba loses election. Little sissy coward afraid of getting kicked in his panties.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347787879053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 05:31:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347804474212-4</Id><Title>FFVs in Nebraska increase by 20% from last year</Title><Msg>FFVs in Nebraska increase by 20 percent Posted: Sunday, September 16, 2012 2:00 am | Updated: 12:29 am, Sun Sep 16, 2012. By Robert Pore 0 comments The number of flex fuel vehicles in Nebraska has increased by more than 20 percent from last year. There are now more than 143,000 registered FFVs in Nebraska, according to the Nebraska Ethanol Board. Flex fuel vehicles can run on any blend of ethanol and gasoline up to E85, which is 85 percent ethanol. According to the Nebraska Ethanol Board, drivers can determine whether their vehicle is an FFV by checking for an FFV logo on the back of the vehicle. Most flex fuel vehicles also have a yellow gas cap. Drivers can also check the U.S. Department of Energy's website to identify all makes and models of flex fuel vehicles. Drivers benefit from E85 and ethanol blends by saving money, reducing greenhouse gas emissions and supporting Nebraska's economy, said Todd Sneller, Nebraska Ethanol Board administrator. Sneller said some Nebraska fuel stations are selling E85 at 68 cents per gallon under regular unleaded prices. Economic studies have also found that ethanol lowers gas prices for everyone - even non-FFV drivers - by extending the country's gas supply. New blender pump opens up in Elgin This past week, there was a grand opening of a blender pump in Elgin. This E85/blender pump is one of approximately 60 in Nebraska to offer a variety of renewable ethanol fuel blends. This station will offer unleaded, E10, E30, and E85. To find a list of retailers that offer E85 and other mid-level ethanol blends, ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347804474212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:07:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347805331307-5</Id><Title>Market access critical for ethanol, CEO says</Title><Msg>Market access critical for ethanol, CEO says 12:10 AM, Sep 16, 2012 Comments Written by Peter Harriman Now it’s Jeff Lautt’s turn to try to scale the blend wall. The Poet president in April followed one of the most significant figures in the renewable fuels industry when he succeeded Jeff Broin as Poet CEO. Beginning in 1986, Broin built the company from a single plant in Scotland, S.D., to 27 plants in seven states with a production capacity of more than 1.6 billion gallons. He put Poet on the forefront of efforts to move the renewable fuels industry beyond ethanol made from corn starch to ethanol distilled from cellulose-based feedstocks. Poet is building the first commercial scale cellulosic ethanol plant in Emmetsburg, Iowa. Broin will remain as Poet’s executive chairman of the board, and he will continue to serve on the board of directors of the ethanol advocacy organization Growth Energy. “Obviously, Jeff Broin was an innovator and an industry leader,” South Dakota Secretary of Agriculture Walt Bones said. “I think his successor has got big shoes to fill.” But Bones adds, “I don’t see this as a one-person industry,” and the leadership change at Poet won’t send disturbing ripples through the ethanol industry. Lautt has been around for much of Poet’s expansion. The company has more than tripled since he’s been there. He joined it in 2005 as a production executive and became executive vice president of corporate operations. He was named president in 2011. Before joining Poet, Lautt was president of the emergency vehicle manufacturer Crimson Fire in Brandon. The blend-wall characterization reflects the history of ethanol production and of Poet. In 2005, the federal government created the Renewable Fuel Standard, a mandate that escalates the percentage of renewable fuel in the nation’s transportation fuel from 4 billion gallons in 2006 to 36 billion by 2022. The RFS led to rapid expansion of the ethanol industry. The mandate is 13.8 billion gallons next year. But with the common formulation of ethanol, 10 percent alcohol and 90 percent gasoline, ethanol production has exceeded the capacity of the nation’s transportation fuel supply to absorb it. Broin, as Poet CEO and a charismatic proponent of ethanol, was instrumental in bringing Poet and the industry to the happy point where it can sell all the E10 it can make. But ethanol leaders now are preoccupied with getting ethanol with higher concentrations of alcohol accepted to leap the blend wall and create growth in the business. Widespread drought this summer has sent the price of ethanol’s major feedstock, corn, skyrocketing. But Lautt shrugs off that concern. “There’s a lot of talk about the drought. But the biggest challenge is access to the market,” he says. The Environmental Protection approved E15 last year. However, representatives of the grocery, auto and oil industries sued to block the move. In August the U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit rejected the lawsuit. Lautt said the decision “helped ensure that groups with ulterior motives will not derail the expansion of domestic, renewable fuel. E15 will allow ethanol to further lower gas prices, lower U.S. dependence on foreign oil and improve our economy.” He noted the new cellulosic plant in Iowa. “Crop residue could be used to produce almost 8 billions of gallons of ethanol for the U.S., but only if drivers are given the option to use it. E15 gives cellulosic ethanol a viable market. “I look forward to seeing E15 become available at fuel stations across the country,” Lautt said. But he acknowledges that persuading gas stations to install new pumps for E15 will be an ongoing battle, state by state. Poet had almost $6 billion in revenue last year as a privately held company. Lautt is coy about whether he will be the CEO who takes Poet public. “It does take capital to grow,” he said. “What the future holds no one knows.” As a private company, Poet is nimble and lean, Lautt said. “With public capital I can see the benefits, and some negatives. If we can remain private and support our growth, that’s an option.” While pointing to the challenge of finding capital for growth, Purdue University agricultural economist Wallace Tyner seconds Lautt’s assessment that Poet is run efficiently as a private company. Tyner calls Poet “the Walmart of the ethanol industry. They do an incredibly efficient, excellent job of managing their facilities.” Though it might take a century to complete the move, Lautt is convinced he is heading Poet at a point in history when the U.S. is transitioning from petroleum to renewable fuels. “Our grandchildren will look back and say: ‘Wow. This was the right way.’ ” argusleader</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347805331307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347806521617-6</Id><Title>Kitimat-Stikine board voted to oppose the Enbridge Northern Gateway pipeline at its Sept 14 meeting</Title><Msg>Pipeline panned Published: September 16, 2012 7:00 AM AFTER MUCH discussion, the Regional District of Kitimat-Stikine board voted to oppose the Enbridge Northern Gateway pipeline at its Sept. 14 meeting. The motion to oppose was brought forward by Telegraph Creek director David Brocklebank at the August meeting and was tabled to allow the other directors time to consult with their constituents. Voting in favour of the motion were Brocklebank, Dease Lake alternate director Joey Waite, Terrace municipal directors Dave Pernarowski and Bruce Bidgood, Nass director (and regional district chair) Harry Nyce, Hazelton mayor Alice Maitland, Kispiox/Kitwanga director Linda Pierre and Diana Penner (who was sitting in for absent regular director Doug McLeod) for the area around Terrace. Voting against the motion were Thornhill director Ted Ramsey, Kitimat municipal director Corinne Scott, New Hazelton mayor Gail Lowry and Stewart municipal director Billie Ann Belcher. During the discussion, Scott said she would vote against the motion because a federal project panel review would look at everything presented to it and supporting the panel was absolutely necessary. “Voting against it is to oppose the political process and I feel strongly we have to allow the [Joint Review Panel] to complete its findings,” she said. Bidgood said the review was supposed to be independent and not political and that he had been greatly influenced by the prime minister and federal finance minister supporting the project. “What attracted me to northern B.C. was its beauty,” he said. “If there was an environmental [disaster], I would have a hard time looking at the next generation and saying I didn’t do anything to oppose it.” Ted Ramsey agreed with Scott, saying his constituents wanted him to remain neutral. Brocklebank said he had yet to talk to anyone who supported the pipeline project. terracestandard</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347806521617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347818421856-7</Id><Title>Rmoney and war in Iran</Title><Msg>Obama recently spoke with mittens and made it very clear if there was any more "wars" that the military would initiate a "draft" which at least 3 of his sons would be elgible for . Mittens said that was fine by him--"bring it on". Obama further explained that any more "wars" would be 100% paid by a war tax on ALL but a "especially progressive" TAX !! After further thought Mittens stated that "there should be no rush to war and diplomacy and sanctions should be given AMPLE time to work". money talks-#$%$ walks</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1347818421856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347819961943-8</Id><Title>what's you're lesser known Oil picks?</Title><Msg>HNL.TO is my fav not directly in the oil it self but with expansion in the oil sands they are a very nice play. The dividend is nice too CDI.TO is good from a value point and has a nice dividend. AEN.TO more on the risky side but as a long term investment I feel it should do well PHX.TO Has some things to work out. The dividend is near 9% though. Seems as though they should be able to keep up the payments on it. The least exciting of all, but at around 9% I can wait it out. What's your pics and thoughts? Side note I listed Canadian stocks since I fell the US dollar will decline with Big Ben printing all that money. My theory is the stocks will go up as well as the Canadian dollar. The best sites for Canadian research is theglobeandmail</Msg><Username>awkward_pause4u</Username><Timestamp>1347819961943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347834204875-9</Id><Title>New Butanol Process Improves Output 100%, Cuts Costs - can be used in unmodified gasoline engines in concentrations up to 85%</Title><Msg>New Butanol Process Improves Output 100%, Cuts Costs September 14, 2012 By Christopher DeMorro 1 Comment Biofuels have sort of fallen by the wayside when it comes to the talk on alternative energy. But a new butanol fermentation and capturing process can double output, while drastically reducing costs. This could make butanol a potentially attractive alternative to the other options on the table. There is a lot of sciency stuff going on in this study that I don’t exactly understand, but the gist of it is this. Butanol production was bottlenecked because the organism used to break down biomass would also be killed by the butanol itself. This effectively limited production, and made producing the fuel quite expensive as well. Researchers at the University of Illinois have developed a process that captures the butanol as its produced, keeping the bacterium alive, doubling butanol production. Researchers also utilized “cloud point separation” to separate the butanol from the remaining water, seriously cutting recovery costs. Solving these two issues could make butanol more attractive. The biggest draw of butanol is that it can be used in unmodified gasoline engines in concentrations up to 85%, unlike more-corrosive ethanol. It can also be made from the same biomass feedstocks as ethanol, though its energy density is much higher. Also, no drilling required! All that said, butanol seems like a long shot when EVs, hydrogen fuel cells, and natural gas get a lion’s share of the money and attention. Race teams like Dyson have had some success with biobutanol on the track, but breaking into the mainstream probably isn’t happening. Perhaps this is just the breakthrough researchers were waiting for. Source: Science Codex gas2</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347834204875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 18:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347838668158-10</Id><Title>What is Ryan's IQ?</Title><Msg>He should make his college transcript available for the voters. He doesn't understand economics, or foreign affairs. Palin would have been better. At least when Palin didn't know she wouldn't lie. Ryan would say anything, true or not, and keep saying it.</Msg><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347838668158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347842287085-11</Id><Topic><Title>What is Ryan's IQ?</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347838668158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But I guess you're all right with a drooling #$%$ like Joe Biden....</Msg><Username>jacobin8</Username><Timestamp>1347842287085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 20:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347842923872-12</Id><Topic><Title>What is Ryan's IQ?</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347838668158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:37:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm certain Ryan's IQ is at least an order of magnitude higher than yours. And, if you want to see transcripts, why not ask for Obamao's?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347842923872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 20:48:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347843037917-13</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney and war in Iran</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1347818421856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:00:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even more asinine than usual wahleee boy. You are surpassing yourself.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347843037917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 20:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347850907848-14</Id><Title>Climate Change Committee condemns UK government’s ‘dash for gas’ - after 2030 would gas be “increasingly” fitted with CCS or used only for back up</Title><Msg>Climate Change Committee condemns UK government’s ‘dash for gas’ The Committee on Climate Change (CCC) has written to the UK government warning that moving towards extensive use of unabated gas-fired capacity would be in breach of legally binding carbon budgets. In an open letter to Energy Secretary Ed Davey and the leadership of the Coalition, the signatories express “great concern” over a recent government statement that gas will continue to play “an important role in the energy mix well into and beyond 2030”. Earlier this week, in a statement defending the forthcoming Energy Bill, Davey himself commented: “Gas is a key part of our energy economy, and will remain so for the foreseeable future… We see a clear role for gas in the medium term, not just providing backup electricity, but baseload too.” But the CCC warns that use of unabated gas-fired capacity without carbon capture and storage (CCS) technology would be “incompatible” with meeting the UK’s carbon budgets up to 2050 and “could not form the basis of government policy”. The letter agrees with Davey that there is a role for gas in the medium term, including the use of the UK’s own gas reserves, primarily for heating buildings and in industry, which has been factored into current carbon budgets. But the government’s “ambivalent” position on whether it wishes to support the building of a low-carbon or gas-based energy system is putting off investors. “The cases for low-carbon business development, capital allocation, innovation and supply chain investment are undermined, damaging prospects for required low-carbon investments,” cautions the letter. The letter, which is signed by the new chair of the Committee Lord Deben, along with chief executive David Kennedy, Dame Julia King, Lord Krebs and Lord May, calls on the government to set a clear carbon objective – such as 50g CO2/kWh by 2030 – in the forthcoming Electricity Market Reform legislation. In response, Davey has issued a statement saying the government is “absolutely committed” to meeting its carbon budgets and is considering a 2030 “electricity decarbonisation” target. But he defended the government’s position on gas-fired capacity, saying: “We have always said this will include gas fired plant, which is quick to build and flexible. A fifth of our power stations are closing over the next decade and we need to build a diverse mix of all the technologies to keep the lights on and lower our emissions.” His statement admitted, however, that only after 2030 would gas be “increasingly” fitted with CCS or used only for back up. Lord Deben’s first act as chair of the Committee has been widely welcomed by environmental groups and renewables advocates. “This is a very stark warning the government cannot ignore: an unabated dash for gas is incompatible with tackling climate change and threatens the UK's growing green economy, which already employs almost one million people,” says Andrew Pendleton, head of campaigns for Friends of the Earth. Gaynor Hartnell, chief executive of the Renewable Energy Association also hailed the letter as “important”. “Gas can be a friend of renewables, if used strategically to support the transition to a low-carbon future. That is the approach we would like to see in the Department of Energy and Climate Change’s forthcoming gas strategy,” she added. energyefficiencynews</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347850907848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 23:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347853300946-15</Id><Topic><Title>Climate Change Committee condemns UK government’s ‘dash for gas’ - after 2030 would gas be “increasingly” fitted with CCS or used only for back up</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347850907848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 23:01:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More EEC idiocy. This is what Obamao wants to emulate.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347853300946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 23:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>