<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350706544617-1</Id><Topic><Title>Swing-state paper cites energy plans in Obama endorsement</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350697230305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Salt Lake Tribune--you know the olympics and adopted son and Mormon Salt Lake Tribune--endorsed Obama sometimes those that know them best--know best Romney was gov of Mass and will no way carry that state it looks like Wisconsin will not vote for Ryan--and you wonder why</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1350706544617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 00:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350708958956-2</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncrap Green Energy Scams Costing Taxpayers Billions</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350680368714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another lie from the desperate village idiot - boring but amusing.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350708958956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 00:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350709329536-3</Id><Topic><Title>The People Republicans Support Are Anything But Patriots</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350171682940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Complete and total idiocy - the blatant symptoms of brain death.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350709329536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 01:02:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350709500833-4</Id><Topic><Title>Sensata Technologies, A US Company, Profitable, Yet Bain Closing, Moving Jobs to CHINA</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350667008844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another complete lie wahleeee boy. Brain death is a serious issue you know. Too bad it's not reversible.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350709500833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 01:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350709793040-5</Id><Title>TransCanada shuts down Keystone pipeline over safety issues</Title><Msg>TransCanada shuts down Keystone pipeline over safety issues By Zoë Schlanger Fri Oct 19, 2012 10:24 PM EDT. The 2,100-mile Keystone pipeline, which hauls dilbit crude from Alberta, Canada, down to facilities in Illinois and Oklahoma, has some "possible safety issues," and Canadian energy company TranCanada has shut down the line temporarily to check it out. Grady Semmens, spokesman for Calgary-based TransCanada, said the pipeline was shut down Wednesday evening as a precaution and was expected to restart Saturday. "We found a small anomaly on the outside of the pipe after analyzing the data from an in-line inspection tool," Semmens said in an email. "As a precaution, we've shut down the line so we can go in and take a closer look." Once the pipeline is restarted the company expects "normal operations and flows" for the rest of October, but TransCanada may have to "make up some volumes in November," Semmens said. Heavy storms that have hit the area recently "are not helping" the operation, he said. The much-contested Keystone XL -- the one Paul Ryan said Mitt Romney would approve on "day one" -- would be a $7 billion extension of this original line. The Canadian government recently took note of TransCanada's safety record, after a fired TransCanada employee claimed in an interview with CBC News that he was terminated after raising concerns "about the competency of some pipeline inspectors and the company’s lack of compliance with welding regulations." “I wrote a series of emails to a series of project managers saying, ‘We can’t do this practice, we can’t do this practice, we can’t do this practice,’” Vokes said. “And I received increasingly pressured emails about how things were OK to do it that way.” The biggest safety concern over these Keystone pipelines is their cargo, diluted bitumen, or "dilbit," which is nothing like its conventional crude counterpart. Bitumen, the oil extracted from tar sands, is thick and sticky, and has to be diluted to flow through pipelines. The chemical mixture used to dilute it is a trade secret, but often includes carcinogens like benzene (pdf). One million gallons of this same stuff gushed into the Kalamazoo River in Michigan in 2010 -- the biggest inland pipeline spill in US history -- and it is yet to be totally cleaned up. Watchdog groups have raised concerns that dilbit is more corrosive than conventional crude, which raises the possibility of leaks (the industry denies this, so pipeline technology has not changed). And once it leaks, as we saw in Michigan in 2010, cleanup of the unconventional material is a whole lot harder. This past summer, TransCanada faced a new kind scrutiny from Nebraska environmental officials: they wanted to see the chemical information about dilbit that's currently protected by trade secret laws. "What are the characteristics of the products being transported?" a feedback report asked. "How toxic are the products being moved through the pipeline?" With Keystone XL front and center in the campaign conversation, talk of pipeline safety has all but disappeared. Now might be the time to have another look at what happened in Michigan. msnbc</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350709793040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 01:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350710300080-6</Id><Topic><Title>Sensata Technologies, A US Company, Profitable, Yet Bain Closing, Moving Jobs to CHINA</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350667008844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama, who is in charge of negotiating trade with China, is a stakeholder in Sensata, according to the New York Times. GM replaced its former CEO, Rick Wagoner, in 2009 at the Obama administration’s request. The auto giant’s new head, Daniel Akerson, who rose to the position after the administration appointed him to GM’s board, has celebrated the company’s move to China. Sensata’s efforts to chase profits abroad, particularly with the Obama administration-controlled GM, could personally benefit the president.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350710300080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 01:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350710531365-7</Id><Title>Breaking His Own Law Obama fails to release mandated stimulus reports</Title><Msg>The president’s administration is not providing the legally mandated reports on the stimulus money, the Weekly Standard has reported. The $831,000,000,000 economic “stimulus” that President Obama spearheaded and signed into law requires his administration to release quarterly reports on its effects. But “the most transparent administration in the history of our country” is now four reports behind schedule and has so far not released any reports whatsoever in 2012. Its most recent quarterly report is for the quarter than ended on June 30, 2011. … Section 1513 of the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act of 2009 (the “stimulus”) explicitly states, “In consultation with the Director of the Office of Management and Budget and the Secretary of the Treasury, the Chairperson of the Council of Economic Advisers shall submit quarterly reports to the Committees on Appropriations of the Senate and House of Representatives that detail the impact of programs funded through covered funds on employment, estimated economic growth, and other key economic indicators.” … In other words, the Obama administration is required by law to submit quarterly reports on the “stimulus” through the third quarter of 2013. Yet the administration has apparently found it more convenient to stop after the second quarter of 2011 — more than two years early. Or perhaps it has just decided to put the release of these reports on hold until after the election. Either way, the Obama administration is now in violation of the president’s most prominent piece of legislation this side of Obamacare. The Standard speculates about why the administration has not issued the reports. Why would the administration not want to release these reports? Presumably because they have shown what a colossal waste of taxpayer money Obama’s “stimulus” has been. In January 2010, Obama’s Council of Economic Advisors reported that, using “mainstream estimates of economic multipliers for the effects of fiscal stimulus” (which it described as a “natural way to estimate the effects of” the legislation), the “stimulus” had at that point cost $263.3 billion and had added or saved about 1.8 million jobs, whether private or public. In other words, for every $148,000 in taxpayer money that had gone out the door, only one job had been added or saved — according to an estimate from Obama’s own economists.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350710531365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 01:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350710863919-8</Id><Title>US Weekly Ignores Michelle Obama’s Expensive Tastes</Title><Msg>Ann Romney wore an expensive dress to the presidential debate Tuesday, and US Weekly wants everyone to know it. In a piece published Wednesday, Us Weekly ran the headline “Ann Romney Wears $1,690 Oscar de la Renta Dress to Presidential Debate.” Fox News points out the magazine chose this headline despite the fact that First Lady Michelle Obama’s outfit cost double that price. Obama’s dress cost more than Romney’s at $1,795—and the first lady topped the ensemble off with a jacket that cost $1,495. And Ann Romney does brag about getting champagne and caviar delivered to her hotel suite.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350710863919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 01:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350729682107-9</Id><Topic><Title>US Weekly Ignores Michelle Obama’s Expensive Tastes</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350710863919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 01:27:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet Ann looked much better to.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350729682107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 06:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350729724673-10</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking His Own Law Obama fails to release mandated stimulus reports</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350710531365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 01:22:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba does everything behind closed doors.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350729724673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 06:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350729758498-11</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncrap Green Energy Scams Costing Taxpayers Billions</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350680368714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What ever happened to Kennedy's statement "do not ask what your country can do for you but what you can do for your country"? If you were a "true" American you would not be looking to find fault in your government but looking to help the government help others. This is a democracy and not a dictatorship and nothing gets accomplished in the U.S. by just 1 person. It is all about the "elected" government making decisions for the population. You should back your government while it is is office and then when elections happen you put your vote in to change the governement and if there are enough against what the elected governors are doing then a change occurs. You are simply a complainer and that means that you only want your way and no other way. You should live in countries such as Venezuela and Iran are when dissenters are simply put in jail or shot and where the government has spent zillions to arm themselves against their own population. That is where you belong, in a country such as that and criticizing the governement.</Msg><Username>luckyone581</Username><Timestamp>1350729758498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 06:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350729832633-12</Id><Topic><Title>Sensata Technologies, A US Company, Profitable, Yet Bain Closing, Moving Jobs to CHINA</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350667008844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Infern, wahlleee lies like the dumbocraps, dont pay any attention to the lobotomy brain he has left.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350729832633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 06:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350729878988-13</Id><Topic><Title>TransCanada shuts down Keystone pipeline over safety issues</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350709793040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 01:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All lies.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350729878988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 06:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350729934721-14</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncrap Green Energy Scams Costing Taxpayers Billions</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350680368714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mr.luck is wahlee commie clown.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350729934721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 06:45:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350729970855-15</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncrap Green Energy Scams Costing Taxpayers Billions</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350680368714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats what nobumba wants for us.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350729970855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 06:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350730060230-16</Id><Topic><Title>The People Republicans Support Are Anything But Patriots</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350171682940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No wahleee is a failed lobotomy, they cut to much brain out.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350730060230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 06:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350730104253-17</Id><Topic><Title>The People Republicans Support Are Anything But Patriots</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350171682940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ wahleee Bush's last 4 years were dumbocrap controlled.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350730104253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 06:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350730183456-18</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder if invest and infernal will disappear ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350525016176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxidopey is a commie c--t.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350730183456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 06:49:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350736653569-19</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder if invest and infernal will disappear ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350525016176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the commie clown POS.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350736653569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350736718865-20</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder if invest and infernal will disappear ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350525016176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better find a good hiding spot commie POS.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350736718865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350736876832-21</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncrap Green Energy Scams Costing Taxpayers Billions</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350680368714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He will go away soon.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350736876832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350736965259-22</Id><Topic><Title>Allen West</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350683300110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>West is the best.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350736965259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350747539799-23</Id><Title>****IMPORTANT WINDOWS info****</Title><Msg>Windows RT is a limited version of Windows 8 that runs on ARM-based devices, not on traditional PCs. It is installed as the operating system for the new “SURFACE” tablet Microsoft has recently introduced. Windows RT will not run any desktop Windows applications beyond the applications that are bundled with the operating system. Bundled applications include virtually every single desktop application found in Windows 8—Paint, WordPad, etc.—except for Windows Media Player. It also includes a fully-functional and full-featured version of Office 2013 called Office Home &amp; Student 2013 RT. This suite includes Word, Excel, OneNote, and PowerPoint. For the umpteenth time, it does not include Outlook. Windows RT will not run any desktop applications beyond the applications that are bundled with the operating system. This means it will not run Windows Essentials 2012, Microsoft Outlook (any version), Microsoft Office (any version, beyond what’s included with RT), Adobe Photoshop or Photoshop Elements, or any other Adobe desktop application. It will not run the SkyDrive desktop application (which is part of Essentials 2012, yes, I know), meaning you cannot sync SkyDrive data to your RT device’s storage. You can only use the SkyDrive Metro app, which lets you access SkyDrive only when connected … just as with any other mobile device. It will not run iTunes. It will not run any desktop Windows application beyond what’s bundled with the OS. Windows RT is not a computer operating system. Windows RT is an operating system for mobile devices. Surface with Windows RT is not a computer. It is mobile computing device, like an iPad. It is a tablet, a hybrid device that bridges the gap between real PCs and media tablets, where you can work and play.</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1350747539799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 11:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350750773765-24</Id><Topic><Title>Memories Or The Reagan Era Make Bengazi Whining Look Political</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350654960649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:56:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your complete idiocy continues to reign supreme. Another symptom of brain death.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350750773765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350752106214-25</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Receives Endorsement of Orlando Sentinel</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350617661523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 23:34:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a lib tool rag that also endorsed Obamao in 08. The Sentinel has switched from Obamao in 08 to Romney for 2012.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350752106214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350755589724-26</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>douglasinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350733187650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 07:39:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well this is not a mind blowing app, but it is useful and I like it - thanks for the tip.</Msg><Username>peelingoutsummer</Username><Timestamp>1350755589724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350755604221-27</Id><Title>TransCanada Plans Natural Gas Pipeline Over Rugged Mountain Route To Kitimat</Title><Msg>TransCanada Plans Natural Gas Pipeline Over Rugged Mountain Route To Kitimat Posted: 10/19/2012 1:23 pm TransCanada plans a rugged over-mountain route for its proposed Coastal Gaslink pipeline to the Shell Canada liquified natural gas project in Kitimat, B.C., company officials said this week in two presentations. The proposal was presented Monday to the District of Kitimat Council and then at a community town hall briefing. The pipeline would initially carry 1.7 billion cubic feet of natural gas per day from the Montney Formation region of northeastern British Columbia along a 48 inch (1.2 metre) diameter pipe over 700 kilometres from Groundbirch, near Dawson Creek, to Kitimat. Rick Gateman, president of Coastal GasLink Project, a wholly owned TransCanada subsidiary told council that the project is now at a "conceptual route" stage because TransCanada can't proceed to actual planning until it has done more detailed survey work and community consultations. At the same council meeting Shell Canada filed documents that notified the District that it has formally applied to the National Energy Board for an export licence for the natural gas. Gateman told council that since the pipeline itself will be completely within the province of British Columbia, it comes under the jurisdiction of the British Columbia Environmental Assessment process and the BC Oil and Gas Commission and that the NEB will not be involved in approving the pipeline itself. At first, the Coastal Gas Link pipeline would be connected to the existing Nova Gas Transmission system now used (and being expanded) in northeastern British Columbia. From Vanderhoof to west of Burns Lake, the Coastal GasLink pipeline would be somewhat adjacent to existing pipelines and the route of the proposed Enbridge Northern Gateway bitumen pipeline and the proposed Pacific Trails natural gas pipeline. Somewhat south of Houston, however, the pipeline takes a different route from the either the Northern Gateway or Pacific Trails Pipeline, going southwest, avoiding the controversial Mount Nimbus route. Howard Backus, an engineering manager with TransCanada told council that route changes so that Coastal GasLink can avoid "congestion" in the rugged mountain region. Backus said that the Pacific Trails Pipeline "is skirting" Nimbus while Enbridge plans to tunnel through the mountain. That tunnel is one of the most controversial aspects to the Northern Gateway project. The local environmental group Douglas Channel Watch has repeatedly warned of the dangers of avalanche and geological instability in the area where the Northern Gateway pipeline emerges from the tunnel. Under TransCanada's conceptual route, the pipeline heads southwest and then climbs into the mountains, crossing what Backus calls "a saddle" (not a pass) near the headwaters of the Kitimat River. The pipeline then comes down paralleling Hircsh Creek, emerging close to town, crossing the Kitimat River and terminating at the old Methanex plant where Shell plans its liquified natural gas plant. (That means that if the conceptual plans go ahead, the TransCanada pipeline would climb into the mountains, while Pacific Trails finds a way around and Enbridge tunnels). Backus assured people at the town hall that energy companies have a lot of experience in building pipelines in mountainous areas, including the Andes in South America. Gateman told council that the pipeline would be buried along its entire route. If Shell increases the capacity of its LNG facility in Kitimat, the Coastal Gaslink pipeline could increase to 3.4 billion cubic feet a day or perhaps even more. For the initial capacity, the company will have one compressor station at the eastern end of the line. If capacity increases or if the route requires it, there could be as many as five additional compressor stations. (TransCanada's long term planning is based on the idea that Shell will soon be adding natural gas from the rich Horn River Formation also in northeastern BC ) TransCanada will begin its field work, including route and environmental planning and "community engagement" in 2013 and file for regulatory approval in 2014. Once the project is approved, construction would begin in 2015. Gateman said that TransCanada is consulting landowners along the proposed right of way and "on a wide area on either side." The company also is consulting 30 First Nations along the proposed route. Gateman told council, "We probably have the most experience of any number of companies in working directly with and engaging directly with First Nations because of our pipelines across Canada." Gateman told council that the pipeline would be designed to last at least 60 years. He said that in the final test stages, the pipeline would be pressured "beyond capacity" using water rather than natural gas to try and find if any leaks developed during construction. He said that the company would restore land disrupted by the construction of the pipeline, but noted that it would only restore "low-level vegetation." Trees are not permitted to close to the pipeline for safety reasons. TransCanada made the usual promises the region has heard from other companies of jobs, opportunities for local business and wide consultations. (TransCanada may have learned lessons from the botched public relations by the Enbridge Northern Gateway. A number of Kitimat residents have said that TransCanada was polling in the region in mid-summer, with callers asking many specific questions about environment and the spinoffs for communities). Kitimat Coun. Phil Germuth questioned Gateman about the differences between a natural gas pipeline and a petroleum pipeline. Gateman replied that the pipelines are pretty much the same with the exception that a natural gas pipeline uses compressor stations while a petroleum pipeline uses pumping stations. Gateman did note that the original part of the controversial Keystone XL pipeline that would carry bitumen through Alberta and U.S. mountain states to Texas was a natural gas pipeline converted to carry the heavier hydrocarbons. Although the natural gas projects have, so far, enjoyed wide support in northwestern British Columbia, environmental groups and First Nations have raised fears that sometime in the future, especially if there is overcapacity in natural gas lines, that some may converted to bitumen, whether or not Northern Gateway is approved and actually goes ahead. huffingtonpost</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350755604221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350767238059-28</Id><Title>Caltex prepares for end to octane 91 sales</Title><Msg>Caltex prepares for end to octane 91 sales WATCHARAPONG THONGRUNG THE NATION October 20, 2012 1:00 am Chevron (Thailand) Ltd, which operates Caltex fuel stations, is ready to boost sales of octane 95 petrol and E20 gasohol once the government ceases octane 91 petrol sales nationwide from the beginning of next year. As part of its corporate social responsibility (CSR) programme, the company will also launch the reality show "Driving Change with Caltex", which Chevron said was aimed at reaffirming its goal of expanding its retail fuel business in Thailand. Adrian Bendeck, country chairman and general manager for products at Chevron (Thailand), said the company was well prepared for the planned end to octane 91 sales. Chevron is studying demand at each of its petrol stations in order to decide whether to convert its fuel pumps from octane 91 petrol to octane 95 or to E20 gasohol. Gasohol is a blend of petrol and the bio-fuel additive ethanol. Caltex currently has the largest share of the octane 95 market. Caltex stations sell about 20 million litres of octane 91 petrol per month and about 3 million litres per month of octane 95. Bendeck said Chevron has joined hands with pay-TV network Fox International to launch Caltex's first CSR activity in Asia-Pacific, the reality programme "Driving Change With Caltex". The programme is being introduced in Malaysia, Hong Kong, the Philippines, Singapore and Thailand between October 5 and November 4. Thailand will be the third market to see the launch of the programme after Malaysia and Hong Kong, where the activity was launched yesterday. "The parent company has selected Thailand as one of those [markets] for this major activity as it emphasises that there would be investment and business expansion in the country," Bendeck said. Chevron (Thailand) earlier announced plans to build an additional 100 petrol stations by the end of 2014. Through the "Driving Change With Caltex" programme, celebrities from each market will be invited to go on a mission with well-known Southeast Asian host Henry Golding to develop a local community. In Thailand, the two-day mission included the establishment of a library for the Nong Plong Pode School in flood-hit Tha Tako district of Nakhon Sawan province. nationmultimedia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350767238059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350767869655-29</Id><Topic><Title>Wind credit uncertainty dents GE revenues</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350672433255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50 Carat Diamond Sells for $9.5 Million at Christie’s By JCK Staff Posted on October 17, 2012. PHOTOS - 3 50.52 ct. pear-shape D-color flawless diamond (image courtesy of Christie's) On Oct. 16, a 50.52 ct. pear-shape D-color flawless diamond pendant sold for $9.5 million to a private collector at Christie's New York Magnificent Jewels sale. The overall sale took in $49.9 million. Other highlights of the auction include a two-strand natural pearl necklace, which sold for $3.7 million, and a pair of 103 ct. t.w. pear-shape fancy yellow and colorless diamond ear pendants, which earned $4.7 million. “Private collectors and dealers reacted more than positively to a 369-lot auction that was finely-tuned in terms of prices and selection of gems to current market conditions,” said Rahul Kadakia, head of jewelry, Christie’s Americas and Switzerland, in a statement. “Natural pearls, colorless flawless diamonds, and colored diamonds of high quality once again dominated the day, making for a vibrant atmosphere in the saleroom.” jckonline</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350767869655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350771655038-30</Id><Title>Washington Post on "Are Mormons Christians?"</Title><Msg>In the present political climate, the question of whether Mormons are Christians has surfaced again and again. I will leave the issue of whether 21st century America is ready for a Mormon chief executive to pundits, pollsters, and, of course, voters. But the underlying question is an important one, a matter whose implications reach well beyond the 2012 election. So far as I can determine, the cry of “Mormons are not Christian” was not heard very often during the formative period of Mormon history. Baptists and Methodists and Presbyterians in the area knew that the followers of Joseph Smith believed in doctrinal matters that deviated somewhat from traditional Christianity. Folks seemed to assume, however, that Mormonism fit under the umbrella of Christianity. The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints is built upon the person, power and teachings of Jesus Christ. He is our King, our Lord, and our God. Now, because Mormons do not hold to the decisions and formulations of the post-biblical church councils, and because we believe in an expanded canon of scripture, some do not consider us to be a part of “orthodox” Christianity. They are correct. We believe a Christian is one who follows Jesus. For us, one is a Christian not simply because he or she possesses a “correct” theology. One’s Christian faith ought to be manifest in the way he speaks to and treats others. The Apostle Paul charged those who professed Christian discipleship: If we live in the Spirit, let us also walk in the Spirit.” I think that means: “If we talk the talk, we really ought to walk the walk.” As Mormons, we ask to be permitted to define ourselves and explain what we really believe. While we have no desire to compromise our distinctiveness or ignore our differences with other groups, we feel it is appropriate to celebrate our similarities and work together to remedy many of the troubling issues in our society. We ask only to be invited more regularly into the larger religious conversation. The United States has been a melting pot for well over two centuries, and we have prospered largely because we have welcomed those who were different ethnically, racially, culturally and religiously. Joseph Smith once asked: “If I esteem mankind to be in error, shall I bear them down? No. I will lift them up, and in their own way too, if I cannot persuade them my way is better; and I will not seek to compel any man to believe as I do, only by the force of reasoning, for truth will cut its own way.” I couldn’t agree more. There is too much at stake in the world for God-fearing people to spend their time attacking one another. We have been called to stand on higher ground.</Msg><Username>demedici</Username><Timestamp>1350771655038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350775434142-31</Id><Title>Saudi Arabia Unveils Plan to be Powered Entirely by Renewable Energy</Title><Msg>Saudi Arabia Unveils Plan to be Powered Entirely by Renewable Energy October 20, 2012 By Nathan Leave a Comment Saudi Arabia recently revealed that it is planning to be powered 100% by renewable and low-carbon forms of energy. One of the state’s main spokesmen, Prince Turki Al Faisal Al Saud, said that he was hoping that Saudi Arabia would be powered completely by low-carbon energy within his lifetime. He made the groundbreaking statement during the Global Economic Symposium in Brazil. He did acknowledge, though, that it was likely to take longer, as he is already 67. Realistically, the process would take at least a few decades, and that’s if the country is serious about it. There have been some observers expressing skepticism about the purpose of the announcement, suggesting it may just be greenwashing. The Saudi prince expressed that the country was most definitely moving forward with investment renewables, nuclear power, and other undefined alternatives to fossil fuels. Noting that their vast oil reserves would still be in demand for their use as plastics and polymers. “Oil is more precious for us underground than as a fuel source,” he said. “If we can get to the point where we can replace fossil fuels and use oil to produce other products that are useful, that would be very good for the world. I wish that may be in my lifetime, but I don’t think it will be.” Joss Garman, political director of Greenpeace, said: “It speaks volumes that a Saudi prince can see the benefits of switching to clean energy sources when [UK chancellor] George Osborne seemingly cannot, but Saudi Arabia will only truly be a green economy when it leaves its fossil fuels in the ground.” Currently, Saudi Arabia’s energy is provided nearly completely by burning fossil fuels, nearly two-thirds from oil and the rest from natural gas. It produces around 12 million barrels of oil every day. That’s more than 12% of the entire world’s production, and the country has at least 1/5 of the world’s proven oil reserves, according to the US government’s Energy Information Administration. And because of how artificially-low oil prices are kept within the kingdom, the per capita energy use there is quite high. As noted by Prince Turki, though, the kingdom has an equally vast potential for solar power. “The cost of solar energy is now 15% of what it was 20 years ago,” he noted. Clean Technica</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350775434142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:23:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350775663757-32</Id><Topic><Title>Memories Or The Reagan Era Make Bengazi Whining Look Political</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350654960649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:56:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ commie wahleee.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350775663757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350775712984-33</Id><Topic><Title>Memories Or The Reagan Era Make Bengazi Whining Look Political</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350654960649</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:56:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are really stupid wahleee the commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350775712984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350778088825-34</Id><Topic><Title>Saudi Arabia Unveils Plan to be Powered Entirely by Renewable Energy</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350775434142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course its about the environment in part, but thinking the Saudi are starting to get a glimpse of peak oil and what is coming at us in terms of challenges to supply side. Notice today yahoo news says Canadians bloc the sale of an oil and gas company to pertronas state oil of Malaysia. nxy deal to China is still under review. Kuwait has also made major investment in a Canada oil sands project. Both oil and gas are going to be in big demand in the future decade. thinking the big oil with the most reserves in the ground is a good investment. dont know how xom stacks up but think it has smart plan to pick up reserves. glta</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1350778088825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350781489370-35</Id><Topic><Title>Any Market Players Here?</Title><Username>luckyone581</Username><Timestamp>1350677742523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:15:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BOYS..it's TRIPLE X time ! One word DIREXION !!!</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1350781489370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 21:04:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>