<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347685114044-1</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans always want war</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347568019150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Call me Captain, nose nozzle lib. I served, fought and lived in GA during the terrorist reign of Jimmy Carter. We like peace, but you win peace by beating the crap out the enemy. Yeah college is nice, MS for me.</Msg><Username>bioditz</Username><Timestamp>1347685114044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 00:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347685410280-2</Id><Topic><Title>Grover Norquist Tax Sandbag Killed This Economy</Title><Username>lordbalzy_the_holy</Username><Timestamp>1347669111039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 20:31:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is no cliff. there is no trade deficit, no problem ,but the f..ing FED bubbling us into oblivion. Get ready for the equity bubble. let's fix the housing market with more liquidity. Oofah!!!!</Msg><Username>bioditz</Username><Timestamp>1347685410280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 01:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347702517843-3</Id><Title>Obama Deserves Credit</Title><Msg>for his "Arab Spring" activities London “About 200 protesters are burning USA and Israeli flags outside the US embassy in London,” Al Jazeera reports. Mauritania “Mauritanian youths also went out in a demonstration that covered the streets of Nouakchott condemning the offensive film,” reports Link TV. “Protestors gathered in front of the American embassy, calling for its shutdown and the expulsion of the American ambassador, which is the least that could be done for this criminal act. They also chanted slogans condemning this offensive film.” Casablanca, Morocco “Between 300 and 400 Muslim activists had gathered outside the US consulate in Morocco’s largest city Casablanca on Wednesday, amid a heavy police presence, protesting against the film and shouting anti-US slogans,” reports Al Jazeera. Sale, Morocco “Hundreds of Salafists burned US flags in Morocco after Friday prayers at a mosque in a poor neighbourhood of Sale, twin town to the Moroccan capital Rabat,” reports Al Jazeera. “Around 200 of the hardline Islamists gathered, shouting anti-US slogans including ‘American satan’, before trampling on two US flags and then ripping them up and setting them ablaze.” Tunisia Protesters in Tunisia have set fire to an American school in the capital Tunis, according to Reuters. The New York Post reports that “Anti-American rioting spread yesterday to Tunisia, where police used tear gas to stop hundreds of protesters from storming the United States Embassy in protest over a film mocking the prophet Mohammed.” Jos, Nigeria “Nigerian troops fired live rounds on Friday to disperse Muslims protesting in the volatile central city of Jos against an American film about the Prophet Mohammad that has triggered unrest in several countries across the Islamic world,” reports Reuters. “Scores of Muslim demonstrators distributed photographs printed out from the trailer of the film, which Muslims say insults the Prophet, after Friday prayers in Jos.” Tripoli, Libya “The US dispatched an elite group of Marines to Tripoli on Wednesday after the mob attack that killed the US ambassador and three other Americans,” reports the AP. “Officials were investigating whether the rampage was a backlash to an anti-Islamic video with ties to Coptic Christians or a plot to coincide with the anniversary of 9/11. Benghazi, Libya “Ansar al Sharia supporters protesting in front of Tibesty Hotel in Benghazi carrying black flags,” reports Al Jazeera via Twitter. “Maximum 50 pple.” Khartoum, Sudan “Britain’s Foreign Office says police in Sudan are confronting a protest outside the British embassy in Khartoum,” reports the AP. Additionally, Reuters reports “Protesters pull down emblem at German embassy in Sudan, raise Islamic flag.” The Guardian is showing photographs of the German embassy on fire. Mombasa, Kenya “A group of Kenyan muslims burn[ed] the US flag in protest over the anti-Muslim film that has spawned mob violence against American embassies across the Mideast, following afternoon prayers outside the Sakina Jamia Mosque in the port city of Mombasa, Kenya Friday,” reports the AP. Mogadishu, Somalia “Thousands of Somali protesters have taken to the streets of capital Mogadishu to express their anger over the anti-Islam movie produced by an Israeli-American in the United States,” reports Iran’s Press TV. “The demonstration in the Somali capital is being held to express anger against the film, which insults the holy Prophet Muhammad (PBUH).” Sanaa, Yemen “In Sanaa, Yemen, the U.S. Embassy was overrun Thursday by protesters who stormed a wall, set fire to a building inside the compound, broke windows and carried away office supplies and other souvenirs before being dispersed by local security forces,” reports The Washington Post. Cairo, Egypt “In Cairo, clouds of tear gas floated through the fortified area around the U.S. Embassy as security forces clashed with protesters for the third straight day,” reports The Washington Post. Sheikh Zuwayed, Sinai “Protesters belonging to ultraconservative groups in Sinai have stormed a camp for the UN multinational peacekeepers in the town of Sheikh Zuwayed,” reports Al Jazeera. “They brought down the flag and placed a black Islamic banner with the words ‘There’s no God but Allah, Mohammed is the Prophet of Allah. The peacekeepers responded with firing on the attackers, said Al Jazeera’s Rawya Rageh. At least one man is believed to be injured.” Gaza Strip “Palestinians on Friday protested an anti-Muslim film, with thousands gathering in the Gaza Strip and hundreds in Jerusalem where there were clashes with Israeli police,” reports Now Lebanon. Jerusalem “Hundreds hurl stones at officers in Jerusalem after Friday prayers at al-Aqsa Mosque while protesters rallied against anti-Islam film,” reports Ynet News. Tel Aviv, Israel “Arab-Israeli Muslim men protest against a film mocking Islam, in front of the U.S. embassy in the Mediterranean coastal city of Tel Aviv, on September 13, 2012,” reports AFP. Nablus, West Bank “In the city of Nablus, about 200 people demonstrated against the film as Muslim clerics throughout the territory preached against it in Friday sermons,” reports the AP. Amman, Jordan “Jordanian protesters burn a US flag in front of the Kurdi Mosque near the USA embassy in Amman,” reports the AP. Iran’s Press TV reports that more than 2,000 Jordanians took to the streets to protest the movie. “We sacrifice our soul and blood for the prophet,” said demonstrators. “We do not want a US embassy on Jordanian territory.” Damascus, Syria “Sana, Syria’s state news agency, said hundreds of pro-government supporters protested outside the US embassy in Damascus today,” reports The Guardian. “Protesters held images of beleaguered president Bashar al-Assad and what appeared to be government-organised demonstration.” According to photographer Louai Beshara, the purpose of the demonstration was to oppose the anti-Islam film. Sidon, Lebanon The AP captured photographs of an anti-film protest in the Palestinian refugee camp of Ain el-Hilweh near Sidon, Lebanon, here. Tripoli, Lebanon “Hundreds of protesters set alight a Kentucky Fried Chicken restaurant in the northern Lebanese city of Tripoli on Friday, witnesses said, chanting against the pope’s visit to Lebanon and shouting anti-American slogans,” reports Reuters. The news agency attributed the violence to the papal visit and the controversial film. Baghdad, Iraq “Several hundred followers of anti-American cleric Moqtada al-Sadr held demonstrations in Baghdad’s Sadr City district, the southern oil city of Basra and other predominantly #$%$ areas of the country, chanting ‘Death to America.’” Kut, Iraq “Iraqi supporters of #$%$ cleric Moqtada al-Sadr’s movement, burn[ed] the Israeli and the US flags during a protest denouncing a film deemed offensive to Islam, on September 13, 2012 in the central Iraqi city of Kut,” reports the AFP. Basrah, Iraq In the southern city of Basra, about 1,000 took to the streets and burned the American and Israeli flags. One banner said: ‘Freedom doesn’t mean offending two billion Muslims,’” reports the AP. Kuwait City, Kuwait “About 500 demonstrators gathered yesterday near the US embassy in Kuwait waving a black Al-Qaeda flag in protest of a film mocking Islam,” reports AFP. “President Barack ‘Obama, we are all Osama,’ they chanted referring to Al-Qaeda’s former leader Osama bin Laden who was killed by US forces last year, an AFP photographer at the site of the demonstration reported.” Diraz, Bahrain “More than 2,000 protesters chanted against the film and burned American and Israeli flags after Friday prayers in Diraz, outside the capital, Manama. Security forces were absent,” reports the AP. “Separately, Bahrain’s Interior Ministry ordered media regulators to attempt to block access to the film clip. Doha, Qatar “Hundreds of worshippers marched near the US embassy in Qatar on Friday over the anti-Islam video,” reports Al Jazeera. “The protest had been reportedly called for by Doha-based Egyptian Sheikh Yusuf al-Qaradawi and began after his Friday sermon at the Omar bin Khateb mosque.” Karachi, Pakistan “JI Chief Munawar Hassan, addressing a protest rally in the Nazimabad area of Karachi, demanded that the US government ban the movie and also demanded the Interior ministry of Pakistan lodge a protest with the US ambassador,” reports the Express Tribune. Lahore, Pakistan “The rally in Lahore was organised by Tehreek-e-Hurmat-e-Rasool which was taken out from Green Chowk to Sohrab Khan, while the one in Multan was organised by Jamiat Talba Arbia and Shehri Mahaz. Protesters threw shoes at US and Israeli flags and set them on fire,” reports the Express Tribune. Islamabad, Pakistan “The protesters in Islamabad said that the film should be banned across the world and the filmmakers should be severely punished,” reports Pakistan’s The Express Tribune. “They also demanded that the US should apologise for the film.” Nangarhar Province, Afghanistan “Afghans burn the U.S. flag in the Ghanikhel district of Nangarhar province, east of Kabul, Afghanistan, on September 14, 2012, during a protest against an anti-Islam film,” reports the AP. Jalalabad, Afghanistan “Hundreds of Afghans – some shouting ‘Death to America’ – have held a protest against an anti-Islam film in the eastern city of Jalalabad,” reports the AP. Srinagar, India “A Kashmiri Muslim with his face covered burn[ed] a mock American flag as others shout slogans during a protest Friday in Srinagar, India,” reports the AP. Kashmir, India “Thousands of angry Kashmiri Muslims protested Friday against an anti-Islam film, burning U.S. flags and calling President Barack Obama a ‘terrorist,’ while the top government cleric here reportedly demanded Americans leave the volatile Indian-controlled region immediately,” reports the AP. “At least 15,000 people took part in more than two dozen protests across Kashmir, chanting ‘Down with America’ and ‘Down with Israel’ in some of the largest anti-American demonstrations against the film in Asia.” Hyderabad, India “A peaceful protest was held here Friday against a blasphemous anti-Islam American movie,” reports News Track India. “Protestors set afire an effigy symbolising the US in the old city of Hyderabad. Police said no untoward incident took place during the protest.” Bangladesh “About 1,000 Bangladeshi Islamists tried to march on the U.S. embassy in Dhaka on Thursday to protest against a U.S. film that is said to insult the Prophet Mohammad but security forces stopped them reaching the mission,” reports Reuters. Sri Lanka Protests have erupted in eastern Sri Lanka, according to the BBC, but details are thin on the size of the demonstration. Ipoh, Malaysia “Malaysian media reported a… protest in the northern city of Ipoh,” reports Ahram Online. Kuala Lumpur, Malaysi Muslims held demonstrations across Malaysia on Friday, calling for the United States to prevent distribution of an anti-Islam film they said was part of a plot by ‘Christian extremists,’” reports Ahram Online. “They included a group of about 30 people representing various Islamic organisations who marched to the US embassy in the capital Kuala Lumpur.” Jakarta, Indonesia “In Indonesia, the world’s most populous Muslim nation, about 200 protesters in Jakarta chanted slogans and held up signs in a largely peaceful protest outside the heavily guarded U.S. Embassy,” reports the Associated Press.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1347702517843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347711462857-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Deserves Credit</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1347702517843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobama deserves a jail cell.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347711462857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 08:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347711559452-5</Id><Topic><Title>Romeny "Bring it on"</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347674057516</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 21:54:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba a complete failure and fool. Those americans who voted for him should be deported for being a communist.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347711559452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 08:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347716378346-6</Id><Topic><Title>Updated: UK breaks 4GW wind energy barrier - 4.131GW, accounting for 10.8% of the UK electricity supply</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347657430982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 17:17:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>quote: Just before 10am today, wind turbines generated 4.131GW, accounting for 10.8 per cent of the UK electricity supply.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347716378346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 09:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347716482325-7</Id><Topic><Title>Updated: UK breaks 4GW wind energy barrier - 4.131GW, accounting for 10.8% of the UK electricity supply</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347657430982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 17:17:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Mitt Romney,... ... do you think America should trail other nations in the technology and deployment of CLEAN, RENEWABLE energy? If you wish America wouldn't subsidize the developement of renewable energy so that all energy may compete on a level playing field are you also willng to abolish the republican sponsored BILLION$$$$$ in taxpayer subsidies and concessions for the fossil fuel industries and also nuclear energy? I assume if you did, most new energy development in America would be inexpensive, clean, renewable energy. CONTACT Mitt Romney</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347716482325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 09:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347722911153-8</Id><Topic><Title>Romeny "Bring it on"</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347674057516</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 21:54:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Pleeease"! "You People", have no idea who runs this country!</Msg><Username>shawn4golf</Username><Timestamp>1347722911153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 11:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347723276653-9</Id><Title>Obummer: obviously, a foreign policy genius.</Title><Msg>NOT...</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1347723276653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 11:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347723922370-10</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE DID THE ARAB SPRING COME FROM?</Title><Username>i.alaric</Username><Timestamp>1347662035084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Military Industrial Complex and the Mossad! Create fear and chaos and you create profits and war! WWIII was started in 2008 launching the Worldwide monatary war to debase currencies and was just excellerated with the announcement of the open ended QE3 on Wed. The inflation generated from this will create chaos and unstable governments. The Arab Spring was just the elitists decision to destablize the Middle East and further their agenda towards war. They don't like over population and plan on decreasing the World's population through war, disease, and starvation. Romney or Obama don't make decisions. They carry them out!</Msg><Username>shawn4golf</Username><Timestamp>1347723922370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 11:45:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347725008067-11</Id><Topic><Title>Updated: UK breaks 4GW wind energy barrier - 4.131GW, accounting for 10.8% of the UK electricity supply</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347657430982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 17:17:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah Solyndra and those other bankrupt companies sure did a lot of good for the billions thrown at them.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1347725008067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347726465475-12</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans always want war</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1347568019150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama went before the Egyptian Parliament and APOLOGIZED for the US.And he forced Hosni Mubarak to invite THE MOSLEM BROTHERHOOD to the speech.It's no coincidence the problems are centered around Egypt. The "apology" legitimized all the whacky arab suspicions about the US and the west.That's why they are reacting with anger instead of the nicey-nice behavior Obama foolishly expected. YES OUR DEAR MUSLIM LEADER MANAGES TO PUT HIS FOOT IN HIS MOUTH QUITE OFTEN. BIDEN HAS TAUGHT HIM WELL....WHEN DOES HE GET TIME TO DO THIS SINCE HE IS ON THE GOLF COURSE ALMOST DAILY....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1347726465475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347729519144-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Deserves Credit</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1347702517843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now THAT would be justice. Along with Pelosi, Reid, Frank, Dodd, Schumer.....</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1347729519144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 13:18:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347734803316-14</Id><Title>Offshore wind energy could power entire U.S. East Coast, Stanford scientists say</Title><Msg>Offshore wind energy could power entire U.S. East Coast, Stanford scientists say Stanford Report, September 14, 2012 Stanford scientists deliver the first-ever quantitative analysis of offshore wind energy on the U.S. East Coast. They conclude there is enough wind energy to fulfill one-third of the U.S. energy demand. By Bjorn Carey A new analysis by Stanford researchers reveals that there is enough offshore wind along the U.S. East Coast to meet the electricity demands of at least one-third of the country. The scientists paid special attention to the Maine-to-Virginia corridor; the historical lack of strong hurricanes in the region makes it a favorable site for offshore wind turbines. They found that turbines placed there could satisfy the peak-time power needs of these states for three seasons of the year (summer is the exception). "We knew there was a lot of wind out there, but this is the first actual quantification of the total resource and the time of day that the resource peaks," said Mark Z. Jacobson, a professor of civil and environmental engineering at Stanford who directed the research. "This provides practical information to wind farm developers about the best areas to place turbines." Some breezes are better than others; wind energy that peaks during times of high electricity demand is more valuable and can offset dirtier generation that runs only a few hours a day. The researchers used a weather model to generate five years of hourly wind speeds at 90 meters above sea surface – the standard height of offshore wind turbines (the projection was validated against real data from offshore buoys and towers). The team inserted about 140,000 wind turbines into their computer model, each capable of generating 5 megawatts of electricity – similar to windmills used in offshore wind farms in Europe – at various ocean depths and distances from shore, from Florida to Maine. After factoring in standard transmission losses and turbine array inefficiencies, the U.S. East Coast offshore winds were found to produce from 965 to 1,372 terawatt hours of electricity annually, enough to satisfy the demands of one-third of the United States, or all of the East Coast, from Florida to Maine. What's really important, the scientists say, is the time of day that electricity can be delivered. "People mistakenly think that wind energy is not useful because output from most land-based turbines peaks in the late evening/early morning, when electricity demand is low," said Mike Dvorak, a recent graduate of Stanford's Atmosphere/Energy PhD program who was part of the research team. "The real value of offshore wind energy is that it often peaks when we need the most electricity – during the middle of the day." Tapping this vast resource shouldn't come at the expense of ocean views, nor should it seriously impact wildlife or recreational and commercial water use, according to the researchers. Many of the turbines would be sited so far offshore that they could not be seen. In fact, the analysis assumed the use of only one-third of available shallow water locations out to 30 meters depth of water, and two-thirds of remaining sites out to 200 meters depth. Jacobson doesn't expect the country to convert completely to wind energy; in practice, he said, we wouldn't want more than 40 to 50 percent of electricity production to be tied up in any one energy source, to ensure power demands could be met in extreme cases. The report, he said, should act as a guide for placing wind farms in the most rewarding locations. For example, there is a substantial amount of peak-time wind energy near the East Coast's largest population centers. "This study enables the planning and development of very large wind farms offshore of New York City or Boston. Connecting the power to the grid would be technically as easy as laying a cable in the sand and hooking it directly into the grid without the need to build often controversial transmission lines on the land," Dvorak said. Both scientists acknowledge that it could take years before developers begin to tap this resource to the extent that it is needed – the country's first offshore wind farm, the Cape Wind Project, was proposed in 2001 and is still not operational – but they believe that if pilot projects are successful, bigger wind farms will follow. Although wind energy currently costs more than natural gas – and installation offshore currently costs two to three times as much as land-based turbines – both the short- and long-range economics of offshore wind power make it attractive. In the near term, the construction would create jobs in states that don't currently have a large energy industry, and it would further wean consumers off fossil fuels. Long term, a greater shift to wind energy would offset pollution, and thereby reduce the associated health and environmental costs. "But the real advantage of wind versus natural gas or coal is that, even though there's a higher cost now for offshore wind, it results in price stability," Jacobson said. "There's zero fuel costs once they're in the water. Coal and gas are depletable resources, so their cost will inevitably go up over time. The cost of wind energy will remain stable, and the wind resource is infinite." The paper, "U.S. East Coast Offshore Wind Energy Resources and Their Relationship to Peak-Time Electricity Demand" is available here. stanford</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347734803316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 14:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347736559622-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Deserves Credit</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1347702517843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen brother.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1347736559622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 15:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347740333811-16</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE DID THE ARAB SPRING COME FROM?</Title><Username>i.alaric</Username><Timestamp>1347662035084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>60 Minutes had the audacity to air the transcripts from the Tariq Haziz April Gilespie meeting where Bush's agent Gillespie assures the Iraqis that the US views the dispute between Iraq and Kuwait as a private dispute that the US would not take sides in. The US practically urged Saddam to invade Kuwait. Muslem-Christian wars are Israel's only hope of surviving.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1347740333811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 16:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347740897624-17</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE DID THE ARAB SPRING COME FROM?</Title><Username>i.alaric</Username><Timestamp>1347662035084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The day the NATO bombing campaign ended in Libya the black al qeda flag was hoisted over government buildings in Benghazi. Al CIAeda are the descendants of the Afghan "freedom fighters" who chased the Soviets from Afghansistan.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1347740897624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 16:28:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347751123933-18</Id><Title>Obama - "We Have Profound Respect For [Radical] Islam"</Title><Msg>That's how it reads in the muslim world.After all,he's the nitwit who forced Mubarak to allow the Moslem Brotherhood to attend his mealy-mouthed,apologetic speech to their parliament.He's now as befuddled as Carter was with Iran. Here's a suggestion,Mr. President. How about standing up for OUR principles.How about demanding THEY RESPECT other faiths,cultures and nationalities.How about mentioning the incredible amount of hate filled programming and imagery spewing forth from THEIR MEDIA,every day,for decades. If for no other reason than to at least "chnage" your approach.Because all your apologizing and endless proclamations of "profound respect" have done a grand job of setting Egypt ablaze.So you got nothing to lose.And who knows,maybe,just maybe YOU'LL get some RESPECT from the AMERICAN PEOPLE YOU IMBICILE!</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1347751123933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 19:18:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347756032821-19</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE DID THE ARAB SPRING COME FROM?</Title><Username>i.alaric</Username><Timestamp>1347662035084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you implying the bush family is nothing but liars and should never be given ANY political power?? that the WHOLE family CANNOT BE TRUSTED?? No need to imply--it is fact</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1347756032821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 20:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>