<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-28"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351400538044-1</Id><Title>Barrons predicting Obama win, but use Barrons as a contrarian indicator</Title><Msg>They are wrong most of the time. Suspect Romney wins and Bonds and economy tank in 2015. Hillary runs in 2016 and repairs the economy by some miracle. Obama is the fall guy for Hillary. It has already been decided long time ago. But before Obama leaves he will start a war with IRan and Romney will pick up the tab.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1351400538044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 01:02:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351401653361-2</Id><Title>Another 4 years of freeloading the message boards</Title><Msg>As it is a full time job to post messages on the boards. Idea here is to collect welfare and post message all day long. This is the Obama dream team. This really draws inspiration from all people around the world. Not!</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1351401653361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 01:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351402768367-3</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The poster boy for brain death speaks again - fully demonstrating the symptoms of that irreversible condition.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351402768367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 01:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351402948905-4</Id><Title>Amir Taheri on how he lost the Middle East</Title><Msg>For almost a century the Middle East has been a fault-line threatening international peace and stability. With the debris of successive empires strewn around it, this theater of big power rivalries has produced many of the convulsions the world has witnessed since World War II. The United States developed an interest in the region in the 1940s as President Roosevelt began thinking about the post-war international order. Since then, under American leadership, a political architecture was shaped guaranteeing the region’s stability. For six decades, under administrations from both parties, American power acted as the pole that kept the tent up. Over the past four years, however, President Barack Obama has pulled that pole away, allowing the tent to sag and, in parts, fold. The American abdication under Obama has led to a transition from a problematic status quo to an uncertain future. It has also created a vacuum that various opportunist powers are trying to fill. Under Obama, Russia has gained a veto over aspects of American foreign policy, ranging from the building of a missile shield in Central Europe to halting Iran’s nuclear program, to humanitarian intervention in Syria. After two decades of virtual absence from the Middle East, Russia is trying to regain at least some of the influence that the Soviet Empire once enjoyed. For its part, Turkey, acting as an opportunist power under its neo-Ottoman leadership, is trying to cast itself as the leader of a new Middle East dominated by the Muslim Brotherhood behind a political facade. Four years ago, Turkey was the region’s only nation that had no problems with its neighbors. Today, it has problems with almost all of them. Because it is a member of NATO, Turkey could drag the alliance into uncertain waters in the service of its own ill-defined ambitions. Meanwhile, Iran is gripped by unprecedented fear and hubris — fear that it might be the next target for regime change and hubris about exporting its anti-West ideology of hate to the rest of the region. As in Russia’s case, Iran is both encouraged and frightened by the American retreat. It is encouraged because it sees new opportunities to project power in Afghanistan, the Persian Gulf and Iraq. But it is also frightened because it might end up facing a new bloc of Arab-Sunni powers determined to push it back into its Shi’ite box. Obama’s worldview was shaped by two factors. The first was his desire to be the opposite of what he thought George W Bush was. He saw his predecessor as a “my way or the highway” cowboy who had dictated to others and hit them on the head when they got out of line. The first half of the Obama presidency was spent on an apology tour of the region during which he blamed the US for much of the region’s troubles and spun the cobweb of new contradictions. For example, in 2009 when Iranians rose against their despot, Obama refused to back them because that would have looked like endorsing Bush’s “Freedom Agenda.” Hatred for Bush also led Obama into backing Tunisian, Egyptian and Yemeni despots until the 11th hour. Even then, he preferred an alliance with the Muslim Brotherhood rather than democratic oppositions that Bush had tried to help, albeit with little success. Not being Bush was also a motive in Obama’s decision to downgrade ties with Iraq which, thanks to American blood and treasure, has emerged as a beacon of light in a dark region. Having established that he was not Bush, he still had to show who he was. The answer was the second factor in his policy: an exaggerated belief in the potency of his own political sex appeal. Obama thinks that things would happen simply by wanting them to. He promised to create a Palestinian state in one year, appointing Sen. George Mitchell as special envoy. But then he forgot about Mitchell — who found out that he had been taken for a ride and resigned. Wishful thinking also shaped Obama’s policy, or simulacrum of policy, vis-a-vis Iran. He stretched his “hand of friendship” to President Ahmadinejad and was roundly rebuffed. Foreign policy is the ultimate preserve of the president. Thus the political persona of the president, in fact his character, plays a crucial role in determining foreign policy success or failure. A prisoner of fantasies about the world and his own prowess, Obama has proved incapable of developing a realistic policy capable of dealing with a complex and dangerous region. In the process he has sown the seeds of storms that he or his successors might face, at a high cost to the United States.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351402948905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 01:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351410068078-5</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HILARIOUS!!!! OMG!! That's too funny!!! ROTFLOL!!!! See,that's what you get for living alone,deep in the woods somewhere,shut away from humanity and getting your "politcal" opinions from slasher movies.DON;T GO TO THE GROCERY STORE!!! IT'S TERRIFYING!! THERE'S "REPUBLICANS" IN THERE!!!! THEY'LL CARRY YOU INTO THE BACK AND EAT YOU!!! LOL!!!!</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1351410068078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 03:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351419220085-6</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahlees brain dead.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351419220085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 06:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351419317926-7</Id><Topic><Title>5 to 1 Obama wins offer still stands</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1351212202113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 20:43:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maxi dosnt have any $ he is broke.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351419317926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 06:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351419354722-8</Id><Topic><Title>AMBER ALERT FROM KENYA !!!!!</Title><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1351369392308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is being sent back after nov.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351419354722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 06:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351419466239-9</Id><Topic><Title>So Far Ohio Not Taking Romney Bait and Switch</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351343138664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are as dumb or brain dead as wahleee.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1351419466239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 06:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351424350687-10</Id><Title>Demoncrap Voter Fraud in Ohio</Title><Msg>Demoncraps have no ethics or morales whatsoever. "Two volunteer poll workers at an Ohio voting station told Human Events that they observed van loads of Ohio residents born in Somalia — the state is home to the second-largest Somali population in the United States — being driven to the voting station and guided by Democratic interpreters on the voting process. No Republican interpreters were present, according to these volunteers. While it’s not unusual for get-out-the-vote groups to help voters get to the polls, the volunteers who talked to Human Events observed a number of troubling and questionable activities. A source, who wishes to remain anonymous, is a volunteer outside the Morse Road polling center. She has witnessed Somalis who cannot speak English come to the polling center. They are brought in groups, by van or bus. The Democrats hand them a slate card and say, “vote Brown all the way down.” Given that Sherrod Brown is the incumbent Democrat Senator in Ohio, one can assume that this is the reference."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351424350687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 07:39:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351424599792-11</Id><Title>Illegal Means More Votes Nationwide for Demoncraps</Title><Msg>Since Demoncraps have no shame, "illegal" means nothing to them as they immediately give legal US citizen "rights" to "illegal" immigrants in order to increase their fraudulent and ignorant voting base. "More than 3,000 young illegal immigrants are applying daily to take part in the administration's new deportation reprieve policy, Homeland Security Secretary Janet Napolitano said last week. Napolitano said a total of roughly 200,000 people have applied since the agency began accepting applications two months ago. She made the announcement Wednesday to a panel of educators from across the country who serve on the Homeland Security Academic Advisory Council, as reported by The Hill newspaper. The agency began accepting applications after President Obama in June made the policy change -- after failing to pass comprehensive immigration reform and during an election year in which he will again need the Latino vote to help him win."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351424599792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 07:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351439486400-12</Id><Topic><Title>Exercise Caution Now!</Title><Username>rileyjohn8857</Username><Timestamp>1350649521024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:25:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already a member since 2006, you really know how to pick them.</Msg><Username>louisestephen5430</Username><Timestamp>1351439486400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 11:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351439501413-13</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will also point out that no one on this board, of either political persuasion, has wished harm on anyone from the hurricane but that YOU, in the past, have wished lots of destruction on the 'conservative south' from other hurricanes. Is total hypocrisy another symptom of brain death? Or is that one just unique to your miserable self hating person?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351439501413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 11:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351442914354-14</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know you want lots of death and destruction so you can point your fecal covered fingers of blame at fellow Americans. You know you do,, You're a disgraceful load of blood soaked cowards. You are one sick puppy, probably an Obama supporter too....Don't believe I've ever seen you post a decent remark.....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351442914354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 12:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351451307540-15</Id><Topic><Title>So Far Ohio Not Taking Romney Bait and Switch</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351343138664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's policies are working. YOU ARE SO FAR OUT OF TOUCH WITH YOUR HATE AND MISS INFORMATION YOU SHOULD NOT BE ALLOWED OFF THE LEASH OR GIVEN PERMISSION TO USE A PC.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351451307540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351451513299-16</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"THERE'S "REPUBLICANS" IN THERE!!!! THEY'LL CARRY YOU INTO THE BACK AND EAT YOU!!!" You got that right. At least you admit you are a member of a bunch of cannibals.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351451513299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351451668798-17</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is nothing decent that could be said about TODAY's Republicans and right wingers of all stripes, especially their actions.. They are fascists and deserve to be smashed back into their post WW II irrelevance.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351451668798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351451905979-18</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've never wished any ills on the South. I have merely taken on the character of the religious fascists you align with who scream and squeal that a storm effects certain people because of their "moral" position. Meanwhile the true immoral blood lust comes directly from these same religious freaks that point to gawd's "will" when such disasters strike people whom they and you enjoy watching be punished.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351451905979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:18:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351452088532-19</Id><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Msg>Keep believing the lies of big oil and big coal as your homes get flooded and blown too shreds. They could care less about you, your children or your grandchildren. All they care about is profit and power and you fascist loving filth look the other way as you put on your steel toed boots. You'll need more that that to stop American freedom you filthy right wing rats.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351452342819-20</Id><Topic><Title>So Far Ohio Not Taking Romney Bait and Switch</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351343138664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Miss Information" ? Is she single you stooge? Ok, if what you say is true then tell me a few of "Mitt's" positions? I can bet that I will find an example of where he changed that position in order to politically pander to a special interest.. You won't dare take this challenge though, because you're a morally bankrupt coward like every other right winger I've engaged on this board.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452342819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351452470572-21</Id><Topic><Title>So Far Ohio Not Taking Romney Bait and Switch</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351343138664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But you don't dare take notice of Bush's $6 Trillion of "what will belong to future generations to repay" and produce a GREAT RECESSION Bigger than ANY SINCE THE GREAT DEPRESSION. Where were you on that spending you hypocritical liar.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452470572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351452600936-22</Id><Topic><Title>So Far Ohio Not Taking Romney Bait and Switch</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351343138664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt is merely a modern day version of Herbert Hoover. Only today he's got an army of propagandized fascists thanks to the likes of Limbaugh and Beck who make the Brownshirts of the 1930's look smart.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452600936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351457469850-23</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How did big oil make the Earth move 7.7 today? Get real, things change every day.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1351457469850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 16:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351462663789-24</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one thinks that there is no climate change. Climate change has been happening for centuries. It is "man-made global warming" that is a joke. Child!</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1351462663789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 18:17:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351464788985-25</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>walhieeeeeeeeeeee. YOU ARE SCHIZOPHRENIC.</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1351464788985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 18:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351465854117-26</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then follow the money " Ground all Jets" They take in air at -30F and send it out at 3000F. What is there5,000 in the air just in the US. NO Way, that would hurt.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1351465854117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351465904601-27</Id><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Msg>worse than VISTA !!</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465904601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351467848816-28</Id><Topic><Title>WINDOWS 8 stinks! No DVD, No JAVA support, NO Accessories, AWFUL &amp; confusing !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1351465904601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry, Windows 75 coming soon. It will have the capabilities of wiping your behind, making a pot of your favorite coffee, taking out the garbage, paying the bills and cooking dinner. Although; you'll need a masters degree in technology just to log on.</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1351467848816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351471696689-29</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Fascists Again Cheering For National Demise With Sandy</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351387194407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 21:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're lying again wahleee boy - but then that's about all you do.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351471696689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 20:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351471941167-30</Id><Topic><Title>So Far Ohio Not Taking Romney Bait and Switch</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351343138664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Complete #$%$ as always from you. BTW: It's OBAMAO's Great Recession. You always seem to forget that. Another symptom of brain death?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351471941167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 20:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351476792028-31</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You'll need more that that to stop American freedom you filthy right wing rats. Most posters use civil words, but not you....When a person is called a fool, it generally is because the poster is just that....I tend to agree....This wahlee should be returned to the humane society and ask them to put this mad dog down....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351476792028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 22:13:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351478023166-32</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fascist like those on the right do not deserve civility. You and yours are equivalent to the Nazi's of the 1930's in so many ways and idiots like you beg others to act like Chamberlain so you can crush their skulls with your steel boots without resistance. I represent resistance to you and that is why you attempt to marginalize those like me. We'll have none of it. You're going down with us, i guarantee it.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351478023166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 22:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351478167720-33</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your comparison is horse manure.. You know the stuff between your ears that stinks like the pollution you consumed to get you where you are.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351478167720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 22:36:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>