<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345435219000-1</Id><Title>I voted for Obuma-trillion cuz he's BLACK</Title><Msg>Boy do I feel stupid. Me and my college professors all voted for the guy just to prove to people how progressive we were.</Msg><Username>socalinvestor50</Username><Timestamp>1345435219000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345436065000-2</Id><Topic><Title>How many Russian Subs will obama allow in the great lakes</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1345382778000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 09:26:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will not allow any Russian subs in the Great Lakes. Russians are White Christians and John Bolton, John McCain and William Kristol insist they must be subdued.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345436065000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345436084000-3</Id><Topic><Title>I voted for Obuma-trillion cuz he's BLACK</Title><Username>socalinvestor50</Username><Timestamp>1345435219000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, it took a black man to stop the financial rot induced by white men.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1345436084000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:14:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345436206000-4</Id><Topic><Title>How many Russian Subs will obama allow in the great lakes</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1345382778000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 09:26:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watching GOP Senators s+ck off the likes of Jamie Dimon and his ilk on live television is part and parcel of the demise of the United States.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345436206000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345436256000-5</Id><Topic><Title>How many Russian Subs will obama allow in the great lakes</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1345382778000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 09:26:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will he give Russian subs free passage up the locks? Your entire premise relies on this being yes, which is as likely as....?</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1345436256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345438686000-6</Id><Title>Biofuel fails EU sustainability test, German researchers claim</Title><Msg>Biofuel fails EU sustainability test, German researchers claim Study says EU-grown rapeseed biodiesel falls under 35% marker, adding weight to calls to end food biofuels Terry Macalister guardian co uk, Sunday 19 August 2012 15.50 BST The growing row over biofuels is ready to flare up again with German researchers claiming to have found evidence that European-produced biodiesel does not meet the sustainability targets claimed by Brussels. Two experts at Friedrich Schiller University in Jena say eight out of their 10 tests on locally produced rapeseed biodiesel failed to show the 35% greenhouse gas savings promised. In most cases it was under 30%. The use of biofuels would be further undermined when the EU emissions target increases, as planned, to 50% in five years' time. Gernot Pehnelt and Christoph Vietze also claim their work has been undermined by a lack of co-operation from the European Union which they believe is on the defensive over championing local energy crops. "Our results indicate that the 'sustainability' of rapeseed biodiesel in the interpretation of the [EU's] renewable energy directive is at best questionable and in most scenarios simply unjustifiable," said Pehnelt. "What we need is transparency. The European commission hesitates to publish all the background data and promises to come up with new calculations for individual biofuels but they have not come up with any values yet." Biofuels are accused by the UN and others of pushing up world food prices, and exacerbating the effect of the most severe drought in the US in half a century. US legislators called on the environmental protection agency this month to waive its ethanol mandate that stipulates 40% of the American corn crop is turned into biodiesel. The US department of agriculture said the corn yield would be the lowest for 17 years, raising grain prices as it means there will be more demand for wheat to be used as animal feed. José Graziano da Silva, director general of the Food and Agriculture Organisation (FAO) at the United Nations, said he wanted to see a halt in US government-backed production of corn-based ethanol, which is mixed with petrol to make "greener" fuel, amid fears the world is heading for another food crisis like the one in 2008 that triggered riots. The EU's lack of transparency on biofuels has already been challenged by non-governmental organisations (NGOs) such as Client Earth, and the German academics say their problems play into the hands of those who believe that Brussels is deliberately overstating the benefits of local rapeseed for political reasons. Germany, France and Italy are the EU's biggest producers of rapeseed oil, and are also home to a car manufacturing industry that actively supports the use of biodiesel for reducing carbon emissions. Europe's renewable energy directive, introduced three years ago, demands that greenhouse gas emissions from production and use of biofuels for transport must be at least 35% lower than those from fossil fuels. In 2017 that marker is meant to rise to 50%. Plans drawn up by EU member states predict that bio-energy, including biomass for power generation and biofuel for transport, will provide more than 50% of the EU share of renewable energy as part of 2020 climate goals. Use of biodiesel is expected to double by 2020 to 19.95m tonnes of oil equivalent from around 10m tonnes in 2010. http://www.guardian.co.uk/environment/2012/aug/19/biofuel-fails-eu-sustainabilty-test</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345438686000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:58:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345438702000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuel fails EU sustainability test, German researchers claim</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345438686000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:58:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brussels faces a big challenge coming up with the investment and technology needed to move to a new feedstock for biodiesel, such as weeds and waste stems that would take the pressure off grain supplies for food. The EU also needs to find inputs that would no longer result in the clearing of environmentally sensitive forests and wetlands to plant fuel crops, an issue known as indirect land use change. The finds of the two German academics have received the support of Fausto Freire, who conducts research on biofuels at the University of Coimbra in Portugal. He told Nature magazine that there are "huge uncertainties" associated with the greenhouse-gas emissions of biodiesel but another academic, Gerhard Brankatschk at Technische Universität Berlin, believed the east German study had "severe shortcomings". Nestlé: End biofuels now" The chairman of the world's biggest food group Nestlé, Peter Brabeck, has called on politicians to lobby to end the use of food in the production of biofuels. "This does not mean that biofuel should be scrapped entirely but that producers should use other organic materials," Brabeck told the Swiss newspaper SonntagsZeitung. He joins a growing chorus of politicians and scientists calling for a rethink in biofuel production. "Our problem is that almost half of US corn production and 60% of European rape is being used for fuel production," he said. Biofuel production is adding pressure on food prices which are already being boosted by climate change. "[Food] prices are increasingly prone to swings and correlate more and more with oil prices," he said. He also called for more transparency in international commodities markets.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345438702000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345439123000-8</Id><Title>Pipelines, glut of cheap crude raise doubts over oil sands expansion</Title><Msg>Pipelines, glut of cheap crude raise doubts over oil sands expansion Shawn McCarthy Ottawa — The Globe and Mail Published Friday, Aug. 17 2012, 12:56 PM EDT Last updated Friday, Aug. 17 2012, 6:44 PM EDT Strained pipeline systems and a glut of North American crude will force Canadian oil sands companies to cut back on their ambitious expansion plans over the next several years, a major new report warns. Based on a review of all major producing regions, the CIBC World Markets report says North American crude production should grow annually over the next five years by a stunning 900,000 barrels a day That scenario would see the United States dramatically cut its dependency on imported crude, forcing Canadian producers to look for markets elsewhere, at the same time that Canadian gas exporters face shrinking U.S. appetite for their supplies due to booming shale gas supplies. Companies will find it increasingly difficult to justify expansion of high-cost oil sands projects, especially when there is a wealth of more profitable, less capital-intensive investment opportunities across the continent, CIBC analysts said in the 276-page report released Friday. “Unfortunately, higher cost oil sands projects seem like the first to get rationalized,” said the study of 28 major oil and gas plays in the U.S. and Canada. In a conference call Friday, the report’s lead author, Andrew Potter, noted that firms like Suncor Energy Inc. and Canadian Natural Resources Ltd. have already started to pull back from their ambitious growth scenarios. He said company expansion plans in aggregate would add 1.4 million barrels per day of production by the end of 2016, and another 2 million barrels by 2020. But he forecast that the longer-term growth will be roughly half of what is now now planned. That more conservative path would be still higher than the most recent outlook from the Canadian Association of Petroleum Producers, which sees an additional 900,000 barrels per day of production by 2016, and 700,000 more by 2020. However, Mr. Potter said many oil sands projects can be competitive. “We still see lower cost SAGD opportunities … as being very competitive with tight oil in terms of rates of return,” he said, referring to an extraction method known as steam assisted, gravity drainage. “It’s more about the mining side of the business and more mediocre SAGD leases that will be the first to fall.” Overall, CIBC expects U.S. onshore production to grow by as much as 700,000 barrels per day each year over the next five years from fields like the Bakken in North Dakota, and the Permian and Eagle Ford in Texas. Throw in increased production from the Gulf of Mexico, from Canadian tight oil and from the oil sands, and North America stands to lead the world in growth of crude oil production for the next five years, at least. However, Mr. Potter said the industry will have to raise massive amounts of capital – in debt, new equity and joint venture partnerships with foreign oil companies – to finance the vast expansion. The key for Canadian oil sands producers is pipeline capacity. Even if all the pipelines being planned were built, there would not be enough capacity to handle the growth that companies have laid out in their expansion plans. And Mr. Potter said there is “less than a 50-50 chance” that the two proposed pipelines through B.C. – Enbridge’s Inc.’s Northern Gateway and Kinder Morgan’s Trans Mountain expansion – will be completed. Without those B.C. pipelines, Canadian producers will lose some $20-billion a year in cash flow due to less production and lower prices. http://www.theglobeandmail.com/globe-investor/pipelines-glut-of-cheap-crude-raise-doubts-over-oil-sands-expansion/article4485891/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345439123000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 01:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345439731000-9</Id><Topic><Title>CBO says Romney is lying about health care reform</Title><Username>more_immediately</Username><Timestamp>1345414379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:12:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU ARE AN IDIOT! They are all liars!</Msg><Username>d.jeff36</Username><Timestamp>1345439731000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 01:15:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345450322000-10</Id><Topic><Title>CBO says Romney is lying about health care reform</Title><Username>more_immediately</Username><Timestamp>1345414379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:12:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an idiot. Its what lies are told. Remember the Iraq invasion. How many innocent people died as a result?</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345450322000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 04:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345463415000-11</Id><Topic><Title>I voted for Obuma-trillion cuz he's BLACK</Title><Username>socalinvestor50</Username><Timestamp>1345435219000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What Obamao actually did was make it several times worse.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345463415000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 07:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345466767000-12</Id><Title>Good Morning.</Title><Msg>Have a nice day</Msg><Username>jimyoung901</Username><Timestamp>1345466767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:46:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345468959000-13</Id><Title>Will new discoveries stop the world from running out of oil?</Title><Msg>Will new discoveries stop the world from running out of oil? Posted Friday, Aug. 17, 20122 Comments By Greg Gordon McClatchy Newspapers WASHINGTON -- After nearly a decade of warnings that the world's oil supply was running out, Americans now are hearing about technology breakthroughs that have unlocked vast U.S. deposits of natural gas, helped reverse a 40-year slide in domestic oil production and could perhaps transform America into the next Middle East. But despite the euphoria, there's a major problem: The looming American oil glut may not be enough to satisfy the United States and the rest of motorized humanity. Some experts say soaring demand from China and India is sure to send oil prices back above $100 a barrel. A supply disruption in the coming years, they say, could trigger panic and gasoline hoarding, and perhaps lead to lines at the pumps reminiscent of the 1973 Arab oil embargo and the 1979 Iranian revolution. Global shortfalls of other fuels also could develop sooner than many people think, as a planet of nearly 7 billion people and more than 1 billion gasoline-gulping vehicles strains the limits of combustible energy resources that are the underpinning of modern civilization. While oil industry officials and prominent consultants take strong issue with these dim views, critics say governments here and abroad have been less than candid about future oil supplies and the ramifications of failing to shift to alternative fuels. One outspoken Energy Department consultant, Robert Hirsch, alleged that the administrations of both Presidents George W. Bush and Barack Obama have engaged in a cover-up of the likelihood of an oil shortage. Hirsch predicted a shortfall will hit in the next four years and send shockwaves through the world economy, possibly leading to gasoline rationing. Few governments have implemented intensive conservation programs to stretch out supplies during a decades-long transition to more fuel-efficient vehicles. There's no shortage of worries: Surging Third World demand could overtake supplies. Industry watchdogs say some U.S. Energy Information Administration forecasts have been wildly optimistic, especially a projection that between 2011 and 2035, global production of liquid fuels will see a 21.6 million-barrel rise in daily output -- the equivalent of the five biggest Middle Eastern oil producers. Others say projections and policies by the Energy Information Administration, which is the Energy Department's independent information arm, as well as the Paris-based International Energy Agency and even the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, have masked mounting risks of shortages of oil and possibly natural gas. A McClatchy computer analysis suggests that proven reserves of all of the world's primary fuels are likely to diminish much faster than the EIA and the IEA have suggested, begging questions about how long mankind can continue to increase consumption of finite resources. The U.S. Energy Information Administration's deputy chief, Henry Gruenspecht, defended his agency's main global oil supply forecast as stemming from "careful consideration of a wide range of factors." He noted, however, that there's "significant uncertainty" about future supply and demand of liquid fuels and a lack of transparency regarding some nations' reserves. An international group of scientists and energy experts argue that global oil production has peaked or soon will as the second half of the oil age begins. The experts, known as peak oil advocates, say that the output of 500 existing giant oil fields that provide most of the world's liquid fuels has begun a gradual decline that will create a 17 million-barrel daily deficit by 2035. http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/08/17/4189340/will-new-discoveries-stop-the.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345468959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:22:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345468974000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Will new discoveries stop the world from running out of oil?</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345468959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:22:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We're facing a situation that is real hard for anyone to grasp," said Kjell Aleklett, the Swedish president of the Association for the Study of Peak Oil. Oil industry officials, as well as one of the industry's foremost consultants, strongly disagree. Daniel Yergin, chairman of IHS Cambridge Energy Research Associates, said peak oil advocates have long underestimated technology advances. While the costs are high, adequate supplies exist "if they can be developed in a reasonable timeframe," he said. Yergin, whose latest book, The Quest: Energy, Security, and the Remaking of the Modern World details the worldwide scramble for fuel, pointed in an interview to an almost 25 percent increase in U.S. oil production since 2008 and major new discoveries in the North Sea and off the coasts of Brazil and Ghana. Exxon Mobil CEO Rex Tillerson told the Council on Foreign Relations recently that high oil prices have spurred the industry to "develop resources that were previously not accessible." The latest technology will enable recovery of trillions of barrels of oil embedded in underground shale in Western states -- enough "to carry us well into the latter part of this century at current production rates," he said. "There's no question the world is running out of cheap oil," said Brookings Institution scholar Charles Ebinger, who has advised 50 countries on energy matters. "Are we running out of expensive oil? I'm not convinced." For example, the United States has seen a natural gas boom in fields like the Barnett Shale in North Texas spawned by a combination of horizontal drilling and hydraulic fracturing, or "fracking," that breaks rock deep below the surface to free oil and gas. Branded "a total game changer" for natural gas recovery by Marcia McNutt, director of the U.S. Geological Survey, new production has driven down natural gas prices. Ebinger said fracking marks a "fundamental change" in the U.S. oil production outlook. Coupled with Canadian imports, he said, the United States could cut its daily oil imports from 9 million to 3 million barrels within a decade. A computer calculation shows how fast an energy-hungry planet could theoretically devour all of the proved reserves -- those with a "reasonable certainty" of being recovered economically at prevailing prices and technology -- of the world's primary energy sources. The Energy Information Administration's 2011 outlook says that at current production rates, the world has 126 years of coal reserves and 60 years of natural gas. Using the same "reserves-to-production ratio," the 1.47 trillion barrels of global conventional oil reserves, as estimated by Oil &amp; Gas Journal in 2011, would last for 46 years. But this yardstick fails to factor in annual growth in energy consumption -- neither the agency's conservative, 1.6 percent projected rate until 2035 nor the 2.2 percent rate of past decades. To get a truer picture of the world's supposedly guaranteed fuel supply, McClatchy compiled the raw energy content, in British thermal units, of the estimated proved reserves of oil, natural gas, coal and uranium. Subtracting from that figure the total BTUs that the Energy Information Administration projects will be consumed each year from those four energy sources, and factoring in yearly consumption growth, shows how long the fuel might last. Using the EIA's modest 1.6 percent growth rate, all proved reserves of oil, natural gas, coal and uranium would be gone in 56 years. Analyzing proved reserves doesn't tell the full story, because the discovery of additional reserves has kept pace or exceeded annual depletions for years. Nor do global reserve figures include unconventional oil discoveries since 2009 -- those from deep-water ocean drilling, Canadian sands or U.S. shale.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345468974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345470455000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation could double based on this report</Title><Username>pauletteturnley</Username><Timestamp>1345469738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:35:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are on on "ignore"</Msg><Username>jhenryallin</Username><Timestamp>1345470455000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345471553000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Todd Akin's hatred or stupidity?</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345433577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, indeed.</Msg><Username>howard_child</Username><Timestamp>1345471553000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:05:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345471619000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Todd Akin's hatred or stupidity?</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345433577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good idea.</Msg><Username>howard_child</Username><Timestamp>1345471619000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345474092000-18</Id><Title>GGR to strike gas and oil</Title><Msg>Any day now offshore in Isreal.</Msg><Username>mjk4080</Username><Timestamp>1345474092000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:48:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345474434000-19</Id><Title>Time to raise gas prices again. Americans used to $4 gal gas.</Title><Msg>No problem filling the SUV with $4/gal gas. Will pay up to $7/gal gas.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1345474434000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345474622000-20</Id><Title>AH, CAPITALISM for EVERYONE!</Title><Msg>http://nymag.com/daily/intel/2012/08/economist-digs-into-us-churchs-finances.html</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345474622000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345479686000-21</Id><Title>Democrats planning complete destruction of Iran civillian infrastructure</Title><Msg>Our Middle East ally has ordered total destruction of Iran's civillian infrastructure. Similiar to Iraq and Libya, the no bid contracts will be awarded to cnnected multi national corporations at six times what a competitive bid would be, and brain dead American taxpayers will obediently pick up the tab.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345479686000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:21:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345482381000-22</Id><Title>WHERE REPUBLICAN MENTALITY IS IN LEADERSHIP!</Title><Msg>http://www.guardian.co.uk/science/the-h-word/2012/aug/20/legitimate-rape-medieval-medical-concept</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345482381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345482764000-23</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE REPUBLICAN MENTALITY IS IN LEADERSHIP!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345482381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:06:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/08/20/massachusetts-school-district-launches-student-condom-policy/?test=latestnews</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1345482764000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345487073000-24</Id><Title>Gateway pipeline deadline set amid B.C. minister's concerns</Title><Msg>Gateway pipeline deadline set amid B.C. minister's concerns James Moore says it's 'simply not true' pipeline will be rammed through by federal government CBC News Posted: Aug 3, 2012 3:50 PM ET Last Updated: Aug 3, 2012 7:56 PM ET Read 683 comments 683 The federal government has set a firm deadline of Dec. 31, 2013, for the review panel deciding the future of the Northern Gateway pipeline, shutting down the possibility of further extensions and putting into place the expedited assessment process pledged in its budget implementation bill. But the written notice issued by the Canadian Environmental Assessment Agency Friday comes on the heels of comments from the senior Harper government minister in B.C., James Moore, who told a radio program in Vancouver on Wednesday that doubts about the Northern Gateway project are "widespread, given the behaviour of Enbridge recently." Moore denied repeatedly that the federal government's goal is to "ram through the pipeline." But he did not reply to interview requests Friday seeking clarification as to whether his comments reflected a possible change in direction or message for federal Conservatives. In an emailed statement provided to CBC News in response to an interview request seeking clarification of the government's position, Natural Resources Minister Joe Oliver's office repeated well-used lines about the federal government's "critical strategic objective" of "diversification of our energy markets" in order to "create jobs and economic growth." "We will continue to work in partnership with the provincial governments to encourage achieving this objective," the statement said. "In particular to the Northern Gateway project, it is currently before the Joint Review Panel who are reviewing all the environmental considerations to make sure it is safe for the environment and Canadians. We look forward to reviewing their report once it is completed." In an interview Friday on CBC News Network's Power &amp; Politics, Peter Julian, the NDP Natural Resources critic who represents the B.C. riding of Burnaby-New Westminster, said the federal government's doublespeak just isn't going to fly with Canadians. "The Conservatives are playing this dangerous game where in B.C. they're acknowledging the widespread negative reaction of the Northern Gateway proposal, and at the same time in Ottawa they're trying to impose and move forward on something that British Columbians will simply not accept," Julian told guest host Hannah Thibedeau. Friday's notice from the federal assessment agency confirmed the changes implemented in the government's budget bill, which came into force on July 6. The changes to the joint review panel's mandate set a maximum time limit for the panel's work, concluding at the end of 2013 without further extensions. Under the changes, the joint review panel can't reject the pipeline project for only environmental reasons. Once the review panel submits its report, the federal government will make the final decision on the pipeline within 180 days (approximately six months), before the end of June 2014. Public opinion against project Public opinion in http://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/story/2012/08/03/pol-pipeline-moore-gateway.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345487073000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345487444000-25</Id><Title>Kitimat refinery would be a game-changer</Title><Msg>Kitimat refinery would be a game-changer http://www.theglobeandmail.com/commentary/columnists/kitimat-refinery-would-be-a-game-changer/article4487586/?cmpid=rss1</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345487444000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345488086000-26</Id><Title>Renewable Diesel And Jet Fuels From Lipids: An Investor's Primer</Title><Msg>Renewable Diesel And Jet Fuels From Lipids: An Investor's Primer August 20, 2012 | 1 commentby: Tristan R. Brown | includes: CORN, DAR, HON, NTOIF.PK, SOYB, SZYM, TSN, UNG, VLO Introduction The recent controversy in Washington, DC over the use of small quantities of expensive algal-based biofuels to power the "Green Navy" has left many investors wondering what these "next-gen" fuels are and how they differ from the existing slate of biofuels that is currently available at gas stations. Meanwhile, in a closely related but underreported event, the same pathway responsible for algal-based biofuels has become the first advanced biofuels pathway to achieve commercial-scale production, both in the U.S. and globally. Indeed, Louisiana - a state better known for its offshore production of fossil fuels than its onshore production of biofuels - is currently expected to be home to a greater volume of advanced biofuels production than the rest of the states combined through at least 2013. The purpose of this article is to provide investors with a primer on this pathway, which produces renewable diesel and jet fuels via lipids hydroprocessing. It examines the differences between the lipids hydroprocessing and lipids transesterification (biodiesel) pathways, while also covering the different feedstocks available for use and discussing how a pathway that has proven competitive with petroleum-based diesel at $4-6/gal is currently costing the U.S. Navy $15/gal. Transesterification versus hydroprocessing Most people are familiar with the lipids transesterification pathway, which yields an output popularly known as biodiesel. The pathway has achieved widespread production globally over the last decade and currently yields nearly 1 billion gallons of transportation fuel per year in the U.S. alone: (click to enlarge) US Biodiesel Production data by YCharts Biodiesel is produced from lipids, which can take the form of either fats (generally animal-based) or oils (generally plant-based). Lipids transesterification consists of reacting the lipid triglycerides with methanol to yield fatty acid methyl esters [FAME] and glycerol (ethanol can also be used to yield fatty acid ethyl esters [FAEE], although methanol is generally a cheaper input). When used as a transportation fuel, these esters have similar combustion properties as petroleum-based diesel, thus the name "biodiesel." (click to enlarge) Lipids transesterification to FAME and glycerol (Credit: Wikipedia) Biodiesel is not chemically identical to diesel despite the similarity in combustion properties, however, and has a few important operational differences as a result. The most important of these are low temperature clouding and water contamination; the former can limit its utility in colder climes while the latter can reduce its energy efficiency. Finally, biodiesel is not suitable for use in jet engines (although I was surprised to hear a senior U.S. cabinet official say differently at a speech on our campus earlier this year, which I used as an ironic teaching tool for my students on the perils of receiving science lessons from lawyers). This greatly limits its aviation and military applications - in addition to the obvious aviation uses, many of the military's heavier land vehicles, such as the M1 Abrams Main Battle Tank, run on turbine engines. The U.S. military has been at the forefront of efforts to develop alternative diesel and jet fuels as a result. One alternative fuel pathway that has only recently gained traction in the U.S. is the reaction of lipids with hydrogen instead of alcohol. This "hydroprocessing" has two important effects: the hydrogen reacts with the http://seekingalpha.com/article/817591-renewable-diesel-and-jet-fuels-from-lipids-an-investor-s-primer</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345488086000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345489051000-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Making Of A Sayanim-The Secret Jewish Network</Title><Username>oakland_athletics_65</Username><Timestamp>1345401583000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:39:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What other nations have Sayanims?</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345489051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345495279000-28</Id><Topic><Title>I voted for Obuma-trillion cuz he's BLACK</Title><Username>socalinvestor50</Username><Timestamp>1345435219000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still read ALL my posts wahleee boy. And you still can't refute anything in them. Pathetic as always.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345495279000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345495454000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Has Infernal Ever Posted Anything of Substance?</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345489781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:09:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope you guys are enjoying your circle jerk. Please give me an example of anything 'of substance' either of you has ever posted. But I love the fact that I bother you so much.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345495454000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345496878000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats planning complete destruction of Iran civillian infrastructure</Title><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345479686000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:21:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Business as usual! We (taxpayers) just picked up the upside-down mortgages in California. The banks were to have participated 50/50 but it's easier to shaft the taxpayer. This will all be over soon....</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345496878000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:07:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499943000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Has Infernal Ever Posted Anything of Substance?</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345489781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:09:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. He posts only opinions of ultra-conservatives and lies.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345499943000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499975000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats planning complete destruction of Iran civillian infrastructure</Title><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345479686000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:21:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're filth raul.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345499975000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345501099000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Todd Akin's hatred or stupidity?</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345433577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it wasn't from a republican congressman, it would be an astonishingly ignorant thing to say.</Msg><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1345501099000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345502107000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Todd Akin's hatred or stupidity?</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345433577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conservatives are very stupid people. Just read the post from one about Russian subs in the great lakes.</Msg><Username>riw9362</Username><Timestamp>1345502107000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:35:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345502592000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Todd Akin's hatred or stupidity?</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345433577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not hatred--not stupid just building his base lots of the gop base is lockstep with akinryan sad but true</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1345502592000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345502936000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Todd Akin's hatred or stupidity?</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345433577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So then is his base stupid or full of hatred? Yes, both.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345502936000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345503406000-37</Id><Topic><Title>The Making Of A Sayanim-The Secret Jewish Network</Title><Username>oakland_athletics_65</Username><Timestamp>1345401583000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:39:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting post. I did not know this.</Msg><Username>wittbilly645</Username><Timestamp>1345503406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:56:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345503436000-38</Id><Topic><Title>A CALL FOR CARTER</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345299350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Taxes will need to be increased, too, to fund the interest, although the higher interest income will help in raising revenues. Still, taxes will have to be raised and they will pushed downward to the backs of low income people. The fools think the Democrats agenda helps them. It does not. They are forging their chains now. WITH THIS WILD SPENDING THAT REALLY HAS HELPED NOBODY, EVERY MAN WOMAN AND CHILD SHARE OF THIS DEBT IS $61,000 TO INCREASE TAXES IS NOT THE ANSWER. THE INTEREST WILL STILL KEEP CLIMBING. WE MIGHT HAVE ONE SHOT LEFT IN NOVEMBER TO RID OURSELVES OF THIS TERRIBLE BLIGHT. VOTE WISELY AND THINK OF YOUR FUTURE.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345503436000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345508110000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Has Infernal Ever Posted Anything of Substance?</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345489781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:09:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't talking to yourself get a little boring wahleee boy? Pleased to see I am still bugging you.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345508110000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345508240000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Todd Akin's hatred or stupidity?</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345433577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kind of like the statements Biden and Obamao make daily I guess.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345508240000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345508347000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Todd Akin's hatred or stupidity?</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345433577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many aliases in this chain wahleee boy - I'm losing count.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345508347000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345511599000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Has Infernal Ever Posted Anything of Substance?</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345489781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:09:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're about the least qualified person (after wahleee boy) to judge competence. But dream on. It seems to make you happy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345511599000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345514859000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Has Infernal Ever Posted Anything of Substance?</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345489781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:09:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxipad is the dopey POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345514859000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345514918000-44</Id><Topic><Title>I voted for Obuma-trillion cuz he's BLACK</Title><Username>socalinvestor50</Username><Timestamp>1345435219000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:00:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahleees brain is dead.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345514918000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:08:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345515968000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Has Infernal Ever Posted Anything of Substance?</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345489781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:09:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're the least qualified person to judge anything. Changing your ID only briefly remits you being ignored.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1345515968000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345516950000-46</Id><Topic><Title>Has Infernal Ever Posted Anything of Substance?</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345489781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:09:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, the doofus chimes in with another alias.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345516950000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345517340000-47</Id><Topic><Title>A CALL FOR CARTER</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345299350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uthink (misnomer) I wonder where your concern for DEBT was for 8 years under w and gop congress when it went from 5+ trillion to 12 trillion (10+ trillion and 1.5 trillion budget left in place = 12 trillion) --where was your concern ?? and just to make your ignorance shine--for that 7 TRILLION can you tell/link any great or worthy spending (in your mind or anyone elses) ?? the TSA--greatest expansion of GOVT since FDR ?? the medicare prescriptions?? the NCLB--but obviously some are ?? the AIG bailout--Lehman--which ?? please tell us where was the outrage please tell us what we have to show for 7 TRILLION $$</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1345517340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345520788000-48</Id><Topic><Title>A CALL FOR CARTER</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345299350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lease tell us what we have to show for 7 TRILLION $$ Nada, Nothing, Zero....Just a $61,000 debt around every man woman and child...</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345520788000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>