<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-10"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344571518000-1</Id><Title>Biofuels industry group pushes lawmakers on corn ethanol views</Title><Msg>Biofuels industry group pushes lawmakers on corn ethanol views By Zack Colman - 08/09/12 04:11 PM ET The so-called advanced biofuels industry is applying new pressure to convince lawmakers that their products will be collateral damage if Congress scuttles the national ethanol mandate. The Biotechnology Industry Organization (BIO) has been warning its political allies on Capitol Hill that attacks against corn ethanol will hinder next-generation fuels, too. BIO has reached out to lawmakers such as Sen. James Inhofe (R-Okla.) and Rep. Brian Bilbray (R-Calif.), who both promote advanced biofuel research, BIO Managing Director Matt Carr told E2-Wire on Thursday. Those lawmakers sponsor legislation that would let states opt out of meeting the renewable fuel standard (RFS) requirement of blending 13.2 billion gallons of corn ethanol into traditional fuel this year, Carr said. “We want to make sure there are not unintended consequences in altering the program,” Carr said. Carr said tinkering with that would spook investors in advanced biofuels, which are generally understood as those made from non-food products such as switchgrass and algae. “If you look at some of the members on those bills, some of them are the biggest advanced biofuels champions,” Carr said. “So we’ve been trying to educate them on how it’s all tied together.” BIO has not used lobbyists for the effort, Brent Erickson, executive vice president with BIO, told E2-Wire on Thursday. BIO spent $2.07 million on lobbyists in the second quarter of 2012. The RFS was one of the many issues it listed on lobbying disclosure forms. Lawmakers have become more vociferous about ending the Environmental Protection Agency’s (EPA) RFS in recent weeks. They say drought has made the corn ethanol mandate untenable as corn stocks dwindle, making it more expensive for livestock producers to continue operations. That rule also requires 21 billion gallons of advanced biofuels to be blended into conventional fuel by 2022, though no such fuels are currently produced at commercial scale. Carr said the spotlight Capitol Hill has shone on the RFS invited an equal amount of concerned calls from corn ethanol and advanced biofuels investors. The availability of advanced biofuels could soon change, as biofuels firm INEOS Bio on Thursday was granted the nation’s first registration for the commercial production and sale of such biofuels at its Florida plant. Mississippi-based firm KIOR also got permission to sell its advanced biofuel on Thursday. INEOS Bio said in a statement that it will begin producing at commercial scale during the third quarter of 2012. Full production will yield 8 million gallons of the fuel, the firm said. http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/242999-biofuels-industry-lobbying-lawmakers-to-change-views-on-ethanol-rule</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344571518000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:05:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344571528000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels industry group pushes lawmakers on corn ethanol views</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344571518000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:05:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BIO contends that the advanced biofuels industry is just about to hit its stride, so preserving investor confidence is essential. The group says advanced biofuels will directly create 29,000 jobs this year and 190,000 by 2022. The oil-and-gas industry is less bullish on those jobs numbers. The American Petroleum Institute (API) filed a lawsuit against EPA last month for imposing the advanced biofuel mandate even though none of it is commercially available. Importers and refiners had to buy 6.6 million gallons worth of credits this year to meet EPA’s target, even though the agency noted there were no gallons to purchase. That means the RFS has failed to have the kind of influence biofuels supporters say it possesses, Carlton Carroll, an API spokesman, told E2-Wire on Thursday. He explained that API has not called for an end to the RFS and is only asking to make changes that better reflect current market and production conditions. “I should point out that EPA’s absurd mandates for cellulosic biofuels have not stimulated the growth of these fuels,” Carroll said in an email. “While we expect these fuels to be available at some point (and our members are investing in them now), setting absurdly high mandates has proven to not stimulate the production of these fuels.”</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344571528000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344573663000-3</Id><Title>Statoil Seeks U.S. Lease for Floating Wind Farm Off Maine Coast</Title><Msg>Statoil Seeks U.S. Lease for Floating Wind Farm Off Maine Coast By Andrew Herndon - Aug 9, 2012 12:43 PM MT Statoil ASA (STL), Norway’s state- controlled oil company, is seeking permission to build a wind farm with floating turbines off the U.S. Atlantic coast. Statoil requested a commercial lease for its Hywind Maine project, which will have four turbines with 12 megawatts of capacity about 12 nautical miles (22 kilometers) from shore, the U.S. Interior Department said today in a statement. The agency has awarded only one commercial lease for offshore wind development, for the Cape Wind project in Massachusetts’s Nantucket Sound, which has been in development for a decade and hasn’t begun construction. The Obama administration is seeking to accelerate the review of renewable- energy projects on the outer continental shelf and is considering proposals for offshore wind farms in 16 states on the Atlantic and Pacific coasts, all using standard turbines. “This is the first time that this innovative floating technology is being considered for development in deeper waters offshore our coasts,” David Hayes, deputy secretary of the Interior, said in the statement. The agency is also evaluating proposals for undersea transmission lines that may connect 7 gigawatts of offshore wind farms in the mid-Atlantic. The Interior Department has begun an environmental review of the proposed area and also will determine whether there’s competitive interest from other developers. The review will be completed faster if Statoil, based in Stavanger, Norway, is the only company planning offshore wind farms in the area, according to the statement. http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-08-09/statoil-seeks-u-s-lease-for-floating-wind-farm-off-maine-coast.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344573663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344573835000-4</Id><Topic><Title>despicable</Title><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344475317000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 21:21:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every time you see the Fox News-induced statement "the rich pay more taxes", perpetuated by the idiot Stephen Moore, the more I'm convinced that the statement "the liberal media" is also a lie. Its all-too-convenient for right-wingers to confuse the incidence of a tax with the burden of a tax. "Liberals" say this the rich pay more tax because the rich earn a larger share of income. What does this means Liberals state facts? I don't want this fact introduced into my slanted argument?</Msg><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1344573835000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:43:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344603220000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Buy And Hold Cannot Die, XOM</Title><Username>combslang487</Username><Timestamp>1344599173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 07:46:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you invest, you will have a financial investment involved. That in of itself, will encourage you to discover more about the stock market and investing in general. Through that new found interest, your knowledge will grow and so will your investment. Initiative is the mother of experience.</Msg><Username>patriciashaffer374</Username><Timestamp>1344603220000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 08:53:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344605766000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Buy And Hold Cannot Die, XOM</Title><Username>combslang487</Username><Timestamp>1344599173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 07:46:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for all your supports and views.It would bring back my confidence i would like to share my money with this organisition.</Msg><Username>wolfmorrow355</Username><Timestamp>1344605766000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:36:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344609572000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Buy And Hold Cannot Die, XOM</Title><Username>combslang487</Username><Timestamp>1344599173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 07:46:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last year was awsome for my financial advisitory;Thanks to you guys who really....</Msg><Username>floydosborne900</Username><Timestamp>1344609572000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 10:39:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344611848000-8</Id><Title>This is due for a correction. Highs on Bollinger Bands</Title><Msg>Cramer says to sell.</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1344611848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344611924000-9</Id><Title>If CF is down 6 from highs, Corn up 50%, this shud b down 3</Title><Msg>points.</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1344611924000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:18:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344613421000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Buy And Hold Cannot Die, XOM</Title><Username>combslang487</Username><Timestamp>1344599173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 07:46:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good article. Having the facts is the first step to making money.</Msg><Username>mooremarlin255</Username><Timestamp>1344613421000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344621435000-11</Id><Title>UN urges US to cut ethanol production</Title><Msg>UN urges US to cut ethanol production By Javier Blas and Gregory Meyer, FT com August 10, 2012 -- Updated 0124 GMT (0924 HKT) (Financial Times) -- The UN has called for an immediate suspension of government-mandated US ethanol production, adding to pressure on Barack Obama to address the food-versus-fuel debate in the run-up to presidential elections. Most US ethanol is made from corn. The dispute over ethanol promotion pits states such as Iowa that benefit from higher corn prices -- and in some cases are swing states in the election -- against livestock-raising states such as Texas that are helped by lower corn prices. The UN intervention will be seized upon by state governors, lawmakers and the meat and livestock industry, who have expressed alarm at surging prices for corn. Members of the Group of 20 leading economies -- including France, India and China -- have already expressed concern about the US ethanol policy. The US is poised to divert around 40 per cent of its corn into ethanol because of the Congress-enacted mandate despite "huge damage" to the crop because of the worst drought in at least half a century, José Graziano da Silva, director-general of the UN's Food and Agriculture Organisation, warned. "An immediate, temporary suspension of that [ethanol] mandate would give some respite to the market and allow more of the crop to be channelled towards food and feed uses," he wrote in an opinion piece in the Financial Times. CNNMoney: U.S. drought drives up food prices worldwide However, some analysts argue such a suspension could have a lower impact on food prices than expected. Even disregarding the mandate, US refiners need billions of gallons of ethanol to meet environmental specifications for their gasoline. Moreover, ethanol is now a huge component of global energy supplies and the suspension of the mandate could push up oil prices. Tom Vilsack, US agriculture secretary, raised doubts about the impact of waiving the ethanol mandate, arguing that the US biofuel industry had reduced petrol prices and created jobs. In addition, high corn prices were already curbing ethanol production, he said. Adjusting the mandate "may not do what some people think it will do", he told the Financial Times in an interview. Mr Vilsack, a former Iowa governor, also cited "fairly high" thresholds for a waiver, including serious economic harm to a region. "It's not going to be an easy decision, clearly, but I think you have to look at this thing more broadly than some have looked at it," he said. Amid worries about a food shortage this year, Mr Graziano da Silva said the situation was "precarious" but was not yet a crisis. He added: "Risks are high and the wrong responses to the current situation could create" a crisis. Corn, soyabean and wheat prices have surged between 50 and 30 per cent since June after the US endured the hottest July since temperature records began 117 years ago. The US Midwest farmbelt has also seen little rain for months. http://edition.cnn.com/2012/08/09/business/un-us-ethanol/index.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344621435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:57:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344621445000-12</Id><Topic><Title>UN urges US to cut ethanol production</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344621435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The world is braced for a repeat of the 2007-2008 food crisis as the worst US drought in 50 years pushes up the prices of staple commodities Corn prices surged on Thursday within striking distance of their all-time record as traders bet that the US Department of Agriculture will reveal a huge drop in the country's crop production in a report on Friday. As America exports nearly half the world's corn, a third of the world's soyabeans and up to a fifth of the world's wheat, changes in US supply have a significant impact on global agricultural markets. "With world prices of cereals rising, the competition between the food, feed and fuel sectors for crops ... is likely to intensify," Mr Graziano da Silva said. A coalition of beef, pork, chicken and dairy producers petitioned the US Environmental Protection Agency last month to waive the ethanol mandate in response to rising corn prices. US lawmakers in the House and Senate, many representing states with large poultry and livestock operations, have also lobbied the EPA. Officials and lobbyists said several governors planned to join lawmakers next week petitioning the EPA, triggering a 90-day legal process that will force the Obama administration to rule whether to waive the ethanol mandate. The EPA in 2008 denied a waiver request from the state of Texas, the nation's biggest cattle producer. But hostility towards corn-made ethanol has grown since then and US lawmakers have already cut billion of dollars in subsidies to the sector.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344621445000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344621757000-13</Id><Title>Convert Richmond refinery to biocrude</Title><Msg>Convert Richmond refinery to biocrude Elizabeth Barrett Published 6:08 p.m., Thursday, August 9, 2012 Comments (5) The Chevron oil refinery in Richmond on San Francisco Bay opened in 1902, before there was a dense population surrounding it. It is incredibly dangerous to have an oil refinery in the middle of an urban area, and any new refinery today would be built far from a dense population. No new refineries have been built in the United States since 1976, because they are an environmental nightmare. Oil refineries are hazardous and carry with them a risk of chemical spills and explosions, which are extremely detrimental to human beings and ecosystems. According to a filing with the California Emergency Management Agency, sulfuric acid and nitrogen dioxide were released during the recent Richmond accident. Sulfuric acid "can cause severe lung damage with a life-threatening accumulation of fluid" (pulmonary edema), and "long term lung damage may result from a severe short term exposure," according to the Canadian Center for Occupational Health and Safety. The federal EPA says nitrogen dioxide can "irritate the lungs and lower resistance to respiratory infections." Fossil fuel should not be refined at any of the facilities in the Bay Area, as the recent fire in Richmond reminds us. The many refineries around the urban Bay Area should be closed or converted into biocrude refineries for clean, renewable plant fuel. Biocrude, from algae or other plant sources, can be refined just like petrocrude in existing facilities to produce the gasoline, diesel fuel, aviation fuel and lubricants made at the Richmond refinery. The algae can be grown in the bay, or in other ways nearby, without needing to ship it into the area, risking oil spills as we do now. The big oil corporations have been investing heavily in research and development of algae and other biofuels as a hedge against future shortages or stricter environmental regulation. Chevron's refinery is Richmond's largest private-sector employer, and the plant now has shut down all production because of the fire. Any future permit for it or the other area refineries should be conditioned on converting the facilities to pure biofuel in the near term. Give them a use permit for pure biocrude processing, and put an end to the damaging production of petroleum products on San Francisco Bay. Elizabeth Barrett of Berkeley is a mediator and facilitator with a focus in public international law, environmental law and conflict resolution. http://www.sfgate.com/opinion/openforum/article/Convert-Richmond-refinery-to-biocrude-3777111.php</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344621757000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344621996000-14</Id><Title>Biodiesel Tax Credit Included in Finance Committee Package</Title><Msg>Biodiesel Tax Credit Included in Finance Committee Package USAgNet - 08/10/2012 Prior to recessing for August, the Senate Finance Committee, on a 19-5 vote, passed a tax extenders package that included a retroactive two-year extension of the $1-per-gallon biodiesel tax credit. The tax extenders package carries a cost of over $200 billion and faces an uncertain future in the full Senate and the House. It is possible that the tax extenders could be included in the large package that is expected in the post-election lame duck session. The main focus of the lame duck session will be the looming expiration of the Bush tax cuts and the political impasse over whether to extend the tax cuts for all income levels or limit the extension of the lower rates to those at certain income levels. The estate tax and Alternative Minimum Tax are also expected to be addressed in the year-end package. http://www.wisconsinagconnection.com/story-national.php?Id=1794&amp;yr=2012</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344621996000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344627254000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report August 9, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344523578000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:46:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weekly U.S. Coal Production Data for week ended August 04, 2012 Release Date: August 09, 2012 http://www.eia.gov/coal/production/weekly/tables/weekly_production.cfm http://www.eia.gov/coal/production/weekly/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344627254000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344629972000-16</Id><Title>Technicals for 1,3,6,12 months are 84 to 88.50</Title><Msg>on Bollinger Bands</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1344629972000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344631353000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Buy And Hold Cannot Die, XOM</Title><Username>combslang487</Username><Timestamp>1344599173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 07:46:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It definitely exceeded my expectations.</Msg><Username>paulmccarthy817</Username><Timestamp>1344631353000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344631405000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Buy And Hold Cannot Die, XOM</Title><Username>combslang487</Username><Timestamp>1344599173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 07:46:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tom can you tell me where you found the sec reports that you got this info from.</Msg><Username>paulmccarthy817</Username><Timestamp>1344631405000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344635017000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Technical Chart Shows Upside on Exxon Mobil Corporation</Title><Username>moonpanton</Username><Timestamp>1344624556000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:49:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Yahoo Message Board Exclusive.</Msg><Username>still_my_dime</Username><Timestamp>1344635017000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344643339000-20</Id><Title>Gas prices spike in U.S.; refinery problems cited</Title><Msg>Gas prices spike in U.S.; refinery problems cited By ASSOCIATED PRESS | 8/10/12 2:47 PM EDT NEW YORK — A surprise surge in gasoline prices is taking some of the fun out of summer. The national average for a gallon of gas at the pump has climbed to $3.67, a rise of 34 cents since July 1. An increase in crude oil prices and problems with refineries and pipelines in the West Coast and Midwest, including a fire in California, are mostly to blame. Analysts don't expect gas prices to get as high as they did in April, when 10 states passed $4 a gallon and the U.S. average topped out at $3.94. But this is still unwelcome news in this sluggish economy, since any extra money that goes to fill gas tanks doesn't get spent on movies and dinners out. The rising prices could also put pressure on President Barack Obama in the heat of his re-election campaign. When Phil Van Schepen recently went to fill up his dry-cleaning delivery van in Coon Rapids, Minn., he found a Post-it note a driver before him had placed on the pump faulting Obama for high gasoline prices. "It's a reminder of his energy policies overall, which I don't agree with," said Van Schepen, who buys about 100 gallons a week and finds he is spending about $40 more than he did in early July. Still, he said the Post-it "was a bit much" because the president isn't responsible for gasoline prices. Analysts and economists agree, saying prices for crude oil and wholesale gasoline are set on financial exchanges around the world based on supply and demand and expectations about how those factors may change. The price at the pump in the U.S. fell more than 60 cents per gallon during the spring as the global economy slowed and turmoil in the Middle East seemed to subside. But crude oil is climbing again, rising to $94 a barrel from a low of $78 in late June. Production outages in South Sudan and the North Sea, Western sanctions that have cut the flow of Iranian oil, Iran's threat to block tankers passing through the vital Strait of Hormuz, and fears that the violence in Syria could escalate into a wider regional conflict have driven up oil prices. Seasonal factors are also sending pump prices higher. Gas usually costs more in the late spring and summer because refiners have to make more expensive blends of gasoline to meet clean air rules and because the summer driving season boosts demand. In the past few weeks, pipelines serving Wisconsin and Illinois ruptured, refineries were shut down unexpectedly because of equipment problems in Illinois and Indiana, and a blaze broke out at a refinery in Richmond, Calif. http://www.politico.com/news/stories/0812/79567.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344643339000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344643349000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Gas prices spike in U.S.; refinery problems cited</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344643339000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:02:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gasoline prices shot up more than 50 cents in the span of a month in Indiana, Vermont, Illinois, Ohio, Kentucky, Michigan and Wisconsin. And California drivers have seen gas climb 13 cents since the fire Monday. Motorists in many cities there are paying well over $4. Drivers in 20 states, including the possible White House battleground states of Colorado, Iowa, Nevada, Ohio and Wisconsin, are paying more for gasoline this year than they did last year, and the list will probably soon include Virginia and North Carolina, said Tom Kloza, chief oil analyst at the Oil Price Information Service. The national average a year ago was $3.64. "If you are paying more than in the past, it does have the potential to hurt the president," Kloza said. Economists said the price bump probably won't have much of an effect on economic growth, at least not yet. The extra 34 cents a gallon translates to $33 per month for a typical household. Prices could go higher if Middle East tensions rise, more refinery problems emerge or hurricanes in the Gulf of Mexico force oil drillers or refiners to shut down. The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration this week said this could be a more active hurricane season than previously thought. But analysts say that without those disruptions, gasoline will probably begin dropping after Labor Day as refiners switch to cheaper blends and drivers hit the road less often. That means voters could be going to the polls as prices are falling.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344643349000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344644038000-22</Id><Title>Biofuels industry prepares message for Obama's Iowa visit</Title><Msg>Biofuels industry prepares message for Obama's Iowa visit By Zack Colman - 08/10/12 02:20 PM ET The biofuels industry is planning a corn ethanol defense strategy for President Obama’s trip to Iowa next week following disappointing corn yield estimates released Friday. Agriculture Department predictions for corn supplies came in lower than expected in its biannual review. The 123.4 bushels per acre yield projected Friday is the lowest since 1995, and the anticipated 10.78 billion bushel haul would be the lowest since 2006. Monte Shaw, executive director with the Iowa Renewable Fuels Association (RFA), said his group will be out in front of the renewable fuel standard (RFS) issue when Obama comes to town. "Our goal is to see where we can put in some factual information," Shaw told E2-Wire on Friday. He said enough flexibility exists in the RFS to mitigate price concerns from low corn yields. That Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) rule requires refiners to blend 13.2 billion gallons of corn ethanol into conventional fuel this year. Livestock groups have said the RFS has exacerbated the low corn yields caused by the drought, in turn driving up costs for feed that will translate into pricier beef and poultry. The Obama campaign likely will harp on the wind production tax credit (PTC) that GOP White House challenger Mitt Romney wants to end as scheduled on Dec. 31. That credit, which pays 2.2 cents for every kilowatt-hour of wind production, is a key economic incentive for the Iowa wind industry. But with Iowa being in the heart of corn country, Shaw said, the RFS could surface during Obama’s visit. The Iowa RFA has conducted an ongoing biofuels messaging campaign since the state’s January presidential caucus. Matt Hartwig, a spokesman with the national RFA, said livestock groups and environmentalists will use the Agriculture report to criticize the RFS. “Enviros and ranchers have to stir the pot because they know many of the claims they are making don’t hold water,” Hartwig said in an email to E2-Wire on Friday. “The drought has been hard on all of agriculture. But it shouldn’t be exploited in search of temporary monetary gains that won’t materialize in the first place. Cooler heads will prevail in this debate." Representatives from the National Cattlemen’s Beef Association as well as the Environmental Working Group said they had no plans to press the RFS issue during Obama’s Iowa visit. "I think we made our position very clear with the petition we sent to" EPA Administrator Lisa Jackson, National Cattlemen's Beef Association Vice President of Governmental Affairs Colin Woodall told E2-Wire on Friday. He was referring to a request livestock groups sent Jackson last month urging her to consider waiving the RFS. Hartwig noted Obama and Agriculture Secretary Tom Vilsack “have been strong advocates of renewable fuels.” Vilsack reiterated administration support for the RFS at a Friday conference held by the American Coalition for Ethanol in Omaha, Neb. Ethanol producers have already cut back in response to high corn prices, which Shaw said means the RFS impact on corn supplies is overstated. Biofuels industry groups also have maintained that ethanol stockpiles and credits from overproduction in previous years will reduce the amount of production needed to meet the RFS this year. The corn estimates came in at about where commodities traders had anticipated, Shaw said. "We are going to approach this on a fact basis, and the facts are good for us," Shaw said. http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/243117-biofuels-industry-prepares-for-attack-during-obama-iowa-visit</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344644038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>