<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349412587894-1</Id><Title>South Korea team converts sewage sludge to biodiesel</Title><Msg>South Korea team converts sewage sludge to biodiesel Jim Lane | October 4, 2012 In South Korea, a team at the Research Institute of Industrial Science and Technology has developed a process to convert sewage sludge into biodiesel, which they say reduces the extraction cost for lipids to as low as $0.03 per liter. The team utilized a heat-based, rather than catalysis-based process for extraction, to overcome the problems associated with impurities in the feedstock causing interference with catalysis, which had resulted in lower yields from the traditional process. biofuelsdigest</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349412587894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 00:49:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349413299994-2</Id><Title>Debunking Romney’s $90 Billion Lie</Title><Msg>Debunking Romney’s $90 Billion Lie October 4, 2012 By Zachary Shahan 3 Comments</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349413299994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 01:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349414012708-3</Id><Topic><Title>wahlee and maxipad</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1349345349644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 06:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is needed is a customized oven just for them two! There is no place for commie #$%$ like that in these United States of America!</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1349414012708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 01:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349414770812-4</Id><Topic><Title>obama got his #$%$ handed to him and the media talks about Romney's lies - no worries about Obama's broken promises.</Title><Username>abbeysmaster</Username><Timestamp>1349392348662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "media" are a bunch of liberal commie skummbags! They cannot hide what millions and millions of folks saw and heard! Its like trying to hide the sun with your hands on a bright sunny day!!! Completely laughable!!!!!</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1349414770812</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 01:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349430813339-5</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking Romney’s $90 Billion Lie</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349413299994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 01:01:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are either f--ked up or a commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1349430813339</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 05:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349430845856-6</Id><Topic><Title>South Korea team converts sewage sludge to biodiesel</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349412587894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 00:49:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1349430845856</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 05:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349431159130-7</Id><Topic><Title>REAL Men Bet with INTRADE</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1349404417308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:33:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba finished and will go to jail for treason.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1349431159130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 05:59:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349443263299-8</Id><Title>Low Carbon Fuel Standards Will Drive Gas Prices Higher</Title><Msg>Low Carbon Fuel Standards Will Drive Gas Prices Higher Nicolas Loris October 4, 2012 at 3:33 pm The national average of gasoline is $3.78 per gallon, with some drivers experiencing a price of more than $4 per gallon. The price at the pump, up nearly 40 cents from a year ago, has faded out of the political limelight but remains a top concern for American families on tight budgets. One policy proposal that will only drive prices higher is the implementation of a low carbon fuel standard. A low carbon fuel standard (LCFS) aims to reduce greenhouse gas emissions by reducing the carbon intensity of fossil fuels. In effect, an LCFS would discourage the use of gasoline, diesel, and home heating oil to promote the use of biofuels, natural gas, propane, and electricity. For instance, California’s adoption of an LCFS requires a 10 percent reduction in carbon intensity—below 2010 levels of emissions—by 2020. Oregon and Washington developed an LCFS over the past few years, and 11 northeastern states have discussed adopting a standard led by the Northeast States for Coordinated Air Use Management (NESCAUM). Low carbon fuel standards contain a number of problems. First and foremost, they will drive up gas prices and hit particularly hard the families in the northeast who are dependent on home heating oil. Higher transportation fuel costs mean higher sticker prices for all goods and services, so American consumers are hit once again. The result is reduced consumer demand and a slower economy. We already have policies in place to promote alternative fuels, such as the federal renewable fuels standard, which is intended to produce 36 billion gallons of ethanol by 2022. The problems with the ethanol mandate demonstrate the inability of the government to determine what fuel types will be economically viable. Cellulosic ethanol, made primarily from non-food sources such as wood chips, switchgrass, or corn stover, is not commercially viable. Yet the 2007 Energy Independence and Security Act (EISA) mandated that 250 million gallons come from cellulosic ethanol in 2011, increasing to 500 million gallons for this year. Thus far, zero gallons have been produced, because no companies have been able to produce commercially viable cellulosic ethanol. As a result, refiners had to pay more than $6 million in waiver credits or surcharges to comply with the Environmental Protection Agency’s (EPA) minimum volume requirements. Undoubtedly, refiners pass these costs on to the consumers. In other words, the federal government’s failure to pick an affordable gasoline alternative is so epic that refiners would lose less money paying a $6 million fine than actually producing a product for which there is a guaranteed market. Further, we have generous tax credit incentives for the production and consumption of other alternative fuel types, like electric vehicles. Yes, we have oil subsidies as well, but they are nowhere near the generosity that President Obama claims they are. Low carbon fuel standards could also prevent access to Canadian tar sands oil, which is the second-largest known reserve of oil in the world and could increase the role Canada plays in supplying U.S. refineries with safe, secure oil. As a Charles River Associates study points out: Although Canadian oil sands-derived crudes are no more carbon intensive than many conventional crudes processed in the U.S., the California LCFS and some other LCFS proposals attempt to account for the carbon emissions that are created during the processing of Canadian oil sands into synthetic crude oil or Diluted Bitumen without giving credit for local greenhouse gas emissions controls in Canada. This type of adjustment raises a complex set of issues including;[sic] emissions from extracting and transporting various types of internationally traded crudes, energy security, and the implications of NAFTA and WTO rules. Complications of calculating carbon intensity are occurring with corn-based ethanol, which demonstrates the arbitrariness of these low carbon standards. A low carbon fuel standard is an “all economic pain, no environmental gain” policy that will drive up prices at the pump and make no discernible difference on the earth’s temperature. The simple reality is that we need to remove the market distortions (subsidies, mandates, low carbon fuel standards) to allow the best technologies and most affordable, efficient sources of energy meet America’s fuel demands. heritage</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349443263299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349444493573-9</Id><Topic><Title>No Breakthroughs Necessary: 95 Percent Renewable Energy Possible By 2050</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349198612229</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 13:23:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mammoth Offshore Turbine Gains a Megawatt POSTED BY: Dave Levitan / Wed, October 03, 2012 We've reported before on the trend to massively upsize offshore wind turbines, and the Vestas V164 was slated to become the first 7-megawatt giant in the next couple of years. Vestas now says the timeline is still intact to roll out the V164, but it won't be 7 MW. Instead, improvements to the control system will up the output to a staggering 8 MW. That means a single turbine would be capable of powering more than 2000 homes, and large offshore wind farms of them would have truly massive capacities. Interestingly, this increase (nearly 15 percent) in capacity comes without increasing the turbine's dimensions. "As we progressed in the technology it was clear that an 8-MW version of the turbine will offer lower cost of energy and at the same time keep the reliability and structural integrity of the turbine unchanged," Vestas's executive VP and chief technology officer Anders Vedel said in a press release. With its massive 80-meter blades—substantially longer than the wingspan of a 747—the V164 was already plenty big. The company plans on testing the first of those blades in the first quarter of 2013 at a U.K. facility on the Isle of Wight. The drivetrain will be tested at a different facility in Denmark, and the first full turbine is expected to be installed in 2014 at Oesterild, Denmark. Other companies, including Sinovel and GE, are working on or producing turbines in the 6-MW range, but no other offshore entry approaches the 8-MW giant. There is one huge onshore turbine, Enercon's 7.5 MW E126, but there is a general consensus that such sizes are best suited to spots away from land. With European offshore wind efforts flying ahead as usual, and hints that the United States might finally start building up an offshore wind industry, these massive hulks will likely be looming over the waves all around the world within a couple of years. Image and video via Vestas ieee url at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349444493573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349446748489-10</Id><Title>Analysis: Jobs report provides political boost for Obama</Title><Msg>Analysis: Jobs report provides political boost for Obama Richard Wolf, USA TODAY 33 Comment The Labor Department's report that unemployment has fallen below 8% for the first time since January 2009 is sure to provide a needed political boost for President Obama. 10:03AM EST October 5. 2012 - For President Obama, the first national unemployment rate to fall below 8% during his presidency couldn't come at a better time. The Labor Department's announcement this morning that the economy gained 114,000 jobs in September and the jobless rate fell from 8.1% to 7.8% represents a big, if temporary, political boost for a president suddenly struggling to overcome a poor performance in the first nationally televised debate. What's more, Obama can even boast that jobs numbers for July and August were better than previously announced. In August, for instance, 142,000 jobs were created, not the 96,000 announced last month. STORY: September unemployment rate drops to 7.8% WALL STREET: Stocks rally on drop in jobless rate to 7.8% "This month's jobs report shows the economy is finally beginning to build some momentum, and this news could not come at a better time for the president," said Thea Lee, deputy chief of staff at the AFL-CIO. "People are coming back into the labor force, and employers are showing some confidence." The White House was customarily cautious in heralding the new jobs figures. "While there is more work that remains to be done, today's employment report provides further evidence that the U.S. economy is continuing to heal from the wounds inflicted by the worst downturn since the Great Depression," said Alan Krueger, chairman of the Council of Economic Advisors. "It is critical that we continue the policies that are building an economy that works for the middle class." Conservatives immediately sought to throw cold water on the upbeat report. Republican nominee Mitt Romney, coming off a strong debate performance and seeking to keep the momentum on his side, noted the number of new jobs got smaller each month during the summer, signifying a downward trend. "This is not what a real recovery looks like," Romney said in a statement. "We created fewer jobs in September than in August,and fewer jobs in August than in July, and we've lost over 600,000 manufacturing jobs since President Obama took office. If not for all the people who have simply dropped out of the labor force, the real unemployment rate would be closer to 11%." GOP REACTION:Republicans see no reason to cheer jobs report The latest numbers are sure to produce a new spate of TV ads. Obama can claim 31 consecutive months of private-sector job growth and an unemployment rate that has dropped to levels not seen since he came into office in January 2009. Romney can say 12.1 million Americans remain out of work -- nearly twice that if those who are underemployed or have stopped looking for jobs are included. The jobs numbers can make or break a presidential campaign -- or, at least, a candidate's momentum. A stagnant unemployment rate in the 7.5% range helped doom Gerald Ford in 1976, Jimmy Carter in 1980 and George H.W. Bush in 1992. Obama's numbers have been worse since his first full month in office, ranging from 8.1% to 10%. He is likely to say on the campaign trail that the latest report continues a pattern of job growth following his first year in office, a period that has seen more than 5 million private-sector jobs created. The president will have one last chance to get further below 8% on Nov. 2, four days before the election, when figures for October and revisions for earlier months are released. By then, however, most voters' minds will have been made up, in part based on their own employment or financial situation. In fact, most economists and political analysts say voters' minds generally aren't swayed by reports or statistics, but by how they feel about the economy and how it affects their families. That sentiment gets firmed up by early summer, they say. Douglas Holtz-Eakin, former Congressional Budget Office director and top economic adviser to John McCain's presidential campaign in 2008, said the 7.8% jobless rate is based on a "statistical anomaly" -- an unusually high estimate of new jobs from the Labor Department's household survey. "The White House will pounce on this," he said. "Being lucky is better than being good." The Labor Department also revised its jobs figures for the previous two months. In all, it said 86,000 more jobs were created in those two months than previously stated. The report comes less than 36 hours after Romney's strong performance and Obama's lackluster one in the first presidential debate. During the debate, Romney pledged again to create 12 million new jobs in the next four years, saying, "My priority is putting people back to work in America." He followed that up with a new TV ad Thursday morning that claimed his energy plan would reap more than 3 million, his tax plan another 7 million, and the remainder from trade policies and job training. Obama acknowledged in the debate that the nation had been through a painful period but said, "We've begun to fight our way back." On the campaign trail Thursday, he vowed to create 1 million new manufacturing jobs and hundreds of thousands in the green energy business. usatoday</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349446748489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 10:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349447192818-11</Id><Title>Jobs Report Another Democrat Lie</Title><Msg>anyone with an IQ greater than 80 knows the job report number is a fabrication and the real unemployemnt rate is actually greater than 15%. Every month for the last 40 months the Democrap controlled government adjusts the unemployemnt rate up after initially reporting it and the Democrap controlled press does not report the adjustment. The under 8% report this month proves just how desperate the Democraps in continually lying to the public t keep their "Dear Leader" in power.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1349447192818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349450912243-12</Id><Title>Our "Free" Press?</Title><Msg>Would anyone care to hazzard a reasonable guess as to why we have become so polarized and, the (so-called) free press looks the other way when reporting the facts? It's as if "they" are willing to sacrifice America to prove a historical negative. The truth is lost in a never-ending wave of biased slant and the very people that "buy in" are the very people that will suffer the most as a result. What could possibly motivate the media to promote and encourage our demise? I don't intend this to be political, one way or the other but, who wins when you cover-up the truth?</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1349450912243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349452509674-13</Id><Topic><Title>Great Info On XOM... Check It!</Title><Username>berniceblevins964</Username><Timestamp>1349442709276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am waiting for. Thanks for giving out this article for free.</Msg><Username>romanroman79</Username><Timestamp>1349452509674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349453181761-14</Id><Topic><Title>Where's your money, Romney believers ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1349398373610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:52:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just your or my money will change hands. Any takers yet ?????????????? BETTER NOT WASTE YOUR MONEY......ROMNEY WILL WIN....YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY WANT A MUSLIM THAT IS NOT A CITIZEN TO LEAD OUR COUNTRY. OBAMA ALREADY IS BANKRUPTING THIS COUNTRY. I'M SURE MOST PEOPLE FEEL AS I DO, I WANT AN AMERICAN WITH A LOVE OF OUR FREEDOMS TO LEAD US.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1349453181761</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 12:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349457630768-15</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like someone is taking a large position today</Msg><Username>louie.maxfield</Username><Timestamp>1349457630768</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 13:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349459292207-16</Id><Title>Rumor the fix is in on RENN 3 or 4 bagger in Oct look at options read rumors why below</Title><Msg>Options seem to be backing these rumors up. 1.Same exact market makers pushing around everyone else in renn just like they did in bidu pre explosion! 2.Same exact underwriters! 3.Same extreme manipulation, 28-4 after RENN IPO, they slammed bidu down 1st 2 years straight also 4. Same pattern of you go against these guys at all and you lose guaranteed! Now they are starting to go higher with RENN, soon they all pounce on prey at once! 5. Rumors, big names, and Billionaire chatter and competition between at least 3 parties regarding RENN 6. The richest man in the entire country of China on your board of directors does not hurt. 7. Lastly 3 rumors 1. Ken Fischer taking a possible 5 million share position 2. At a live dinner event, CEO CHEN and the richest man in China gave a toast and said they will not rest or be happy till RENN has a mnimum of a 100 billion dollar marketcap! 3. At a seperate event a caterer to the TRIAD CHINESE MAFIA said they will run RENN to at least 60 themselves! The fireworks are suppose to start in Oct with a triple or 4 times the stock price! Options have been being bought as if this will indeed happen! I have a broker at Raymond James I went to college with, he says something is up with RENN because much of the trading is being hidden, they appear to be either making it look like it is coming from many different places or the buys really are.</Msg><Username>namfong43</Username><Timestamp>1349459292207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 13:48:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349459842333-17</Id><Title>You heard it here: Northern Gateway's dead</Title><Msg>You heard it here: Northern Gateway's dead Globe and Mail-11 hours ago The Northern Gateway pipeline that Enbridge proposes to build from Alberta’s bitumen oil to the Pacific coast of British Columbia is, for all intents and purposes, dead. Yes, regulatory hearings before the National Energy Board will continue until the NEB approves the project. And yes, Enbridge will keep pushing for it. And yes, the Harper government, which is so publicly committed to the project, will continue to extol its virtues as part of the need to get Canadian resources to Asia. ... theglobeandmail url at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349459842333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 13:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349460495181-18</Id><Title>EPA appeals decision that struck down new limits on air pollution</Title><Msg>EPA appeals decision that struck down new limits on air pollution By Ben Geman - 10/05/12 11:39 AM ET The Environmental Protection Agency is appealing a federal court decision that vacated a major regulation to curb soot- and smog-forming power plant emissions that cross state lines. Justice Department lawyers representing EPA are asking the full U.S. Court of Appeals for the D.C. Circuit to review the 2-1 August decision by a three-judge panel that nullified the agency’s Cross-State Air Pollution Rule. The rule, a cornerstone of the Obama administration’s air quality agenda, forces sulfur dioxide and nitrogen oxide emissions cuts from power plants in 28 states in the eastern half of the country. The Obama administration’s request Friday for review by a wider group of judges bashes the August ruling. “The panel’s decision upends the appropriate relationship of the judicial, legislative and executive branches of government by rewriting clear legislation, ignoring explicit statutory jurisdictional limits, and stepping into the realm of matters reserved by Congress and the courts to the technical expertise of administrative agencies,” the petition for “en banc” review states. The August decision that struck down the rule stated that the regulation had allowed EPA to “impose massive emissions reduction requirements on upwind states without regard to the limits imposed by the statutory text.” Click here for more on the decision that vacated the rule. EPA issued a statement Friday that says the appeal reflects its commitment to ensuring public health gains the rule is forecast to provide when phased-in. “EPA proposed a cost-effective and common-sense approach that would help states meet their Clean Air Act obligations to cut air pollution and meet air quality health standards, preventing more than 30,000 premature deaths and hundreds of thousands of illnesses each year. Our filing today signals our commitment to this goal,” the agency said. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349460495181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 14:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349461431812-19</Id><Topic><Title>obama got his #$%$ handed to him and the media talks about Romney's lies - no worries about Obama's broken promises.</Title><Username>abbeysmaster</Username><Timestamp>1349392348662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought that what was not said was much more telling. The cost of war, NDAA, Eric Holder, fast &amp; furious, MFGlobal, Jon Corzine, PFGBest, Glass Steagle (sp?), mortgage fraud (by banks). Why Jon Corzine / MFGlobal or Eric Holder / fast and furious, either one of these should have been enough for Romney to send Obama scurrying off stage like a kid caught next to the cookie jar with chocolate chips melted in his hands.</Msg><Username>t_snacey</Username><Timestamp>1349461431812</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 14:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349462670122-20</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gooooooood.... position</Msg><Username>pattonjohnny51</Username><Timestamp>1349462670122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 14:44:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349466964265-21</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looking for information ... check the site.......................</Msg><Username>p_kime</Username><Timestamp>1349466964265</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349467258503-22</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looking for information ... check the site.......................</Msg><Username>p_kime</Username><Timestamp>1349467258503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 16:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349475927885-23</Id><Topic><Title>Romney, CO2 and 100 million deaths.</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1349451104447</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:31:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Posting on a subject that you know nothing about does not make it the truth. It only proves that you belive anything so long as it fits your agenda. The CO2 mendacity is nothing more than an excuse for redistribution. Do some research on motives and, examine your sources.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1349475927885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 18:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349476798243-24</Id><Topic><Title>obama got his #$%$ handed to him and the media talks about Romney's lies - no worries about Obama's broken promises.</Title><Username>abbeysmaster</Username><Timestamp>1349392348662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 19:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is easy enough to see that the media is willing to sacrifice the nation to promote a historical negative. Our "mainstream" media has NO journalistic qualities whatsoever.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1349476798243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 18:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349478003412-25</Id><Topic><Title>Romney, CO2 and 100 million deaths.</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1349451104447</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:31:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's just Wahleee with one of his numerous aliases. There is a picture of Wahleee in the dictionary by the definition of "looney".</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1349478003412</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:00:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349478503636-26</Id><Title>ExxonMobil returns fire at Obama</Title><Msg>ExxonMobil returns fire at Obama By Ben Geman - 10/05/12 05:30 PM ET ExxonMobil is returning fire after President Obama singled out the oil giant in Wednesday’s debate when calling for an end to billions of dollars in industry tax breaks. “To hear President Barack Obama in last night’s first presidential debate, you would think he was running against ExxonMobil this November given his tendency to single us out for criticism,” wrote Ken Cohen, an Exxon executive, on the company’s blog Thursday. He cited other instances in which Obama has cited Exxon, the world’s largest publicly traded oil company, when touting proposals to raise taxes on an industry that the president says does not need the incentives. “Because we’ve been pulled into this debate, I feel like asking the moderator to let me respond with several points,” said Cohen, the company’s vice president of public and government affairs. Obama threw his latest jab at Exxon during Wednesday night’s debate with Mitt Romney, citing industry tax breaks among the deductions that he said should be jettisoned to help curb the deficit. “The oil industry gets $4 billion a year in corporate welfare,” Obama said. “Now, does anybody think that ExxonMobil needs some extra money when they're making money every time you go to the pump? Why wouldn't we want to eliminate that?” Cohen’s post in defense of the industry’s tax incentives calls the “corporate welfare” claim inaccurate, and argues in favor of the oil industry’s ability to claim a lucrative deduction, the so-called Section 199 deduction, on domestic manufacturing income. Cohen noted it’s among the benefits available to “virtually all” manufacturers and producers, and that the deduction for oil producers is smaller than what’s available to other industries. The 2008 Wall Street bailout bill capped the industry’s deduction at a lower level. “Keep in mind, too, that ExxonMobil’s U.S. tax expense amounts to more than $1 billion per month. In 2011, our total U.S. taxes of $12.3 billion exceeded our U.S. earnings by almost $3 billion, and our effective income tax rate in the U.S. was 31.4 percent — far higher than many critics have claimed,” Cohen writes. While Exxon returned fire at Obama, it was Romney who drew attention Wednesday when he said that oil industry tax breaks are “probably not going to survive” if the GOP nominee is able to reduce the overall corporate tax rate from 35 percent to 25 percent. Romney cited roughly $2.8 billion in annual benefits that would be “on the table” for removal. The GOP nominee's campaign noted that the figure stems from a 2011 Energy Information Administration report that tallied tax breaks and other federal aid to energy producers and consumers in fiscal 2010. That figure does not include the Section 199 deduction. The White House and Democrats have floated a number of plans to strip industry incentives. While some proposals would only target major integrated companies like Exxon, Chevron and Shell, the White House wants to raise roughly $40 billion over 10 years with a plan that would hit both “Big Oil” and, in some cases, independent producers. The White House plan would repeal the so-called percentage depletion allowance, which isn’t available to the big integrated companies, as well as repeal expensing of “intangible” drilling costs, which is fully available to independent companies and partially for the others. “Oil and gas subsidies are costly to the American taxpayer and do little to incentivize production or reduce energy prices,” the fiscal 2013 White House budget plan states. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349478503636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349480096645-27</Id><Title>The Strongest Argument For Renewable Energy Comes From The US Military</Title><Msg>The Strongest Argument For Renewable Energy Comes From The US Military Geoffrey Ingersoll|Sep. 25, 2012, 3:11 PM|6,274|19 It started with a simple directive: bring down the casualty numbers. At the time, Former Lt. Gen. Richard C. Zilmer was the commanding general of the most restive province of Iraq in 2006—al Anbar. And at the time, there was primarily one reason for the dramatic spike in American casualties: Fuel. It was in the months preceding "The Anbar Awakening," the grass roots movement that turned the tide of war in Iraq, and the Al Qaeda insurgency was fighting like a cornered animal to keep a grip on the region. As a result, Improvised Explosive Device casualties had skyrocketed. "What we saw in Anbar was the dramatic increase in use of IEDs, side attacks, inside of roads, buried IEDs, very destructive, even to uparmored humvees," said Zilmer. "So we started taking a hard look at everything we were doing to expose Marines to IED attacks." What Zilmer noticed when looking at graphs of the IED attacks was thick, red lines running along the Main Supply Routes, or MSRs, like veins along the province. Zilmer said many of the casualties were caused just from convoys moving place to place. "We had units all over Anbar, because that's what you do during counterinsurgency, you cover down on the enemy," said Zilmer. "You have to be able to supply those outbound areas. Mostly fuel, diesel, combustibles, (and there was bullets, bandages, and beans, but mostly) all that energy that was being consumed was drawing us out, the more energy you needed the more convoys you needed to sustain." So Zilmer issued what was called at the time a "Priority 1" rapid resource response: “(The Marine Corps must) augment our use of fossil fuels with renewable energy, such as photovoltaic solar panels and wind turbines, at our outlying bases. By reducing the need for [petroleum-based fuels], we can decrease the frequency of logistics convoys on the road, thereby reducing the danger to our Marines, soldiers, and sailors . . . . If this need is not met, operating forces will remain unnecessarily exposed to IED, RPG [rocket propelled grenade], and [small arms fire] threats and will continue to accrue preventable Level III and IV serious and grave casualties resulting from motor vehicle accidents and . . . attacks. Continued casualty accumulation exhibits potential to jeopardize mission success. In other words, the U.S. addiction to oil in regards to the military was threatening to lose the war in Iraq. This threat can be seen more recently in Pakistan, where the Coalition's 11-year long effort almost sputtered to a close because of convoy disputes and fuel tanker bombings. It seems as if Zilmer's warnings have gone the way of that oft mentioned tree in the woods. The US is currently dedicating massive resources to making sure the Strait of Hormuz remains open at all cost. In total, maintaining the flow of oil out of the Persian and Arabian Gulf costs the U.S. anywhere between $86 billion and $104 billion dollars a year (according to a 2009 Rand report); which doesn't seem that bad until it's compared to the only "credible" threat to that flow, Iran, which has a yearly defense budget of about $20 billion—that particular strategic cost benefit analysis expressed in one word: yikes. In other words, enemies can stop America's mega-multibillion dollar military machine with a handful of chump change (and America out there right this very second practicing in case they try). "Our analysis shows that if you close the straight of Hormuz for 30 days you'll bring the global economy to it's knees in 30 days," said Zilmer. Since retiring, Zilmer acknowledges how the addiction to fossil fuels has drawn the U.S. out not just on the battlefield, but into international conflict. "We have to start being honest about our presence in these regions. The deployments take us over there, and if you're a cynic, there are a couple of interests, clearly one of them is petroleum and we have this mortgage as the United states, to make sure the petroleum is flowing," said Zilmer. He went on to list a number of conflicts, starting with the Iraq war, that were ultimately initiated by America's dependence on fossil fuels. "Politically, I'm not a greenie, I'm not an advocate, I'm not an alarmist, this is strictly from a national security, military perspective," said Zilmer. "We've qualified how we or advance our argument - from a military perspective, lighter faster and more lethal on the battlefield, if we have a smaller footprint, if we if can lighten the load, inherently we're going to make us a fiercer fighting force." And Zilmer isn't alone. Once he issued that "Priority 1," he retired, and found himself a position with the Center for Naval Analyses and Public Research; and CNA, as it's exclusively called now, has issued four major papers about the effects of oil addiction and climate change on national security. All told, 10 other 4- and 3-star generals joined Zilmer in their latest paper, titled "A National Security Imperative to Reduce U.S. Oil Dependence." Among them is the former commandant of the Marine Corps, General James T. Conway. Conway had the distinction of leading a battalion during the legendary battle for Fallujah as well as leading the entire Marine Corps when it succeeded in the entire province. The chief finding of the paper, signed by all eleven generals, states simply "America’s dependence on oil constitutes a significant national security threat." The remaining three main points are as follows: A 30 percent reduction in our use of petroleum would significantly improve America's national security. America can achieve a significant portion of a 30 percent reduction through greater efficiency in how we use oil. There are many promising alternatives to oil as a transport fuel—some available today, others on the horizon. If managed properly, all of the most promising alternative fuels examined can lower overall national security risks rather than continuing America's over reliance on oil as a singular fuel source. There are, right now, several different initiatives within the military to initiate biofuels and renewable energy, but they do face considerable push back from firmly entrenched interests. (Even the incredibly on-the-ball outfit at Wired's Danger Room had to walk back a story of theirs that they based off an inaccurate report, filed by Congressmen using cherry picked information, for obvious, self-serving reasons.) "The bottom line is—energy from a national security perspective, holds us hostage as a nation. Now, the DoD has historically been an innovator—jet propulsion, gps, computers, the world wide web— a large forcing function to get all of our society and economy moving in particular directions," said Zilmer. But how does this get by Republicans in the House and the Senate, even so called Blue-Dog Democrats, who uniformly oppose, to put it lightly, any "investment" in new energy? Well that's where ZIlmer and the CNA crew don't get greedy. This is not about hugging trees, this is not about 'picking winners.' It's about maintaining U.S. supremacy, militarily and economically. So the language the advisers offer is simple, diversify the portfolio. "Half our trade deficit every year is made up of petroleum—see, in order to motivate congress, you have to articulate in dollars and cents. Along with not remaining hostage to unsavory partners that are out in the Middle Eastern region, we want to lead the world in this technology," said Zilmer. Americans did invent solar and wind energy, but are right now not leading the globe in their production. Leading the globe in these technologies, Zilmer indicated, will bring unexportable jobs to American shores. "From a national security perspective, we can insulate ourselves from any outside state influence in our energy if we can reduce dependence on fossil fuels by just 30 percent," said Zilmer, in conservative Republican pitch mode. "That requires diversifying the portfolio. No one thing we have right now contains the energy of a gallon of gas, but a couple different things, working in conjunction, that will do the trick." As for the lawmakers who cry only for domestic fossil fuel production, Zilmer had a simple response—"Sure, we can do that too, but the simple fact is these resources are finite. The development of renewables is happening right now, and we're not going to follow China or anybody, or else we'll be dependent on them." Zilmer said he and his constituents are always up on Capitol Hill, trying to start a grass roots movement, talking to Congressmen, especially Republicans, trying to convince them to break away from protecting entrenched industry. "[They] have to look at it like a corporation. Big businesses need to make independent, corporate decisions without being influenced by special interests. That's what the government needs to do when it's making decisions about these energies,'" said Zilmer. Zilmer emphasized that sequestration, or automatic across the board cuts, need to be looked at tactically, not arbitrarily, if the U.S. wants to save some of these burgeoning energy programs in the military. "That when you get all the smart guys in one room and say, 'okay, we've got a problem, so what do we get rid of in order to keep these," said Zilmer. He also noted, that the prevailing political sentiment, in the contemporary Washington landscape, is that the initiatives are "liberal" ideas. "That's why this needs to be bipartisan. We need a bipartisan effort on this to make sure it's legislation that transcends administrations," said Zilmer. Zilmer doesn't see it as "liberal vs. conservative," as much as it is safeguarding our military interests in the coming years, especially as climate change and population growth have an exponential effect on competition over dwindling resources. He said the barest mention of "climate change" in Congress instantly "brings force fields up." But as the extremes in climate begin to target the areas Americans typically get their domestic oil, then the U.S. will be "drawn out" even further into the Middle East to defend its interests. Then the argument to the naysayers is again, pretty simple, "Then that's what you want, 15 or 20 years from now, your sons and daughters are going to be out on fringes in the Middle East doing what we've been doing for thirty years." This last argument is an overt reminder that what initially turned Zilmer to this personal mission, one he shares with many of his contemporary, high-level military strategic leaders, what kicked this of for him and probably many of them was that simple directive, 6 years ago: bring down the casualty numbers. Author's note: The author of this piece was a U.S. Marine writer deployed to Anbar from June '06 to February '07, what many consider one of the bloodiest periods of the war. Among his first and last articles published as a Marine journalist were about servicemen lost during convoy operations to improvised explosive devices, carrying, among other things, fuel. businessinsider</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349480096645</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349480755593-28</Id><Topic><Title>Great Info On XOM... Check It!</Title><Username>berniceblevins964</Username><Timestamp>1349442709276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, I'm gonna hold for now and wait for positive news. What a good plan. I don't like being hasty. The data looks good.</Msg><Username>monroenicholson62</Username><Timestamp>1349480755593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349483028292-29</Id><Title>buy new car</Title><Msg>yes I'm going electric gas prices in california are a joke ---exxon is so greedy on are backs this has gone on to long-i will not take anymore.</Msg><Username>a.hudkins</Username><Timestamp>1349483028292</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349483175343-30</Id><Title>BPT pays big $1.82 Ex-Dividend Date 10/11/12</Title><Msg>Like dividends? Catch the run-up to x-div.</Msg><Username>borderlaw</Username><Timestamp>1349483175343</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:26:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349490164065-31</Id><Topic><Title>Where's your money, Romney believers ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1349398373610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:52:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't read very well. Why don't you back up your bully bluster and take the bets I offered you? And why don't you explain exactly why you are so racist?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349490164065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 22:22:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349490484351-32</Id><Topic><Title>buy new car</Title><Username>a.hudkins</Username><Timestamp>1349483028292</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 20:23:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can thank Obamao for the high gasoline prices. XOM has nothing to do with it.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349490484351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 22:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>