<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353924228426-1</Id><Topic><Title>Such a tiresome pack of losers...</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353894548615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:49:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Instead of giving me three thumbs down, whomever you are, why not express some well thought out reason why the democrats, why they had the opportunity to bring some sort of regulation to the commodities market to rid it of speculation and didn't?</Msg><Username>dogshitforbrains</Username><Timestamp>1353924228426</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 05:03:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353926405997-2</Id><Title>Petraeus Scandal Reveals Massive Islamic Infiltration In Obama Administration</Title><Msg>Petraeus Scandal Reveals Massive Islamic Infiltration In Obama Administration beforeitsnewsDOTcom/global-unrest/2012/11/petraeus-scandal-reveals-massive-islamic-infiltration-in-obama-administration-2447904DOThtml Read it before it is pulled!</Msg><Username>dogshitforbrains</Username><Timestamp>1353926405997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 05:40:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353927170760-3</Id><Title>Greedful Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Msg>Wahleee does that sometimes - pretends to have some sort of logic but when he tries to explain details you can tell his logic falters and all he can do is blame the GOP for something that a sane person knows is the Demoncraps fault. We will now see the Wahleee posting and greedful gone for a while. Wahleeee is entertaining with his insanity.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1353927170760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 05:52:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353958049413-4</Id><Title>EPA OKs Massachusetts offshore wind staging facility</Title><Msg>EPA OKs Massachusetts offshore wind staging facility A $100 million Marine Commerce Terminal in New Bedford, Mass., USA could be a key offshore-wind project-staging area for offshore wind turbines and blades. Posted on: 11/26/2012 Source: CompositesWorld New England Cable News (NECN) reported on Nov. 20 that the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) has approved a $100 million Marine Commerce Terminal in New Bedford, Mass., USA, that could be a key offshore-wind project-staging area. “The south terminal project holds the potential for the generation of jobs like nothing else that has materialized in this city in over a half-century,’’ New Bedford mayor Jonathan Mitchell said at a press event at the Bigelow Street boat ramp, just south of the planned 28-acre site, which will include seven acres of fill in the harbor. According to the report, the terminal, which will be able to handle ships up to 500 ft/152m long and giant shipments like railroad cars and industrial boilers, is being touted as a potential hub for staging construction of offshore wind projects like Cape Wind or others that may be built in Rhode Island Sound and areas south of Martha’s Vineyard and Nantucket. Wind turbine blades and towers and cables would be shipped to the pier and assembled there for delivery offshore. The report says that Cape Wind, however, has opened discussions with Rhode Island, fearing the New Bedford facility may not be open soon enough to accommodate what Cape Wind is now saying will be a 2014 construction start. Cape Wind has said it wants to use the New Bedford terminal as much as is feasible. The state has about $60 million of the $100 million cost lined up and authorized now, but several property owners in the area still need to agree to be bought out and relocated. Mitchell told NECN that he’s confident that even if offshore wind project Cape Wind — which has been mired in lawsuits for years, and which could lose the support of the federal production tax credit that is now set to expire Dec. 31 — does not happen, there are of other offshore wind projects that could make good use of the marine terminal. “This is where the wind is,” Mitchell says, noting that just south of New Bedford lie areas estimated to represent 25 percent of all practical U.S. near-shore wind generation territory. compositesworldDOTcom/news/epa-oks-massachusetts-offshore-wind-staging-facility</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353958049413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 14:27:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353959368769-5</Id><Title>What Buffett Is Missing in His Tax Plan</Title><Msg>The central premise of Warren Buffett's important op-ed in The New York Times today is that the rich pay a lower tax rate on their taxes than the middle class does. He calls for enacting a "Minimum Tax on the Wealthy" (aka the "Buffett Rule") that would apply a minimum 30 percent tax to those making $1 million or more a year, and 35 percent for incomes above $10 million. The rule, he writes, would "keep the ultrarich paying rates well below those incurred by people with income just a tiny fraction of ours." The trouble is, the rich as a group don't pay less than the middle class. Buffett talks about half of the country's 400 highest earners paying less than 20 percent. And he says a few "actually paid none." True enough. And that's an outrage to someone who pays the 25 percent or 35 percent official tax rate. But what Buffett doesn't mention is that, on average, very few Americans actually pay the official tax rate, due to deductions and credits. On average, everyone pays less. When it comes to what Americans actually pay, the high earners and "wealthy" still pay more than twice the rate as the middle class. The latest data from the IRS shows that people who make $1 million or more had an average tax rate of 20.4 percent in 2010. (Read more: The Millionaires Who Pay the Highest Tax Rate). Tax filers who earned $30,000 to $50,000 paid an average rate of 4.8 percent, while those who made between $50,000 and $100,000 paid 7.7 percent. Those making under $30,000 had a negative effective rate, meaning they paid no federal income taxes after deductions and credits. Put another way, millionaires pay a rate that's nearly three to four times the rate paid by the middle class. Even the super-rich, or those who make more than $10 million and rely more on investment income taxed at 15 percent, have an effective rate of 20.7 percent. "Very few people actually pay 35 percent," said Roberton Williams Senior Fellow of the non-partisan Tax Policy Center. Yes, there are some super-earners who pay less than some in the middle class. But they are the exception not the rule. According to data from the Tax Policy Center, there would be 603,000 Americans in 2015 who make $1 million or more. Only about a third of them would be subject to the Buffett Rule, which means that two thirds already pay more than 30 percent. Buffett's op-end implies that our tax system is regressive, that the rich pay less because of their power and lobbyist friends. The fact is, our tax system is progressive -- the wealthy pay a higher rate than the rest of America. This is not an argument for or against the Buffett Rule. There is surely symbolic value is making sure that everyone making $1 million pays more than the rest of America. But it is largely that -- symbolic.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353959368769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 14:49:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353963954115-6</Id><Topic><Title>What Buffett Is Missing in His Tax Plan</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353959368769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 14:49:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forget taxes for a moment. You could take everything (all assets) from each of the Forbes 400 and it would pay for our congressional waste and mismanagement for 8 weeks. Then do it again and again for 525 years and the national debt would be retired. We have a spending problem! Simple as that.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1353963954115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 16:05:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353972203034-7</Id><Topic><Title>Such a tiresome pack of losers...</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353894548615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:49:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have been saying "NO" to it,for the last four years,that's why they lost so badly in the last election, and will continue to lose until they can learn to say "Yes", it's best for the country,even if not for the Party.</Msg><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1353972203034</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 18:23:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353977278451-8</Id><Topic><Title>Such a tiresome pack of losers...</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353894548615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-25 20:49:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People want more jobs, not more taxes.</Msg><Username>dogshitforbrains</Username><Timestamp>1353977278451</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 19:47:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353987841757-9</Id><Title>Doha climate talk urges more emission cuts by developed world - legally binding accord requiring industrialized countries to cut their carbon emissions</Title><Msg>Doha climate talk urges more emission cuts by developed world Xinhua | 2012-11-27 9:19:41 By Agencies The latest UN climate change conference opened Monday in Doha, Qatar, where developing countries called for more commitment and actions by the developed world to tackle the challenges of a warming globe. At the beginning of the opening ceremony, president of the last conference Maite Nkoana-Mashabane from South Africa announced that the conference presidency was handed over to Abdullah bin Hamad Al- Attiyah, chairman of Qatar's Administrative Control and Transparency Authority. Attiyah said in a speech that climate change is confronting all human beings and effective actions need to be taken to cope with it. He added that the ongoing two-week conference is a precious opportunity for every participant to advance their efforts in salvaging the warming globe. UN Framework Convention on Climate Change (UNFCCC) Executive Secretary Christiana Figueres said at the conference that negotiators will try to complete some of the work that was initiated in past Conference of Parties (COPs), especially the progress started in Bali. The UN climate chief also said the talks here will work out detailed arrangements of the second commitment period of the Kyoto Protocol, a legally binding accord requiring industrialized countries to cut their carbon emissions. Apart from issues relating to the extension of the Kyoto Protocol, planning the work under the Durban Platform (a new negotiating mechanism) and charting the way forward on long-term climate finance are high on the agenda as well. Figueres called for the participants' attention to the financial and technical support that the developing countries urgently need to bolster their anti-warming efforts, and said that improvement can be done in this area in Doha. Days before the conference began, Figueres said in Bonn of Germany, where the office of the UNFCCC is based, that the Doha conference must deliver its objectives to speed up global action towards a low-emission future where everyone has the chance of a sustainable life. At the conference, deputy chief of the Chinese delegation Su Wei expressed the stance of the BASIC nations, namely China, India, Brazil and South Africa, on stemming climate change. "Climate change is a cross-cutting challenge that undermines the ability of developing countries to achieve sustainable development," he said. "The international community needs to strengthen the current multilateral rules-based climate regime and take concrete actions in accordance with all the principles and provisions of the Convention," Su added. He stressed that concerned parties should protect the climate system on the basis of equity and in accordance with the principle of common but differentiated responsibilities and respective capabilities. EU representative at the conference reiterated the bloc's compliance to the second commitment period of the Kyoto Protocol despite the grave economic environment, while stressing its financial support to the poor countries in their fight against the climate change. The bloc, which prides itself on its leading role in anti- warming efforts, claimed it has contributed 9.3 billion US dollars to the Fast Start Finance, though details of the donation are not given. It also pledged to deliver its share of the annual aid of 100 billion dollars promised by developed countries by 2020, but the program, called Green Climate Fund, remains largely an empty shell. The Naurun representative, on behalf of the Alliance of Small Island States, said his fellow countries, which are most vulnerable to the climate change, are in urgent need of help from the developed countries to combat the warming weather. "A month ago, hurricane Sandy hit America and caused great casualties and damages. Small island countries experience disastrous weather events more and more frequently," the Naurun representative said, urging the establishment of a mechanism to deal with the loss inflicted by extreme weather events upon human beings so as to ensure a healthy living environment for future generations. The Gambian representative, on behalf of the group of the least developed countries, said extreme weather events including flooding and hurricanes have claimed the lives of 1.3 million people in Gambia since 1980, urging the rich countries to hear the voice of his fellow countries and take drastic actions to address the warming climate. The Doha conference came amid a raft of warnings that efforts to cap the temperate rise may fail if deeper cuts of carbon emissions are not made in time. Ahead of the talks, a report by the UN Environment Program warned that levels of greenhouse gas emissions are now 14 percent above where they need to be in 2020 if the target of capping the temperature rise below 2 degrees is to be made. Therefore, negotiations in Doha are faced with the daunting task of persuading participants to make greater commitment to carbon emission cuts, particularly the rich countries that are responsible for 80 percent of the existing greenhouse gas in the atmosphere. As the Kyoto Protocol's first commitment period is set to expire at the end of this year, whether the rich countries at the Doha conference can pledge deeper cuts for the second term -- agreed upon in Durban last year -- is key to curbing the temperature rise. globaltimesDOTcn/content/746676.shtml</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353987841757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 22:44:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>