<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351656367900-1</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming Low IQ Sheeple</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351507436062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 06:43:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the 70's the universities were teaching 'global cooling'. The professors could not get grant money for research until they changed it to 'global warming '. University scammers.</Msg><Username>onions2089</Username><Timestamp>1351656367900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 00:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351658223939-2</Id><Title>More for max: Some questions:</Title><Msg>1. What does the "Unlawful Internet Gambling Enforcement Act of 2006" have to do with Intrade or Ireland. It is a law of the USA, and as the attorney you claim to be, you surely know this. 2. What does "JDD" stand for? JD stands for the "Juris Doctor", so what does JDD translate to in words. (If you can anwer one of two of these questions please do so, as I believe that would make it a major accomplishment for someone with a "JDD" from "Stetson University". (not exactly Harvard or the Sorbonne, is it?</Msg><Username>iggybiggies</Username><Timestamp>1351658223939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 00:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351662285941-3</Id><Title>Al Gore calls Sandy a ‘disturbing sign of things to come,’ urges climate action</Title><Msg>Al Gore calls Sandy a ‘disturbing sign of things to come,’ urges climate action By Ben Geman - 10/30/12 02:15 PM ET Al Gore said Tuesday that Hurricane Sandy is a “disturbing sign of things to come” in a warming world and should prompt action to curb greenhouse gas emissions from fossil fuels. “We must heed this warning and act quickly to solve the climate crisis. Dirty energy makes dirty weather,” the former vice president said in a statement on his website. Gore cited Sandy, which slammed ashore late Monday, and smaller-scale flooding in his hometown of Nashville two years ago, noting “both storms were strengthened by the climate crisis.” “Scientists tell us that by continually dumping 90 million tons of global warming pollution into the atmosphere every single day, we are altering the environment in which all storms develop. As the oceans and atmosphere continue to warm, storms are becoming more energetic and powerful,” he said. Gore also said that as Sandy approached the East Coast, it drew power from abnormally warm coastal waters and that the storm surge was worsened by sea-level rise. “Scientists tell us that if we do not reduce our emissions, these problems will only grow worse,” he said. Environmentalists and a number of scientists, as Sandy menaced the East Coast, have highlighted the nexus between global warming and extreme weather such as heat waves, droughts and powerful storms. (E2-Wire has more on that here.) New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo (D) also sees the hand of climate change in Sandy, a storm that caused widespread flooding, power outages and a number of deaths in the Empire State. “Anyone who says there's not a dramatic change in weather patterns I think is denying reality,” Cuomo said at a press conference Tuesday. Cuomo said officials must take into account the new reality of “extreme weather patterns,” and that he recently told President Obama “we have a 100-year flood every two years now.” “There is no weather pattern that could shock me at this point,” he said. Cuomo said in the late-morning press conference that 15 people in the state had been killed in the “catastrophic” storm, and predicted the tally would rise. Nearly two million customers are without power in New York state, according to an Energy Department report Tuesday morning, including what Cuomo said were 90 percent of residents on Long Island. The storm created major flooding in New York City, where the stormwater poured into the subway system, shutting it down. “The damage to the tracks, tunnels that are under water, is unlike this city has seen in decades, if ever,” Cuomo said. Mayor Michael Bloomberg said parts of the subway system would be out for days at least, according to The Wall Street Journal. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351662285941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351662693425-4</Id><Title>Al Gore: Hurricane Sandy is a global-warming warning</Title><Msg>Al Gore: Hurricane Sandy is a global-warming warning By ANDREW RESTUCCIA | 10/30/12 2:16 PM EDT Former vice president-turned-climate-change-activist Al Gore warned Tuesday that the storm that ravaged the East Coast Monday is “a disturbing sign of things to come.” “We must heed this warning and act quickly to solve the climate crisis. Dirty energy makes dirty weather,” Gore said in a statement posted on his blog Tuesday afternoon. Gore, one of the country’s most high-profile advocates of measures to reduce greenhouse gas emissions, compared this week's massive storm to 2010 floods that devastated Nashville, Tenn. “For me, the Nashville flood was a milestone,” he said. “For many, Hurricane Sandy may prove to be a similar event: a time when the climate crisis — which is often sequestered to the far reaches of our everyday awareness became a reality.” Both natural disasters, Gore said, “were strengthened by the climate crisis.” “Scientists tell us that by continually dumping 90 million tons of global warming pollution into the atmosphere every single day, we are altering the environment in which all storms develop. As the oceans and atmosphere continue to warm, storms are becoming more energetic and powerful. Hurricane Sandy, and the Nashville flood, were reminders of just that,” he said. Activists have criticized President Barack Obama and Mitt Romney for rarely mentioning climate change on the campaign trail. But, in the aftermath of Sandy, some politicians have begun connecting the storm to climate change. “We have a 100-year flood every two years now,” New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo told reporters Tuesday. “We have a new reality when it comes to these weather patterns. We have an old infrastructure and we have old systems and that is not a good combination.” New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg added: “What is clear is that the storms that we’ve experienced in the last year or so around this country and around the world are much more severe than before. Whether that’s global warming or what, I don’t know. But we’ll have to address those issues.” Meanwhile, former Michigan Gov. Jennifer Granholm said Monday: “There’s a clear link to climate change. And, yet, for the first time in over a quarter century, climate change was not brought up even once at the presidential debates.” politico</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351662693425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351663110976-5</Id><Title>ADM reports 60% drop in 1Q profit - Weak U.S. ethanol exports and slow E15 implementation were among the reasons for keeping industry margins negative</Title><Msg>ADM reports 60% drop in 1Q profit 2 hours ago • Chris Lusvardi, Decatur Herald &amp; Review (0) Comments DECATUR, Ill. — Archer Daniels Midland Co. executives continue to look for ways to cut costs as the company reported Tuesday a 60 percent drop in its fiscal first quarter profit. ADM said its earnings were down to $182 million, or 28 cents per share, from $460 million, or 68 cents per share, in the same quarter last year. Charges from the planned sale of Mexican food company Gruma dipped into ADM’s profits along with losses from ethanol production and a small harvest in the U.S. Its adjusted profit was 50 cents per share with a $146 million charge for Gruma. A comprehensive look at its portfolio is already well under way, ADM chairman, President and CEO Patricia Woertz said during a conference call with analysts. All employees are undergoing additional training to better manage cash expenses, Woertz said. A plan to save $150 million from workforce reductions announced earlier this year is ahead of schedule and should be in place by the end of the current fiscal quarter, Woertz said. A pension settlement will save the company additional money depending on the acceptance rate, said Ray Young, ADM chief financial officer. “We should see improvement over the next year,” Woertz said. ADM’s corn processing segment earnings were $68 million, down $115 million from a year ago, said Juan Luciano, the company’s chief operating officer. Its bioproducts results decreased $179 million to a loss of $26 million, Luciano said. Weak U.S. ethanol exports and slow E15 implementation were among the reasons for keeping industry margins negative, Luciano said. Ethanol production was the lowest in September since July 2010, Luciano said. “We see the industry becoming a little more disciplined,” Luciano said. Implementation of gasoline blends with 15 percent ethanol, or E15, will need to take place at more gas stations before helping the earnings of ethanol makers, Luciano said. Only eight stations in two states currently offer E15, Luciano said. “It’s a slow climb,” Luciano said. The company’s Ag Services segment performed well despite the summer’s drought, said Craig Huss, ADM chief risk officer. ADM’s transportation network has helped move grain across regions as quantities of crops have been lower in some areas, Huss said. Concerns about mold found on corn known as aflatoxins have provided additional opportunities to move grain, Huss said. ADM was able to make adjustments to its plans in anticipation of the drought, Huss said. Some analysts on the call were still dealing with flooding and power outages in the aftermath of superstorm Sandy. With its annual shareholder meeting set for 10:30 a.m. Thursday at the James Randall Research Center in Decatur, ADM went ahead with its scheduled earnings report as at least 28 other U.S. companies decided to delay their reporting plans with Wall Street closed for a second straight day. ADM’s stock did not trade because markets were shut down. The New York Stock Exchange has already announced trading will resume today. qctimes</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351663110976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:58:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351663624296-6</Id><Title>ZeaChem Completes Construction of Cellulosic Ethanol Biorefinery</Title><Msg>ZeaChem Completes Construction of Cellulosic Ethanol Biorefinery $25 million Series C closes with new investors ITOCHU Corp. and Macquarie LAKEWOOD, Colo., Oct 29, 2012 (BUSINESS WIRE) -- ZeaChem Inc., developer of highly-efficient biorefineries, today announced that it has completed construction of its 250,000 gallons per year (GPY) cellulosic ethanol biorefinery in Boardman, Oregon. The project was completed on budget and is expected to begin production of cellulosic ethanol by the end of 2012. ZeaChem's core process, completed earlier this year, enables the production of acetic acid and ethyl acetate which are intermediate chemicals for applications including paints, lacquers and consumer goods representing a $10 billion market worldwide. The core process has been commissioned and fermentation of sugar feedstocks has been replicated in 40,000 gallon tanks. These results met and exceeded the company's design targets. The next step in ZeaChem's phased development and start-up approach is to begin operations of the integrated facility for cellulosic ethanol production. With the support of a $25 million investment from the U.S. Department of Energy's Integrated Biorefinery program, ZeaChem has added process components to the core facility enabling the utilization of locally-sourced biomass, including wood and wheat straw, to be fermented and converted into intermediate chemicals and ethanol. "With construction completed, ZeaChem looks forward to starting integrated operations and the production of cellulosic ethanol this year," said Jim Imbler, president and chief executive officer of ZeaChem. "We are executing a phased start-up approach to limit risk, stabilize and optimize operations, and ensure safety. ZeaChem is focused on successfully demonstrating integrated operations and commercializing its highly efficient, economical and sustainable biorefining process." ZeaChem also announced it has closed its Series C financing totaling $25 million in new equity to advance its business strategy and commercial deployment. New investors include Tokyo, Japan-based ITOCHU Corporation, a multi-national trading company, and Macquarie, a global investment banking and financial services group based in Sydney, Australia. Additional Series C investors include: Birchmere Ventures, Firelake Capital, Globespan Capital Partners, Mohr Davidow Ventures, PrairieGold Venture Partners, and Spring Ventures. ZeaChem will utilize Series C funds to support operations at the integrated biorefinery and develop its first commercial biorefinery. "We are pleased to expand our investor support to new partners in Asia and Australia, which demonstrates ZeaChem's global potential for biofuels and bio-based chemicals," added Imbler. "ITOCHU and Macquarie have established track records in co-developing energy projects worldwide and the ZeaChem platform is uniquely qualified for this due to our feedstock flexibility and diverse product portfolios. These new international partners provide us with a foundation to expand the company's operations globally." marketwatch</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351663624296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 02:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351679280506-7</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore calls Sandy a ‘disturbing sign of things to come,’ urges climate action</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351662285941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:44:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think in the future all extreme weather, climate, and geological events should be blamed on manmade global warming. While we are at it why not blame the continental glaciation which covered Chicago and created Lake Michigan when it receded on manmade global warming. Also blame continental drift on manmade global warming. The undersea volcanos which gradually emerged above sea level and formed what man now calls Hawaii, should also be blamed on manmade global warming. And when the lump of matter we call the Moon separated from the Earth and was hurled into its orbit around Earth, that too was manmade global warming.........</Msg><Username>iggybiggies</Username><Timestamp>1351679280506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 06:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351682571164-8</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming Low IQ Sheeple</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351507436062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 06:43:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"bluecheese" is the former poster Canadian "michael" and he is a great example of a low IQ sheeple who believes in Al "Sore Loserman" Gore. Keep posting all your little greenie weenie tidbits of info Michael since it is a continual reminder that Liberalism is indeed a mental disorder.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351682571164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 07:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351682860496-9</Id><Topic><Title>Blacks are Out in the Northeast</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351598116227</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 07:55:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maxwizard can't handle the truth that many of his creed are worthless scumsuckers who live off the taxpayer dollarsall of their useless lives and take advantage of achieving people anytime they can, even during natural disasters such as hurricane Sandy. Certainly not all of his creed are worthless, but such a high percentage are and the Presidency of Barack Hussein Obama Hmmm..... Hmm.... Hmm.. has really brought that to light.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351682860496</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 07:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351684206393-10</Id><Title>Bailout of Wall St</Title><Msg>Once all the water is bailed out of the NY banking district, they will come to the taxpayer again and ask for a Federal "bailout" for the money they could have scammed from us if they had been able to do business the last three days. No doubt we won't have a vote in this taxpayer funded Insurance fraud. All of NYC will be rebuilt by us. They ought to have enough money hidden to do it on their own.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351684206393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 07:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351691174171-11</Id><Title>Ethanol Climbs to One-Week High on Signs of Tightening Supply</Title><Msg>Ethanol Climbs to One-Week High on Signs of Tightening Supply By Mario Parker on October 30, 2012 Ethanol futures in Chicago climbed to the highest price in a week on speculation that plant shutdowns will help soak up a supply glut. Prices jumped for a third day after producers including Valero Energy Corp. (VLO), Bunge-Ergon Vicksburg LLC, Abengoa SA (ABG) and Biofuel Energy Corp. (BIOF) idled output starting in late September, citing poor margins to manufacture the fuel from corn. Ethanol stockpiles, which totaled 18.8 million barrels in the week ended Oct. 19, were 8.5 percent higher than a year ago, Energy Department data showed. “My feeling is that stocks would be lower,” said Ian Jackson, an ethanol trader at SCB &amp; Associates in Chicago. “Certainly, you’ve seen some tightness in the physical market.” Denatured ethanol for November delivery rose 2.8 cents, or 1.2 percent, to $2.413 a gallon on the Chicago Board of Trade, the highest price since Oct. 22. Futures have gained 9.5 percent this year. In cash market trading, ethanol was unchanged in New York at $2.47 a gallon and in the U.S. Gulf at $2.46, data compiled by Bloomberg shows. Ethanol on the West Coast plunged 7 cents, or 2.8 percent, to $2.46 a gallon and in Chicago the additive increased 1 cent, or 0.4 percent, to $2.395. Corn Prices Corn for December delivery gained 4.75 cents, or 0.6 percent, to $7.4175 a bushel in Chicago. One bushel makes at least 2.75 gallons of ethanol. Based on December contracts for ethanol and corn, producers are losing about 30 cents on each gallon of the biofuel made, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. That doesn’t include profit from the sale of dried distillers’ grains, a byproduct of ethanol production that can be fed to livestock. Gasoline for November delivery decreased 2.8 cents, or 1 percent, to $2.7288 a gallon in New York. The contract covers reformulated gasoline, made to be blended with ethanol before delivery to filling stations. Ethanol’s discount to the motor fuel narrowed to 31.58 cents from 37.18 cents yesterday. Gasoline traded at a premium of 99.8 cents to ethanol as recently as Sept. 28. businessweek</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351691174171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351696695671-12</Id><Title>Time to buy, Joe Terranova says headed higher,</Title><Msg>..............</Msg><Username>causinginflation</Username><Timestamp>1351696695671</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:18:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351700154018-13</Id><Title>Fast Money Halftime: Bullish on Exxon, charts see $100</Title><Msg>near term.</Msg><Username>causinginflation</Username><Timestamp>1351700154018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351700245585-14</Id><Title>Breaking news!!!!!! Increase in dividend~!</Title><Msg>major earnings power</Msg><Username>causinginflation</Username><Timestamp>1351700245585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351700419389-15</Id><Title>$1.98 eps, $112.45B Revs, nice quarter!</Title><Msg>Guidance good, $94 open</Msg><Username>causinginflation</Username><Timestamp>1351700419389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351701699136-16</Id><Title>Barclays PLC Q3 2012 Interim Management Statement 30 September 2012</Title><Msg>Barclays PLC Q3 2012 Interim Management Statement 30 September 2012 31 October 2012 barclays barclays barclays Presentation slides barclays URLs at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351701699136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351707671530-17</Id><Title>E.ON Climate &amp; Renewables Raises Needed Financing For 203MW Texas Wind Farm</Title><Msg>E.ON Climate &amp; Renewables Raises Needed Financing For 203MW Texas Wind Farm October 31, 2012 By Nathan Leave a Comment E.ON Climate &amp; Renewables (EC&amp;R) North America announced yesterday that it had secured institutional equity financing of around $167.7 million dollars and a commitment to fund the expected capital contributions of nearly $55.9 million dollars for its 203MW wind farm project in Texas. The financing was raised of from their investors in exchange for a partial interest in EC&amp;R’s recently completed Magic Valley Wind Farm. These investors include JPM Capital Corporation (J.P. Morgan) and Wells Fargo Wind Holdings LLC (Wells Fargo). With J.P. Morgan acting as lead investor in the financing. “We’re delighted to demonstrate continued success in the tax equity market and we’re pleased to show the attractiveness of our wind energy portfolio,” said Dr. Verena Volpert, Senior Vice President Finance, E.ON AG. “Working with an investor team that includes J.P. Morgan and Wells Fargo proves our ability to raise capital in a tax-efficient manner.” The project is the first wind farm located in Willacy County, Texas. It began operating in September at its location about 5 miles east of Raymondville. The 203MW wind farm is composed of 112 Vestas 1.8 megawatt turbines and provides enough electricity to power more than 60,000 homes. “This project is expected to generate more than $53 million in local taxes, pay $12 million in local salaries, and earn landowners more than $87 million. At the height of construction, the Magic Valley Wind Farm project brought more than 200 jobs to the area.” Texas is a clear leader in wind power, with more wind power installed than all but a few countries. Though, less than about 10 other states as a percentage of their total electricity generation capacity. cleantechnica</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351707671530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351708008651-18</Id><Title>New Solar Module Efficiency Record Set, 33.5% Efficiency</Title><Msg>New Solar Module Efficiency Record Set, 33.5% Efficiency October 31, 2012 By Nathan Leave a Comment A new solar photovoltaic efficiency record has been set. The new module achieved a solar efficiency rating of 33.5%. One of the leading concentrator photovoltaic (CPV) solar power systems companies, Amonix Inc., just announced that it has broken the efficiency record for photovoltaics operating in real-world conditions. Setting a new high with a 33.5% efficiency rating, peaking at 34.2%. That means that the solar module successfully converted more than a third of the energy of direct sunlight into electricity. The National Renewable Energy Laboratory (NREL) tested the module back in May, confirming “an outdoor operating efficiency rating of 33.5% for an Amonix module, breaking the previous 30.3% record also held by Amonix. Over several days of on-sun testing conducted by NREL, the module efficiency peaked at 34.2%. This is the highest efficiency ever reported under real-world, operating conditions for a solar PV module,” a news release has just stated. “While the mainstream PV industry has made critical reductions in large-scale production costs and incremental improvements in power-conversion efficiencies, much of the world is unaware of the dramatic progress that has been made by CPV companies toward achieving high power-conversion efficiencies” “This is a huge milestone for Amonix and the CPV industry,” said Vahan Garboushian, Amonix Founder and CTO. “We have been at the forefront of CPV technology breakthroughs and have consistently proven that CPV offers the highest efficiencies of all solar technologies in the right operating conditions with plenty of headroom. Amonix is focused on driving CPV costs down and breaking efficiency records in the near future.” Achieving an efficiency greater than 33.3% for a commercial module is a huge milestone. That efficiency, one-third, has been targeted by the Department of Energy as a major goal for some time. cleantechnica</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351708008651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351710726762-19</Id><Topic><Title>Time to buy, Joe Terranova says headed higher,</Title><Username>causinginflation</Username><Timestamp>1351696695671</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:18:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll never forget the look on Joe Terranova's face in September of 2008 when the stock market CRASHED! He looked like the scared coward that he probably truly is. Who gives a rats #$%$ what Joe Terranova says?</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351710726762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:12:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351710839298-20</Id><Title>Romney Said Gut FEMA Last Year NOW He Says Something Completely Different</Title><Msg>The gut is a complete sham. He's just dying to slash the throats of hard working Americans so his wealthy buddies can have it all.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351710839298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351711721740-21</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Said Gut FEMA Last Year NOW He Says Something Completely Different</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351710839298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You underestimate their effort to subvert millions of votes and steal the election. If one of them asks you or anyone around you questions at the polls make sure to humiliate them and then crack em upside the head as hard as you can.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351711721740</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351712176378-22</Id><Topic><Title>$1.98 eps, $112.45B Revs, nice quarter!</Title><Username>causinginflation</Username><Timestamp>1351700419389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:20:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they usually miss the estimates</Msg><Username>powereng1040</Username><Timestamp>1351712176378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351712376833-23</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Said Gut FEMA Last Year NOW He Says Something Completely Different</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351710839298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Per usual walhieeeeesan....you have no idea what you're talking about....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351712376833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:39:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351714138064-24</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Said Gut FEMA Last Year NOW He Says Something Completely Different</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351710839298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dunno Rmoney would vote for Obama for tax reasons but if that last debate woulda gone 20 mins more--Rmoney woulda endorsed Obama Rmoney said "I agree with the president" more times in 1 nite than Biden has in 4 years</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1351714138064</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351715513111-25</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore calls Sandy a ‘disturbing sign of things to come,’ urges climate action</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351662285941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:44:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When did Algore's "Global Warming" start? Storms have been hitting the east coast for a long time- Early New York Hurricanes 1821 HURRICANE Reaching the City on September 3, 1821, the storm was one of the only hurricanes believed to have passed directly over parts of modern New York City. The tide rose 13 feet in one hour and inundated wharves, causing the East River to converge into the Hudson River across lower Manhattan as far north as Canal Street. However, few deaths were attributed to the storm because flooding was concentrated in neighborhoods with far fewer homes than exist today. 1893 HURRICANE In 1893, a category 1 hurricane destroyed Hog Island, a resort island off the Rockaways in southern Queens. Waves striking a seawall, 1938 (NWS Historic Collection) 1938 HURRICANE The most powerful hurricane known to have made landfall nearby — a category 3 hurricane — occurred in 1938. Its eye crossed over Long Island and into New England, killing nearly 200 people. The storm killed 10 people in New York City and caused millions of dollars in damage. Its floods knocked out electrical power in all areas above 59th Street in Manhattan and in all of the Bronx, the new IND subway line lost power, and 100 large trees in Central Park were destroyed. Fortunately, New York City experienced the weaker "left side" of the 1938 hurricane — the City was 75 miles from the eye when it passed over Long Island. The hurricane could have caused far more deaths and damage if it passed closer to the five boroughs. An excellent history of the 1938 hurricane is provided at Scott Mandia's website: The Long Island Express: The Great Hurricane of 1938.</Msg><Username>g026978</Username><Timestamp>1351715513111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351718186324-26</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Denying Climate Change You Propagandized Fools</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351452088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More brain death! At least you are consistent Leave it to global warming alarmists to exploit the innocent victims of a human tragedy like Hurricane Sandy to spread the laughably false notion that global warming caused the storm. While our nation should be coming together to support the victims and repair the damage, far too many alarmists are cynically prostituting the tragedy under Rahm Emanuel’s theory of “You never want a serious crisis to go to waste.” Shame on those alarmists for asserting a false connection to global warming to “make lemonade” out of this tragedy. As Hurricane Sandy prepared to strike the Northeast, climate scientists from alarmist and skeptical camps alike reported the storm had little if anything to do with global warming. Martin Hoerling, who chairs the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration’s (NOAA’s) climate variability research program, and who oversees NOAA’s Climate Scene Investigators, observed, “neither the frequency of tropical or extratropical cyclones over the North Atlantic are projected to appreciably change due to climate change, nor have there been indications of a change in their statistical behavior over this region in recent decades.” Got that? Global warming models project no appreciable change in North Atlantic storm behavior, yet global warming alarmists now say global warming caused Hurricane Sandy. Hoerling further explained, “In this case, the immediate cause is most likely little more that the coincidental alignment of a tropical storm with an extratropical storm. Both frequent the west Atlantic in October…nothing unusual with that. On rare occasions their timing is such as to result in an interaction which can lead to an extreme event along the eastern seaboard.” So global warming models say global warming has little or no impact on North Atlantic storms and meteorologists report a convergence of natural factors that made Sandy especially powerful. To objective scientists not trying to sell global warming snake oil, this is yet another example of the very strong storms that always have – and always will – occur on our planet. Scientists, moreover, report a striking decline in hurricane activity during recent years. National Hurricane Center data show a dramatic decline in major hurricanes striking the United States during the past half century (see my recent column on this here). As the earth gradually recovers from the Little Ice Age (which lasted from approximately 1300 to 1900 A.D.), the frequency of major hurricane strikes is declining rather than increasing. Sure, there will still be hurricanes and strong storms as the planet warms. But when the frequency of hurricanes and strong storms declines in a warming world, it defies common sense to claim that global warming is causing the increasingly rare hurricanes and strong storms that do still occur. Far too many prominent global warming alarmists are ignoring these facts in their rush to exploit the victims of Hurricane Sandy. It goes without saying that Al Gore claimed global warming caused Hurricane Sandy. Other Al Gore wannabes are piling on. With a backdrop containing the words, “The New Normal?” NBC News aired a video claiming, “Most scientists have no doubt of the overall cause” of Hurricane Sandy. To emphasize this false narrative, the video claims, “Even some politicians agree.” Got it? EVEN some politicians agree! In other words, if any of you anti-science deniers buy into what NOAA climate scientist Martin Hoerling reports, here’s a big slice of Democrat New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo saying global warming IS to blame. So THERE, you deniers! The Huffington Post, New York Times, Politico and others have added their voice to the shameless exploitation of Hurricane Sandy victims. Nevertheless, all the alarmist bullying and media bullying in the world cannot change the scientific facts. It is time for alarmists to stop soiling themselves in their rush to score cheap political points off Hurricane Sandy. Let’s instead come together and focus on assisting those victimized by the storm.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351718186324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351718289058-27</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore calls Sandy a ‘disturbing sign of things to come,’ urges climate action</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351662285941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:44:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave it to global warming alarmists to exploit the innocent victims of a human tragedy like Hurricane Sandy to spread the laughably false notion that global warming caused the storm. While our nation should be coming together to support the victims and repair the damage, far too many alarmists are cynically prostituting the tragedy under Rahm Emanuel’s theory of “You never want a serious crisis to go to waste.” Shame on those alarmists for asserting a false connection to global warming to “make lemonade” out of this tragedy. As Hurricane Sandy prepared to strike the Northeast, climate scientists from alarmist and skeptical camps alike reported the storm had little if anything to do with global warming. Martin Hoerling, who chairs the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration’s (NOAA’s) climate variability research program, and who oversees NOAA’s Climate Scene Investigators, observed, “neither the frequency of tropical or extratropical cyclones over the North Atlantic are projected to appreciably change due to climate change, nor have there been indications of a change in their statistical behavior over this region in recent decades.” Got that? Global warming models project no appreciable change in North Atlantic storm behavior, yet global warming alarmists now say global warming caused Hurricane Sandy. Hoerling further explained, “In this case, the immediate cause is most likely little more that the coincidental alignment of a tropical storm with an extratropical storm. Both frequent the west Atlantic in October…nothing unusual with that. On rare occasions their timing is such as to result in an interaction which can lead to an extreme event along the eastern seaboard.” So global warming models say global warming has little or no impact on North Atlantic storms and meteorologists report a convergence of natural factors that made Sandy especially powerful. To objective scientists not trying to sell global warming snake oil, this is yet another example of the very strong storms that always have – and always will – occur on our planet. Scientists, moreover, report a striking decline in hurricane activity during recent years. National Hurricane Center data show a dramatic decline in major hurricanes striking the United States during the past half century (see my recent column on this here). As the earth gradually recovers from the Little Ice Age (which lasted from approximately 1300 to 1900 A.D.), the frequency of major hurricane strikes is declining rather than increasing. Sure, there will still be hurricanes and strong storms as the planet warms. But when the frequency of hurricanes and strong storms declines in a warming world, it defies common sense to claim that global warming is causing the increasingly rare hurricanes and strong storms that do still occur. Far too many prominent global warming alarmists are ignoring these facts in their rush to exploit the victims of Hurricane Sandy. It goes without saying that Al Gore claimed global warming caused Hurricane Sandy. Other Al Gore wannabes are piling on. With a backdrop containing the words, “The New Normal?” NBC News aired a video claiming, “Most scientists have no doubt of the overall cause” of Hurricane Sandy. To emphasize this false narrative, the video claims, “Even some politicians agree.” Got it? EVEN some politicians agree! In other words, if any of you anti-science deniers buy into what NOAA climate scientist Martin Hoerling reports, here’s a big slice of Democrat New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo saying global warming IS to blame. So THERE, you deniers! The Huffington Post, New York Times, Politico and others have added their voice to the shameless exploitation of Hurricane Sandy victims. Nevertheless, all the alarmist bullying and media bullying in the world cannot change the scientific facts. It is time for alarmists to stop soiling themselves in their rush to score cheap political points off Hurricane Sandy. Let’s instead come together and focus on assisting those victimized by the storm.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351718289058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351718388214-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Said Gut FEMA Last Year NOW He Says Something Completely Different</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351710839298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not per usual, per ALWAYS. Same can now be said of maxwiz.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351718388214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351721180919-29</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Said Gut FEMA Last Year NOW He Says Something Completely Different</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351710839298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your spoon-fed talking points hit the liberal media first. You need a different source of information. You are so far left and lost that you can't even see the center................But, thank you for what you do.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1351721180919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351721371274-30</Id><Title>Market Closed 2 days</Title><Msg>I didn't miss it. Did you? It proves that Wall St is way overrated and overstaffed by thousands. We could get by with three trading days a week, say Monday Wednesday and Friday. The banks and brokerages could lay off thousands of staff, thereby bailing out themselves should the economy turn down again. Heck the market could've been closed all week as far as I am concerned.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1351721371274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351721480751-31</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore calls Sandy a ‘disturbing sign of things to come,’ urges climate action</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351662285941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 01:44:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>algore is a beached whale. All he wants is your money and, he will say or do anything to get it.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1351721480751</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351727095927-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intrade: Obama 66% Romoney 33% ........deal with it !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1351708675620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll be out canvassing fellow Democrats door to door on Saturday and Tuesday in the Pgh area. Many thousands of other Dems will be joining in the fun - every day from now until the polls close on Election Day. Meanwhile, the Rethugs claim to have a "ground game" but the only evidence of it I have seen is an obnoxious robocall this morning from a young RNC operative based in DC. Romney's campaign is a joke - what a terrible way to waste over $900 Million!</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1351727095927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351728417412-33</Id><Title>EPA waives fuel regs in storm states</Title><Msg>EPA waives fuel regs in storm states Published: Oct. 31, 2012 at 6:25 PM WASHINGTON, Oct. 31 (UPI) -- U.S. environmental regulators say they are waiving federal clean gasoline requirements for gasoline sold and distributed in states hit by Hurricane Sandy. The waiver -- granted by the Environmental Protection Agency in coordination with the Department of Energy -- covers Tennessee, North Carolina, South Carolina, Mississippi, Georgia, Alabama, District of Columbia, New York, Maryland, Connecticut, Delaware, Massachusetts, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, Virginia, New Hampshire, and Rhode Island. As a result of the effects of Hurricane Sandy, extreme and unusual supply circumstances exist that may result in a temporary shortage of gasoline compliant with federal regulations, EPA Administrator Lisa P. Jackson said in an agency release Wednesday. The federal waiver will help ensure an adequate supply of fuels in states affected by the storm, the release said. The waiver will temporarily allow the mixing of reformulated gasoline and conventional gasoline to remove potential barriers to the supply of gasoline to the region, officials said. upi</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351728417412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351740100404-34</Id><Title>ABC Story of 4 Year-Old Crying Over 'Bronco Bamma' and Mitt Romney Seems to Betray NPR's Anti-Romney Bias</Title><Msg>A video of a mother trying to console her crying four year-old daughter about the fact that the election campaign season will soon be over has allegedly gone viral. I say "allegedly" because the original of the video involved shows ove 700,000 hits at its YouTube results listing, but only about 19,000 at the original video itself. Anyway, the four-year old is Abigael Evans, and her reaction was to hearing yet another NPR report on the election in the car while riding with her mother Elizabeth. ABC's Jilian Fama has covered the story. A revealing statement from Abigael's mother appears to demonstrate how blatantly biased NPR's coverage of the presidential election campaign has been: Sick of the elections yet? So is four-year-old Abigael Evans from Colorado. Her mother, Elizabeth Evans, 27, posted a Youtube video of her daughter saying that she is tired of "Bronco Bamma and Mitt Romney." The 22-second YouTube clip, published yesterday, shows the little girl with a frown on her face and tears rolling down her cheeks, telling her mother she is tired of this election. Elizabeth Evans told ABC News that her daughter got emotional listening to NPR. "I just picked her up from daycare so she was grumpy after a long day and we were driving to the grocery store listening to NPR," Evans said. "And I wasn't really listening and when I was getting her out of the car, she started saying that she was tired of Bronco Bamma and Mitt Romney." "That's why you're crying?" the girl's mother asks. After she replies with an affirmative shake of her head, Abby's mother says, "The election will be over soon, O.K?" "O.K.," replies the disheartened little girl. Abigael's mother says ... "We don't watch TV or anything in our house, so even just listening to radio and hearing people talk about politics was all she could handle." For a four-year-old who isn't exposed to politics at home, the young YouTube star seems to know a lot. "She talks about Mitt Romney and Barack Obama all the time," Evans continues to tell ABC. "She always says that Obama is the president and that Mitt Romney is a bad guy who just wants money and wants to be the president… She is very precocious." Mom says that Abigael doesn't watch TV, so it appears that the only time the child is exposed to political discussion and news is when she accompanies her mom as she runs errands, which based on her "knowing a lot," seems to be pretty often. There are precious few places on the radio dial where one would consistently hear that "Mitt Romney is a bad guy who just wants money," and NPR is the "leader" of that pack. NPR has apologized to Abigael for upsetting her. We'll never get an apology from NPR for abusing their government funding by feeding the nation left-driven drivel day after day.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351740100404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 23:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351742294993-35</Id><Title>Wind farms: 'No change' on policy, says David Cameron</Title><Msg>Wind farms: 'No change' on policy, says David Cameron 31 October 2012 Last updated at 13:07 ET Comments (937) There has been no change in the government's policy on renewable energy, the prime minister has said. It comes after a Tory energy minister sparked a coalition row by claiming the UK had "enough" onshore wind farms. John Hayes was slapped down by his Lib Dem boss Ed Davey after suggesting future projects would be blocked. Mr Davey said he was in charge of energy policy and, echoing the PM, said the wind farm policy had not changed. "The government is still committed to renewables including onshore wind," said Mr Davey. "They are the cheapest available major renewable source and as the Prime Minister made clear today in the House of Commons the policy on renewables hasn't changed." "There will still be lots of investment in onshore wind farms," he added, saying they were vital as a "clean" and "secure" alternative to oil from other countries as North Sea oil diminished. Mr Davey refused to answer when the question "Is John Hayes just wrong then?" was shouted at him by reporters. 'New Jerusalem' Mr Hayes, a longstanding critic of wind farms, was handed the junior ministerial role in September's reshuffle, prompting Mr Davey to take personal control of wind farm policy to protect a key Lib Dem priority. The Tory minister, who is in charge of "renewable energy deployment", is understood to have wanted to announce a moratorium on new wind farms in a speech on Tuesday evening but was prevented from doing so by Mr Davey. Instead, he told the Daily Mail and Daily Telegraph there were enough wind farms in the planning pipeline to meet government environmental targets - and there should be no more. He said: "We can no longer have wind turbines imposed on communities. I can't single-handedly build a new Jerusalem but I can protect our green and pleasant land. "We have issued a call for evidence on wind. That is about cost but also about community buy-in. We need to understand communities' genuine desires. We will form our policy in the future on the basis of that, not on a bourgeois Left article of faith based on some academic perspective. "If you look at what has been built, what has consent and what is in the planning system, much of it will not get through and will be rejected. Even if a minority of what's in the system is built we are going to reach our 2020 target." He also suggested reviews would be launched into the noise and impact on the landscape created by turbines - something denied by a DECC source, who said Mr Hayes had "totally over-egged" things in the newspaper interviews. Mr Hayes told reporters on Wednesday morning "I stand by what I said". 'Playing politics' Speaking at Prime Minister's Questions, Mr Cameron denied there had been any change to the government's policy on wind energy, but did back a future debate on renewables, once the government had met its environmental targets. He said: "There has been no change towards renewable energy. "We have got a big pipeline of onshore and offshore wind projects that are coming through, but frankly all parties are going to have to have a debate in this House and outside this House about what happens when those targets are met." Labour leader Ed Miliband described this as a "useless answer," adding "there are investors all round this country who want certainty about energy policy". There are 3,400 onshore wind turbines across the UK at 324 different sites, generating 3% of the UK's electricity. A further 4,000 turbines are due to be built by 2020. Maf Smith, deputy chief executive of RenewableUK, said his organisation was "disappointed" by Mr Hayes' comments, which came after he addressed a renewables conference on Tuesday evening. Mr Smith told BBC Radio 4 Today's programme: "At our conference he was talking about the importance of renewables in the mix, the importance of wind, the importance of jobs and securing benefits for renewables. "What we would like is clarity about those views." Earlier this year, more than 100 Conservative MPs wrote to Prime Minister David Cameron urging him to get rid of the subsidies paid to wind farm operators funded from household energy bills. Shadow energy secretary Caroline Flint, for Labour, accused Mr Hayes of "playing politics" with clean energy jobs and the country's energy security. http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-20150316</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351742294993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 23:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>