<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-14"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355461445508-1</Id><Title>Michigan House of Fascists March In Lock Step..</Title><Msg>Michigan legislators did not write the so-called “right to work” legislation that they have enacted in a mad rush of anti-democratic excess. They simply did as they were told. The ideas, the outlines and the words themselves came from the American Legislative Exchange Council, the right-wing “bill mill” that produces “model legislation” at the behest of Koch Industries, Rupert Murdoch’s NewsCorp, ExxonMobil and the corporate cabal that is always looking to “buy” states. As the Center for Media and Democracy’s “ALEC Exposed” project revealed (in conjunction with The Nation), ALEC has developed binders full of “model legislation” that assaults the rights of working people, consumers and communities. ALEC’s package of “model legislation” includes numerous bills and resolutions that, by any reasonable measure, would be referred to as “no rights at work” schemes. Those measures formed the basis for HB 4003, the Michigan “Right-to-Work Act” that has provoked mass demonstrations in Lansing and other Michigan communities. Section after section, line after line, of the Michigan legislation mirrors the ALEC model legislation, as revealed by the “ALEC Exposed” project. “The legislation is straight out of the Koch-funded ALEC playbook,” explains Brendan Fischer, the staff counsel with the Center for Media and Democracy. At some points, the Michigan lawmakers shifted words, from “resign or refrain from…a labor organization” in the ALEC model legislation to “refrain or resign from…a labor organization” in one of the two Michigan bills.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461445508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:04:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355461490350-2</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan House of Fascists March In Lock Step..</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461445508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:04:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At other points, the Michigan Republicans simply lifted whole sections verbatim, outlining how workers who get the advantage of union representation will not have “to pay any dues, fees, assessments or other charges, of any kind or amount” to a labor organization. The willingness of legislators in Michigan and, it should be noted, other states to simply take marching orders from ALEC is troubling enough. But even more troubling is the reason why corporations and politicians in states where the middle class was forged by organized labor agree on the “need” to advance anti-labor legislation. This is not about economic development, growth or job creation. And it is certainly not about “freedom,” as Michigan Governor Rick Snyder claims. This is about warping democracy so that corporations have a consistent upper hand, with the result being that those politicians who are willing to do the bidding of corporations and wealthy donors are more likely to prevail. In this sense, the best way to understand the recent rush to enact anti-labor legislation is as part of the same initiative that has produced restrictive Voter ID laws, schemes to limit early voting and proposals to eliminate same-day registration. What distinguishes the anti-labor initiatives is that they do not explicitly seek to make voting more difficult. They seek to make it harder for groups that seek high turnout to get voters motivated, to get voters organized and to get them to the polls. Ultimately, however, the end result of the assault on labor rights is the same as a direct assault on voting rights: a diminished democracy.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461490350</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:04:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355461568754-3</Id><Title>Capitalist Criminals Washing $ For Murderous Drug Cartels</Title><Msg>The banking giant HSBC has escaped indictment for laundering billions of dollars for Mexican drug cartels and groups linked to al-Qaeda. Despite evidence of wrongdoing, the U.S. Department of Justice has allowed the bank to avoid prosecution and pay a $1.9 billion fine. No top HSBC officials will face charges, either. We’re joined by Rolling Stone contributing editor Matt Taibbi, author of "Griftopia: A Story of Bankers, Politicians, and the Most Audacious Power Grab in American History." "You can do real time in jail in America for all kinds of ridiculous offenses," Taibbi says. "Here we have a bank that laundered $800 million of drug money, and they can’t find a way to put anybody in jail for that. That sends an incredible message, not just to the financial sector but to everybody. It’s an obvious, clear double standard, where one set of people gets to break the rules as much as they want and another set of people can’t break any rules at all without going to jail."</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461568754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:06:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355462711115-4</Id><Title>China’s New Solar Target: 40 GW By 2015 (8 Times More Than Its Initial 5 GW Target)</Title><Msg>China’s New Solar Target: 40 GW By 2015 (8 Times More Than Its Initial 5 GW Target) December 13, 2012 Zachary Shahan It’s been pretty astounding to watch China essentially double its 2015 solar target three times in the past year and a half or so. Each step of the way, what’s clear is that solar power keeps getting more and more competitive… fast. Image Credit: China &amp; solar panel via Shutterstock Before this week, China’s latest 2015 solar target increase was in July, when the official target was brought up to 21 GW. Then, just a couple months later (in September), it was rumored that China was going to increase the target to 40 GW. Now, all the buzz is that’s finally happening. Giles Parkinson of Renew Economy writes: “Talk out of China suggests that official bodies in that country are finally ready to lift their target for the deployment of solar to 40GW by 2015.” He also cites this interesting stat: “Just 18 months ago, the 2015 target for 2015 was just 5GW. But more than that has been installed this year alone.” More than the initial target has been installed in 2012 alone. Pretty astounding, eh? This is, for one, a sign of China’s tremendous focus on clean energy, as well as its tremendous overall economic and energy growth. But it’s also a sign that solar power has arrived. Solar has many benefits, and now that its price has dropped to a competitive rate in many places (and is still dropping), those benefits are catapulting it above competing options. Here’s more from Giles on this week’s news: “Deutsche Bank analysts noted that the updated forecast suggests that more than 10GW of solar will be installed in China in each of the next three years. Assuming that solar deployment will continue to increase rather than slow; that suggests a cumulative total of well over 100GW by 2020. “On Tuesday, the government announced that the total amount of projects approved under the 2nd batch of its Golden Sun program was 2.8GW, well ahead of the 2GW expected, taking this year’s allocation to 4.5GW.” Another key point noted in the Renew Economy piece was that oversupply of solar modules and solar module components (especially in China), which is partly triggered by cuts in solar feed-in tariffs in Europe, is further stimulating solar-friendly policies and deployment in the world’s largest country. With the 2015 target increased from 5 GW to 10 GW in June 2011, from 10 GW to 15 GW in December 2011, from 15 GW to 21 GW in July 2012, and now from 21 GW to 40 GW, does anyone want to make a prediction what the 2015 target will be when Summer 2013 rolls around? Putting 40 GW Into Perspective As I did back in July, why don’t we put the current 41 GW target into a bit of perspective. At the end of 2011, the top 5 countries for total installed solar PV power capacity (and their capacity) were: 1.Germany — 24.7 GW 2.Italy — 12.8 GW 3.Japan — 4.9 GW 4.Spain — 4.4 GW 5.USA — 4.4 GW In other words, 41 GW of solar power is really a big deal. US solar installations at the end of Q3 already broke the US record for previous years. That record? Nearly 2 GW. In total, 2012 installations are expected to hit about 3.2 GW, and that will bring cumulative US solar capacity to over 7 GW. That sounded like a lot on Tuesday, but China’s expected 4.5 GW this year definitely raises the bar. And what about China’s 2020 target, which was 20 GW back when its 2015 target was 5 GW? We’ll have to wait and see. Before closing off with this good news, here’s one more thing to consider: the 2015 target is simply a target, with the country expecting to surpass the target by a good amount. Let’s hope those expectations just keep on increasing. Clean Technica</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355462711115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:25:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355462828558-5</Id><Title>China’s New Solar Target: 40 GW By 2015 (8 Times More Than Its Initial 5 GW Target)</Title><Msg>China’s New Solar Target: 40 GW By 2015 (8 Times More Than Its Initial 5 GW Target) December 13, 2012 Zachary Shahan It’s been pretty astounding to watch China essentially double its 2015 solar target three times in the past year and a half or so. Each step of the way, what’s clear is that solar power keeps getting more and more competitive… fast. Image Credit: China &amp; solar panel via Shutterstock Before this week, China’s latest 2015 solar target increase was in July, when the official target was brought up to 21 GW. Then, just a couple months later (in September), it was rumored that China was going to increase the target to 40 GW. Now, all the</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355462828558</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:27:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355463590536-6</Id><Topic><Title>China’s New Solar Target: 40 GW By 2015 (8 Times More Than Its Initial 5 GW Target)</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355462828558</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:27:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The infrastructure required to export LNG is very expensive and by the time it'll be available the market will have shrunk. BILLION$$$$$$$$$$ invested will vanish! Goodbye LNG! Peak natural gas consumption in America, .... December 2013 &amp; January 2014. My opinion.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355463590536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:39:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355466176065-7</Id><Title>Texas judge lifts order that halted work on Keystone XL pipeline</Title><Msg>Texas judge lifts order that halted work on Keystone XL pipeline By Molly Hennessy-Fiske December 13, 2012, 3:11 p.m. HOUSTON -- A Texas judge has lifted a temporary restraining order that had stopped oil company TransCanada from building a portion of the controversial Keystone XL pipeline through the eastern part of the state. The decision came after Michael Bishop, 64, a retired paramedic and chemist in East Texas, filed a lawsuit arguing that TransCanada defrauded him and other landowners in promising that the Keystone XL pipeline would transport crude oil, not tar sands. Texas County Court at Law Judge Jack Sinz lifted the temporary restraining order Thursday morning after a hearing in Nacogdoches. The proposed Keystone XL pipeline would carry oil from Canada to the Gulf Coast. TransCanada has yet to secure federal permission to build the vast majority of the route, but already had the go-ahead to build portions of the pipeline through Texas. TransCanada has been purchasing property for the project and, in some instances, condemning land through the power of eminent domain. Sinz had signed the temporary restraining order, which took effect Tuesday, after finding sufficient cause to stop work on the pipeline for two weeks. But he changed his mind after hearing from TransCanada's attorneys, who argued that Bishop understood what he was doing when he signed off on an easement agreement with the company three weeks ago. “TransCanada has been open, honest and transparent with Mr. Bishop at all times. We recognize that not everyone will support the construction of a pipeline or other facilities, but we work hard to reach voluntary agreements and maintain good relationships with landowners,” Shawn Howard, a TransCanada spokesman, said in a statement to the Los Angeles Times. “If we didn’t have a good relationship with more than 60,000 landowners across our energy infrastructure network, we wouldn’t be in business.” Howard added: “Since Mr. Bishop signed his agreement with TransCanada, nothing about the pipeline or the product it will carry has changed. While professional activists and others have made the same claims Mr. Bishop did today, oil is oil.” Bishop, a libertarian former Marine, had initially fought the company's attempt to condemn the land — 20 acres in the town of Douglass, about 160 miles east of Dallas — but eventually relented “under coercion and duress,” he said, because he could not afford his legal fees. The agreement with TransCanada was for $75,000, but after his lawyer and a Texas land agency took their cuts, Bishop said, he was left with about $3,800. Bishop represented himself, filing suit first against the Texas Railroad Commission, the state agency that oversees pipelines. He alleged that the commission failed to properly investigate the pipeline to protect public health and safety. He followed up with the latest lawsuit against TransCanada. “I’m disappointed, but by the same token a lot of ground was gained today,” Bishop told The Times, adding that the lawsuit drew public attention to the pipeline project. “This case is far from over,” he said. Next Wednesday both sides are scheduled to return to the Nacogdoches courthouse for a hearing before Judge Sinz. TransCanada will argue that Bishop should abide by the easement agreement, Howard said. Bishop will argue once more for an injunction to halt construction. “If I stop them on my property, other landowners are going to sit up and take notice. I look for landowners to start rebelling,” Bishop said. Other Texas landowners have gone to court and tried, so far unsuccessfully, to fight the company's land condemnations, which they argue have allowed TransCanada to seize land without owners' consent. On Thursday, some opponents of the pipeline protested outside the courthouse in Nacogdoches, toting signs with the words “Toxic tar sands” crossed out. Environmentalists have converged on East Texas this year to protest the pipeline's construction, arguing that if it leaks or spills, tar sands oil could cause dangerous contamination. Groups such as Tar Sands Blockade have protested at construction sites and highlighted the cases of landowners, including Bishop and Eleanor Fairchild, an East Texas great-grandmother arrested after a protest with actress Daryl Hannah on her property in October. President Obama encouraged construction of the Texas portion of the Keystone XL pipeline, but the administration has declined to approve the rest of the project, suggesting that TransCanada reroute the pipeline to avoid areas in Nebraska that environmentalists argue should be protected. Howard said the company has proposed a new route for that portion of the pipeline and was awaiting approval from state officials. latimesDOTcom/news/nation/nationnow/la-na-nn-texas-transcanada-pipeline-20121213,0,1239279DOTstory</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355466176065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 01:22:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355483881053-8</Id><Topic><Title>Infernal: Still stupid after all these years !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1355446591604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 19:56:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And your buddy nobumba stepping all over his dik you #$%$ #$%$ And he lied and cheated to win, numbers proved he didn't win. A town in ohio voted all dumbocraps and not 1 repub., now thats stupid cheating.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1355483881053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 06:18:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355496351314-9</Id><Title>How to Rebuild America</Title><Msg>1. Electrified rail system to service every urban area and town. Just give the contract to Deutsche Bahn and let them build it. 2. 70% tax on dividend income over $50,000/year. 3. 70% tax on capital gains income over $50,000/year 4. 70% tax on wages over $1,000,000/year. 5. Nationalized healthcare system and price controls on healthcare. 6. National drug monopoly to dictate prices to drug companies. 7. Free college education &amp; government funding to double the number of universities - focused on the sciences. 8. End foreign wars, and abolish aid to middle east countries.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355496351314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:45:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355497027685-10</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalist Criminals Washing $ For Murderous Drug Cartels</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461568754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:06:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but, but, those are small businesses! ...Legalize drugs and let big pharma supply it with a tax. Problem solved.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355497027685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355497629308-11</Id><Topic><Title>China’s New Solar Target: 40 GW By 2015 (8 Times More Than Its Initial 5 GW Target)</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355462828558</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:27:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AP-GfK Poll: Science doubters say world is warming By SETH BORENSTEIN — Dec. 14 9:50 AM EST Five Images WASHINGTON (AP) — Nearly 4 out of 5 Americans now think temperatures are rising and that global warming will be a serious problem for the United States if nothing is done about it, a new Associated Press-GfK poll finds. Belief and worry about climate change are inching up among Americans in general, but concern is growing faster among people who don't often trust scientists on the environment. In follow-up interviews, some of those doubters said they believe their own eyes as they've watched thermometers rise, New York City subway tunnels flood, polar ice melt and Midwestern farm fields dry up. Overall, 78 percent of those surveyed said they thought temperatures were rising and 80 percent called it a serious problem. That's up slightly from 2009, when 75 percent thought global warming was occurring and just 73 percent thought it was a serious problem. In general, U.S. belief in global warming, according to AP-GfK and other polls, has fluctuated over the years but has stayed between about 70 and 85 percent. The biggest change in the polling is among people who trust scientists only a little or not at all. About 1 in 3 of the people surveyed fell into that category. Within that highly skeptical group, 61 percent now say temperatures have been rising over the past 100 years. That's a substantial increase from 2009, when the AP-GfK poll found that only 47 percent of those with little or no trust in scientists believed the world was getting warmer. This is an important development because, often in the past, opinion about climate change doesn't move much in core groups — like those who deny it exists and those who firmly believe it's an alarming problem, said Jon Krosnick, a Stanford University social psychologist and pollster. Krosnick, who consulted with The Associated Press on the poll questions, said the changes the poll shows aren't in the hard-core "anti-warming" deniers, but in the next group, who had serious doubts. "They don't believe what the scientists say, they believe what the thermometers say," Krosnick said. "Events are helping these people see what scientists thought they had been seeing all along." Phil Adams, a retired freelance photographer from Washington, N.C., said he was "fairly cynical" about scientists and their theories. But he believes very much in climate change because of what he's seen with his own eyes. "Having lived for 67 years, we consistently see more and more changes based upon the fact that the weather is warmer," he said. "The seasons are more severe. The climate is definitely getting warmer." "Storms seem to be more severe," he added. Nearly half, 49 percent, of those surveyed called global warming not just serious but "very serious," up from 42 percent in 2009. More than half, 57 percent, of those surveyed thought the U.S. government should do a great deal or quite a bit about global warming, up from 52 percent three years earlier. But only 45 percent of those surveyed think President Barack Obama will take major action to fight climate change in his second term, slightly more than the 41 percent who don't think he will act. Overall, the 78 percent who think temperatures are rising is not the highest percentage of Americans who have believed in climate change, according to AP polling. In 2006, less than a year after Hurricane Katrina devastated New Orleans, 85 percent thought temperatures were rising. The lowest point in the past 15 years for belief in warming was in December 2009, after some snowy winters and in the middle of an uproar about climate scientists' emails that later independent investigations found showed no manipulation of data. Broken down by political party, 83 percent of Democrats and 70 percent of Republicans say the world is getting warmer. And 77 percent of independents say temperatures are rising. Among scientists who write about the issue in peer-reviewed literature, the belief in global warming is about 97 percent, according to a 2010 scientific study. The AP-GfK poll was conducted Nov. 29-Dec. 3 by GfK Roper Public Affairs and Corporate Communications. It involved landline and cellphone interviews with 1,002 adults nationwide. Results for the full sample have a margin of error of plus or minus 3.9 percentage points; the margin of error is larger for subgroups. The latest AP-GfK poll jibes with other surveys and more in-depth research on global warming, said Anthony Leiserowitz, director of Yale University's Project on Climate Change Communication. He took no part in the poll. When climate change belief was at its lowest, concerns about the economy were heightened and the country had gone through some incredible snowstorms and that may have chipped away at some belief in global warming, Leiserowitz said. Now the economy is better and the weather is warmer and worse in ways that seem easier to connect to climate change, he said. "One extreme event after another after another," Leiserowitz said. "People have noticed. ... They're connecting the dots between climate change and this long bout of extreme weather themselves." Thomas Coffey, 77, of Houston, said you can't help but notice it. "We use to have mild temperatures in the fall going into winter months. Now, we have summer temperatures going into winter," Coffey said. "The whole Earth is getting warmer and when it gets warmer, the ice cap is going to melt and the ocean is going to rise." He also said that's what he thinks is causing recent extreme weather. "That's why you see New York and New Jersey," he said, referring to Superstorm Sandy and its devastation in late October. "When you have a flood like that, flooding tunnels like that. And look at how long the tunnel has been there." bigstoryDOTapDOTorg/article/ap-gfk-poll-science-doubters-say-world-warming</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355497629308</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:07:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355497733592-12</Id><Topic><Title>China’s New Solar Target: 40 GW By 2015 (8 Times More Than Its Initial 5 GW Target)</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355462828558</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:27:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously China is acting to control climate change. Is there a republican in America who'll react to control climate change today? Contact your senators senateDOTgov/general/contact_information/senators_cfm.cfm Contact your representatives houseDOTgov/htbin/findrep Contact Speaker of the House John Boehner, R-Ohio speakerDOTgov/Contact/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355497733592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:08:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355498123066-13</Id><Title>Tougher Fracking Regulations Backed by 66%, Poll Shows</Title><Msg>Tougher Fracking Regulations Backed by 66%, Poll Shows By Mark Drajem - Dec 13, 2012 6:00 PM MT. 10 Comments Support for regulation of hydraulic fracturing has increased in the past three months, a sign that the gas-drilling practice is facing greater public scrutiny. A Bloomberg National Poll found that 66 percent of Americans want more government oversight of the process, known as fracking, in which water, chemicals and sand are shot underground to free gas trapped in rock. That’s an increase from 56 percent in a September poll. The poll found 18 percent favored less regulation, down from 29 percent three months ago. “More people are aware of fracking, and they are a little bit more opposed to it,” Sheril Kirshenbaum, director of the University of Texas Energy Poll, said in an interview. The school’s polls also have asked questions on the topic, and “it’s becoming more familiar,” she said. The Dec. 7-10 Bloomberg poll of 1,000 adults was conducted by Des Moines, Iowa-based Selzer &amp; Co. Public awareness will likely increase after “Promised Land,” a film starring Matt Damon, is released in January. The film highlights the affects of gas drilling on a small Pennsylvania town, as farmers get a boost in income while confronting the risk of contamination to their land and animals. Damon’s character seeks to get landowners to lease their land to his gas company. Water Supply “I’m a big proponent of natural gas, but I still need to be sure that we are not damaging our water supply,” Dan Lowery, a poll respondent from Warrenton, Virginia, said in explaining his support for greater regulation. “You can’t stick your head in the ground.” Industry groups for chemical, fertilizer and steel companies are trumpeting gains for the U.S. economy as natural gas supplies become more accessible. Low-cost natural gas could generate $72 billion in capital investment as petrochemical companies relocate or boost investments in the U.S., according to the American Chemistry Council. “This trend is vital to America’s prosperity,” Rayola Dougher, chief economist at the American Petroleum Institute, told reporters yesterday. “However, costly or duplicative regulation of hydraulic fracturing could be incredibly” harmful, she said. Global Warming On another subject, the poll showed 62 percent of those surveyed agreed the Earth’s temperature is rising “because of human activity,” up from 58 percent in September. Twenty-eight percent said it’s not, down from 34 percent three months ago. The Bloomberg Poll results reflect other surveys showing mounting public acceptance of the scientific consensus about global warming, reversing a drop in support during the global economic downturn that began in 2008. “We now have regained much, if not all, of that” loss in backing, said Edward Maibach, director of the Center for Climate Change Communication at Fairfax, Virginia-based George Mason University. There are differences in support by age. More than seven in 10 adults less than 35 years old support the proposition that human activity is causing global warming, while less than half of seniors do, according to the poll. Carbon-dioxide emissions since the Industrial Revolution have led to rising average temperatures in the past 50 years, according to the U.S. Global Change Research Program. A U.S. drought, about to enter its second year, has caused major economic damage from shriveled crops to low Mississippi River levels that are slowing barge traffic. Some researchers link the devastating affects of superstorm Sandy, which pummeled the East Coast in October, to rising sea levels and climate change’s propensity to lead to more and bigger storms. Skeptical Republicans Republicans are more skeptical of the science of climate change and have opposed steps to combat global warming, such as the failed cap-and-trade legislation aimed at reducing carbon and other harmful emissions that passed the House of Representatives in 2009. In the poll, 72 percent of Republicans rejected the notion that President Barack Obama gained a mandate to tackle climate change with his re-election last month. Democrats by 69% do read the election results as a call to action. Americans generally are split on the issue with 46 percent saying the president has a mandate to act on climate change and 46 percent saying he doesn’t. “The schisms between Republican and Democrats on this remain,” Maibach said in an interview. The poll has a margin of error of plus or minus 3.1 percentage points. bloombergDOTcom/news/2012-12-14/tougher-fracking-regulations-backed-by-66-poll-shows.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355498123066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:15:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355500885937-14</Id><Topic><Title>Infernal: Still stupid after all these years !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1355446591604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 19:56:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5 years and the stock has returned nothing - from Dec 07 to Dec 12 nothing. Treasury bonds are up about 60% over that period. And that is with oil over $100 just about the entire time. Wait and see what it will look like with oil at $40/bbl Epitaph: Wahleee boy! Wahleee boy! Wahleee boy!</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355500885937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:01:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355501256381-15</Id><Topic><Title>Tougher Fracking Regulations Backed by 66%, Poll Shows</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355498123066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:15:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lost in Germany. You will never win in America. It's two or three times more conservative on carbon issues... There are ways to get what you want but ranting mindlessly, as the Greens do, is not how.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355501256381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:07:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355502089067-16</Id><Topic><Title>How to Rebuild America</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355496351314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:45:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>other minor tweaks: 1. Introduce firm discipline in schools. 2. Punish truancy by removal of truants to state run boarding schools. 3. Hire a national police force, consisting of former military personnel, to impose order in the cities. 4. Put a 10,000% excise tax on all guns &amp; ammo sold in America.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355502089067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 11:21:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355504775961-17</Id><Topic><Title>We've got a bleeder</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355432571676</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over the last 5 years, XOM has performed at parity or better than the S&amp;P and DJI. The Naz has outperformed XOM, but the Naz has still not recovered from and/or caught up from its crash in '00-'01. Against peers, XOM has over the last 5 years out performed them except for CVX. Even in the case of CVX, its out performance is limited to a relatively short winodw over 2 yrs ago. In the last 2 years they have basically matched each other. The XTO purchase may have been a natgas purchase but it has also provided XOM access to NGLs and shale crude which have been very profitable. Plus over time, the length in US natgas will be soaked up. NG vehicles are coming, LNG exports have been approved and are coming, and there is a 20+ billion GTL facility to be constructed in the US. Natgas will recover closer to world pricing levels. XOM plays a long term game not in a qtr to qtr swing traderworld.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1355504775961</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:06:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355505169942-18</Id><Topic><Title>How to Rebuild America</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355496351314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:45:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>12 ideas and only 3 that have any realistic merit and even there your ideas a simplistic.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1355505169942</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:12:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355505758907-19</Id><Topic><Title>We've got a bleeder</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355432571676</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The stock has returned 1.7%/year on average the past 5 years and most of the time it was trading at loss to the Dec '07 level. That is a nothing return - savings accounts did that much. Treasury bonds have returned 10.4%/year, compounded, over the same period. The risk is lower on a Treasury bond as there is 0% chance of it ever defaulting, unless the United States collapses, and if that happens XOM will go to 0 anyway, as the U.S. government has the power to tax its dividends to near 100%, or its profits to break its own collapse. The US stock market as a whole and the indexes you mentioned have failed to beat Treasury Bonds since 1980, so looking for them as an excuse to explain Exxon's poor record the past 5 is not very helpful. Japanese stocks have failed over the same period against Japanese government bonds, as have the European stock markets against there's. Whenever interest rates go down it helps stocks by reducing what fixed income investors can earn, reducing the opportunity cost of capital, and increasing stock prices. Even so the stocks have still failed despite the push. How much more can interest rates go down? .. just about at 0 now. Exxon Mobil has been a failure the past 5 years, despite a highly unusual and statistically improbable high level of oil prices, one even the company admits is nothing but a bubble, and the benefit of falling Treasury bond rates reducing the required rate of return. It did well if you go back farther than 5 years, mainly by profiting from the commodity bubble that built up from 2000 on, and unusual good luck in many of its foreign investments, plus falling interests rates since the early 1980. It will not repeat that performance... The longer you hold it the more money you will lose, both in opportunity costs, and, going forward, outright losses as oil plummets with new supply and new technology...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355505758907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:22:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355506707540-20</Id><Topic><Title>How to Rebuild America</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355496351314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:45:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is progress. 3/12 from the libertarian camp...or whatever it is. The left would like some of them too and is actively pushing for it favorites. Of course they work well in practice. Europe has fabulous railroads, high taxes, and has pursued the national health system route for quite some time now. Germans are wealthier in assets now than Americas, per capita, and have equivalent income outside East Germany... With luck America can reach the superior European model, by which I mean the German middle way. You will like it fore, but it will take some adjustments to your personal interest most likely... Push for your 3 if it pleases you.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355506707540</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:38:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355507254833-21</Id><Topic><Title>How to Rebuild America</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355496351314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:45:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't even know which ones are the 3. But the facts are Europe is dying. Germany is doing well as they consume the carcass of the balance of the continent. But once that carcass is gone, they will suffer the same fate. High taxes and cetralized control will not ever succeed in the long run. The US is well on its way down that road, but just less so than some others. If the US continues the path their fate will be the same. Liberals like you (and yes you are definitely a liberal well on your way to socialist) always believe 'they know best' and 'the past doesn't matter, they did not do it right but we will this time'. Fact is that individuals working for their own best interest, forming their own unified groups, etc ultimately find better answers than a centralized state.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1355507254833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:47:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355507774051-22</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>Getting set to bust 88. 80 coming soon. Going back down to levels of 7 years ago. This stock's performance is awful.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355507774051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 12:56:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355509405348-23</Id><Topic><Title>How to Rebuild America</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355496351314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:45:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trivial pursuit doesn't entertain me. As for your statement that Europe is dying - back it up. Finding examples of countries with lower taxes (like Greece) or more Democratic governance (like Greece) or higher rates of real estate and other forms of speculation (like Spain &amp; the UK) doesn't back it up. I don't see Germany's relationship to the rest of Europe as parasitic either. Certainly many people move to Germany to take advantage of the fabulous infrastructure, public services, and low unemployment rate. I have no doubt that if America's current libertarian inspired policies continue there will be a flood of Americans who move to Germany rather than go down with a sinking ship. for information on Germany see: Statistisches Bundesamt. Click English and it translates... Back up your claims. I don't see how you can, but you can try. Germany has been following the strategy of very high level of government involvement in the economy since the 1870s. I don't see that strategy failing anytime soon. The Progressives copied what works, and much of it was German. Really, World War II was German v. German, only with more natural resources on the American end of the scale... Socialist? No... that is silly, but expected.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355509405348</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:23:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355510791033-24</Id><Title>ABC, NBC and CBS ignore union thugs</Title><Msg>It’s a sad day for American TV journalism when The Huffington Post is a more honest news outlet than ABC, CBS or NBC. On Tuesday, after Michigan union protests escalated into violence, HuffPo led with several stories, including one headlined: “Fox News Contributor Punched.” That story was about how Fox News contributor Steven Crowder and others were attacked by union thugs during the protest against the new “right-to-work” law. ABC, CBS and NBC covered the protests but only ABC made mention of police having to deal with protesters. None of them mentioned the attack on Crowder or showed the videos of that attack and the thugs tearing down a tent with people in it, both widely available on the Internet hours before the evening news show broadcast. No network quoted Teamsters head Jimmy Hoffa predicting “civil war” between lawmakers and union members. Network reporters don’t want to show union thugs and conservative victims, especially anyone connected to Fox News. That doesn’t fit with their world view. NBC anchor Brian Williams referred to it all meekly as “a boisterous day in the state capital.” According to The Detroit Free Press, three people were arrested and “Capt. Harold Love of the Michigan State Police confirmed police used pepper spray on at least one demonstrator.” The article added that the union protesters “tore down a tent being occupied by Americans for Prosperity, a pro right-to-work group,” while chanting “Tear it down, tear it down.” On broadcast news, the best they could all agree on was that the union thugs were some form of “angry.” On CBS “Evening News,” correspondent Elaine Quijano explained, “Union workers from across Michigan and other states voiced their anger at the Michigan capital.” ABC’s “World News with Diane Sawyer” correspondent Alex Perez did slightly hint at the escalation, but showed nothing at all scary. “The anger boiling over, officers turning to pepper spray to control the crowd, at last 10,000 deep,” he told viewers as one man was shown rubbing his eyes. Anchor Sawyer referred to the law as one that supporters “believe could be an ominous sign for unions and worker paychecks everywhere.” NBC “Nightly News” mentioned that there were at least police there at the protest, as correspondent Ron Mott admitted protesters operated under the “watchful gaze of police, some in riot gear.” Even The Washington Post mentioned that “Former Rep. Mark Schauer (D-Mich.) was hit with pepper spray while protesting ‘right to work/ legislation outside the Michigan state capitol on Wednesday.” None of that appeared on the evening news shows. That’s how reporters can control an agenda. Had journalists’ favorite villain the Tea Partiers beaten a liberal commentator, it would have led every newscast and would be talked about for days. Nor did they want to admit that union leadership was making threats and union thugs were carrying them out in vile and violent fashion. But network reporters don’t want to show union thugs and conservative victims, especially anyone connected to Fox News. That doesn’t fit with their world view. Ain’t that a punch in the head – or several in Crowder’s case?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1355510791033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:46:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355511295991-25</Id><Title>Another school tragedy</Title><Msg>Solution: 10,000% excise tax on guns &amp; ammo or pick a number. It would run just about every gun shop in America out of business... Something could be done about the existing stock of guns by putting an enormous property tax on each one...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355511295991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:54:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355511337055-26</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalist Criminals Washing $ For Murderous Drug Cartels</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461568754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:06:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Legalize drugs and stop all the killing both here and away. When a kid can stand on the street and look for cops and make $500/day why go to school. Do gooders think by looking and passing judgment on others they can throw money and the problem will just go away.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1355511337055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:55:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355512401041-27</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalist Criminals Washing $ For Murderous Drug Cartels</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461568754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:06:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The religious right has a vendetta against drugs- it is a vice as far as they are concerned. It was part of Nixon &amp; Reagan's pandering to the base. The policy has cost America a fortune in gun violence, prisons, court costs, police deaths and costs, and fueled the Mexican and Colombian cartels and their wars... It is time it ended.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355512401041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:13:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355512866860-28</Id><Topic><Title>Infernal: Still stupid after all these years !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1355446591604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 19:56:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was on this board long before you arrived and will still be on it after you leave. Learn to deal with it.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1355512866860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:21:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355513470669-29</Id><Title>EPA orders tougher limits on soot</Title><Msg>EPA orders tougher limits on soot By Ben Geman - 12/14/12 11:59 AM ET The Environmental Protection Agency is toughening air quality standards for fine particulate matter, or soot, over the objections of some industry groups and lawmakers. The agency unveiled final rules on Friday that ratchet down the annual exposure standard to 12 micrograms per cubic meter, a 20 percent reduction from the current standard of 15 micrograms. EPA had faced a court-ordered deadline Friday to complete the rules, which will cover a dangerous microscopic pollution that is emitted by factories and power plants, diesel vehicles, ships and many other sources. The agency touted the benefits of the rules Friday. “EPA estimates that meeting the annual primary fine particle standard of 12.0 μg/m3 will provide health benefits worth an estimated $4 billion to $9.1 billion per year in 2020 — a return of $12 to $171 for every dollar invested in pollution reduction. Estimated annual costs of implementing the standard are $53 million to $350 million,” EPA said in a summary of the rule. Public health and environmental groups cheered the action to further reduce emissions of the microscopic pollution, which reaches deep into the lungs and enters the bloodstream. Soot is linked to respiratory and cardiovascular problems such as asthma, bronchitis and irregular heartbeat. “We know clearly that particle pollution is harmful at levels well below those previously deemed to be safe. Particle pollution causes premature deaths and illness, threatening the millions of Americans who breathe high levels of it,” said Norman H. Edelman, the chief medical officer for the American Lung Association (ALA). “By setting a more protective standard, the EPA is stating that we as a nation must protect the health of the public by cleaning up even more of this lethal pollutant,” he said. ALA, along with other environmentalists and 11 states, had sued EPA to force revised soot rules. They were issued in draft form in June. Several industry groups, including the National Association of Manufacturers (NAM) and the American Petroleum Institute, opposed the tougher rules and warned they would thwart economic growth. NAM CEO Jay Timmons slammed EPA's decision on Friday and said the agency should stick with the standards set in 1997. “This new standard will crush manufacturers’ plans for growth by restricting counties’ ability to issue permits for new facilities, which makes them less attractive for new business. Essentially, existing facilities will have to be shuttered for new facilities to be built in these areas,” Timmons said in a statement. EPA disputed the industry criticisms, arguing that other existing EPA and state initiatives will ensure that most regions would be able to meet the new fine particulate matter requirements. “Emission reductions from EPA and states rules already on the books will help 99 percent of counties with monitors meet the revised PM2.5 standards without additional emission reductions. These rules include clean diesel rules for vehicles and fuels, and rules to reduce pollution from power plants, locomotives, marine vessels and power plants, among others,” EPA said . EPA plans to make designations about which counties aren't in attainment with the rules by the end of 2014, and states must provide implementation plans to EPA in 2018. States must come into compliance in 2020, but may seek extensions to as late as 2025, “depending on the severity of an area’s fine particle pollution problems and the availability of pollution controls,” EPA said. EPA went ahead with final rules despite eleventh-hour appeals from industry groups and Capitol Hill opponents of the tougher standards. In a letter Friday, five Republican senators and one Democrat — Louisiana Sen. Mary Landrieu — urged EPA Administrator Lisa Jackson to maintain the existing standard and work with states that are still implementing it. The senators say the tougher standards will “impose significant new economic burdens on many communities, hurting workers and their families just as they are struggling to overcome difficult economic times.” GOP Sens. Orrin Hatch (Utah), James Inhofe (Okla.), Rob Portman (Ohio) Roy Blunt (Mo.), and Mike Lee (Utah) signed the letter. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/273003-epa-rejecting-industry-pleas-toughens-soot-standards-</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355513470669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:31:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355514526557-30</Id><Topic><Title>EPA orders tougher limits on soot</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355513470669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:31:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gigantic Italian Oil Refiner Switches To Green Diesel November 13, 2012 By Tina Casey Leave a Comment In the midst of continuing economic travails across Europe, the largest petroleum refiner in Italy is placing a bet on biofuels. The Italian energy company Eni S.p.A. will retrofit one of its diesel refineries in Venice to produce renewable diesel, using a system designed by the Illinois-based Honeywell company UOP. The switch will eventually ecompass Eni’s entire operation in Venice and, if the project is a success, it could serve as a model for putting underused fossil fuel facilities back to work in the new green economy right here in the U.S.A. Converting a Diesel Refinery to Renewable Diesel Honeywell calls the new process UOP/Eni Ecofining, since it was developed jointly by UOP and Eni. Converting an existing refinery to Ecofining is fairly straightforward. The process does not require unusual extremes of heat or pressure and the resulting product, Green Diesel, is chemically identical to its petroleum counterpart. “The process for producing green diesel operates in mild conditions and integrates well within existing petroleum refineries,” according to UOP. // // The two-step process can use oils from conventional biofuel crops like soy and palm, but in practice UOP and Eni have already moved on to next-generation, non-edible oils such as algae oil. Also notably included are inedible animal tallow (waste from meat processors) and waste grease, which otherwise present thorny disposal issues. How Ecofining Works To simplify the procedure down to the bones (you can find complete details at UOP’s Green Diesel pages) — first the feedstock is pressurized and mixed with hydrogen, then sent to a catalytic reactor where it is deoxygenated. This part of the process yields propane, water, and carbon dioxide as byproducts. After the byproducts are removed, the resulting diesel gets another dose of hydrogen gas and is sent to a second reactor for further processing. The final distillation steps yield more byproducts including additional propane. Leftover hydrogen is also recaptured and sent back to the two reactors. As for the Green Diesel product itself, because it is chemically identical to petroleum, it can be used as a drop-in substitute, without any modifications to the vehicle or its engine, or to the fueling infrastructure. UOP also claims that Green Diesel provides better performance than conventional biodiesel, especially in cold weather. Ecofining in the U.S.A. Ecofining is already making inroads in the U.S. market, with the announcement last spring of a new Ecofining facility in Louisiana, built by the Chicago-based biofuel company Emerald Biofuels. That’s great as far as new refinery construction goes, but of much greater interest to environmental advocates in the U.S. is the potential for switching existing petroleum refineries to biofuel, since that could pull the rug out from under the controversial Keystone XL Pipeline. The Keystone XL project would not necessarily provide more oil to the U.S. market. Its purpose is to convey tar sands oil from Canada to the global market, through Gulf Coast refineries. So far, the</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355514526557</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:48:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355515613618-31</Id><Topic><Title>EPA orders tougher limits on soot</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355513470669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 14:31:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The conversion to renewable ALGAE oil is available. Eliminating subsidies for big oil along with a NEW implimentation of a five year phase out of production subsidies for GREEN diesel and ethanol. Refineries will make the conversion rather than installing expensive pollution controls on existing oil refineries.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355515613618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:06:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355516827724-32</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalist Criminals Washing $ For Murderous Drug Cartels</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461568754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:06:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The religious right is also the ones who blocked the vaccine for cancer because their child would not have sex before they were 18. Did they have sex by 18?</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1355516827724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:27:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355516868923-33</Id><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Msg>The school shooting will reduce the chances of a deal. Obama has another issue to mobilize his base now - a very logical and rational one and one he can count on the libertarians in the House digging trench lines to defend. The NRA and the radical Southerners can always be counted on to wave the flag for unlimited right to bear arms... If one looks at what Obama is asking for as well: unilateral power to borrow as much money as he wants without Congress' say, plus the lapse of the Bush tax cuts, except for his base (the majority of the USA), and meaningless cuts, it is obvious he does not want a deal at all. Why would he want one? If he does nothing the tax rates will increase, the GOP will take the blame, and the new Congress (with more Democrats in it) can come to the rescue in January... The enormously bloated military needs to be cut anyway, and it will make it easier to prevent war in the middle east next year if the military's ability to fight a war is reduced.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355516868923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:27:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355519351005-34</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>Will bust 88 Monday . Again worst large cap oil today. No chance for shareholders with idiotic Rex and his wrecking crew and their XTO. Total #$%$ destroying shareholders life savings- disgusting!</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355519351005</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:09:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355519431970-35</Id><Topic><Title>Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355519351005</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:09:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiots runnIng this company plain and simple.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355519431970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:10:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355519505272-36</Id><Topic><Title>Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355519351005</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:09:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tillerson wrecking crew couldn't run a lemonade stand.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355519505272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:11:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355524286966-37</Id><Title>Facts That Will Make Tea Bag Fascists Cheer!</Title><Msg>Just what you asked for you miserable rats. You hate working Americans and have sold out to the CEO Class that offshores jobs and takes their profits to foreign countriesWell here’s a depressing fact: Americans earning hourly wages didn’t see their average pay go up at all over the last year. Not even a little bit. Real average hourly earnings and real average weekly earnings were unchanged at 0.0 percent over the past year, adjusting for inflation, according to the Department of Labor. The data point is part of a troubling trend: American workers have been getting squeezed for decades. In some sectors, the problem is more extreme than in others. Minimum wage for restaurant workers has remained stagnant for 20 years thanks to lobbying. At the same time, CEO pay has skyrocketed, increasing more than 725 percent from 1978 to 2011, according to the Economic Policy Institute.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355524286966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:31:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355524584459-38</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan House of Fascists March In Lock Step..</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461445508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:04:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazing how the Hannity Hamsters disappear when they stick it to the working class. Shhhh! Don't mention how you're making life harder for working Americans you filthy maggots.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355524584459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:36:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355524926309-39</Id><Topic><Title>Another school tragedy</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355511295991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:54:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fox news will have experts palin and ted nugent on 2nite--their views will be countered by the prez of the NRA. then fox will convince their viewers that they have presented ALL sides of gun debate. the ref infern 4skin will all lick their tv screen in worship and know they have complete understanding--of ALL issues--once again</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1355524926309</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:42:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355525343423-40</Id><Topic><Title>Another school tragedy</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355511295991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 13:54:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Right Wing Fascists are inspired by the death.. They'll look to her Beck to re assure them and push them toward more death and destruction.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355525343423</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:49:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355526227281-41</Id><Title>Dead GOP Taking American Middle Class With Them To The Graveyard</Title><Msg>We are not having a debt crisis. Fred R. Conrad/The New York Times Paul Krugman Go to Columnist Page » Blog: The Conscience of a Liberal Opinion Twitter Logo. Connect With Us on Twitter For Op-Ed, follow @nytopinion and to hear from the editorial page editor, Andrew Rosenthal, follow @andyrNYT. Readers’ Comments Readers shared their thoughts on this article. Read All Comments (835) » It’s important to make this point, because I keep seeing articles about the “fiscal cliff” that do, in fact, describe it — often in the headline — as a debt crisis. But it isn’t. The U.S. government is having no trouble borrowing to cover its deficit. In fact, its borrowing costs are near historic lows. And even the confrontation over the debt ceiling that looms a few months from now if we do somehow manage to avoid going over the fiscal cliff isn’t really about debt. No, what we’re having is a political crisis, born of the fact that one of our two great political parties has reached the end of a 30-year road. The modern Republican Party’s grand, radical agenda lies in ruins — but the party doesn’t know how to deal with that failure, and it retains enough power to do immense damage as it strikes out in frustration. Before I talk about that reality, a word about the current state of budget “negotiations.” Why the scare quotes? Because these aren’t normal negotiations in which each side presents specific proposals, and horse-trading proceeds until the two sides converge. By all accounts, Republicans have, so far, offered almost no specifics. They claim that they’re willing to raise $800 billion in revenue by closing loopholes, but they refuse to specify which loopholes they would close; they are demanding large cuts in spending, but the specific cuts they have been willing to lay out wouldn’t come close to delivering the savings they demand. It’s a very peculiar situation. In effect, Republicans are saying to President Obama, “Come up with something that will make us happy.” He is, understandably, not willing to play that game. And so the talks are stuck. Why won’t the Republicans get specific? Because they don’t know how. The truth is that, when it comes to spending, they’ve been faking it all along — not just in this election, but for decades. Which brings me to the nature of the current G.O.P. crisis.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355526227281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:03:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355526291520-42</Id><Topic><Title>Dead GOP Taking American Middle Class With Them To The Graveyard</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355526227281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:03:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since the 1970s, the Republican Party has fallen increasingly under the influence of radical ideologues, whose goal is nothing less than the elimination of the welfare state — that is, the whole legacy of the New Deal and the Great Society. From the beginning, however, these ideologues have had a big problem: The programs they want to kill are very popular. Americans may nod their heads when you attack big government in the abstract, but they strongly support Social Security, Medicare, and even Medicaid. So what’s a radical to do? The answer, for a long time, has involved two strategies. One is “starve the beast,” the idea of using tax cuts to reduce government revenue, then using the resulting lack of funds to force cuts in popular social programs. Whenever you see some Republican politician piously denouncing federal red ink, always remember that, for decades, the G.O.P. has seen budget deficits as a feature, not a bug. Arguably more important in conservative thinking, however, was the notion that the G.O.P. could exploit other sources of strength — white resentment, working-class dislike of social change, tough talk on national security — to build overwhelming political dominance, at which point the dismantling of the welfare state could proceed freely. Just eight years ago, Grover Norquist, the antitax activist, looked forward cheerfully to the days when Democrats would be politically neutered: “Any farmer will tell you that certain animals run around and are unpleasant, but when they’ve been fixed, then they are happy and sedate.” O.K., you see the problem: Democrats didn’t go along with the program, and refused to give up. Worse, from the Republican point of view, all of their party’s sources of strength have turned into weaknesses. Democratic dominance among Hispanics has overshadowed Republican dominance among southern whites; women’s rights have trumped the politics of abortion and antigay sentiment; and guess who finally did get Osama bin Laden. And look at where we are now in terms of the welfare state: far from killing it, Republicans now have to watch as Mr. Obama implements the biggest expansion of social insurance since the creation of Medicare. So Republicans have suffered more than an election defeat, they’ve seen the collapse of a decades-long project. And with their grandiose goals now out of reach, they literally have no idea what they want — hence their inability to make specific demands. It’s a dangerous situation. The G.O.P. is lost and rudderless, bitter and angry, but it still controls the House and, therefore, retains the ability to do a lot of harm, as it lashes out in the death throes of the conservative dream. Our best hope is that business interests will use their influence to limit the damage. But the odds are that the next few years will be very, very ugly.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355526291520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:04:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355528688366-43</Id><Title>Management</Title><Msg>Shareholders are stuck with a management that 1) can't find oil (production shortfalls every year and steadily dwindling reserves) 2) can't seem to run an oil company (steadily falling earnings and earnings misses) 3) carried out the worst acquisition in the history of American business-XTO (read the contemporaneous accounts of the deal they all said that Exxon overpaid and that was before anyone knew NG would plunge as it has-even at then prevailing NG prices it was clear the deal was awful. This management is so out of its depth running Exxon that it would be funny if it weren't so destructive of shareholder wealth Five years of dismal underperformance of this dog and no end in sight.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355528688366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:44:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355531608121-44</Id><Topic><Title>Infernal: Still stupid after all these years !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1355446591604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 19:56:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The typical lib reaction to those who disagree with their idiotic notions. Aren't you going to threaten to beat me up - one of your favorite tactics? (developed in the courtroom I'm sure)</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1355531608121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:33:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355531861458-45</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan House of Fascists March In Lock Step..</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461445508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:04:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr brain death opines again - and wrongly as always.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1355531861458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:37:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355531984995-46</Id><Topic><Title>Management</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355528688366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:44:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is your short position not doing as well as you had hoped?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1355531984995</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 19:39:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355543491453-47</Id><Topic><Title>Dead GOP Taking American Middle Class With Them To The Graveyard</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355526227281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:03:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Krugman?!! He's almost as big a joke as you are.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1355543491453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 22:51:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>