<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-01"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354344366817-1</Id><Title>Doha, focus on laying the groundwork 4 a deal limiting fossil fuel emissions that would take effect by 2020</Title><Msg>focus on laying the groundwork for a deal limiting fossil-fuel emissions that would take effect by 2020. The plan would revisit the effort to enact targets that failed in Copenhagen in 2009, when the meeting dissolved into finger-pointing between rich and poorer nations over which should move first on emissions. The new effort would require the biggest emitters, the United States, China and India, to join carbon dioxide curbs in force in the European Union and Australia.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354344366817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:46:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354344437286-2</Id><Topic><Title>Doha, focus on laying the groundwork 4 a deal limiting fossil fuel emissions that would take effect by 2020</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354344366817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:46:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>URL at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354344437286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 01:47:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354372775068-3</Id><Title>GOP lawmakers say fracking study could hurt job growth</Title><Msg>GOP lawmakers say fracking study could hurt job growth By Zack Colman - 11/30/12 03:21 PM ET A group of GOP House energy leaders advised Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius to exercise caution in a possible study on the health impacts of natural-gas drilling. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is considering examining a potential link between hydraulic fracturing, or fracking, and drinking water contamination. The lawmakers sent a letter to Sebelius Friday stating that such a study could stymie job growth if not properly executed. They expressed concern in the letter that naturally occurring substances in groundwater could be improperly labeled as contaminants. “Despite the significant growth of natural gas development, we are greatly concerned that the scientific objectivity of the Department of Health and Human Services is being subverted and countless jobs could be in jeopardy,” the lawmakers said. Signatories included House Energy and Commerce Committee Chairman Fred Upton (Mich.); Rep. Ed Whitfield (Ky.), the committee’s Energy and Power subcommittee chairman; Rep. Joe Pitts (Pa.), the committee’s Health subcommittee chairman; Rep. John Shimkus (Ill.), the committee’s Environment and the Economy subcommittee chairman; and past committee chairman Rep. Joe Barton (Texas). Fracking is the drilling method credited with driving the nation’s shale gas boom. It involves injecting a high-pressure mixture of water, sand and chemicals into tight rock formations to tap hard-to-reach gas deposits. Environmentalists, along with many congressional Democrats, argue fracking pollutes drinking water. But industry, along with lawmakers from both sides of the aisle, says the practice is safe. They contend state regulators have ably handled fracking oversight, and that connections between fracking and groundwater contamination are faulty. The Obama administration also has praised states’ regulatory record on fracking, while simultaneously calling for new regulations on federal lands. The Environmental Protection Agency already is conducting a national study on fracking’s effects on drinking water. A progress report on that study is expected by the end of the year. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/270387-house-gop-members-urge-caution-on-fracking-study</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354372775068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 09:39:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354374784210-4</Id><Title>US to sell offshore wind leases Massachusetts, Rhode Island, and Virginia</Title><Msg>US to sell offshore wind leases Federal plans to sell competitive leases next year for offshore wind farms off Massachusetts, Rhode Island, and Virginia are a first. Each offshore wind farm could power 700,000 homes. By Michelle R. Smith, Associated Press / December 1, 2012 PROVIDENCE, R.I. The federal government plans to sell leases for wind farms off the coasts of Rhode Island, Massachusetts and Virginia, marking the first time it has sold competitive leases for wind energy on the outer continental shelf, officials said Friday. The leases for the two areas, which total more than 430 square miles, will be sold next year, the Department of Interior and its Bureau of Ocean Energy Management said. "Wind energy along the Atlantic holds enormous potential, and today we are moving closer to tapping into this massive domestic energy resource to create jobs, increase our energy security and strengthen our nation's competitiveness in this new energy frontier," Interior Secretary Ken Salazar said in a written statement. The announcement was hailed by the conservation group Oceana, which called it a major step in developing domestic clean energy. "We're getting a step closer to seeing real turbines out there in the water," said Nancy Sopko, the group's ocean advocate. "The more progress is made, it sends that signal out to the rest of the world that the U.S. is serious about developing wind energy here." The zone off Rhode Island and Massachusetts, which sits a little about 10 miles off Rhode Island's shore, will be leased in two parcels. The Virginia area, about 27 miles off the southern part of the state, will be available as a single lease, the Department of Interior said. Officials said each area could be developed to generate enough electricity to power 700,000 homes. The plan is part of an Obama administration strategy to focus energy development in areas with the greatest potential and to work with states, commercial fishermen and other stakeholders early in the process to address possible conflicts, said Tommy P. Beaudreau, director of the Bureau of Ocean Energy Management. There are no offshore wind farms in the United States, although several are already in development off Massachusetts, Rhode Island, New Jersey and Delaware. The Rhode Island and New Jersey developments are in state waters, while the Delaware lease was not awarded in a competitive process, Sopko said. The Cape Wind project, in federal waters off Cape Cod in Massachusetts, was the nation's first offshore wind project to be approved and predates the system that has since been put into place, Sopko said. It is scheduled to be up and running in 2015. A project under development in Rhode Island, which includes just a handful of turbines, is scheduled to go online in 2014, which is would make it the nation's first offshore wind farm. csmonitorDOTcom/Environment/Latest-News-Wires/2012/1201/US-to-sell-offshore-wind-leases</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354374784210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 10:13:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354379975597-5</Id><Title>The left is aroused...</Title><Msg>The oligarchs in Congress have been meeting behind closed doors and working on a plan to shift the military cuts that begin in Jan to the poor and middle class, with cuts to entitlements, instead. The entitlement programs are excellent methods of wealth redistribution, especially Medicaid, which should be expanded to cover the entire population not on Medicare. The idea of cutting them to preserve wasteful military spending is just economically idiotic. Obama is pushing a much harder line now though. Yes, he touched the fence and realized it is live.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354379975597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:39:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354384537190-6</Id><Topic><Title>The left is aroused...</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354379975597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:39:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no doubt there are PLENTY of govt programs that need REDUCTION the military waste/spending needs the biggest CUT--20-25% right now--stop the nonsense maybe a trigger mechanism??--for every 1% cut in "social programs" a 2% cut in military so 5% in medicare gets 10% in military cut 5% in medicaid gets another 10% in military 5% in social security gets another 10% in military cut looks like a GREAT place to start--all the "giveaways" get a 5% cut and military gets a 30% cut DO IT NOW</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1354384537190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 12:55:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354386220270-7</Id><Topic><Title>The left is aroused...</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354379975597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:39:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2000 defense spending was $358.6 billion, which includes $47 billion in veterans spending. FY 2012 came in at $902.2 billion, which includes $129.6 billion in veterans spending. The increase in veterans spending is mostly the result of Bush's Iraq war. A more reasonable would be 2% of GDP in defense spending, which is about $320. If you add the wastage from the Iraq War on top, accruing in VA benefits the total comes to $450 billion/year. -- A 50% cut in the overall military outlay ($450 billion), and about 40% of the deficit plugged. $1 in entitlement cuts for every $2 of defense spending, as you mentioned, would comes to another $225 billion/year. 225 + 450 + ending the Bush tax cuts for the top 2%, and abolishing corporate welfare just about balances the budget.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354386220270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 13:23:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354389554616-8</Id><Topic><Title>The left is aroused...</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354379975597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:39:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roman, Your $450B per year spent on our military is less than half of what we spend on the illegal community (Food, Education, Jail Space, etc.).Rule that!</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1354389554616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:19:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354390311305-9</Id><Topic><Title>The left is aroused...</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354379975597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 11:39:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Federal military spending in 2012 is $902.2 billion. Federal welfare spending was $451.2 billion. Federal spending on police, prisons, and courts was $62 billion. Your math does not add up... Cut the military outlay 50% (really 60% as you cannot really cut VA) End the drug war. Close foreign military bases. Abolish the Bush tax cuts for the top 2%. End Corporate welfare. The budget balances... Immigrants are key to achieve this. They destroy the GOP's grip on the country, and they pay taxes.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354390311305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 14:31:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354392323360-10</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner growing a tail?</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354303041141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:17:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is headed for Hawaii for 3 weeks of vacation soon, so really there are only 2 weeks left for the tax negotiations. Boehner is ranting about no progress, and I'm sure there is none, as he has not kissed the ring and admitted his manifold errors yet. Time is running short for Boehner. Obama gets about 90% of what he wants by doing nothing so he is in a comfortable position. They can patch over the other 10% with a new bill in January when there are more Democrats in the Congress to pass it.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354392323360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 15:05:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354407327887-11</Id><Title>Dec 31, 2013</Title><Msg>The economy should have gone into a deep recession by then and I will be buying stocks heavily on that day, perhaps even Exxon Mobil. Between the taxes, and the oil price, and the utter rout of a major political party (always bad for short term financial stability) the stars are aligned for that day to be a buy - certainly not now of course. I will spend a year and month touring the Alps and squandering as much money as I can (short selling profits collected courtesy of Barack Obama's win mostly lol) Auf Wiedersehen</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354407327887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 19:15:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354416264424-12</Id><Title>See No Evil Media avert eyes from Democratic campaign finance hypocrisy</Title><Msg>f a campaign finance story is not about David Koch or Sheldon Adelson, do liberals care? Consider the reaction to Kenneth Vogel’s important report on the winter meeting of the Democracy Alliance, the secretive organization of progressive millionaires and billionaires who finance an extraordinarily byzantine network of liberal foundations and Super PACs that operate with undisclosed “dark money.” What reaction? Exactly. There wasn’t any. The left-wing VIPs assembled at the luxury W Hotel across the street from the White House, but only Vogel reported on the story. The gathering did not merit inclusion in either the Washington Post or the New York Times, both of which have offices within blocks of the W, and both of which have devoted reams of newsprint to Mitt Romney’s donor retreats and various Koch-affiliated fundraising summits. Was New York Times campaign finance reporter Nicholas Confessore too busy appearing on NOW with Alex Wagner to cover the event? More likely the media simply ignore data that complicate their preferred narrative. When it comes to the fraught relationship between money and politics, that narrative is as follows: Money in politics is corrupting only because rich businessmen trade campaign donations to Republicans for low taxes and fewer environmental regulations. The 2010 Supreme Court ruling in the Citizens United case, the narrative continues, assisted such transactions by treating corporate and union PAC donations as protected speech. Republicans are better at fundraising because they are selfish, whereas Democrats are more concerned with the common good. And when Democrats abandon the principles of campaign finance reform, they do so with heavy hearts and the tragic sense that they could not compete otherwise. The end. Not only is this fairy tale nonsense, it is the biggest myth in American politics. Liberals use this just-so story to salve their consciences and reinforce their collective prejudices against conservatives. They cannot conceive that progressive donors engage in the exact sort of influence peddling they so lustily condemn. This willful refusal to face facts leads to repression and confusion. A liberal whose understanding of the 2012 election derived from mainstream media and Team Obama emails would not know that the president’s campaign outraised and outspent Mitt Romney’s campaign by hundreds of millions of dollars. She would be unaware that three of the top five Super PACs were aligned with Democrats. Indeed the overall Republican financial advantage was minimal, a little more than 10 percent. That figure does not include the indirect spending by labor unions that is hard to track. The Democratic Party, meanwhile, has outraised the Republican Party in each of the last three election cycles. Remind me where the GOP’s huge money advantage lies? The liberal handwringing over Citizens United is all for show. Obama reversed himself on Super PACs in 2012 just as he reversed himself on public financing in 2008.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354416264424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:44:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354416338953-13</Id><Topic><Title>See No Evil Media avert eyes from Democratic campaign finance hypocrisy</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354416264424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:44:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earlier this year the Democracy Alliance scraped away groups that were not affixed like barnacles to the hull of the Democratic Party and left alone the groups that were. One of the founders of the Democracy Alliance, the hedge fund investor George Soros, announced at an Alliance luncheon in New York City in late September that he would donate $1 million to Priorities USA Action, the pro-Obama Super PAC that accused Mitt Romney of killing a woman with cancer. Progressives bemoan the influence of big money even as they write seven-figure checks. Did Obama campaign on removing money from politics or on altering our ridiculous and clearly ineffective campaign finance laws? Has he put such reform at the top of his agenda? Do pigs fly? The president understands the importance of dark money to the Democratic machine. So do his fellow partisans. We learn from Vogel that the speakers at the three-day Democracy Alliance conference this month included Nancy Pelosi, Sen. Charles Schumer of New York, Sens.-elect Elizabeth Warren of Massachusetts and Tammy Baldwin of Wisconsin, New York Attorney General Eric Schneiderman, representatives from Priorities USA, opposition research outfit American Bridge 21st Century, and pro-abortion rights lobby EMILY’s List. So the upper echelon of the political party that controls the White House, the Senate, the executive bureaucracy, and is 17 seats away from a House majority is committed to a group of insanely wealthy people who avoid disclosure and accountability by indirectly funding nonprofits. Yet this same party howls that Republicans are in the pocket of wealthy individuals. If only George Soros could buy the Democrats a sense of irony. Elizabeth Warren is a special case. She and her opponent famously signed a “People’s Pledge” to limit outside spending in the Massachusetts Senate election. But so much depends on the meanings of “spending” and “outside.” Not only is Warren linked to the Soros-affiliated think tank Demos through her daughter, who runs it, her campaign was launched with donations from the Soros family and received $2 million in assistance in the final weeks of the contest from the Harry Reid-affiliated Majority PAC. She outraised and out-spent Scott Brown. The Center for Responsive Politics found that she disclosed far less of the sources of her funding than Brown did. Yet no one can doubt she told her secret donors at the Democracy Alliance meeting that as a United States senator she would fight against the influence of the rich. “Ah,” liberals will say, “you haven’t mentioned that these rich liberal donors have no economic interest to pursue.” I haven’t because that idea is self-serving baloney. These men and women who have inherited or made their fortunes already may not care whether taxes rise on households making more than $250,000 a year. They can afford it. Yet to assume that tax rates are the only economic interest at work is to hold a crimped and facile view of politics. Taxes on income, capital gains, and dividends are just the beginning. The individuals and foundations that comprise the Democratic fundraising base in general and the Democracy Alliance in particular benefit from tax subsidies and mandates for non-carbon energy; from government-funded research and development; from trade and tax policies that favor Hollywood and Silicon Valley; from measures that increase union membership and therefore dues to union bosses; from infrastructure spending that directs funds to construction unions; and from housing and development projects that provide well compensated livelihoods to social workers, foundation executives, and—dare one say it—community organizers. Money buys access and patronage. A New York Times review “showed that those who donated the most to Mr. Obama and the Democratic Party since he started running for president were far more likely to visit the White House than others.” The Huffington Post “found 28 individuals of ambassadorial rank who had raised a total of more than $14 million for the president.” One such ambassador, Matthew Barzun, grandson of the recently deceased historian Jacques Barzun, quit his post to raise money for Obama’s reelection and was a speaker at the Democracy Alliance’s winter meeting. Another Times review of the administration’s relationship with utility giant Exelon “shows how familiarity has helped foster access at the upper reaches of government and how, in some cases, the outcome has been favorable for Exelon.” The administration assisted DreamWorks Animation CEO and Priorities USA donor Jeffrey Katzenberg in negotiating a deal with Chinese leader Xi Jinping. Performance artist Will Smith felt his donations to Obama earned him the privilege to lobby the administration for rapper T.I.’s release from jail. It is easy to lose track of these stories since they are buried by a press that focuses myopically and quizzically on the hapless Republicans, on who gives conservatives donations and why, on the minutest hypocrisy in which those conservatives indulge, on the tiniest divisions between the traditionalists and the neocons and the libertarians, on the endless and navel-gazing “soul searching” in which the party of Lincoln and TR and Reagan seems endlessly to engage, on whether or not Obama “likes” McCain and Romney, and on who is preparing to run in a presidential election that is four, yes four, years away. A press interested in equal treatment of the two parties would have noted for example that one of the first meetings Obama held after his reelection was with “labor and civic leaders” (his words) many of whom are tied to the Democracy Alliance. Among the messages conveyed at the discussion was the president’s avowal to keep the money flowing. The left’s investment would continue to earn a dividend. “We’re not going away,” Priorities USA adviser Paul Begala told Politico. Nor would one expect the outside groups and networks to vanish after their remarkable success. Left-wing institutions and pressure groups have recovered after years of retreat from a unified and energetic right. They have resumed construction of the intricate, inefficient, and over-budget public works project known as the American welfare state. The liberal donors want in on the action. There are stories to be told. But is the mainstream media even awake?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354416338953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-01 21:45:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>