<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345262895000-1</Id><Topic><Title>False Left vs Right Paradigm</Title><Username>joe_rudi_49</Username><Timestamp>1345131394000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When has Bibi's agenda ever been in America's interests</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345262895000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345292722000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Medicare "Plan" Will Cost $10,000\Yr Out of Pocket</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345264170000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:29:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More lies wahleee boy. Tiresome. Try the truth sometime and see how it feels.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345292722000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:25:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345292852000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Family Fortune Leveraged On Gov Highway Projects</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345265500000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:51:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahlee the commie spokesman is the liar.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345292852000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345292986000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Reduces Payments To Companies, Ryan Cuts $$ To Patients</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345264254000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:30:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wahlee lies so bad you could sit at the tip of his nose and take a ride to the moon. Come back from the moon at the end of nobumbas nose.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345292986000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:29:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345293038000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Medicare "Plan" Will Cost $10,000\Yr Out of Pocket</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345264170000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:29:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahlleee must have his lips wrapped around nobumba.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345293038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345293332000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Stock split</Title><Username>joelverburg</Username><Timestamp>1345160833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stench dos'nt have 2 nickels to rub together nor does he have any shares of stock.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345293332000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:35:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345293443000-7</Id><Topic><Title>World Business Leaders Say Obama Better 4 Economy</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345233738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forget it wahlee your bomb commie nobumba lost. Big business in america putting the screws to the commie regime. You and maxi dopey get packing.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345293443000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345295347000-8</Id><Topic><Title>B.C. newspaper tycoon proposing $13-billion oil refinery for Northern Gateway oil (with poll)</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345226572000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Process Bitumen Here Says Councilor By 250 News Saturday, August 18, 2012 03:53 AM Prince George, B.C. – Five of the nine members of Prince George City Council have now given some response to the question of whether they support or oppose the Enbridge Northern Gateway Pipeline proposal. 250 News posed the question to learn where council, collectively, and members of council, individually, stand on the highly controversial proposal to pipe bitumen to tankers off the B.C. coast. City council has not taken a formal position one way or the other at this point. Councilor Frank Everitt says much work remains to be done on the project. “I believe we must go through the environmental review, as well as (holding) consultation through the area of the suggested route. Once that has been done and has been approved, then and only then does it make sense to have a plan.” Everitt continues that there must be economic benefits to British Columbia. “We should not be just the province that the pipeline goes through. We should be manufacturing the bit-chum in this province to provide good paying jobs for our citizens.” Everitt draws a parallel with raw log exports, which he says “should be manufactured here so we are selling a finished product to the rest of the world.” Councilor Murray Krause responds “the City does not have an official position on Northern Gateway and I will be reserving my opinion for that debate.” Councilor Albert Koehler has voiced support for the project while councilor Brian Skakun has not, to this point, been supportive. Mayor Shari Green will not respond to 250 News. The remaining four members of council have also been asked for their thoughts on the pipeline project. http://www.opinion250.com/blog/view/25421/1/process+bitumen+here+says+councilor</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345295347000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345295507000-9</Id><Title>This doesn't change anything, pipeline opponents say</Title><Msg>This doesn't change anything, pipeline opponents say By Judith Lavoie, Times Colonist August 18, 2012 4:03 AM Opposition to the proposed Enbridge Northern Gateway pipeline is not diminished by a proposal to build a $13-billion refinery near Kitimat, First Nations and environmental groups said on Friday. "This doesn't change anything," said Grand Chief Stewart Phillip, Union of B.C. Indian Chiefs president. "We are still faced with the spectre of a very high-risk pipeline going through rugged terrain and being sponsored by a company that has an absolutely atrocious safety record." If the pipeline and refinery are approved, tankers would carry refined fuel, which, if there is a spill, is easier to clean up than bitumen. But tankers would still face treacherous navigation issues, storms and a rugged coastline, Phillip said. The unchanging opposition was echoed by Geraldine Thomas-Flurer, co-ordinator of the Yinka Dene Alliance. About 25 per cent of the pipeline would be on Yinka Dene Alliance traditional territory and chiefs have made it abundantly clear that they will not allow it to cross their rivers, Thomas-Flurer said. That will not be changed by the prospect of an oil refinery, which would pollute the air, or the promise of refinery jobs, she said. "We have 130 First Nations who have signed on in support of a tanker ban and 130 First Nations can't be wrong," Thomas-Flurer said. Heiltsuk First Nation Chief Marilyn Slett said the community was taken aback by the sudden announcement about the planned refinery. "Our concerns are still the great risk to the coast," she said. The severity of an oil spill depends not only on the substance spilled, but also on the area in which it happens and whether there are salmon runs or animals such as whales in the immediate vicinity, said Eric Swanson of the Dogwood Initiative. Like others, Swanson is concerned about the lack of community consultation. "The best ideas are the ones that start at the community level, with First Nations and local government support, and work up from there," he said. "This is a $13-billion mega-project that came out of nowhere." Josh Paterson, West Coast Environmental Law staff lawyer, said the refinery plan appears to be a desperate attempt to salvage the Northern Gateway pipeline. "I don't think dumping an oil refinery in the middle of the Great Bear Rainforest and right beside the Kitimat River is the way to do that," Peterson said. "This is not a game changer." Tankers would still be plying dangerous waters and the Queen of the North sinking demonstrates the lasting effects of refined oil, Paterson said. "Beaches are still contaminated around there and First Nations can't use them for harvesting," he said. http://www.timescolonist.com/business/This+doesn+change+anything+pipeline+opponents/7111131/story.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345295507000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:11:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345295544000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Medicare "Plan" Will Cost $10,000\Yr Out of Pocket</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345264170000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:29:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are very busy these days. I hear the govt is now sibsidizing another program, this one for Wahlee and his profession. No wonder we are a 3rd world country. wahlee has no accoutability to perform well!!!! he will be deported soon enough, tailand has several shops he can work in. they pay very well</Msg><Username>wahleee_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1345295544000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345295723000-11</Id><Title>Oil producers say economics will decide fate of Black’s refinery plan</Title><Msg>Oil producers say economics will decide fate of Black’s refinery plan By GORDON HAMILTON, VANCOUVER SUN August 17, 2012 •Photos ( 9 ) http://www.vancouversun.com/business/2035/producers+economics+will+decide+fate+Black+refinery+plan/7108636/story.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345295723000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:15:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345296277000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Family Fortune Leveraged On Gov Highway Projects</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345265500000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:51:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are truly an idiot wahleee boy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345296277000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345296903000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Medicare "Plan" Will Cost $10,000\Yr Out of Pocket</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345264170000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:29:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Several lies in one post. Still tiresome.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345296903000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345296974000-14</Id><Title>No Iran Attack this year</Title><Msg>Google debka file. Possibly one next spring.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345296974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345297100000-15</Id><Title>"level the playing" field for wind versus fossil fuels - 2nd last paragraph</Title><Msg>Wind Tax Credit at Center of Presidential Election Spat By Jon Hurdle Published: August 16, 2012 The scheduled expiration of a production tax credit for the wind industry has taken center stage in the energy policy debate between President Obama and Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney. Recommended for you Technology The Controversial 2011 Wind Technologies Market Report Source: Department of Energy The credit, which allows taxpayers to claim 2.2 cents for every kilowatt hour of wind energy produced by a utility-scale wind farm, is due to expire on Dec. 31, 2012, a prospect that is already causing layoffs in the wind industry, according to its advocates. For much more on the PTC, download AOL Energy's Wind Rush white paper here. That's fine with Governor Romney who says he would allow the credit to expire and end other renewable-energy subsidies in order to foster more competition between all forms of energy. The Four Letter Word: "Jobs" But President Obama is urging Congress to extend the credit, saying 37,000 jobs could be lost if it expires. "We're at a moment right now when homegrown energy, like wind energy, is creating new jobs all across Iowa and all across the country," Obama said in speech in Iowa this week, a leading wind-producing state. "And guess what? Governor Romney said let's get rid of tax credits for wind-energy production." Faced with the policy uncertainty, some makers of wind technology have already been laying off workers. They include 182 at Vestas, a leading manufacturer of wind turbines; and 167 workers who will lose their jobs at DMI in Tulsa, Oklahoma by November, according to data from the American Wind Energy Association. "Unfortunately, the industry has begun letting workers go up and down our manufacturing supply chain," said AWEA CEO Denise Bode. On the same day that President Obama visited Iowa, the Department of Energy released a report saying wind power contributed almost a third of all new electric capacity last year, and accounted for $14 billion in new investment. The industry employs 75,000 people, and about 70% of the equipment installed at U.S. wind farms is now American-made, up from 35% in 2005, the DOE said. But the industry would face a "dramatic slowing" in 2013 if the PTC is allowed to expire, the DOE said in its Wind Technologies Market Report. A spokeswoman for Romney said he supports concentrating alternative energy funding on basic research but does not favor supporting specific industries. "He does not believe we should be in the business of picking winners and losers or steering investment toward politically favored approaches," she said. http://energy.aol.com/2012/08/16/wind-tax-credit-at-center-of-presidential-election-spat/#?icid=apb1#page1</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297100000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345297110000-16</Id><Topic><Title>"level the playing" field for wind versus fossil fuels - 2nd last paragraph</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297100000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Governor Romney's opposition to the PTC is at odds with some fellow Republicans on the US Senate Finance Committee, who voted on August 2 to extend the credit until the end of 2013, as well as extending dozens of other tax incentives, in a 19-5 vote that PTC supporters say is a clear signal of bipartisan support for the measure. The panel also approved a one-year extension of an investment tax credit for the offshore wind industry. Republican support for the wind industry may be no surprise given recent donations from the industry, according to Federal Election Commission filings. The donations include $5,000 to Senator Chuck Grassley of Iowa, a leading supporter of extending the PTC. Grassley said the extension would "level the playing" field for wind versus fossil fuels, and predicted the committee's strong vote for the measure puts the PTC in a "strong position" for a vote of the full Senate this Fall. Democrats have also benefited from donations by the AWEA's political action committee. They include Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid who received $5,000 this year, according to FEC filings.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297110000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345297385000-17</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Dropping like the Titanic! Need some Relief</Title><Username>weberchandler470</Username><Timestamp>1345294671000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 08:57:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every thing has its own ups and downs.More likely if i had to invest,i would have invested my amount on it! i think u would be a more profitable person.thank u.</Msg><Username>everette_h</Username><Timestamp>1345297385000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345297805000-18</Id><Title>Interior secretary outlines development plan for NPRA</Title><Msg>Interior secretary outlines development plan for NPRA Posted 08/17/2012 by - Margaret Bauman A proposed plan that would allow for additional oil and gas development, while protecting wildlife in the National Petroleum Reserve-Alaska, was unveiled in Anchorage on Aug. 13 by Interior Secretary Ken Salazar. Salazar said the plan, which is to be finalized by December, will assure the conservation values of the national reserve, subsistence use and the nation’s need for oil are taken into account. “This is the first time we have had an integrated management plan for the whole 22 million acres,” he said. He spoke passionately about the importance of proceeding with development in a manner that would not harm the region’s iconic environment. “We want to make sure we don’t mess it up,” he said. “It has to be done right so that the conservation values that are so unique to the 22 million acres are in fact honored and are in fact protected.” He noted the dependence of a number of people in villages scattered across the Arctic in Alaska on the Western Arctic and Teshekpuk caribou herds, as well as other wildlife. Salazar, fresh from two days of traveling on the North Slope, had spent one night at Nuiqsit, talking with residents and playing basketball too. He also met with officials from the U.S. Coast Guard and federal Bureau of Land Management and former North Slope Borough Mayor Ed Itta at Itta’s subsistence camp. “To harness the oil and gas potential of the NPR-A, we need a plan that will help the industry bring energy safely to market from this remote location, while also protecting wildlife and subsistence rights of Alaska Natives,” he said. “This proposal would allow us to continue to expand our leasing in the NPR-A, as we have done over the last three years as part of the Obama Administration’s focus on expanding safe and responsible oil and gas development, and builds on our efforts to help companies develop the infrastructure that’s need to bring supplies online. “This plan also strikes an important balance by recognizing the need to protect America’s treasures in the Arctic, from the raptors of the Colville River and the polar bears of the Beaufort Sea coast, to Teshekpuk Lake, Peard Bay and some of the largest caribou herds on Earth.” Under the proposed plan about 11.8 million of the 22 million acres would be available for leasing. That area is http://www.thecordovatimes.com/article/1233interior-secretary-outlines-development-plan</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345297839000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Interior secretary outlines development plan for NPRA</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:50:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That area is estimated to hold approximately 549 million barrels of discovered and undiscovered economically recoverable oil and approximately 8.7 trillion cubic feet of discovered and undiscovered economically recoverable natural gas. Salazar said the preferred alternative will also identify areas within the reserve that will receive special protection from development, including Peard Bay and Kasegaluk Lagoon, that serve as habitat for seals, polar bears and other marine mammals, plus the Colville River raptor nesting areas; calving areas for the Teshekpuk caribou herd and the Western Arctic herd, and areas important for subsistence, he said. Asked about the prospects of Shell Oil Co. doing offshore exploration this year, Salazar said no decision has been made yet. It is “a matter of whether or not Shell has the mechanical capability to be able to comply with the exploration effort that had been approved by the government,” Salazar said, noting that Shell has not yet successfully tested its oil response vessel. “They have not been able to get it done. If they had got it done, they may already be up there today. Salazar said of Shell “we will hold their feet to the fire to make sure we are doing everything we can to abide by the standards and regulations we have set, and to make sure that the environment and the arctic seas are protected by their activities.” Sen. Mark Begich, D-Alaska, was critical of the proposed plan, saying that “the new preferred alternative still seems to close off several options for building a pipeline across the NPR-A.” Begich said the decision creates more questions than answers about how to get billions of barrels of oil from the Chukchi Sea into the trans-Alaska pipeline. But the plan as proposed won kudos from Wendy Loya, lead ecologist for the Alaska regional office of The Wilderness Society and a member of the North Slope Science Initiative’s technical advisory panel. “We are encouraged that the Bureau of Land Management is taking steps to balance oil and gas development with the need to protect important wildlife habitat in the Western Arctic’s NPR-A,” she said.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297839000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345299350000-20</Id><Title>A CALL FOR CARTER</Title><Msg>Please come back jimmy carter, you weren't the worst president after all!</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345299350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345300497000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Interior secretary outlines development plan for NPRA</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:50:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many Democrats are indeed corporate Democrats. They are that way because they know corporations are highly efficient means of organizing economic activity. This fact could not have escaped them in their education at places like Columbia Business School or Harvard, etc... It is confusing to many, surely, when Democrats advocate a bigger government role - what they really mean in most cases is enlarging the role of the corporate sector and using the corporation as a tool to implement public policy.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345300497000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301958000-22</Id><Topic><Title>A CALL FOR CARTER</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345299350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good One.....LOL</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1345301958000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345303853000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Medicare "Plan" Will Cost $10,000\Yr Out of Pocket</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345264170000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:29:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>walhieee... once again, y'all quite true... we support our elderly parents, for which medicare/social security issues are rather important... in as lil as nine years from now, with the GOP plan, out of pocket expenses for those already utilizing medicare, will more than double, versus keeping the present system... our parents will be okay, yet most senior citizens won't... the idea that our country can bail out the banks, yet can't bail out medicare and social security is hogwash... bail out the rich, yet scr*w everyone else... won't fly come election day... the GOP is also trying to prevent filing bankruptcies due to medical costs... thus foreclosures will go thru the roof with the GOP plan, of which will make the rate of foreclosures in the past few years look like a cakewalk... it's rather shocking how the GOP is puttin' it to seniors and also to those who aren't yet seniors... perhaps, given how many don't like ObamaCare, the GOP believes that it can be as outrageous as possible...</Msg><Username>be.pick</Username><Timestamp>1345303853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:30:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345304408000-24</Id><Title>Good Morning</Title><Msg>Have a nice day</Msg><Username>nancymortin818</Username><Timestamp>1345304408000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345304828000-25</Id><Topic><Title>A CALL FOR CARTER</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345299350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right! Not the Worst one, the best one, still talking, still unafraid, go Jimmy Go! You're the best there ever was!</Msg><Username>carl_cessman</Username><Timestamp>1345304828000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345305723000-26</Id><Topic><Title>A CALL FOR CARTER</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345299350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you think bush/cheney are worst ever also yeppers the supreme court noms and our military occupying other nations leave no doubt</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1345305723000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:02:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345305883000-27</Id><Topic><Title>"level the playing" field for wind versus fossil fuels - 2nd last paragraph</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297100000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Asinine as always wahleee boy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345305883000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:04:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345305977000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Interior secretary outlines development plan for NPRA</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:50:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"corporation as a tool" there are several that spring to mind AIG--Enron--Lehman--ADM--Koch</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1345305977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345306413000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Medicare "Plan" Will Cost $10,000\Yr Out of Pocket</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345264170000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:29:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO, full of lies as always.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345306413000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:13:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345306997000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Interior secretary outlines development plan for NPRA</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:50:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Asinine as always wahleee boy. There are corporate management teams that fail to achieve good results - no system is perfect - but set against the record of government it is no contest which system of management is better. Example of successes: Pennsylvania Railroad, New York Central, B&amp;O, etc when railroads ran transportation. Add also Western Union, AT&amp;T, then Bell Labs, IBM, etc... New York Life, Metlife, General Electric, Ford Motor, Alcoa, Carnegie Steel, then U.S. Steel, Dupont, Dow Chemical, Standard Oil New Jersey, New York, Amoco, ARCO, etc... Shell oil company. Monsanto. Pfizer, Merck, Lockheed, Boeing, MMM, International Paper, Cisco, Microsoft, Apple Computer, Silcon Valley in general... We could go on and on. And what does the government have to list in its column? The Post Office and the Pentagon, or in the USSR the collection of incompetently run government run corporations that the Soviets called communism - the ones that could not even deliver bread to the shelf much of the time or even usually even copy products made by the private sector corporations...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345306997000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345307378000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Medicare "Plan" Will Cost $10,000\Yr Out of Pocket</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345264170000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:29:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney will be the President, not Ryan. You can expect Romney to push for some sort of coordinated system. There is no way it will be coordinated by the government at a management level. Obamacare is nothing more than uncoordinated chaos. It combines the worst aspects of the current free market competition with government mandates. All it will succeed at is driving down wages as businesses pass the costs through to workers, or dump the costs on the government which will be forced to meet them by taxation, which will fall on low income people no matter where they place the taxes in the Tax Code...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345307378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:29:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345310313000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Romney\Ryan Depend On "Greedy Geezers"</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345297116000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DO WHAT YOU DO BEST</Msg><Username>wahleee_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1345310313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345311769000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Getting Killed</Title><Username>maria_stephen45</Username><Timestamp>1345296210000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks.</Msg><Username>renee_jaime96</Username><Timestamp>1345311769000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 13:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345312989000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Romney\Ryan Depend On "Greedy Geezers"</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345297116000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waleee boy - the poster child for brain death.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345312989000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345313369000-35</Id><Title>Romney's Secretary of State Joe Leibermen</Title><Msg>One of the United States' most prolific anti border Senators, Joe Leibermen, has been appointed Mitt's Secretary of State should he win. A fanatic about keeping US borders wide open, he will insure that US schools, hospitals and prisons continue to be filled with illegals. The terror and drug wars will be managed in a way that keeps the free flow of narcotics from the world's number one narco-terrorist state, Mexico streaming into US schools and neigborhoods under Mitt and Paul.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345313369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345315725000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Interior secretary outlines development plan for NPRA</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:50:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The government provided financial backing for many Western railroad bonds to speed the development of the country, and whenever they were involved in the management of railroads the result was not good. The Union Pacific Railroad is a perfect example of their failure, and it was bankrupt by the 1890s thanks to the government meddling in its management, which was a legacy of the Congressional Act that financed it and which it operated under. It was turned around by Harriman and his private sector team of management after the U.S. Treasury was paid off - it was worth money to pay them off to get rid of them. For the major railroad systems I mentioned - the Pennsylvania RR, New York Central, Baltimore &amp; Ohio - the government was not involved at all in management and not involved in financing. Vanderbilt money built those, and Boston commercial money, and New York financier money. Those railroads covered the Northeast U.S. and Great Lake region, the economic powerhouse of America in those years. The management techniques were developed by professional engineers and economists, not by government. The universities the government built included curriculum designed by those managers in their professional associates. The government just wrote checks, which is about the limit of its competence. The Bell System was always privately owned and managed as was Western Union. A regulated utility is not a government run corporation. The difference is in who is managing it and how. Other examples included IBM and its corporate forerunners, which provided computer systems to compile the Census as far back as 1900/1910 , and later manage the Social Security System in 1935. The government did not invent those computer systems, and despite its efforts to steal and copy some of IBM's equipment in the early years had nothing to do with the management of IBM. The government did not manage IBM at any time thereafter either, although it was a major purchaser of its equipment. Your views are not supportable. They are simply wrong. If you want to find an academic source to educate yourself fully on these topics see the Visible Hand by Chandler, 1977. That's Harvard Business School level material...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345315725000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345320721000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Interior secretary outlines development plan for NPRA</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:50:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A charter of incorporation was granted to give the RRs powers of imminent domain, and facilitate the selling of shares and bonds. It did not give the government management control of the railroads. You could find tens of thousands of examples of local cities and governments subscribing to railroad bonds to get railroads to built certain extensions or lines. The bonds were carefully written to give the government no management control. Equity shares gave control of the board and the power to appoint managers, not bonds. The most the bonds would allow was the power to obstruct the sale of the lines in the event of bankruptcy - they did not offer positive management control. The role of the government, even in backing of special project bonds, became almost totally irrelevant by the 1850s when the Wall Street investment banking houses came into being. No, I'm not lying either. Read the book. You just sound ridiculous going on this way trying to use wikipedia source etc for your "facts." Context is important, and a thoroughly knowledge of the financial structure of firms and their management. Without that you are just shooting wildly in the dark. That is entertaining, but really ridiculous.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345320721000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 16:12:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345323946000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Interior secretary outlines development plan for NPRA</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345297805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 09:50:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More facts for you: A railroad SYSTEM is an integrated group of lines covering a region of the country. This is quite a bit different than your local municipal railroad with a few trains running, of the sort that the government had some hand in financing in the early days before the Wall Street banks and major financiers got involved. A system has about 1000 times the capital as the railroad line, capital which the government did not provide - except that is for one notorious project the Transcontinental Railroad/Union Pacific/Central Pacific, which was a financial an economic basket case. It was financed by government precisely because it was uneconomic. A second fact since early American finance seems to interest you: The government was so inept in the area of finance it did not even have the personnel or contacts to sell enough bonds to finance the Civil War. For this it had to turn to Jay Cooke and the group of Wall Street financiers he had contacts with to sell them. The abilities of the financiers whose skills were honed financing the railroads bailed out the hopelessly incompetent U.S. Treasury and allowed them to sell the bonds to win the Civil War. Without those financiers it is highly doubtful the Union would have won the war at all. The South had a huge advantage in the early days of the war and could easily have taken Washington if the New York financiers not been there... The government is just a hapless imbecilic organization... It does excel and taking credit for other people's achievements - there is a name for that sort of thing, but of course the government has exempted itself from the designation.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345323946000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:05:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345327620000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Elderly Broke Ayn Rand Killed Squirrels To Eat</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345299967000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:26:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Squirrels are great Wahleee, full of protein, free of AG drugs and small enough to not upset your diet! Bob Taylor's book; "How to live by the side of the road", has some great Squirrel, and cat, recipes! Check it out, insurance for trying times!</Msg><Username>donny_d_drivle</Username><Timestamp>1345327620000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345328555000-40</Id><Title>Tory</Title><Msg>I disagree with you from time to time but, today you are right. Well done.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345328555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345328870000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Tory</Title><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345328555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:22:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're filth raul.</Msg><Username>cats_cades</Username><Timestamp>1345328870000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345333707000-42</Id><Title>NDP leader considers Northern Gateway pipeline dead</Title><Msg>NDP leader considers Northern Gateway pipeline dead New Democrats prepared to start a provincial party in Quebec CBC News Posted: Aug 18, 2012 11:41 AM ET Last Updated: Aug 18, 2012 11:46 AM ET Read 792 comments 792 VIDEO - NDP coming to Quebec for next provincial election NDP Leader Tom Mulcair says he supports the idea of refining Alberta's oil in Canada instead of shipping crude to Kitimat, B.C., and then on to Asia, as would be the case with Enbridge's proposed Northern Gateway pipeline project — which he calls a "non-starter." In an interview that aired Saturday on CBC Radio's The House, the leader of the Official Opposition told guest host Chris Hall he supports the overall idea "of adding the value in Canada, developing, upgrading, processing, refining our own natural resources here." On Friday, B.C. community newspaper tycoon David Black proposed building a $13-billion oil refinery near Kitimat to process all of the crude from Enbridge's controversial Northern Gateway pipeline. RELATED: B.C. publisher proposes $13B crude refinery near Kitimat "So whether it's that idea of having more refining capacity on the B.C. coast or what we've talked about, which is to move some of the bitumen in those pipelines, moving it east. Maybe that's a win-win situation," Mulcair said. "We can start taking care of our own energy security — add the jobs in Canada instead of shipping both the bitumen and the jobs to the U.S. raw," he said. As for the proposed Northern Gateway pipeline, Mulcair thinks the project is dead, especially after a U.S. government report looking into an Enbridge oil spill in Michigan found there was a "complete breakdown of safety at Enbridge" and that employees at Enbridge acted like the "Keystone Kops," failing to quickly recognize the pipeline had ruptured and continuing to pump oil into the surrounding area. RELATED: Scathing U.S. report missing from Northern Gateway hearings "That was probably the last nail in the coffin," said Mulcair, recalling his reaction to hearing the "Keystone Kops" label. Mulcair also took aim at Prime Minister Stephen Harper, suggesting his approach to sustainable development is failing. "Mr. Harper seems to, over the summer, to have discovered the merits of science. The problem is he keeps firing his scientists and the ones he doesn't fire, he's muzzling. "So if we can at least come up with a common understanding and use the highest level of environmental assessment and get the best results then maybe these things can move forward in other places, but the Northern Gateway, I think, is a non-starter," Mulcair said. While speaking with http://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/story/2012/08/18/pol-mulcair-northern-gateway.html#socialcomments</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345333707000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345333752000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Tory</Title><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345328555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:22:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor sad wahleee boy got shown up gain - as always. And your typical reaction. The poster boy for brain death.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345333752000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345333861000-44</Id><Topic><Title>NDP leader considers Northern Gateway pipeline dead</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345333707000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:48:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While speaking with reporters after an announcement in B.C. last week, the prime minister said science, not politics, would decide the fate of the proposed Northern Gateway pipeline. RELATED: Harper defends independence of pipeline approval process Last month, B.C. Premier Christy Clark vowed to oppose the proposed pipeline project if the federal government and the province of Alberta didn't meet B.C.'s specific conditions, including getting a "fair share" share of the economic benefits. When asked whether a possible alliance with Clark were possible, Mulcair said he will be working closely with Adrian Dix, the leader the B.C. NDP, to defeat Clark and her Liberal B.C. government in next year's provincial election. "I'm going to be working very closely with Adrian Dix, the extraordinary leader of the NDP in B.C., to make sure the NDP forms a strong, progressive government in B.C." Although NDP support is strong in B.C., the party holds only three seats in the Prairies. This week, Saskatchewan Premier Brad Wall let it be known he had not forgotten Mulcair's diagnosis that the Canadian economy is suffering from a case of Dutch Disease, in which sales of natural resources increase the value of the dollar, hurting manufacturing through declining exports. On Thursday, Wall tweeted: "Sask manufacturing up and leading the nation. Canada's up year over year 6.9%. That's quite a case of Dutch Disease." RELATED: Harper's pipeline dilemma: can't reject, can't ram through Mulcair stood by his comments, saying he had not hurt the party in the Prairies and that the New Democrats intended to win "lots of seats" there in the next federal election. "What we have talked about in the beginning is that we haven't been applying the basic rules of sustainable development, like polluter pay. We've been giving them a free ride. A whole series of statutes are not being enforced — the Fisheries Act, the Navigable Waters Act, Migratory Birds [Convention Act] and so on. So instead of making the companies change their practices to respect the law, Mr. Harper is changing the laws to make it correspond to the practices. That's been his approach. "What we're also saying is that because we're not internalizing those costs — we're not including them — we're bringing in an artificially high number of U.S. dollars. And all other statistics aside, we do know that since the Conservatives came to power in 2006, we've lost 500,000 good paying manufacturing jobs. Several hundred thousands of those were lost as a direct result of the artificially high U.S. dollar." NDP eyes Quebec election It's no secret that</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345333861000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345333894000-45</Id><Topic><Title>NDP leader considers Northern Gateway pipeline dead</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345333707000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:48:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's no secret that Mulcair has asked his NDP MPs and their staffers not to wade in to the Quebec election, just as he asked them to stay out of the Quebec student protests in the past few months. But with a majority of federal seats in that province and his Quebec caucus being the youngest in federal history, Mulcair was asked whether the NDP could stay mum on an election that could have a profound impact on federal politics. "I'm not going to start wading in on a provincial campaign where we are not playing a role. My job is to work with whoever is going to be chosen," he said. However, Mulcair said, that could all change in the next three to four years and that Quebecers "can be sure that the NDP will be running in the next provincial election in Quebec — and that will change things, of course." Even with the possibility of a sovereigntist government returning to power and Canadians looking to see what federal leader would best handle the situation, Mulcair vowed to stay out of the Quebec election. "My track record is clear — people know that I'm a strong federalist. I fought the 1980 referendum, but I also fought in the 1995 referendum. Quebec City is a very tough neighbourhood to practise politics when you are a federalist, but I stood up for Canada and I'll continue to do that," he said. "That'll always be my vision." The NDP believes a simple majority, 50 per cent plus one vote, is enough to decide a future Quebec referendum.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345333894000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 19:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345340885000-46</Id><Topic><Title>Tory</Title><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345328555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:22:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All I was doing today was quoting Alfred Dupont Chandler Jr, the late professor of business history at Harvard Business School and Johns Hopkins University.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345340885000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345341047000-47</Id><Topic><Title>Tory</Title><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345328555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:22:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you, wahleee boy, can't even remember that you are supposed to half both the "lemming" and me on ignore. You revert to circular argument quickly, of course, which is your hallmark - that and misrepresenting of flat our lying about the historical record. This is to be expected though. It is amusing all the same.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345341047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345341397000-48</Id><Topic><Title>obama 120 rounds of golf, 23 vacations, and 0 Budgets</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1345335260000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:14:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is probably going to win, though, despite his total lack of management ability and utter incompetence - incompetence, except as a warmonger and money waster; he excels at that. The country has degenerated quite a bit the past decade, and it is getting worse every year. If he does win the debt will just keep spiraling up. The debt will eventually increase interest rates as it competes for other uses of capital, and the higher interest rates will grind the living standard of the lower classes into dust...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345341397000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 21:56:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345344533000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Family Fortune Leveraged On Gov Highway Projects</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345265500000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:51:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are of course lying again wahleee boy. Your link says nothing about Paul Ryan and you have no evidence to present. So you make things up. Since you love Wikipedia so much - this is what they say: "Ryan's great-grandfather, Patrick William Ryan (1858–1917), founded an earthmoving company in 1884, which later became P. W. Ryan and Sons and is now known as Ryan Incorporated Central.[12][13][14] However, Paul Ryan's branch of the family has not been involved with the company."</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345344533000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 22:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>