<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346563597000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Betting time...</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346524319000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Before you go, could you try to explain why the mathematical assurance that tax increase for the wealthy will reduce jobs/wages, when tax cuts for the wealthy did not increase jobs/wages (for reasons like technological advances as you mentioned)?</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346563597000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346564522000-2</Id><Topic><Title>War &amp; Peace</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346517933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The economy is still feeling the effects of the GFC that Obama rescued from oblivion. People still don't like "Wall Street". People also see Romney aligned with Wall Street. Obama shifting the cost of energy will have no effect on the economy. Once large institutions fell comfortable they will spend the huge cash reserves they have. In the meantime, that Heavens the Govt. is spending to keep the economy going. Romney's alignment with Wall Street is a factor in his inevitable loss, but not the major reason. Most it will be because he's a Mormon.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1346564522000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346564558000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Betting time...</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346524319000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Globally,there's no evidence moderately higher rates on the highest income earners impacts growth.But it will also have little impact on the debt.If the psychological thing,you know,the "fairness" issue is so important,well,ok,raise taxes on the rich.Just don't expect it to solve THE problem. However,there's a world of evidence that lower corporate and investment rates do jack growth.And growth is the source of rising tax revenues rather than higher rates.In fact,tax revenue grwoth is more important than budget cutting.Spending cuts have never balanced any budget.Only growth can produce the tax revenues that really reduce the debt to GDP ratio.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1346564558000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 01:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346577776000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Betting time...</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346524319000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When you can't stand the heat it is time to get out of the kitchen"</Msg><Username>maxchatrman</Username><Timestamp>1346577776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 05:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346585652000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Koch Brother Supports Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1346531965000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:39:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You wish I were like you Wahleee but, as usual, your view is 180 degrees from the truth. Better pray you don't fall into the hands of radical MZLMs, since they will kill you when they find out about your sexual preference.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1346585652000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 07:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346588693000-6</Id><Topic><Title>War &amp; Peace</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346517933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another blatantly idiotic lie. You are so transparent it's ridiculous.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346588693000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346591798000-7</Id><Title>Enhanced and Expanded Domestic Gitmo with Obama's re-election</Title><Msg>NDAA, America's domestic GITMO legislation passed with flying colors at the behest of the Obama administration. Pelosi rallied the Dems to build a massive network of prison FEMA camps during the end of the Bush administration, so it seems that both parties are aware that the pitch forks are poised to come out. Middle class anger, despite the powers of persuasion and education by the Manhattan media, is escalating, and the upcoming election will put militancy into the Occuppy Wall Street crowd and give Obamney or Robama cause to declare a state of emergency. Both parties are hellbent on spending trillions abroad on military occupations while cutting social security and other services diomestically.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346591798000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 09:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346592710000-8</Id><Topic><Title>War &amp; Peace</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346517933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Solar and wind will go like the pet rock. You still must keep fuel fired plants on standby to come on line when the wind does not blow and at night. (THINK)</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1346592710000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 09:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346595517000-9</Id><Title>OBAMA ! WILLING TO RELEASE HIS SECRET BEER RECEIPE , YET HE WILL RELEASE HIS GRADES</Title><Msg>From college that he sealed so no one can see ! idoit obama and everyone who vote for that crook</Msg><Username>hekillingamerica</Username><Timestamp>1346595517000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:18:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346597031000-10</Id><Title>Wolk's CA RENEWABLE energy access bill stopped</Title><Msg>Wolk's CA RENEWABLE energy access bill stopped Published By Daily Democratdailydemocratcom Created: 09/02/2012 12:30:53 AM PDT Legislation to provide millions of consumers in California access to clean, renewable energy died in the Assembly Committee on Utilities and Commerce Friday as a result of lobbying from energy companies. PG&amp;E and Southern California Edison lobbied against the bill but there was broad support for the bill, including that of major investor-owned utility, San Diego Gas &amp; Electric, according to a news release from Sen. Lois Wolk, D-Davis. "Unfortunately, PG&amp;E and Southern California Edison control the committee," said Wolk, the author of Senate Bill 843. "There was an agreement between the Assembly Speaker, the Committee Chair, and me that would have scaled the bill down to a pilot program under the Public Utilities Commission's guidance and oversight. That agreement wasn't honored and the bill died in committee, depriving the public of innovative energy policy in line with Governor Brown's initiatives." SB 843 would have transformed California's energy market by allowing all customers in the state's three major utilities to utilize solar, wind, and other renewable energy sources, according to Wolk. The bill would have given Californians the option of buying a portion of the power generated at an off-site renewable energy facility--and to receive a credit on their utility bill for the clean energy they purchase. "Three out of four Californians are currently unable to take advantage of affordable and clean, renewable energy through the state's renewable power programs," Wolk said. "SB 843 would have changed that, giving consumers the opportunity to save on their energy bill while encouraging more investment and creating thousands of jobs in an important sector of our state's economy, all without spending any state funds or shifting costs to consumers who chose not to participate." The bill was sponsored by the City of Davis and Superintendent of Public Instruction Tom Torlakson, and supported by a broad coalition that included business, school and environmental groups, affordable housing advocates, as well as the Department of Defense and many local governments. "There was a tremendous effort on the part of the bill's sponsors and supporters, particularly the Ella Baker Center for Human Rights, Department of Defense, U.S. Navy, Vote Solar, Clean Path Ventures, Environmental Entrepreneurs, Recurrent Energy and Renewable Funding," Wolk said. "I want to extend my personal thanks to all those who gave their time and effort in a last stitch effort to get this measure to the governor. "Unfortunately, the coalition of support behind this measure was simply no match for the high paid lobbyists and the campaign contributions of these monopoly corporations." Consumers are currently unable to generate their own on-site power from solar, wind, and other renewable energy for a variety of reasons, Wolk said. Many business owners, particularly small business owners, don't own their building and are unable to install renewable energy generation systems on site. The same problem faces the state's millions of renters. Shaded roofs, or roofs that don't get sufficient direct sunlight, also prevent consumers from generating their own renewable energy. http://www.dailydemocrat.com/news/ci_21455294/wolks-energy-access-bill-stopped</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346597031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346598836000-11</Id><Topic><Title>SPEAKING of MITT ROMNEY!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346524558000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:35:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.tabletmag.com/scroll/110916/mormons-steal-the-show-at-rncs-final-night?print=1</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346598836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:13:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599139000-12</Id><Topic><Title>War &amp; Peace</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346517933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Another blatantly idiotic lie." Another blatant idiot! We are all idiots here, the fact that we are here proves that. So why do we come and post "our" drivel? To show people how many books we have read? To show how fervent and steadfast we are in our beliefs? Wahleee, I think, is on a mission to shine light into dark corners and to do what he can to protect the poor and down trodden and all the other forgotten unfortunates, he is secure in his mission and he realizes; the more criticism he gets the more effective he is, I respect Wahleee he has never deviated from his mission. I come here because I enjoy writing things down and when you post here at least someone will read your stuff! Why do you come here? Does anyone post because their mission is to save the World? To save America, to speak for your favorite cause? What, in your secret Heart of hearts, would you like to achieve from your efforts? Tell us, it doesn't matter we are all, well not exactly friends, but we are anonymous to each other here, so spill it out, publish you manifesto!</Msg><Username>donny_d_drivle</Username><Timestamp>1346599139000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599371000-13</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ! WILLING TO RELEASE HIS SECRET BEER RECEIPE , YET HE WILL RELEASE HIS GRADES</Title><Username>hekillingamerica</Username><Timestamp>1346595517000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America would be a happier and more prosperous place if people made and drank more beer, chill out with a cool one friend don't carry the worries of the World on your shoulders!</Msg><Username>carl_cessman</Username><Timestamp>1346599371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599517000-14</Id><Topic><Title>THEY GOTTA BE KIDDING!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346335047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 09:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.adl.org/presrele/asus_12/the_talmud.pdf</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346599517000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346602056000-15</Id><Title>SPEAKING of REALITY!!</Title><Msg>http://moneymorning.com/ob/jim-rogers-its-going-to-get-really-bad-after-the-next-election/?utm_expid=5485297-8&amp;utm_referrer=http%3A%2F%2Fpaid.outbrain.com%2Fnetwork%2Fredir%3Fkey%3D9b749afe0a597feb817e74899db1b05b%26rdid%3D372071458%26type%3DP2P_d%2Ft2_la%26in-site%3Dfalse%26pc_id%3D9513251%26req_id%3D989abbfbcb10f00ac14cc563f521fab2%26agent%3Dblog_JS_rec%26recMode%3D7%26reqType%3D1%26wid%3D106%26imgType%3D0%26adsCats%3D1708%2C-1%2C-1%26refPub%3D388%26prs%3Dtrue%26scp%3Dfalse%26fcapElementId%3D6439</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346602056000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346603658000-16</Id><Topic><Title>SPEAKING of REALITY!!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346602056000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:07:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/48876172/ns/world_news-europe</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346603658000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:34:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346604115000-17</Id><Topic><Title>THEY GOTTA BE KIDDING!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346335047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 09:57:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://antiwar.com/blog/2012/08/30/california-passes-resolution-equating-criticism-of-israel-with-anti-semitism/</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346604115000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346605899000-18</Id><Topic><Title>SPEAKING of REALITY!!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346602056000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:07:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qOP2V_np2c0&amp;feature=relmfu</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1346605899000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346606626000-19</Id><Title>Dems to *livestream* Charlotte convention</Title><Msg>Dems to *livestream* Charlotte convention http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_W/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=20003&amp;tid=990339&amp;mid=990339&amp;tof=1&amp;frt=2</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346606626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346609023000-20</Id><Topic><Title>GE Introduces 1.85-82.5 Wind Turbine for Brazil’s Promising Wind Energy Sector</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346556046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:20:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GE sure has an interesting looking chart: http://finance.yahoo.com/echarts?s=GE+Interactive#symbol=ge;range=my;compare=;indicator=volume;charttype=area;crosshair=on;ohlcvalues=0;logscale=off;source=undefined;</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1346609023000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346611840000-21</Id><Title>WOULD YOU BELIEVE ....</Title><Msg>http://now.msn.com/western-scrub-jay-birds-hold-funerals</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346611840000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:50:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346617307000-22</Id><Title>Domestic Gitmos aka Fema camps</Title><Msg>Obama encouraged the GOP to pass his detain indefinitely without trial Americans who oppose tax increases and war.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346617307000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 16:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625484000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Pulling Ahead</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346515659000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rather than use secondary sources why not use the primary source. Here is a link ... http://www.treasurydirect.gov/govt/reports/pd/histdebt/histdebt.htm Now tell us what year the debt was less than the previous one? Like was alread pointed out. Clinton came closer than any recent president. But he did not balance the budget. And just because GWB was or became s spendthrift, doesn't make what Obama is doing any better.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346625484000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:38:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625665000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Pulling Ahead</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346515659000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is slick but since he loves to make up facts, it is easy for someone who can command the true facts to debate him. You don't do it based styly. You simply call him a liar every time he creates his own facts. Obama can deliver a message but get him in a non -scripted environment and challenge his commands of the facts and he will melt like butter on a Phoenix sidewalk in July.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346625665000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346627762000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Dems to *livestream* Charlotte convention</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346606626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:23:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just "livestreamed" Dems into the toilet. LOL!</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1346627762000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346629257000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Pulling Ahead</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346515659000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These Colas are neck and neck folks, this race is still too close to call, who will be the winner, will the old tried and true Coke or the new comer Pepsi be crowned America's favorite? Who knows, the one saving grace in all this is, both brands are owned by the same interests, so it is unlikely you will experience any changes in your personal life, your role is the consumer role so drink it all in and enjoy, this is your show brought to you by the people who care about you! The new Savior, and America's favorite beverage, will be the one you choose! It is a serious responsibility you have been given, think wisely, choose well!</Msg><Username>maxchatrman</Username><Timestamp>1346629257000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:40:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346630302000-27</Id><Topic><Title>War &amp; Peace</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346517933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still must keep fuel fired plants on standby to come on line when the wind does not blow and at night. (THINK) The only thing that blows in the night is WAHLEEEEE matser of BLO</Msg><Username>wahleee_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1346630302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346630690000-28</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTTRADE Sucks !!!!!</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1325985500000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-01-07 20:18:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hear that harry.....</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1346630690000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346631789000-29</Id><Topic><Title>War &amp; Peace</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346517933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America lost WWI and every war since. 80 million dead Christians resulting from WWI and WWII counts as a win in the eyes of the chosenites' media. The money printers also love the prolonged loser wars against Korea and Viet Nam. Exporting US jobs to the slave labor countries that prevailed in the wars of the last century is "free trade" and glorious globalism if your obeying your television or txt books.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346631789000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346637136000-30</Id><Title>How democrats govern</Title><Msg>http://www.nytimes.com/2012/09/03/us/in-california-banning-bonfires-and-library-napping.html?google_editors_picks=true</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346637136000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346640596000-31</Id><Title>The True Story of Mitt Romney and Bain Capital</Title><Msg>Wahleee's probably posted this already: http://www.rollingstone.com/politics/news/greed-and-debt-the-true-story-of-mitt-romney-and-bain-capital-20120829</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346640596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346643431000-32</Id><Topic><Title>The True Story of Mitt Romney and Bain Capital</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346640596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:49:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"By making debt the centerpiece of his campaign, Romney was making a calculated bluff of historic dimensions – placing a massive all-in bet on the rank incompetence of the American press corps. The result has been a brilliant comedy: A man makes a $250 million fortune loading up companies with debt and then extracting million-dollar fees from those same companies, in exchange for the generous service of telling them who needs to be fired in order to finance the debt payments he saddled them with in the first place. That same man then runs for president riding an image of children roasting on flames of debt, choosing as his running mate perhaps the only politician in America more pompous and self-righteous on the subject of the evils of borrowed money than the candidate himself. If Romney pulls off this whopper, you'll have to tip your hat to him: No one in history has ever successfully run for president riding this big of a lie." The liberal media?</Msg><Username>proponentsists</Username><Timestamp>1346643431000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>