<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-31"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343751338000-1</Id><Title>How the H does this go from day's high to low in minutes,</Title><Msg>and why?</Msg><Username>riskreversal777</Username><Timestamp>1343751338000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343753598000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Is Exxon Mobil Corporation about to plunge? I think I have figured it out</Title><Username>harmonybushfield</Username><Timestamp>1343753130000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:45:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much do they pay you to post that crap. It used to be 15 cents each.....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1343753598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343754249000-3</Id><Title>Jimmy Carter in 1976 said we'd have no more oil by 1990</Title><Msg>In 1914, the Bureau of Mines said U.S. oil reserves would be exhausted by 1924. In 1939, the Interior Department said the world had 13 years worth of petroleum reserves. Then a global war was fought and the postwar boom was fueled, and in 1951 Interior reported that the world had ... 13 years of reserves. In 1970, the world's proven oil reserves were an estimated 612 billion barrels. By 2006, more than 767 billion barrels had been pumped and proven reserves were 1.2 trillion barrels. In 1977, Scold in Chief Jimmy Carter predicted that mankind "could use up all the proven reserves of oil in the entire world by the end of the next decade." Since then the world has consumed three times more oil than was then in the world's proven reserves</Msg><Username>sirola1</Username><Timestamp>1343754249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:04:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343755512000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carter in 1976 said we'd have no more oil by 1990</Title><Username>sirola1</Username><Timestamp>1343754249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:04:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oil will never run out. It will simply be produced until its price rises to the point where its marginal value is less than its marginal cost... As this happens it will go through the foundations of the economy, wiping out land values as transportation costs rise, and causing still more mortgage defaults, and reducing wages... The wealth of society will become more and more concentrated at the top.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1343755512000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343756526000-5</Id><Title>Drought sparks request to halt ethanol mandate</Title><Msg>Published July 30, 2012, 09:12 PM Drought sparks request to halt ethanol mandate Livestock, poultry producer groups say high feed costs jeopardizing meat production WASHINGTON, D.C. — Livestock and poultry groups from across the country have banded together to request the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency implement an immediate waiver of the nation’s Renewable Fuels Standard for corn-based ethanol in light of continued drought conditions. By: Julie Buntjer, Worthington Daily Globe WASHINGTON, D.C. — Livestock and poultry groups from across the country have banded together to request the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency implement an immediate waiver of the nation’s Renewable Fuels Standard for corn-based ethanol in light of continued drought conditions. In a press conference Monday morning, representatives from the National Pork Producers Council, the National Cattlemen’s Beef Association, National Turkey Federation and National Chicken Council announced a petition had been delivered to EPA Administrator Lisa Jackson asking to waive “in whole or in substantial part” the mandate for the remainder of this year and into 2013. The RFS requires 13.2 billion gallons of corn-based ethanol to be produced in 2012 and 13.8 billion gallons in 2013 — amounts that will use about 4.7 billion and 4.9 billion bushels, respectively, of the nation’s corn. The mandate requires ethanol to be blended with gasoline in an effort to keep fuel costs dow. Some agricultural forecasters now estimate just 11.8 billion bushels of corn will be harvested this year, down from nearly 13 billion bushels harvested in 2011. Demand for corn in both the food and fuel industries is driving corn prices to record highs, creating concern for livestock producers from coast to coast. The RFS has “directly affected the supply and cost of feed in major agricultural sectors of this country, causing the type of economic harm that justifies issuance of an RFS waiver,” said the coalition of agricultural groups in its petition. This is the second time since the RFS Standard was expanded in 2007 that a request has been made to slow or halt the production of corn-based ethanol. In 2008, Texas Gov. Rick Perry was unsuccessful in his request to the EPA. John Burkel, National Turkey Federation vice chair and turkey grower from Badger in northwest Minnesota, said major cutbacks in turkey production occurred in 2008 when the waiver was not granted, and that will only continue if changes aren’t made. “I don’t have a mandate that says when you leave the grocery store, you throw a whole bird in your cart,” Burkel said. “I have to compete for corn on a whole different level than they do.” That competition has forced many turkey growers out of production, and will ultimately lead to higher prices for consumers at the grocery store. http://www.dglobe.com/event/article/id/58881/group/News/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343756526000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343756546000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Drought sparks request to halt ethanol mandate</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343756526000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:42:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Burkel said turkey will still be found in grocery stores this fall, but if the high cost of corn remains, there will be a drop in production across not only the turkey industry, but all industries. “(That will) put consumers in a position where they can’t afford to buy meat anymore, or very little of it,” he added. Since 2007, the wholesale cost of turkey has risen by more than 50 percent. Producers cutting back Burkel, a fourth-generation turkey producer, has to buy approximately 100,000 bushels of corn per year to feed his turkey flocks. With corn nearing $8 per bushel, he said price plays a “critical role” in his ability to feed his family. “The availability of corn this year is uncertain,” he said. “I’ve already cancelled my last flock of turkeys for this year.” In northeast Nebraska, National Cattlemen’s Association President and cattle finisher JD Alexander has also made cuts in his rural Pilger feedlots. “We are about 60 percent of capacity — we just can’t make the numbers work,” Alexander said. “I’m having trouble finding corn. My neighbors have either sold out or they’re not sure they will be able to fill contracts with the corn they’re producing this year. As a direct result we’ve cut back and are being very conservative.” In addition, Alexander said for the first time in his life, he’s cutting corn for silage to feed his beef animals. “The corn is not making an ear and we’re not getting kernels. We’re taking an early crop and putting it into roughage,” he said. “The (corn) prices are at record highs that I’ve never had to pay before and it’s really hard to get it. In the long run it’s really putting a burden on our operation and many other producers across the nation.” While Alexander said he supports America’s ethanol industry and what it has done for rural communities, he does not stand for a federal mandate that “picks winners and losers.” “We do not stand for manipulation of corn prices. We do not stand for a federal government sitting by patiently, forking over taxpayer dollars to artificially inflate the price of corn for livestock producers and other end users,” Alexander said. “This isn’t rocket science. Let the market work and embrace free market principles.” Randy Spronk, a rural Edgerton pork producer and president-elect of the National Pork Producers Council, said a large portion of the country — the proverbial bread basket — is in the midst of the worst drought in 50 years. “Livestock and poultry producers are struggling because of it,” Spronk said. “We’re worried about having enough corn, soybeans and other crops — at any price — to feed our animals. These aren’t unfounded fears.” Spronk said the latest U.S. Department of Agriculture crop report showed just 31 percent of the nation’s corn crop is rated good or excellent, with 38 percent rated poor or very poor. “USDA also forecasts because of the drought, food prices will rise 4 percent next year,” he added.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343756546000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343756558000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Drought sparks request to halt ethanol mandate</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343756526000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:42:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waiver needed now Alexander said livestock and poultry producers are willing to compete for corn, but he said they need to have a level playing field. “The ethanol industry is a mature market now,” Alexander said. “They’ve been held up with a three-legged stool for many years. At some point … you need to wean it and it’s time to wean the ethanol industry and let it stand on its own. Michael Formica, chief environmental counsel for the National Pork Producers Council, said there’s no other option at this point for livestock and poultry producers to get “immediate relief” other than through a waiver of the ethanol mandate. “As we look forward, we’ve got a dire situation on availability of corn,” Spronk said. “That’s why we’re trying to act early here. “In writing the energy bill that set up the RFS, Congress included the waiver exactly for the situation farmers and ranchers now face,” he added. “We need a waiver now.” “If we’re not going to put this (waiver) in now, with an historic drought, when will we do this,” asked Burkel. “Relief from the Renewable Fuels Standard is extremely urgent,” added Michael Welch, president and CEO of Bethlehem, Ga.-based Harrison Poultry and past chairman of the National Chicken Council. “A very short corn crop will undoubtedly prove to be devastating to the animal agriculture industry, food manufacturers, food service providers and consumers not just in the United States, but in the entire world.”</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343756558000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343756951000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Drought sparks request to halt ethanol mandate</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343756526000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:42:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Energy Futures Prices Below you may find all the futures prices &amp; quotes for: Crude Oil, Heating Oil, Gasoline RBOB, Natural Gas, ICE Brent Crude Oil, Ethanol (E) and more. Real Time Streaming Futures Quotes (CFDs) http://www.forexpros.com/commodities/energies ------------------------------------------------ Grains Futures Prices Below you may find all the futures prices &amp; quotes for: Wheat (E), Corn (E), Soybeans (E), Soybean Meal (E), Soybean Oil (E), Oats (E) and more. Real Time Streaming Futures Quotes (CFDs) http://www.forexpros.com/commodities/grains ------------------------------- National Weather Service Enhanced Radar Image http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/index.php Upper Mississippi Valley Sector http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/uppermissvly.php Central Great Lakes Sector http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/centgrtlakes.php</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343756951000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343757234000-9</Id><Title>Olympic fleet trials new biofuels</Title><Msg>Olympic fleet trials new biofuels Some of BMW’s Olympic fleet cars will be trialling new biofuels during their official duties. Games sponsor BP is trialling what it calls ‘game-changing’ biofuel technology, with three new advanced biofuel blends. Around 100 of BMW’s 4,000 strong Olympic fleet are trailing the new fuels; one fuel is an cellulosic ethanol developed from specially grown energy grasses, another is a sugar-to-diesel fuel which can be produced any source of sugar and the third is a biobutanol, made by the advanced fermentation of plant sugars by a special micro-organism. What is genuinely impressive is that the cellulosic fuel, when blended with regular unleaded fuel it is, at 103, the highest-octane fuel ever pumped from a UK forecourt. The biobutanol has been produced at the Butamax demonstration plant in Hull. This plant was established through a joint venture with DuPont, with the aim to developing biobutanol technology which can be deployed globally at full commercial scale. Announcing the use of the three new fuels, Philip New, CEO BP Biofuels, explained: “These breakthrough technologies will redefine biofuels. By incorporating them in the fuels for London 2012 we have taken the next generation of biofuels from the laboratory to the road.” “We are the only company in the world with the capability to connect expertise from the laboratory to the farm, to the factory and through to the driver.” BP, one the more controversial sponsors of the London Olympic due to environmental criticism levelled at the firm in recent years (remember that oil spill in the Gulf of Mexico two years ago?), is now keen to assert that it believes that biofuels have a real part to play in meeting the energy demands of the future (presumably in a cleaner and safer manner than its met them in the past). With biofuels already make up three per cent of transport fuels used around the world, the oil giant estimates they could account for seven per cent of all transport fuels by 2030. See also Biofuels ‘only way’ to decarbonise road transport Biofuel rules could price older car drivers off the road EU approves ‘green’ biofuel schemes EPA gives final approval to E15 fuel Europe’s biofuel plans put ‘millions of lives in danger’ Top 10 strange ways to fuel your car. The Green Piece Morrisons expands biodiesel B30 availability Biofuels target to be slowed Reliance on biofuels to increase Idle drivers wasting £60 million in fuel http://www.thegreencarwebsite.co.uk/blog/index.php/2012/07/31/olympic-fleet-trials-new-biofuels/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343757234000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343757900000-10</Id><Title>Valero to split off retail unit; Q2 net up 12%</Title><Msg>July 31, 2012, 9:08 a.m. EDT Valero to split off retail unit; Q2 net up 12% By Victoria Stilwell Valero Energy Corp. /quotes/zigman/186158/quotes/nls/vlo VLO +6.08% unveiled plans to potentially break off its retail business from the rest of the company, as it reported second-quarter earnings rose 12%. The oil-refining company said it is reviewing several potential separation transactions, including a tax-efficient distribution of the retail business to shareholders. "As independent companies, both retail and the remaining business will be better-positioned to focus on their industry-specific strategies," Chief Executive Bill Klesse said. Shares rose 5.8% to $27.58 in recent premarket trading. The stock is up 24% so far this year through Monday's close. ConocoPhillips (COP) and Marathon Oil Corp. (MRO) and a number of consumer product and media companies have unveiled similar plans in the past couple of years, determining the sum of their parts is worth more than the whole. The largest refiner in the U.S. has increased revenue in recent quarters as global distillate demand grows, despite continuing weakness in the U.S. gasoline market. Major shifts in fuel demand and in energy production have wiped out the profitability of such former refining hubs as the U.S. East Coast and the Caribbean. Meanwhile, record corn prices and sluggish gasoline demand are squeezing profits for U.S. ethanol producers including Valero, prompting some to idle plants or slow production. Valero Energy reported a profit of $831 million, or $1.50 a share, up from a profit of $744 million, or $1.30 a share a year earlier. Revenue increased 11% to $34.66 billion. Analysts surveyed by Thomson Reuters recently expected earnings of $1.43 a share on revenue of $32.62 billion. Operating margin narrowed to 3.9% from 4.1%. At Valero's refining business, operating income rose 8.9% as the throughput margin per barrel shrank to $10.63 from $11.41 and volume grew 15%. At its smaller U.S. retail operations, operating profit jumped 27% amid higher fuel margins and volumes. Valero's ethanol segment reported an operating income of $5 million, down 92% from the year before as excess ethanol inventories held margins at low levels. The company in July reduced its ethanol production rates as margins were negative due to rising corn prices and already-high ethanol inventories http://www.marketwatch.com/story/valero-to-split-off-retail-unit-q2-net-up-12-2012-07-31</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343757900000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343765344000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carter in 1976 said we'd have no more oil by 1990</Title><Username>sirola1</Username><Timestamp>1343754249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:04:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tory, I am certainly no expert but, it seems to me that if we were drilling where the oil is instead of drilling where it is not, supply would exceed demand. It will be necessary however, to get the government (at all levels) out of the business of interference. That may be somewhat of an overstatement but, a free market can only produce when left alone to produce. As it is now, we are swimming upstream to the bear.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1343765344000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343765837000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carter in 1976 said we'd have no more oil by 1990</Title><Username>sirola1</Username><Timestamp>1343754249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:04:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It depends what the marginal cost of the supply is. If the new supply is more of the same high cost oil currently setting the price, the best it will do is keep oil prices from rising for a period. There is no more cheap oil in the United States, except for a few areas like ANWR, which is too small to make much of a difference. The US could go the Imperialist route and start conquering more territory, something it was very good at in the 19th century. It seems totally unprepared for the realities of what must be done to make that profitable... nation building is not in order. More like what Jackson did to the Indians of the southeastern United States would be called for...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1343765837000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343776403000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Olympic fleet trials new biofuels</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343757234000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is genuinely stupid is this statement..."What is genuinely impressive is that the cellulosic fuel, when blended with regular unleaded fuel it is, at 103, the highest-octane fuel ever pumped from a UK forecourt. " 1) From context it is difficult to tell precisely what octane they mean, but given that Europe tends to go by RON (not the road octane used in US), this statement is likely false. I strongly suspect back when leaded fuel was sold in England the RON was over 100 for their "ethyl". 2) The statement assumes or at least implies that higher octane gasoline is inherently better. It is not. Octnae is a single parameter and higher does not alone imply better. Bascially if all other properties are identical, once you are using a gasoline with enough octane, any additional octane is 'wasted' and you are wasting our $'s is you have pay more for the higher octane. 3) There is nothing magic about cellulosic ethanol vs. any other ethanol with respect to the octane. Where or how the ethanol is produced in no way impacts the resulting octane of a blend. They could take ethanol from corn or sugar cane or even from petroleum (yes it is possible to produce ethanol from oil), blend it in the regular unleaded fuel and you would get exactly the same octane for the blend. Like I said, the statement made is stupid. It basically says nothing and what it does imply is in effect wrong. The statement doesn't even make a case for why biofuels are good.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1343776403000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 19:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343777261000-14</Id><Title>Rentier and Welfare Ant Heap</Title><Msg>An passage from Peaceful Conquest: the Industrialization of Europe 1760-1970, Sidney Pollard, 1981. The similarities between many of the major cities of de-industrializing America and Europe and the backward ones from the past is striking: "These cities, despite the similarity in their outward trappings, with their town halls, squares, mayors, and city police, were not only different from those of the West: they were also, on balance, a strongly negative influence on industrialization. Whereas in Inner Europe the city frequently provided capital, labor, mass markets, transport advantages, enterprise, and competition, and soon became almost symbolic for the industrializing region, the peripheral city, particularly the capital or administrative center that was generally the fastest growing, was its very antithesis. There the landed classes (modern day stock and bond holders) spent their money wastefully, instead of improving their estates or the land and thus laying the foundation for economic progress. The army of lackeys withdrew labor from useful work, as did the garrisons (government employees) and the commodity demand generated was precisely of a kind to inhibit industrial progress and strengthened the guild-ridden (union), expense-no-object, luxury crafts. Such cities overburdened the transport system - Madrid, indeed, killed off the agriculture of a whole region in order to keep itself going in its artificial location, diverted enterprise and ambition, misdirected intelligence, as in the case of the lawyers, and drew attention away from local resources."</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1343777261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 19:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343789000000-15</Id><Title>More Evidence That It's Time to Dump Ethanol</Title><Msg>http://www.usnews.com/news/blogs/rick-newman/2012/07/31/more-evidence-that-its-time-to-dump-ethanol?google_editors_picks=true</Msg><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1343789000000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:43:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>