<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350792620354-1</Id><Topic><Title>Any Market Players Here?</Title><Username>luckyone581</Username><Timestamp>1350677742523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:15:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On rare occasion there are. Although I am more a long term investor than a player....usually.</Msg><Username>iggybiggies</Username><Timestamp>1350792620354</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 00:10:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350819985031-2</Id><Topic><Title>Washington Post on "Are Mormons Christians?"</Title><Username>demedici</Username><Timestamp>1350771655038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you wouldn't know where you came from poor boy commie.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350819985031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 07:46:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350836745444-3</Id><Title>Iowa’s renewable energy boom: Headed for a bust? Navy/Marines operational platform scheduled to be using 50% alternative energy by 2020</Title><Msg>Iowa’s renewable energy boom: Headed for a bust? Backers remain optimistic despite obstacles Updated: 21 October 2012 | 6:30 am A  renewable energy boom that’s been a pillar of Iowa’s recession-resistant economy seems to be running out of fuel in shark-infested waters. Ethanol producers have scaled back production in recent months, and wind energy machinery manufacturers have been forced to lay off hundreds of workers across the state as production stalled. On any scale, Iowa’s renewable energy boom was one of biggest economic development success stories of any state in the past decade. Iowa’s ethanol production increased 733 percent from 2000 to 2011, to 3.6 billion gallons per year. The industry supports about 83,000 jobs, according to the Iowa Renewable Fuels Association. The emerging wind industry created close to 7,000 jobs in the state, according to the American Wind Energy Association. The state’s wind power capacity of 4,322 megawatts allows it to produce 23 percent of all the power generated in the state, ranking second among the states. These mainstays of the renewable energy industry are all facing headwinds. Wind power equipment manufacturers have stumbled as business dried up over the last year because a key tax credit for wind farm developers is due to expire Dec. 31. The Production Tax Credit has been renewed repeatedly, but kept on a short expiration cycle that’s made long-term planning for wind developers and utilities difficult. “It’s forced a lot of people (wind developers) to look outside the United States,” said Peter Gray, a spokesman for ACCIONA North America in West Branch, which is now building huge 3 megawatt wind turbines for a project in Canada. Potential plant closings loom over Iowa’s ethanol industry. With corn prices in record territory due to the drought and high demand, producing more ethanol can simply mean bigger losses. Biodiesel producers, too, are trimming production, stung by high costs of soybean oil that constitutes their main ingredient due to the drought. MULTIPLE ATTACKS Amid it all, the renewables industry faces the strongest attack yet from its opponents in the petroleum, grocery and food manufacturing industries. A lawsuit challenging the Environmental Protection Agency’s decision to allow a higher blend of ethanol, E15, for 2007 and newer vehicles has been filed by trade associations representing snack food manufacturers, grocery manufacturers, oil companies, and meat suppliers. Governors from Arkansas and North Carolina have petitioned the U.S. EPA to waive the Renewable Fuel Standard that maintains high ethanol demand. The governors of Virginia, Texas, Georgia, New Mexico, Delaware and Maryland have all lent their support. All this adversity generates much less anxiety than you might expect from renewable energy supporters. Iowa Economic Development Authority chief Debi Durham sees a bright future for Iowa’s renewables sector. She sees the greatest potential for growth in cellulosic ethanol, which typically uses less valuable plant material such as stalks and leaves instead of grain, and in factories that produce bio-based products and chemical compounds called biorationals. Durham said low natural gas prices are making it more economical to make the biorationals than to make similar products from petroleum. She expects biorational plants to spring up around biofuels plants to take advantage of infrastructure that supplies ethanol plants with water, grain and finished product shipping. NEW PLANTS Valent Biosciences is building a $146 million plant in Osage that the Iowa Economic Development Authority calls the “first-ever facility designed and dedicated to manufacturing biorationals.” Its output will include microbial products and plant growth regulators. Durham points to new cellulosic ethanol plants set to open in Emmetsburg (POET/Royal DSM) Nevada (du Pont) and Blairstown (Fiberight Blairstown LLC). The Emmetsburg and du Pont plants will make ethanol from cornstalks and leaves, while the Blairstown plant will use municipal and industrial paper waste. The legislative attacks on the wind energy Production Tax Credit and ethanol’s Renewable Fuel Standard are a concern to Durham, but not one that keeps her awake nights. Both presidential contenders have platforms supporting the Renewable Fuel Standard. “These are not partisan issues,” Durham said. “They are more geographic issues — where do you come from?” Besides increasing the nation’s energy independence and environmental benefits, Durham said a lot of jobs are riding on the renewable energy industry. “I don’t think public policy leaders in Washington can completely write off these industries,” she said. Even Hunter Lovins, a widely respected sustainability author and consultant, isn’t predicting the end of the ethanol boom. On a recent trip to Iowa, Lovins told The Gazette that demand for ethanol will surge partly due to the move for energy security in national defense. For instance, the entire Navy/Marines operational platform is scheduled to be using 50 percent alternative energy by 2020. “Is using 150-year-old distillation technology and putting into it a lot of chemicals sustainable? No,” said Lovins, the head of Natural Capitalism Solutions. “Is it better than importing oil from the Middle East? Yes.” STILL OPTIMISTIC Iowa Renewable Energy Association Executive Director Monte Shaw says the next year will see “attacks on ethanol like you can’t imagine,” because petroleum companies will no longer be able to obtain enough of the federal credits called RENs to meet Renewable Fuel Standard requirements with E10 ethanol. Instead, they will have to also begin offering E15, which has 50 percent more ethanol per gallon. Despite that prospect, Shaw says the industry’s long-term prospects for the next 10 years are significantly brighter than the impressive growth of the last 10 years. The sales that will come from the release of E15 to the mass market is one reason for Shaw’s optimism, but there are other less tangible reasons. The ethanol industry has been in talks with the automotive industry about ways to use ethanol to meet the need for higher octane fuels that will be required to meet new federal fuel economy standards, Shaw said. “They’re telling us, “to meet these standards you need engines that are small and powerful. You need 90 percent octane, and to get that you need to run somewhere between 20 and 30 percent ethanol.” Walt Wendland is CEO of Golden Grain Ethanol in Mason City and Homeland Energy Solutions in Lawler. He sees hopeful signs for ethanol’s future even though it’s a mature industry. Ethanol plants are getting more efficient, Wendland said, requiring less corn and less of ingredients such as urea to make each gallon of ethanol. They are also producing more co-products, such as corn oil. The delayed arrival of cellulosic ethanol plants has provided fodder to ethanol critics, some of whom say the technology will not prove feasible. “They (critics) think cellulose ethanol has to compete with corn ethanol,” Shaw said. “It doesn’t. It has to compete with petroleum, which is trading at $100 a barrel in the middle of a recession. A lot of things are possible with $100 a barrel crude oil.” TRANSMISSION LINES Durham’s high hopes for Iowa’s wind power industry are supported partly by plans to build two long-distance transmission lines across the state to move wind power to big-city markets. “We could very easily see our installed capacity developing in the next five years to 10,000 megawatts,” said Harold Prior, executive director of the Iowa Wind Energy Association. Prior said the efficiency of wind turbines is improving with larger blades and turbines that require less wind speed to operate. He cites legislative initiatives to improve wind turbine land lease payments to Iowa farmers. In addition, Prior said there’s a large untapped marketplace for what’s called “distributed wind,” smaller turbines installed on or near the site where the power will be consumed, such as colleges or businesses. As electric power and transmission costs rise, he said distributed power will become more attractive. The growth in core renewable energy industries is fueling more growth in related industries, such as construction. Three solar panels were being installed last week at the union hall of International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 405 in Cedar Rapids. The union already has a solar array and wind turbine at its training facility on Johnson Avenue. With solar panel prices coming down, “it’s going to become a large part of what we do, along with LED (light-emitting diode) lighting,” said Rich Good, IBEW Local 405 business agent. A decision on waiving the Renewable Fuel Standard is expected from the EPA early next month. Congress isn’t expected to act on extending the Production Tax Credit for wind energy until after the presidential election. thegazette</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350836745444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 12:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350837587550-4</Id><Title>Firm Says It's Making Crude Oil from Algae - algae fuel has the properties of a light, sweet crude oil, easily refined into diesel fuel or heating oil</Title><Msg>Firm Says It's Making Crude Oil from Algae Oct. 21, 2012 Randy Griffith, The Tribune-Democrat, Johnstown, Pa. Oct. 21--Howard Walker III of Westmont says he's found a recipe to convert algae into what is essentially crude oil, like the petroleum pumped from wells. "This is a direct result of using acidic mine discharge to grow the algae," he said. "Anybody using (other) algae is not doing anything like this." A unique situation with polluted water from an abandoned Shade Township mine site led to the potentially world-changing results, Walker said at his company plant in the Hornerstown section of Johnstown. U.S. Alternative Fuels at 432-438 Horner St. has been working on the production of biodiesel from the algae for about six years. The idea was to take the technology being used to make ethanol from corn oil and adapt it to get fuel from algae oil. Similar work has been going on since the 1970s in different parts of the country. Walker is vice president and chief executive officer of the family business. His wife, Paula, is president. They decided to focus on algae because it has been estimated the water-grown plant can produce 10,000 gallons of biofuel for every acre of "crop." Corn produces about 18 gallons an acre, he said. In Walker's research to launch the project in 2006, he came across a study by Adam P. Jarvis of England's Newcastle University presented that year at the International Conference on Acid Rock Drainage. Jarvis' group found carbon dioxide levels can be 100 times higher in water discharged from deep mines. Since carbon dioxide is normally added during biofuel production, the study made Walker think of mine treatment pond algae. The algae in the treatment ponds absorb metals and help clean the water. Those metals then become part of the elements used to produce fuel. Certain other surface water biological pollutants are reaching the Shade Township water and helping create a unique algae that was being converted to fuel in U.S. Alternative Fuels' Johnstown plant. A few weeks ago, the fuel being produced took on its unique characteristics. The company has already applied for a patent. "Once we know it is secure, we will announce how we are actually doing it," Walker said. "It will change how the petroleum industry operates. I have full confidence we can actually control how the process is done so we don't have to worry about any major environmental disaster like the BP spill (in 2010 in the Gulf of Mexico)." U.S. Alternative Fuels got its production equipment from Behrens Energy, Agriculture &amp; Robotics, or BEAR Oceanics. The Montgomery County company has gotten some attention for its robotic harvesting of ocean algae for biodiesel production. BEAR also tested U.S. Alternative Fuels' latest product. While company President Rudy Behrens wasn't ready to call it synthetic crude oil, he said the chemical properties were encouraging. "They have an organic compound they want to convert to fuel," Behrens said. "We tested it and it tested very well. It fell into the range of conventional fuel." The results did not shock Behrens, who noted almost any organic material can be processed into fuel. Behrens said BEAR's process, known as cavitation, "forces liquid at high velocity to change it to a gas and reach a temperature of 5,000 degrees." The process brings the material under 3,000 pounds of pressure to break down the molecules, he said. Quality of the Johnstown company's fuel is not the big issue, Behrens stressed. "It isn't:'Can you do it'" he said. "It is:'Can you do it economically?' The process will work. Everybody's system works." Walker said his company's system will be profitable because of the quality of the product and the simplicity of its raw material. Other systems have to add some of the materials already found in acid mine discharge-grown algae. He believes the cavitation system's heat and pressure acts on the algae in the same way eons of sediment pressing down on algae and other materials for millions of years originally created the petroleum now being pumped from oil wells. "Not all algae turned into oil," Walker said, explaining his conclusion that the unique mix of mine discharge-grown algae reproduces the ancient natural process in an infinitely shorter time period. But the process will not, ultimately, be limited to mine-discharge algae, Walker stressed. Now that his company has stumbled upon the right ingredients, those conditions can be duplicated to produce crude oil from algae grown anywhere. Walker expects the Johns-town plant can be in commercial production within two years, without any outside investment. The small system currently operating can produce about 51/2 gallons of fuel an hour from 30 gallons of algae. He estimates the cost at less than $30 for a 42-gallon barrel. The small system can collect fuel in a tank behind the former planing mill building. "We are going to fill that sucker, send it to the refinery and take our $100 a barrel," Walker said, explaining that the algae fuel has the properties of a light, sweet crude oil, easily refined into diesel fuel or heating oil. Alternative fuel and petroleum experts contacted by The Tribune-Democrat said they were not prepared to comment directly on Walker's claim of producing crude oil from algae. But all said they were interested in hearing more about the project. "This is the first time I've heard of anything like this," said Robert Enick, vice chairman for research in the University of Pittsburgh department of chemical and petroleum engineering. Like crude oil, traditional biofuels are composed of hydrocarbon molecules, Enick said. But the petroleum molecules are much longer chains of hydrogen and carbon atoms, he stressed. "It is difficult for me to comment on the claims," said Daniel Ciolkosz, senior associate for bioenergy at Penn State Cooperative Extension. "I'd have to see a lot more detail to understand exactly what they are doing. "It is possible that algae grown in acidic conditions may produce oil with unique properties, but the biggest challenge in algal biodiesel production is usually not the properties of the oil but the cost of growing and harvesting the stuff. So far, field crops like canola or sunflower have been a much more economical source of oil." hispanicbusiness</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350837587550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 12:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350838237451-5</Id><Topic><Title>Saudi Arabia Unveils Plan to be Powered Entirely by Renewable Energy</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350775434142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you propose for crude oil to yield profits when it's left underground and totally replaced by inexpensive renewable energy?</Msg><Username>moooooooooooooooooooooooo4u</Username><Timestamp>1350838237451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 12:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350842637096-6</Id><Title>TROPICAL WEATHER OUTLOOK</Title><Msg>Tropical weather outlook nws national hurricane center miami fl 200 pm edt sun oct 21 2012 for the north atlantic...caribbean sea and the gulf of mexico... 1. A broad area of low pressure...associated with a tropical wave...is producing a large area of showers and thunderstorms over the central caribbean sea. Environmental conditions are expected to be conducive for the formation of a tropical depression during the next couple of days...and this system has a high chance...70 percent...of becoming a tropical cyclone during the next 48 hours as it moves slowly westward and becomes nearly stationary well south of jamaica. Heavy rains from this disturbance are likely to spread over jamaica...hispaniola...and eastern cuba over the next several days. These rains could produce life-threatening flash floods and mud slides...especially in areas of high terrain. 2. A tropical wave interacting with an upper-level low is producing a small area of showers and a few thunderstorms over the central atlantic about 850 miles east-northeast of the leeward islands. environmental conditions are expected to be conducive for some development before upper-level winds strengthen on tuesday. This system has a medium chance...30 percent...of becoming a tropical cyclone during the next 48 hours as it moves northwestward to north- northwestward at about 10 mph. elsewhere...tropical storm formation is not expected during the next 48 hours. $$ forecaster berg url at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350842637096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 14:03:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350844159633-7</Id><Title>EPA Sued Over Vehicle Fees for Ozone Pollution</Title><Msg>EPA Sued Over Vehicle Fees for Ozone Pollution Saturday, October 20, 2012 :: Staff infoZine Clean air advocates want industrial polluters in San Joaquin Valley to share the cost of fines and clean-up San Francisco, CA - infoZine - Environmental and health groups have challenged a decision by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) that shifts the fines for ozone pollution in central California away from major industrial sources and onto San Joaquin Valley residents through an additional tax on vehicle registration. The lawsuit, filed in the U.S. Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals in San Francisco, claims that EPA violated the federal Clean Air Act when it waived the fines on most stationary sources of ozone in the Valley. “The Clean Air Act imposes fees on polluters to create a financial incentive to stop polluting,” said attorney Paul Cort with the public interest law firm Earthjustice. “When the EPA decided that vehicle drivers should pick up the tab, the agency ignored not just the letter of the law but the whole purpose of the law itself.” The health impacts of ozone air pollution—often called smog—are well documented, ranging from asthma attacks to respiratory disease to death. The San Joaquin Valley in central California has some of the worst ozone pollution in the country. Even though the Clean Air Act provided a twenty-year period to reduce ozone levels, the Valley failed to attain the national 1-hour standard for ozone by the 2010 statutory deadline. That failure triggered a per-ton fee on ozone-related emissions from major industrial sources. The San Joaquin Valley Air Pollution Control District, however, gutted this mandated incentive by adopting an ozone fee rule that exempts most industrial sources. Instead, the district began collecting “equivalent” funds from a vehicle registration surcharge of $12 per year for each automobile. In August 2012, EPA approved the rule, claiming the discretion to permit equivalent alternatives even if they do not comply with statutory requirements. “The Environmental Protection Agency’s decision is a direct contradiction to its mission of protecting human health and the environment, and fails to take comprehensive steps forward in reducing air pollution in the San Joaquin Valley,” said Emily Schrepf, Central Valley Program Manager for the National Parks Conservation Association. “Yosemite and Sequoia National Parks reported more than 70 days of ozone standard violations last year, and the agency’s decision continues to put millions of annual national park visitors, and the economies that they help support, at risk.” “As a Registered Respiratory Therapist, I see first-hand the effect that ozone pollution has on the health of my patients,” said Kevin Hamilton, founder of the group Medical Advocates for Healthy Air of Fresno. “For decades the residents of the San Joaquin Valley have been subsidizing polluters with their lungs, and now EPA wants them to subsidize them financially as well.” The petition for review asks the court to overturn the EPA’s decision that permits the local air board to waive fees for industrial polluters. The suit was filed by Earthjustice on behalf of Medical Advocates for Healthy Air, the Natural Resources Defense Council, Latinos United for Clean Air, the National Parks Conservation Association, and the Sierra Club. infozine</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350844159633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 14:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350858607434-8</Id><Title>Davey outlines four steps of UK Energy Bill - “move from price setting by ministers to price discover by market.”</Title><Msg>Davey outlines four steps of UK Energy Bill 19/10/2012 By Kelvin Ross Deputy Editor UK Energy Secretary Ed Davey yesterday confirmed that the government’s Energy Bill will be published next month. He said the ultimate intention of the Bill was to “move from price setting by ministers to price discover by market.” “Eventually I want to see low carbon power sources competing on cost alone,” he told a meeting of energy players, journalists and members of the CBI (Confederation of British Industry). “But we can’t just flick a switch and make that happen instantly. Our reforms are explicitly intended to move to a market-based, price-discovery model. He said the government’s Electricity Market Reform would come in four phases. “In Phase One, we’ll introduce a mechanism that will offer reliable contracts, delivered in a way that is trusted by investors. That mechanism is the feed-in tariff with contracts-for-difference. Prices will be set administratively, aiming to bring all technology groups down in cost and begin levelling the playing field. The generator sells its electricity in the market, and is paid a variable premium to top up if necessary. And if the market price is higher than the strike price, the generator pays back the difference.” He said Phase Two would see “the first technology-specific auctions, where prices will be set competitively by the market and, for example, onshore wind generators will start to compete with other onshore wind generators, as early as 2017”. Phase three would bring about the introduction of technology-neutral auctions. “So in the 2020s, low-carbon technologies should start to compete with each other in a true low-carbon electricity market.” This, said Davey, would lead to Phase 4: “When all technologies are mature enough, and if the carbon price is high enough and sustainable enough, all generators could compete without any intervention.” He also announced that a Network Innovation Competition in the gas industry, “which would see industry invest £160m over an eight-year period in innovation and greater efficiencies in the grid”, would “go ahead at the earliest opportunity”. And he unveiled proposed changes to Section 36 of the Electricity Act 1989, which came into force before the current Planning Act. He explained that currently “if a biomass developer with Section 36 consent wanted to change the type of fuel it burns, or a wind farm developer with consent wanted to add a couple more turbines, they would have to submit a completely new application to the Planning Inspectorate under the Planning Act – a process which could take over a year”. This he said was “unnecessary red tape” and revealed that developers wishing to apply for changes to their project’s Section 36 consents will soon, in most cases, need to undertake only a three-month consultation. “This could unlock investment decisions across a range of technologies, bringing thousands of new jobs and billions of pounds of investment to the UK economy,” Davey added. powerengineeringint</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350858607434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:30:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350859031424-9</Id><Title>TransCanada delays Keystone restart to Monday</Title><Msg>TransCanada delays Keystone restart to Monday CALGARY, Alberta | Sun Oct 21, 2012 11:28pm BST (Reuters) - TransCanada Corp (TRP.TO) said on Sunday that the restart of its 590,000 barrel per day Keystone oil pipeline would be delayed until Monday, a day later than expected. James Millar, a spokesman for the country's largest pipeline company, said in an email that TransCanada was working with regulators to finalize restart plans for the line, which carries a quarter of Canada's crude oil exports to the United States. "We are finalizing re-start plans with the regulator and are targeting Monday to begin operations," he said. The company said a day earlier that it expected a Sunday restart for the line. It shut the pipeline late on Wednesday after an in-line inspection tool detected what it referred to as a "small anomaly" on the pipe. The outage pushed up U.S. oil prices on Thursday. TransCanada has not given the location of the potential defect, but the U.S. Pipelines and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration said it had sent an inspector to observe repairs on a section between Missouri and Illinois. The pipeline extends to Wood River, Illinois, and the major storage hub at Cushing, Oklahoma, from Hardisty, Alberta. reuters</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350859031424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 18:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350861433617-10</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Sees Middle Class Tax 1.7 Trillion Increase Victory - Read &amp; Vote Obama if You Love It. The Largest Tax Hike in US History has just been upheld by the Supreme Court of the United States and President Obama sees this assault on the middle class as a victory. The already unpopular 2010 health care reform law has been converted by the court into a $1.76 trillion tax increase funded by escalating taxes to be paid the vast majority of taxpayers. The high court’s ruling leaves in place 20 tax increases in the health-care law, of those, 12 tax hikes would affect families earning less than $250,000 per year, including a “Cadillac tax” on high-cost insurance plans, a tax on insurance providers, and an excise tax on medical device manufacturers. By formally converting ‘Obamacare’ into ‘Obamatax,’ the court allows Obama to raise taxes on the middle-class. The decision is a distressing blow to taxpayers and represents the single largest tax increase on young people in the nation’s history. When it takes full effect, the Internal Revenue Service will have immense new power and authority to persecute and prosecute a whole new group of taxpayers. If the law takes full effect, it will devastate small businesses and destroy any chance for a sustainable economic recovery. It will add trillions of dollars to the national debt and push the country toward bankruptcy even faster than current projections. Any individual who believes that this decision must be overturned must do everything possible to undo the damage that has been done, especially at the ballot box on November 6. –Obamacare law contains 20 new or higher taxes on American families and small businesses– WASHINGTON, DC – Obamacare contains 20 new or higher taxes on American families and small businesses. Arranged by their respective effective dates, below is the total list of all $500 billion-plus in tax hikes (over the next ten years) in Obamacare, where to find them in the bill, and how much your taxes are scheduled to go up as of today: Taxes that took effect in 2010: 1. Excise Tax on Charitable Hospitals (Min$/immediate): $50,000 per hospital if they fail to meet new “community health assessment needs,” “financial assistance,” and “billing and collection” rules set by HHS. Bill: PPACA; Page: 1,961-1,971 2. Codification of the “economic substance doctrine” (Tax hike of $4.5 billion). This provision allows the IRS to disallow completely-legal tax deductions and other legal tax-minimizing plans just because the IRS deems that the action lacks “substance” and is merely intended to reduce taxes owed. Bill: Reconciliation Act; Page: 108-113 3. “Black liquor” tax hike (Tax hike of $23.6 billion). This is a tax increase on a type of bio-fuel. Bill: Reconciliation Act; Page: 105 4. Tax on Innovator Drug Companies ($22.2 bil/Jan 2010): $2.3 billion annual tax on the industry imposed relative to share of sales made that year. Bill: PPACA; Page: 1,971-1,980 5. Blue Cross/Blue Shield Tax Hike ($0.4 bil/Jan 2010): The special tax deduction in current law for Blue Cross/Blue Shield companies would only be allowed if 85 percent or more of premium revenues are spent on clinical services. Bill: PPACA; Page: 2,004 6. Tax on Indoor Tanning Services ($2.7 billion/July 1, 2010): New 10 percent excise tax on Americans using indoor tanning salons. Bill: PPACA; Page: 2,397-2,399 7. Medicine Cabinet Tax ($5 bil/Jan 2011): Americans no longer able to use health savings account (HSA), flexible spending account (FSA), or health reimbursement (HRA) pre-tax dollars to purchase non- prescription, over-the-counter medicines (except insulin). Bill: PPACA; Page: 1,957-1,959 8. HSA Withdrawal Tax Hike ($1.4 bil/Jan 2011): Increases additional tax on non-medical early withdrawals from an HSA from 10 to 20 percent, disadvantaging them relative to IRAs and other tax- advantaged accounts, which remain at 10 percent. Bill: PPACA; Page: 1,959 Tax that took effect in 2012 9. Employer Reporting of Insurance on W-2 (Min$/Jan 2012): Preamble to taxing health benefits on individual tax returns. Bill: PPACA; Page: 1,957 Taxes that take effect in 2013 10. Surtax on Investment Income ($123 billion/Jan. 2013): Creation of a new, 3.8 percent surtax on investment income earned in households making at least $250,000 ($200,000 single). This would result in the following top tax rates on investment income: Bill: Reconciliation Act; Page: 87-93 Capital Gains Dividends Other* 2012 15% 15% 35% 2013+ 23.8% 43.4% 43.4%</Msg><Username>obama_tax_secrets</Username><Timestamp>1350861433617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 19:17:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350861958405-11</Id><Title>Insider</Title><Msg>"Inside Bain's Chinese Sensata Factories, Where Workers Put in 12-Hour Days for $.99 - $1.35 an Hour. Bain didn't build that new factory -- the Chinese Government Did October 20, 2012 | Mitt romney has made Obama's out-of-context “you didn't build that” quote a central theme of his campaign. It's ironic, as Mitt Romney is going to profit just before the election when Bain-owned Sensata Technologies moves 170 high-tech jobs from Freeport, Illinois, to a plant in China built for the firm by the Chinese government. Sensata enjoyed record revenues last year – this isn't about making the “hard choices” necessary to save a failing enterprise. The workers in Freeport have been working 24 hours a day, in three shifts. They make $14-17 per hour, with benefits. According to a report by the Institute for Global Labour and Human Rights, one of Bain's first actions after buying Sensata was to set up “12 Sensata/Bain capital funds 'organized under the laws of the Cayman Islands' so as to avoid paying taxes.” They'll get a small tax break for relocating the plant – the one Mitt Romney insisted did not exist during the first debate – and then use those offshore funds to defer taxes on some of the income the company generates. American tax-payers, on the other hand, have paid $780,000 to retrain some of Sensata's laid off workers in Illinois, according to the New York Times . One would be hard pressed to come up with a clearer example of capturing private gains while socializing the costs. Mitt Romney is not directly involved in Bain Capital, but he did build its business model. In 1998, when he was actively running Bain, he personally visited the Global-Tech Appliances plant in Dongguan, China. He witnessed, personally, the horrific conditions the plant's workers were toiling in for .24 cents an hour, and didn't hesitate to invest millions in the firm." -Alternet dot org. "Romney's Bain Capital Is Sending a Bunch of High-Tech Jobs to China on the Day Before the Election. The story of Sensata Technologies is about the hollowing out of America's economy by a rapacious 1 percent. October 16, 2012 | On the day before an election that's supposed to hinge on jobs, taxes and the middle class, Bain Capital, the company Mitt Romney founded, will close the doors of a factory in Freeport, Illinois, and ship 170 good, high-tech jobs to China. The employees of Sensata Technologies were forced to train their Chinese replacements, and the American flag that long flew over the factory was reportedly removed while the Chinese engineers were visiting the site. A group of workers have set up camp across from the factory -- calling it “Bainport” -- and some supporters have tried to block the trucks hauling equipment out of the plant. According to Dave Johnson , there have been several arrests. Sensata workers have asked to meet with Mitt Romney and hoped to enlist his help keeping their jobs in the United States, but he has refused, instead remaining on the campaign trail where he speaks often about “getting tough” with China. The most important part of the story is that Sensata Technologies is profitable operating in Illinois. Net income last year was $355 million, up 16 percent from 2010. The company reported total revenues of $1.8 billion in 2011, up almost 19 percent from the year before. According to a company financial statement , “both 2011 net revenue and adjusted net income represent record levels for the company.” So this has nothing to do with “making hard choices” in the process of turning around a failing business, which is how the Romney campaign describes Bain's corporate raiding. Bain's partners are looking for a modest boost in profits by locating the plant closer to the booming Asian automotive market (Sensata makes high-tech automotive parts). They'll get a small tax break for relocating the plant – the one Mitt Romney insisted did not exist during the first debate – and possibly defer taxes on some of the income the company generates. It takes both capital and labor to make a successful business like Sensata Technologies. In order to make a few more bucks, 170 of the people who helped make the company thrive will be cast aside like so much trash. The layoffs will surely have a ripple-effect in Freeport – a town of 25,000 with a declining population and a poverty rate well above the national average. The move is the epitome of corporate America's lack of patriotism – it's capital unmoored from any sense of responsibility for the people that make the profits or the communities where they live. The city passed a resolution Monday asking Romney to intervene. But the Sensata story has, so far, had little impact on the presidential race, mostly because Mitt Romney has no direct involvement in the operations of the company he established (despite continuing to make millions as a “passive retired partner”). But this is reading the story of Bain Capital too narrowly. Mitt Romney is directly responsible for its business model. As Tom Gaulrapp -- a lifelong resident of Freeport and 33-year employee of Sensata – told the Huffington Post's Amanda Terkel, “They're still using his business model. He's the one who taught them how to do this. These guys were put there by him. So you can say he doesn't run the day-to-day operations, but he's still at blame for the way they do business." Mitt Romney started the firm, and built it up on a strategy of buying firms with little money down, loading them with debt, raiding their pension funds and breaking their unions and then “harvesting them” – in his words – for a profit. Romney is the only person to ever serve as Bain's CEO – since his departure, the firm has been run by a managing committee. The story is bigger than Sensata, and bigger than Bain. The issue is the turn America's corporate culture has taken, and what the consequences of its model are for our economy and, indeed, our society. And it is Mitt Romney's embrace of that model – ravage capitalism that is loyal to no nation-state and blind to every human virtue but profit – that should be disqualifying. In the New York Times , Chrystia Freeland, author of “Plutocrats: The Rise of the New Global Super-Rich and the Fall of Everyone Else,” wrote about the historical tendency of elites to self-destruct by extracting wealth from the broader community to such a degree that the society becomes dysfunctional and mired by social problems. She recalls how the Venetians became the most prosperous society in the world during the 14th century by opening their economy to a broad swath of the population. Then, at the height of its golden age, “the upper class acted to lock in its privileges, putting a formal stop to social mobility with the publication of the Libro d’Oro, or Book of Gold, an official register of the nobility. If you weren’t on it, you couldn’t join the ruling oligarchy.” She then notes parallels to the United States, which featured one of the most egalitarian economies through much of the last century, but is now plagued by rising inequality and decreasing economic mobility. She writes: The 1 percent cannot evade its share of responsibility for the growing gulf in American society. Economic forces may be behind the rising inequality, but as Peter R. Orszag, President Obama’s former budget chief, told me, public policy has exacerbated rather than mitigated these trends. Even as the winner-take-all economy has enriched those at the very top, their tax burden has lightened. Tolerance for high executive compensation has increased, even as the legal powers of unions have been weakened and an intellectual case against them has been relentlessly advanced by plutocrat-financed think tanks. In the 1950s, the marginal income tax rate for those at the top of the distribution soared above 90 percent, a figure that today makes even Democrats flinch. Meanwhile, of the 400 richest taxpayers in 2009, 6 paid no federal income tax at all, and 27 paid 10 percent or less. None paid more than 35 percent... Educational attainment, which created the American middle class, is no longer rising. The super-elite lavishes unlimited resources on its children, while public schools are starved of funding. This is the new [Venice]. An elite education is increasingly available only to those already at the top. Bill Clinton and Barack Obama enrolled their daughters in an exclusive private school; I’ve done the same with mine. Much of this is the result of the 30-year assault on organized labor. It's worth noting that Sensata Technologies is a non-union shop, which is a big reason the firm can move profitable operations abroad without much resistance. Employment, in raw jobs numbers, should not be the defining issue of this election viewed in isolation. We also need to consider what kinds of jobs are being created. A recent study conducted by the National Employment Law Project (NELP) found that while only 21 percent of the jobs lost during the recession were low-paying (with median hourly wages from $7.69 to $13.83), a majority of those created during the recovery – 58 percent – have come with such low wages. These trends are not Mitt Romney's doing, but he is the walking, talking personification of what's been happening in the American economy. Mitt Romney was an innovator in offshoring. He and his family will make a few more dollars as a result of shipping those jobs to China, at the expense of the workers who “built that” in the first place. That's why the story of Sensata Technologies should have an impact in this race. -Endquote. -Alternet dot org</Msg><Username>sunnsailor</Username><Timestamp>1350861958405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 19:25:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350862132964-12</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Sees Middle Class Tax 1.7 Trillion Increase Victory - Read &amp; Vote Obama if You Love It. The Largest Tax Hike in US History has just been upheld by the Supreme Court of the United States and President Obama sees this assault on the middle class as a victory. The already unpopular 2010 health care reform law has been converted by the court into a $1.76 trillion tax increase funded by escalating taxes to be paid the vast majority of taxpayers. The high court’s ruling leaves in place 20 tax increases in the health-care law, of those, 12 tax hikes would affect families earning less than $250,000 per year, including a “Cadillac tax” on high-cost insurance plans, a tax on insurance providers, and an excise tax on medical device manufacturers. By formally converting ‘Obamacare’ into ‘Obamatax,’ the court allows Obama to raise taxes on the middle-class. The decision is a distressing blow to taxpayers and represents the single largest tax increase on young people in the nation’s history. When it takes full effect, the Internal Revenue Service will have immense new power and authority to persecute and prosecute a whole new group of taxpayers. If the law takes full effect, it will devastate small businesses and destroy any chance for a sustainable economic recovery. It will add trillions of dollars to the national debt and push the country toward bankruptcy even faster than current projections. Any individual who believes that this decision must be overturned must do everything possible to undo the damage that has been done, especially at the ballot box on November 6. –Obamacare law contains 20 new or higher taxes on American families and small businesses– WASHINGTON, DC – Obamacare contains 20 new or higher taxes on American families and small businesses. Arranged by their respective effective dates, below is the total list of all $500 billion-plus in tax hikes (over the next ten years) in Obamacare, where to find them in the bill, and how much your taxes are scheduled to go up as of today: Taxes that took effect in 2010: 1. Excise Tax on Charitable Hospitals (Min$/immediate): $50,000 per hospital if they fail to meet new “community health assessment needs,” “financial assistance,” and “billing and collection” rules set by HHS. Bill: PPACA; Page: 1,961-1,971 2. Codification of the “economic substance doctrine” (Tax hike of $4.5 billion). This provision allows the IRS to disallow completely-legal tax deductions and other legal tax-minimizing plans just because the IRS deems that the action lacks “substance” and is merely intended to reduce taxes owed. Bill: Reconciliation Act; Page: 108-113 3. “Black liquor” tax hike (Tax hike of $23.6 billion). This is a tax increase on a type of bio-fuel. Bill: Reconciliation Act; Page: 105 4. Tax on Innovator Drug Companies ($22.2 bil/Jan 2010): $2.3 billion annual tax on the industry imposed relative to share of sales made that year. Bill: PPACA; Page: 1,971-1,980 5. Blue Cross/Blue Shield Tax Hike ($0.4 bil/Jan 2010): The special tax deduction in current law for Blue Cross/Blue Shield companies would only be allowed if 85 percent or more of premium revenues are spent on clinical services. Bill: PPACA; Page: 2,004 6. Tax on Indoor Tanning Services ($2.7 billion/July 1, 2010): New 10 percent excise tax on Americans using indoor tanning salons. Bill: PPACA; Page: 2,397-2,399 7. Medicine Cabinet Tax ($5 bil/Jan 2011): Americans no longer able to use health savings account (HSA), flexible spending account (FSA), or health reimbursement (HRA) pre-tax dollars to purchase non- prescription, over-the-counter medicines (except insulin). Bill: PPACA; Page: 1,957-1,959 8. HSA Withdrawal Tax Hike ($1.4 bil/Jan 2011): Increases additional tax on non-medical early withdrawals from an HSA from 10 to 20 percent, disadvantaging them relative to IRAs and other tax- advantaged accounts, which remain at 10 percent. Bill: PPACA; Page: 1,959 Tax that took effect in 2012 9. Employer Reporting of Insurance on W-2 (Min$/Jan 2012): Preamble to taxing health benefits on individual tax returns. Bill: PPACA; Page: 1,957 Taxes that take effect in 2013 10. Surtax on Investment Income ($123 billion/Jan. 2013): Creation of a new, 3.8 percent surtax on investment income earned in households making at least $250,000 ($200,000 single). This would result in the following top tax rates on investment income: Bill: Reconciliation Act; Page: 87-93 Capital Gains Dividends Other* 2012 15% 15% 35% 2013+ 23.8% 43.4% 43.4%</Msg><Username>obama_tax_secrets</Username><Timestamp>1350862132964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 19:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350864077647-13</Id><Topic><Title>It's the WEIRDOS(Dems) vs The Good(Reps)...and that's reality.....</Title><Username>pierreperrone</Username><Timestamp>1350837168153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 12:32:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBAMA...start packing....</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1350864077647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 20:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350865907954-14</Id><Title>IPAB: President Obama's NICE Way To Ration Care To Seniors</Title><Msg>Health care reform has been one of the most polarizing discussions in all of public policy. Assertions decrying poor access and low quality of U.S. medical care relative to nationalized systems, despite often being wholly contradicted by facts in the medical journals, have served to justify the dramatic changes to the U.S. health care system fundamental to the Affordable Care Act of 2010. Only after being signed into law by President Obama has the nature of those changes become visible. While many of the law’s provisions and their implications are necessarily complex, wordsmithing by the crafters of the ACA and strident denials by its supporters have masked some of the most significant impacts of the law. What Do Actual Doctors Think About Obamacare Now? Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Contributor The Unraveling Of Obamacare Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Contributor Where's The Outrage From Young Americans About Obama's Health Reforms? Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Contributor How To Save America's Health Care Safety Net Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Contributor But common sense still matters. President Obama’s ACA established the Independent Payment Advisory Board (IPAB), a 15-member panel of unelected federal employees; its members to be appointed by the president and confirmed by the Senate. The law does not require the IPAB to be bi-partisan in structure, as is required for almost all other independent agencies. Its mission is specific – to restrict payments to doctors and hospitals in order to achieve a reduction in Medicare spending beneath a specified cap. The reality is that the IPAB represents an unprecedented shift of power from individual Americans and their families to a centralized authority, a controlling Board of political appointees that is virtually unaccountable, and destined to become President Obama’s version of the NICE rationing board in Britain’s socialized medical system, the National Health Service. But wait – President Obama and the ACA supporters point to specific language in the ACA law that explicitly prohibits “rationing.” Beyond the obvious – the absence of any definition of rationing in the law – is that this is implausible deniability, since all evidence points to the de facto rationing that will clearly result from IPAB’s dramatic payment cuts to doctors and hospitals. We know that doctors cite the money-losing reimbursement rates for government insurance as the Number One reason for refusing new Medicaid and Medicare patients. And we know, even before the ACA payment cuts of 31 percent in 2013, more than 20 percent of primary care doctors already were not accepting any new Medicare patients (five times the rate of doctors who refuse private insurance), and about 40 percent of primary care doctors and 20 percent of specialists already refused most new Medicare patients. By 2019, Medicare cuts under the Obama law will be so severe that payments will become even lower than Medicaid, a system by which almost one half of doctors already refuse to accept new patients. But what about the claim by Obama supporters that rationing by the IPAB in government insurance is no different from having private insurance, where coverage can be denied? No, it is not at all the same. When a government body, or any single entity, is the overwhelmingly dominant insurer for a group of people, or when such an entity is given vast and unaccountable authority over decisions, like IPAB, that body’s decisions to restrict care are essentially absolute. On the contrary, a private insurer has no monopoly – in a competitive environment, consumers can shop for insurance that meets their coverage needs. Just as in any other good or service, competition not only reduces prices, it improves choices for individuals. The difference is that in this case, choice can save lives. All that said, the clout of IPAB is even broader and more nefarious than on initial consideration. Beyond overpowering authority to directly cut payments for care under Medicare, the IPAB has the power to regulate all health care in the U.S., including private health care and private health insurance, so long as such action is deemed to “help reduce the growth rate [of national health expenditures] while maintaining or enhancing [Medicare] beneficiary access to quality care.” For instance, IPAB can reduce reimbursement via private insurance down to, or even below, the reduced Medicare rates, thereby maintaining (equal) access to care for Medicare enrollees and limiting overall national spending. Can we predict the future of IPAB? Over a decade ago, Britain set up its National Institute of Health and Clinical Excellence (NICE), a group of appointees whose pronouncements limit medication and technology usage based on costs. Despite the endless complaints and numerous lawsuits by doctors and citizen groups in Britain, NICE served as the model upon which IPAB was based. A Board of appointees like the IPAB, its role is to reduce health spending.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350865907954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 20:31:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350866139655-15</Id><Topic><Title>IPAB: President Obama's NICE Way To Ration Care To Seniors</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350865907954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 20:31:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NICE has become a rationing Board, holding costs down by limiting available treatments. Ninety percent of England’s hospital trusts are now rationing care by following NICE’s long list of “recommendations” that includes stopping access to drugs that prolong life or cure breast cancer, stomach cancer, kidney cancer, macular degeneration (causing progressive blindness), multiple myeloma, rheumatoid arthritis, early Alzheimer’s disease, MS, and osteoporosis that causes hip fractures and premature death. NICE also restricts hip and knee replacements, cataract surgery, procedures for back pain, infertility, steroid injections and cancer screening like PAP smears. David Stout of the NHS Confederation representing primary care trusts explained to the BBC that “the NHS faces considerable financial pressures and scarce resources have to be used as effectively as possible.” Under NICE, treatments are routinely refused on the grounds of limited resources and the need to make decisions based not on individual’s or family’s choice, but on the government’s assessment of the benefit. Ironically, according to its own annual reports, NICE is spending more money on propaganda about its decisions than it would have spent if it allowed patients access to the very medicines it is denying. Britain’s Daily Mail reported that money that the institute spends on public relations campaigns “could have paid for 5,000 Alzheimer’s sufferers to get £2.50-a-day drugs for a year” or “nearly 200 patients with advanced kidney cancer to have a drug for 12 months that would double their life expectancy.” Regardless of how strident the denials by ACA supporters about IPAB, nothing was more revealing about President Obama’s true agenda than his personal choice for Administrator of Medicare and Medicaid, Donald Berwick, officially appointed within a few months of the bill’s signing. Berwick proclaimed to the NHS in 2008 that individual choice is not appropriate in structuring health care – “that is for leaders to do” – as he continued, “I’m romantic about the NHS. I love it” despite its proven inferior outcomes and scandalous limits of access to care. And one year later, Berwick praised the UK’s rationing Board specifically, saying “NICE is extremely effective and a conscientious, valuable, and — importantly — knowledge-building system.” This is the same Donald Berwick, who declared before his stealth appointment by President Obama while Congress was in recess that “The decision is not whether or not we will ration care — the decision is whether we will ration with our eyes open.” What Do Actual Doctors Think About Obamacare Now? Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Contributor The Unraveling Of Obamacare Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Contributor Where's The Outrage From Young Americans About Obama's Health Reforms? Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Contributor How To Save America's Health Care Safety Net Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Scott W. Atlas, M.D. Contributor IPAB’s lack of accountability for such authority over the personal decisions of Americans by government appointees is unprecedented. Beginning January 15, 2014 and every year thereafter, the law requires the board to submit specific recommendations to the President and Congress to “slow the growth” in national health expenditures. However, decisions by the panel are not simply recommendations to Congress; if the Senate, the House, and the president do not concur on an alternative proposal, or if Congress does not act at all, the HHS Secretary is required to implement the board’s recommendations. The Secretary’s actions are immune from any administrative modification, presidential veto, or judicial review. As of August 15, 2014, if the IPAB does not submit such recommendations and Congress does not enact its own Medicare payment restrictions, the Secretary of HHS, an unelected official, is authorized to make and implement them unilaterally, i.e. without any other approval. Why the great lengths to isolate IPAB decisions from review or rejection? Apparently, this was designed to isolate such decisions from political “pressures”, like, for example, facing the electorate in our accountable representative government, pressures that have supposedly interfered with previous attempts to forcibly reduce health care costs by price fixing (see former Director of the Office of Management and Budget for President Obama, Peter Orszag’s “Too Much of a Good Thing: Why We Need Less Democracy,” New Republic, September 14, 2011). Ultimately unaccountable and nearly omnipotent to an unprecedented degree, IPAB has been called“…“independent” in the worst sense of the word: it is independent of Congress, independent of the President, independent of the judiciary and independent of the will of the people,” as stated by Senior Attorney Diane Cohen of the Goldwater Institute, a government watchdog organization, in testimony to the House of Representatives on July 14, 2011. Most Americans understand the reality of ObamaCare and want its repeal, no matter how vociferous the denials by President Obama and his administration. It does not require a degree in economics to realize the obvious – that reducing payment by IPAB decree for a procedure below what a doctor would accept will severely restrict access to that care –and that is a way of rationing care, whether or not the word “rationing” appears in the edict itself. And the attempt to justify such rationing by equating it with the truism that nothing is available without limits is frankly disingenuous and even offensive, a cynical argument meant to obscure what is completely antithetical to a America’s free society – the imposition of government dictates onto the personal lives of an unwilling American public.</Msg><Username>infernalequinoxa</Username><Timestamp>1350866139655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 20:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350867330638-16</Id><Topic><Title>Insider</Title><Username>sunnsailor</Username><Timestamp>1350861958405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 19:25:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama, who is in charge of negotiating trade with China, is a stakeholder in Sensata, according to the New York Times. Sensata’s efforts to chase profits abroad, particularly with the Obama administration-controlled GM, could personally benefit the president.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350867330638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 20:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350868591570-17</Id><Title>Americans readily accept new retirement age of 72</Title><Msg>Obama and Romney seem eager to appease Bibi and put two trillion dollars on the taxpayers credit card</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1350868591570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 21:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350870665185-18</Id><Title>1 of every 3 voters expected to vote before Nov 6th. Here is the early voting info! Get out there!</Title><Msg>State Early Voting Timeframe Absentee Ballot Request Deadline Deadline to Return Regular Absentee Ballots (mail) Deadline to Return Military and Overseas Ballots (mail) When Absentee Ballot Counting May Begin Alabama N/A Nov 1 - Postmark by Nov 5 - Received by Noon Nov 6 Same as regular ballot 7:00 PM Nov 6 Alaska Oct 22 - Nov 6 Nov 6 - Postmark by Nov 6 - Received by Nov 16 - Postmark by Nov 6 - Received by Nov 21 (from outside US) 8:00 PM Nov 6 Arizona Oct 11 - Nov 2 Oct 26 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Oct 30 Arkansas Oct 22 - Nov 5 Nov 5 7:00 PM Nov 6 - Postmark by Nov 6 - Received by Nov 16th Prior to close of polls Nov 6 California Oct 8 - Nov 6 Oct 30 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Oct 26 Colorado Oct 22 - Nov 2 Nov 2 7:00 PM Nov 6 Received by Nov 14 Oct 22 Connecticut N/A Nov 5 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot 10:00 AM on Nov 6 Delaware N/A Nov 5 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Upon open of polls on Nov 6 District of Columbia Oct 22 - Nov 3 Oct 30 - Postmark by Nov 6 - Received by Nov 16 - Postmark by Nov 6 - Received by Nov 16 8:00 PM Nov 6 Florida Oct 27 - Nov 3 Oct 31 7:00 PM Nov 6 - Postmark by Nov 6 - Received by Nov 9 Oct 22 Georgia Oct 15 - Nov 2 Nov 6 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot 7:00 AM on Nov 6 Hawaii Oct 23 - Nov 3 Oct 30 6:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 Idaho Sept 21 - Nov 2 Oct 31 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 Illinois Oct 22 - Nov 3 Nov 5 - Postmark by Nov 5 - Received by Nov 20 Same as regular ballot 7:00 PM Nov 6 Indiana Oct 9 - Nov 5 Oct 29 6:00 PM Nov 6 - Postmark by Nov 5th - Received by Nov 12th Upon open of polls Nov 6 Iowa Sept 27 - Nov 5 Nov 5 - Postmark by Nov 5 - Received by Noon Nov 13 Same as regular ballot Nov 5 Kansas Oct 17 - Nov 5 Nov 2 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 Kentucky N/A Oct 30 6:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot 10:00 AM Nov 6 Louisiana Oct 23 - Oct 30 Nov 2 4:30 PM Nov 5 Same as regular ballot 1:00 PM Nov 6 Maine Date Available - Nov 6 Nov 1 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Upon close of polls Nov 6 Maryland Oct 27 - Nov 1 Oct 30 - Postmark by Nov 6 - Received by 10:00am Nov 16 Same as regular ballot 10:00 AM Nov 8th Massachusetts N/A Nov 5 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot After polls close Nov 6 Michigan N/A Nov 3 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 Minnesota N/A Nov 5 3:00 PM Nov 6 7:00 PM Nov 6 Upon close of polls Nov 6 Mississippi N/A Nov 3 5:00 PM on Nov 5 Same as regular ballot Upon close of polls Nov 6 Missouri N/A Nov 5 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Upon close of polls Nov 6 Montana Oct 9 - Nov 5 Nov 5 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 Nebraska Oct 1 - Nov 5 Oct 31 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 5 Nevada Oct 20 - Nov 2 Oct 30 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 New Hampshire N/A N/A 5:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Upon close of polls Nov 6 New Jersey Date Available - Nov 5 Oct 30 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 New Mexico Oct 9 - Nov 3rd Nov 2 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Upon close of polls Nov 6 New York N/A Nov 5 - Postmark by Nov 5 - Received by Nov 13 - Postmark by Nov 5 - Received by Nov 19 Nov 6 North Carolina Oct 18 - Nov 3 Oct 30 - Postmark by Nov 6 - Received by 5:00 PM Nov 9 Nov 6 5:00 PM Nov 6 North Dakota Oct 22 - Nov 5 Nov 5 - Postmark by Nov 5 - Received by county canvass - Postmark by Nov 6 - Received by Nov 9 or 12 (depends on county) Nov 5 Ohio Oct 2 - Nov 5 Nov 3 - Postmark by Nov 5 - Received by Nov 16 - Postmark by Nov 5th (within US) - Postmark by Election Day (outside US) - Received by Nov 16th Nov 6 Oklahoma Nov 2- Nov 5 Oct 31 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 Oregon N/A N/A 8:00 PM Nov 6 Same are regular ballot Begin scanning Oct 30 Pennsylvania N/A Oct 30 Received by Nov 2 - Postmark by Nov 5 - Received by Nov 13 Upon close of polls Nov 6 Rhode Island N/A Oct 16 9:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 South Carolina N/A Nov 5 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot 9:00 AM Nov 6 South Dakota Sept 21 - Nov 6 Nov 6 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Upon close of polls Nov 6 Tennessee Oct 17 - Nov 1 Oct 30 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Upon close of polls Nov 6 Texas Oct 22 - Nov 2 Oct 30 7:00 PM Nov 6 - Postmark by Nov 6 (from outside US) - Received by Nov 12 (from outside US) - Received by Nov 6 (from within US) Upon open of polls Nov 6 Utah Oct 23 - Nov 2 Nov 2 - Postmark by Nov 5 - Received by Noon date of canvass - Postmark by Nov 5 - Received by Nov 19 Before date of canvass Vermont Sept 24 - Nov 5 Nov 5 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 Virginia N/A Nov 3 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6 Washington N/A N/A Postmark by Nov 6 Nov 26 8:00 PM Nov 6 West Virginia Oct 24 - Nov 3 Oct 31 - Postmark by Nov 6 - Received by Nov 13 Nov 13 Nov 6 Wisconsin Oct 22 - Nov 2 Nov 1 8:00 PM Nov 6 - Postmark by Nov 6 (military) - Received by Nov 16 (military) - Same as regular ballot (overseas citizen) Nov 6 Wyoming Sept 27 - Nov 5 Nov 5 7:00 PM Nov 6 Same as regular ballot Nov 6</Msg><Username>demedici</Username><Timestamp>1350870665185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 21:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350875203258-19</Id><Title>Brazil may boost ethanol exports to U.S. next season * U.S. seen as growth market for ethanol</Title><Msg>Brazil may boost ethanol exports to U.S. next season Wed Oct 17, 2012 4:12pm GMT * United States seen as growth market for ethanol * Centre-south Brazil cane output seen higher next season * Additional cane seen allocated to ethanol By David Brough LONDON, Oct 17 (Reuters) - Brazil could substantially boost ethanol exports to the United States next season, depending on price trends and changes in fuel policy, participants at London Sugar Week events said on Wednesday. Julio Borges of Sao Paulo-based analyst JOB Economia told Reuters that total Brazilian ethanol exports could rise by up to 30 percent in 2013/14. The fastest growing market was the United States, after a severe drought there inflated corn costs and boosted the U.S. appetite for ethanol imports. Speaking on the sidelines of a JOB Economia-Sugaronline seminar, Borges said the main growing region of centre-south Brazil was set to increase cane production to 574 million tonnes in 2013/14 from 510 million tonnes in 2012/13. In Brazil, the Datagro consultancy said on Monday the centre-south Brazil cane crop will produce 545 million to 575 million tonnes of sugar cane in 2013/14. Datagro's President Plinio Nastari held the consultancy's forecast for the 2012/13 cane crush, made in September, at 512.13 million tonnes of cane and 31.34 million tonnes of sugar for the world's top producer of the sweetener. Plantings for the 2013/14 crop in centre-south Brazil, were seen up year-on-year, auguring for significantly higher cane output compared with 2012/13, several analysts participating in London Sugar Week events said. London Sugar Week brings together several hundred traders from around the world, culminating in a sugar trade dinner on Thursday. Sugar production from cane in centre-south Brazil in 2013/14 was likely to be little changed year-on-year at around 32 million tonnes, according to JOB Economia. This suggests that additional cane in 2013/14 was likely to be allocated to ethanol rather than sugar, with soft sugar prices due to a glut of the sweetener giving an incentive to mills in Brazil to produce ethanol from cane instead of sugar. Borges, and several delegates attending the F.O. Licht conference in London on Tuesday, said they expected Brazil's government to increase the required amount of ethanol blended into regular gasoline to 25 percent from the current 20 percent next season, which could prompt producers to favour ethanol production over sugar. Borges said he believed that gasoline prices could potentially be increased in Brazil by some 10 percent in the next few months, noting that energy group Petrobras was having to make huge payments to import fuel to Brazil. Brazil's millions of flex-fuel cars, launched about a decade ago, can run solely on gasoline or ethanol or any mixture of the two, enabling drivers to switch at will to the cheapest option. Total ethanol exports from Brazil in 2012/13 stood at 2.73 billion litres, up from 1.89 billion litres in 2011/12, according to JOB Economia figures. From April to August 2012, Brazil's ethanol exports to North America stood at 824.1 million litres, sharply up from 205.6 million litres in the same year ago period. Brazilian cane industry group Unica has raised its estimate for ethanol exports this season by 38 percent to 2.55 billion litres (675 million gallons). Brazilian ethanol exports to North America could potentially reach 1.6 billion litres in the period from April 2012 to March 2013, according to Borges. Leonardo Bichara Rocha, a senior economist with the International Sugar Organization (ISO), said the export price of Brazilian ethanol was higher than the domestic price, boosting incentives for export. ETHANOL EXPORTS Brazilian ethanol is competitive in the U.S. market, due only to credits from the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, which requires that fuel companies use 500 million gallons (1.9 billion litres) of so-called advanced biofuels to blend into gasoline this year. The EPA recognized Brazilian ethanol as advanced in February 2010. Brazil has the only ethanol industry with the scale to meet the current U.S. advanced fuel mandate. The question is whether it can ramp up capacity for next year, when the EPA is expected to triple the requirement to 1.75 billion gallons. The increased demand from North America could push sugar prices higher, given that corn stocks won't recover soon to ease the cost of U.S. ethanol production. (Reporting by David Brough; Editing by Anthony Barker) reuters</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350875203258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 23:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350877621634-20</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder if invest and infernal will disappear ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350525016176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are delusional and getting more so each day. You can go back over 10 years and demonstrate to yourself that I have been posting under the same, single ID the whole time (on this board). As irrational as you are, I can only presume that the only thing you do in a courtroom is mop the floors. As for what happens in two more weeks, dream on.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350877621634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 23:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>