<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348114917901-1</Id><Title>GOP ‘war on coal’ bill gets veto threat</Title><Msg>GOP ‘war on coal’ bill gets veto threat By Ben Geman - 09/19/12 07:03 PM ET The White House is threatening to veto House GOP legislation that would scuttle an array of current and planned environmental rules that Republicans call harmful to coal industry jobs. In a statement Wednesday evening, the White House said the package contains “harmful measures that would undermine landmark environmental laws and adversely affect public health, the economy, and the environment.” The bill, H.R. 3409, is slated for a vote later this week. It's aimed at preventing what Republicans call a White House "war on coal." It would nix the Environmental Protection Agency’s power to regulate greenhouse gas emissions; take aim at other air emissions rules; prevent the agency from issuing stringent rules on storage and disposal of coal ash, a waste product from coal-fired power plants; and limit the agency’s Clean Water Act powers, among other provisions. The White House called the bill a major rollback of vital protections. “H.R. 3409, for example, would block landmark Clean Air Act public health regulations, such as the Mercury and Air Toxics Standard, which would reduce harmful air pollution that threatens public health, especially the health of children and seniors. The Environmental Protection Agency estimates that emissions reductions resulting from meeting these standards will prevent as many as 11,000 avoidable premature deaths and 4,700 heart attacks annually,” the White House said in threatening to veto the bill. The measure – which packages several bills that have previously passed the House – is expected to win approval Friday but won’t advance in the Senate. It’s nonetheless providing Republicans a platform for election-season attacks against White House policies that GOP lawmakers say are costing jobs in regions where coal is mined and widely used for electric power. But the White House, in the statement, pushes back against the claims. “As has been noted in previous statements on related legislative proposals contained within H.R. 3409, the Administration strongly rejects the notion that economic growth and protecting the health of our communities and families are mutually exclusive,” the White House said. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348114917901</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 00:21:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348121442556-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he can’t remember the national debt</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348102086012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:48:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We could say he was being disingenuous if he didn't seem so befuddled and vague. "Short term"? In reality there is no countdown to default.There will be no "moment" where the govt. can act at the midnight hour to avert default.It will arrive as it usually does - in the middle of the night,without warning,signaled by global markets.And once the meltdown begins the govt. will go into crises mode. A state of emergency will be declared and austerity will be imposed.DEEP, emergency cuts to all social programs will have to take effect immediately. And Obama's only answer is to make like Alfred E. Neuman act - "What ME Worry?"</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348121442556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 02:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348135376635-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he can’t remember the national debt</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348102086012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:48:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America will be gone forever if he is re-elected.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348135376635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348135522015-4</Id><Topic><Title>PLEASE GIVE OS A REAL AMERICAN PRESIDENT ! NOT A MUSLIM PRESIDENT ! LOOK WHAT HAS HAPPEN TO THE USA ! OBAMA LOVE'S HIS MUSLIM LIFE MORE THAN HE DOES AMERICA !!</Title><Username>americagreatest</Username><Timestamp>1348052746993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 07:05:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch the movie 2016. Be aware of what he will do to america. He is not a dumbocrap but a communist.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348135522015</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348135591816-5</Id><Topic><Title>CRS report: number of able-bodied adults on food stamps doubled after Obama suspended work requirement</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348102230703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:50:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are these people going to do when nobumba runs out of $. And it will be soon.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348135591816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348135672018-6</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s policy on wind energy is a real job-killer</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348079688663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More like commie rat traitor. After america falls dumbocraps will be held responsible for this mess RRRRRRRRR</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348135672018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:07:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348135743068-7</Id><Topic><Title>'Death to America' -- how did Obama's 'new beginning' get so old, so quickly?</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348078928756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:22:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wahleee the commie POS nut job. Maxipad is also a commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348135743068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348138494212-8</Id><Title>I am new to the board</Title><Msg>but wanted to share ZERO. Exxon may be looking at installing this across the world! ZERO has tripled in the last two weeks and may be a good bet going forward. Sorry for the off topic but I thought I would pass this along. And no, I am not a dot head spammer!</Msg><Username>brenda.young27</Username><Timestamp>1348138494212</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348139287767-9</Id><Title>LOOK !!!!! HITLER GAIN HIS POWER BY STARTING WITH THE SUPPORT OF THE LABOR PARTY !!!!! SOUNDS FAMILIAR</Title><Msg>THINK ABOUT YOUR KIDS AND GRAND KIDS</Msg><Username>helpusa730</Username><Timestamp>1348139287767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348141911988-10</Id><Title>Stephens: Muslims, Mormons and Liberals</Title><Msg>Why is it OK to mock one religion but not another? 'Hasa Diga Eebowai" is the hit number in Broadway#$%$ musical "The Book of Mormon," which won nine Tony awards last year. What does the phrase mean? I can't tell you, because it's unprintable in a family newspaper. On the other hand, if you can afford to shell out several hundred bucks for a seat, then you can watch a Mormon missionary get his holy book stuffed—well, I can't tell you about that, either. Let's just say it has New York City audiences roaring with laughter. The "Book of Mormon"—a performance of which Hillary Clinton attended last year, without registering a complaint—comes to mind as the administration falls over itself denouncing "Innocence of Muslims." This is a film that may or may not exist; whose makers are likely not who they say they are; whose actors claim to have known neither the plot nor purpose of the film; and which has never been seen by any member of the public except as a video clip on the Internet. No matter. The film, the administration says, is "hateful and offensive" (Susan Rice), "reprehensible and disgusting" (Jay Carney) and, in a twist, "disgusting and reprehensible" (Hillary Clinton). Mr. Carney, the White House spokesman, also lays sole blame on the film for inciting the riots that have swept the Muslim world and claimed the lives of Ambassador Chris Stevens and three of his staff in Libya. So let's get this straight: In the consensus view of modern American liberalism, it is hilarious to mock Mormons and Mormonism but outrageous to mock Muslims and Islam. Why? Maybe it's because nobody has ever been harmed, much less killed, making fun of Mormons. Here's what else we learned this week about the emerging liberal consensus: That it's okay to denounce a movie you haven't seen, which is like trashing a book you haven't read. That it's okay to give perp-walk treatment to the alleged—and no doubt terrified—maker of the film on legally flimsy and politically motivated grounds of parole violation. That it's okay for the federal government publicly to call on Google to pull the video clip from YouTube in an attempt to mollify rampaging Islamists. That it's okay to concede the fundamentalist premise that religious belief ought to be entitled to the highest possible degree of social deference—except when Mormons and sundry Christian rubes are concerned.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348141911988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348141977364-11</Id><Topic><Title>Stephens: Muslims, Mormons and Liberals</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348141911988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, finally, this: That the most "progressive" administration in recent U.S. history will make no principled defense of free speech to a Muslim world that could stand hearing such a defense. After the debut of "The Book of Mormon" musical, the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints responded with this statement: "The production may attempt to entertain audiences for an evening but the Book of Mormon as a volume of scripture will change people's lives forever by bringing them closer to Christ." That was it. The People's Front for the Liberation of Provo will not be gunning for a theater near you. Is it asking too much of religious and political leaders in Muslim communities to adopt a similar attitude? It needn't be. A principled defense of free speech could start by quoting the Quran: "And it has already come down to you in the Book that when you hear the verses of Allah [recited], they are denied [by them] and ridiculed; so do not sit with them until they enter into another conversation." In this light, the true test of religious conviction is indifference, not susceptibility, to mockery. The defense could add that a great religion surely cannot be goaded into frenetic mob violence on the slimmest provocation. Yet to watch the images coming out of Benghazi, Cairo, Tunis and Sana'a is to witness some significant portion of a civilization being transformed into Travis Bickle, the character Robert De Niro made unforgettable in Taxi Driver. "You talkin' to me?" A defense would also point out that an Islamic world that insists on a measure of religious respect needs also to offer that respect in turn. When Sheikh Yusuf Qaradawi—the closest thing Sunni Islam has to a pope—praises Hitler for exacting "divine punishment" on the Jews, that respect isn't exactly apparent. Nor has it been especially apparent in the waves of Islamist-instigated pogroms that have swept Egypt's Coptic community in recent years. Finally, it need be said that the whole purpose of free speech is to protect unpopular, heretical, vulgar and stupid views. So far, the Obama administration's approach to free speech is that it's fine so long as it's cheap and exacts no political price. This is free speech as pizza. President Obama came to office promising that he would start a new conversation with the Muslim world, one that lectured less and listened more. After nearly four years of listening, we can now hear more clearly where the U.S. stands in the estimation of that world: equally despised but considerably less feared. Just imagine what four more years of instinctive deference will do. On the bright side, dear liberals, you'll still be able to mock Mormons. They tend not to punch back, which is part of what makes so many of them so successful in life.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348141977364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348142192499-12</Id><Title>Welfare Reform as We Knew It Inside the Obama work waiver: It's worse than Romney says.</Title><Msg>It's hard to remember now, but this summer Mitt Romney opened a useful debate about "dependency"—concerning President Obama's regulation to rewrite the 1996 welfare reform. Democrats deny any such intent, but as early as this week the House plans to hold a vote to override the new rule. So it's a good moment to dissect what the Administration is really trying to do, because in this case Mr. Romney is right: The Administration has made welfare's work requirements far weaker, and for ideological reasons that the press corps has failed to report. *** The 1996 welfare landmark is among the few serious bipartisan reforms of government since the Great Society. State innovators like Tommy Thompson's Wisconsin gave Contract-with-America Republicans a model, while Bill Clinton promised to "end welfare as we know it." Their insight was that both welfare recipients and the bureaucracies built around them needed better incentives to end dependency, such as time limits on cash benefits and asking the able-bodied to work or train to prepare for work. Unreconstructed liberals—then about half of Democrats in Congress—predicted a return to Bleak House. Some Clinton officials resigned when he signed the bill. They were wrong in every way. Caseloads plunged by half, to 5.9 million in 2000 from 12.6 million in 1996. Health and Human Service Department studies show that most found work and saw their incomes rise. The anti-reformers have nonetheless looked for an opening to resurrect the old system. They have now found a way via an HHS regulatory "information memorandum" in July that said the agency would waive workfare requirements if states asked. HHS is selling this under the guise of "flexibility" and says the point is to get more people working, not fewer. But recall that the joint state-federal welfare program has always had "work" requirements. Prior to 1996, they included such demands as journaling, bed rest and massage therapy. For this reason, the statute specifically enumerated a 12-point definition of "work." People who can but don't meet the work terms eventually lose benefits. States have enormous flexibility to help recipients back into the job market. But they forfeit a portion of their federal money unless a certain percentage of their caseload complies—generally between 30% and 40%. HHS has unilaterally upended these incentives. States can now get a waiver if they want "to test approaches and methods other than those set forth in section 407," the work requirement provision, including new "definitions of work activities and engagement." But states are already allowed to experiment now, as long as beneficiaries meet the work quotas defined by current law. The crucial change is that HHS is saying they can experiment instead of complying with the law. HHS suggests, for example, that states adopt "a comprehensive universal engagement system in lieu of certain participation rate requirements." Universal engagement means that everybody is doing something constructive with their time "for at least one hour per week," even if that's as simple as "researching child care options" or "a job readiness workshop," as a 2008 HHS document put it. So everybody can spend an hour looking into day care instead of—"in lieu of"—the work that 30% to 40% are supposed to be doing. This new standard didn't appear out of thin air, but is part of a liberal critique of welfare reform that has made its way into the Administration. In 2005, Mark Greenberg of the Center for Law and Social Policy told Congress that welfare needs to be retargeted to families that are "not in work and not receiving welfare" and states ought to "work with, rather than drive away, families with serious employment barriers."</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348142192499</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:56:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348142250376-13</Id><Topic><Title>Welfare Reform as We Knew It Inside the Obama work waiver: It's worse than Romney says.</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348142192499</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a 2006 article for the journal Policy &amp; Practice, Mr. Greenberg worried that "the challenge is to ensure that compliance and penalty avoidance do not become the central goals of welfare reform." He added that the work rate "was never a good measure of state efforts to help families get and keep jobs" and called for "more balanced approaches," including "promoting sustainable employment" and "supporting labor market progress." Where's Mr. Greenberg now? Well, he's an HHS deputy assistant secretary for policy and the architect of the workfare waiver. The problem with the waiver is also its illegality. Congress went to great lengths to ensure that work requirements aren't subject to waivers to prevent backsliding. Yet with no more than a paragraph of legal analysis, HHS simply ruled it could suspend enforcement of laws that Mr. Obama does not like. This is unconstitutional, as the Washington lawyers David Rivkin and Lee Casey noted in these pages. When its welfare rewrite became a political issue, HHS then invented a new standard that appears nowhere in its original memorandum and says that 20% more people need to move to work from welfare than before to get a waiver. The Heritage Foundation's Robert Rector points out that this metric is bogus. The easiest way to achieve it statistically is to put 20% or more people on the rolls and then get credit when some naturally leave. HHS's last line of political defense is that the Republican Governors of Nevada and Utah asked for this change. They did, though they claim they weren't trying to weaken the work requirements. In any case, in 2005, 29 GOP Governors including Mr. Romney asked for waivers on "allowable" work activities. Yet the principle—those that can work must—isn't partisan. The drafters of reform knew that Governors of either party might try to take the path of political least resistance. Many Republican Governors are as bad as Democrats on Medicaid spending, for instance. That's why reformers created a structure that would resist gaming. *** This is the reform that the Administration has, in fact, gutted. There's flexibility to innovate and there's "flexibility." In the first case, HHS has denied Governors the running room to redesign Medicaid to be more cost effective. But now it tells states that they don't have to comply with the most basic obligation of welfare reform. It's as if HHS told states they can have the "flexibility" not to cover health care for poor people. Americans support a safety net for those who fall on hard times, but they don't want welfare to become a way of life. Mr. Obama seems to disagree, even if he denies it for the purposes of getting past Election Day. The House resolution to override the HHS waiver is an important reform moment, and if the Romney campaign were competent it would let every American know about it.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348142250376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348142386770-14</Id><Title>Taxpayers to Recover a Mere $24 Million from Solyndra; Networks Ignore</Title><Msg>The three networks have, thus far, ignored the revelation that American taxpayers will only recover a mere $24 million of the $527 million lost on Solyndra, a new report by the Dow Jones newswire revealed last week. The evening newscasts and morning shows have skipped the announcement. The Washington Examiner explained on Thursday, "In a little-noticed move, Solyndra LLC officially released it bankruptcy plan this week. The official word from it is that taxpayers will recover only $24 million of the about $527 million." The only utterance of Solyndra last week came when Republican National Committee Chairman Reince Priebus brought it up on Sunday's This Week. Talking to an unhappy-looking George Stephanopoulos, the RNC chairman zinged, "The entire philosophy of...Barack Obama can be summarized in one word and that's Solyndra. That's Barack Obama's philosophy." The Examiner piece quoted the Dow newswire as pointing out that "documents filed Friday evening in a Delaware bankruptcy court say private equity firms, including one whose chief has ties to the Obama administration, will get back at least half of the $70 million they put into Solyndra early last year as the company battled for survival." As the Examiner's Sean Higgins reminded, "US taxpayers, on the other hand, won't be so lucky." U.S. taxpayers will lose 95.5 percent of their investment, but Obama-connected investigators will get back "at least half." Imagine how the media would react if the situation was reversed and this were true of a Republican president and his or her wealthy donors.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348142386770</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:59:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348144689286-15</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like DC Schools</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348094454555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:40:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well since you brought up race and DC I'd have to say our Black President is 10 times smarter than the silver spoon fed white republican candidate.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348144689286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348144873103-16</Id><Title>A Failure to Disclose ‘Nonpartisan’ Obama Donor Authors Pro-Tax-Hike Report</Title><Msg>BY: Andrew Stiles September 19, 2012 3:17 pm The author of a study that says tax cuts on high-incomes and small businesses have little to no impact on economic growth has personally donated at least $3,400 to President Obama since 2008—a fact that the media outlets touting the study have failed to disclose. The author, Thomas L. Hungerford, also gave at least $2,450 to Democratic campaign committees during that same period. Hungerford is a public finance specialist at the Congressional Research Service (CRS), the nonpartisan agency that provides “policy and legal analysis” for members of Congress. “CRS is well-known for analysis that is authoritative, confidential, objective and nonpartisan,” reads the CRS website. “Its highest priority is to ensure that Congress has 24/7 access to the nation’s best thinking.” Hungerford has also donated at least $500 to Al Gore, the Current TV executive and chakra guru who lost to George W. Bush in the 2000 presidential election. At the time of the donation Hungerford was working for the Social Security Administration. He previously worked at the Office of Management and Budget during the Clinton Administration. Hungerford and CRS director Mary Mazanec did not immediately return requests for comment. The conservative Heritage Foundation, meanwhile, slammed the CRS report, arguing that the findings represent little more than “stylistic correlations” that “prove nothing.” The flawed study, wrote Heritage senior policy analyst Curtis Dubay, “called into question the quality of CRS analysis and the institution’s credibility as non-partisan.” Hungerford has previously conducted analysis for the AARP, which used his work to help defeat President Bush’s Social Security reform efforts in 2005. The Obama campaign frequently cites “independent” analysis to support its claims about the economy. In a number of cases, the analyses they have cited were authored by economists with close ties to the Democratic Party. Obama has repeatedly cited a study by the “nonpartisan” Tax Policy Center, which was co-authored by Adam Looney, an economist who previously served on Obama’s Council of Economic Advisers. When the president proposed his $450 billion jobs plan—the American Jobs Act—in September 2011, the administration touted a favorable “independent” study from Macroeconomic Advisers, a forecasting firm run by Laurence Meyer. Meyer is an economic consultant and former Clinton appointee who has donated at least $3,000 to Obama since 2008.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348144873103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348144879873-17</Id><Title>Mitt Is So Unappealing They're Hiding Him</Title><Msg>Rather than having him out campaigning. I don't think I've ever seen a worse candidate for President of the United States than Mitt Romney. But I must say I'm kinda glad he's as bad as he is. It'll keep the psychopath's on the right in their holes for another 4 years.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348144879873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348144970172-18</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Is So Unappealing They're Hiding Him</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348144879873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You want to see a MUCH worse candidate - try looking at Obamao.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348144970172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348145227532-19</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like DC Schools</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348094454555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:40:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More of your completely unsupported tripe. Neither Obamao nor Romney have released transcripts but we do know that Romney graduated at or near the top of his college class and graduated cum laude with dual degrees from Harvard. What has been reported about Obamao's sterling record? If it was out there it would be all over the liberal press.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348145227532</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348145622639-20</Id><Topic><Title>I am new to the board</Title><Username>brenda.young27</Username><Timestamp>1348138494212</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 06:54:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thankd Brenda, thanks for contributing ZERO to thr discussion, BTW what is the ZERO you mentioned?</Msg><Username>carl_cessman</Username><Timestamp>1348145622639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348145652311-21</Id><Title>How democrats govern</Title><Msg>Convicted New York Legislator Accused of a Final Swindle By MOSI SECRET Published: September 19, 2012 It was no surprise when the Soundview Healthcare Network in the Bronx began to liquidate its assets this summer. After all, its founder and chief executive, Pedro Espada Jr., the bombastic former state legislator, had been convicted of stealing hundreds of thousands of dollars from the nonprofit organization, and soon afterward, seemingly a casualty of corrupt management, it stopped accepting patients and began laying off staff members. But when what was left of the network was finally sold off for $600,000, the bulk of the proceeds went to some surprising recipients: Mr. Espada, his relatives and companies they controlled. Now prosecutors are seeking to revoke the bail of Mr. Espada, who has been free pending his sentencing, arguing in a document unsealed on Wednesday that the deal represents one final swindle. It was a stunning new twist in the slow, strange undoing of Mr. Espada, a Democrat who had sidestepped decades of rumors of corruption to bruise his way to the heights of New York State government, including staging an audacious power grab that won him a brief stint as Senate majority leader. Throughout his career, Mr. Espada cast himself as a man of the people, dedicated to providing health care to a poverty-stricken borough. But allegations that he was stealing from the nonprofit organization followed him for years. In May, after nearly six weeks of testimony and two weeks of deliberation, a jury decided there was enough evidence to convict him. Mr. Espada is still facing charges in federal courts in both Brooklyn and Manhattan, including a trial for tax evasion scheduled for November.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348145652311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:54:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348146986729-22</Id><Topic><Title>Taxpayers to Recover a Mere $24 Million from Solyndra; Networks Ignore</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348142386770</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:59:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what! What about the 1 billion cash that went missing in Bagdad under the Bush Administration! What about the Trillion lost for nothing in Iraq and we get nothing from the oil fields like promised! What about the banks getting bailed out under Bush/Paulson to the tune of 800 billion! What about Clinton and NAFTA and all the jobs lost becaused of it! What about the trickle dow economics and all the de-regulation that Ronnie Ray-gun promised that would trickle down to the middle class, but led to the banks and escentually Wall Street being broke and held up by QE to infinity! GEEEE I glad we've been in such good hands before Obama got here!!!!</Msg><Username>shawn4golf</Username><Timestamp>1348146986729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348147649951-23</Id><Topic><Title>LOOK !!!!! HITLER GAIN HIS POWER BY STARTING WITH THE SUPPORT OF THE LABOR PARTY !!!!! SOUNDS FAMILIAR</Title><Username>helpusa730</Username><Timestamp>1348139287767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:08:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny that's how Reagen started too. Joos thought they were going to a bake sell.</Msg><Username>besttoyou1</Username><Timestamp>1348147649951</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:27:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348149722162-24</Id><Topic><Title>LOOK !!!!! HITLER GAIN HIS POWER BY STARTING WITH THE SUPPORT OF THE LABOR PARTY !!!!! SOUNDS FAMILIAR</Title><Username>helpusa730</Username><Timestamp>1348139287767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:08:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Bush created the Patriot Act which stomped on your Constitution Rights and moved forward Fascism! John McCain authored NDAA which put civil arresting powers into the military's hands which stomped on your Constitution Rights and moved you further towards Fascism! Geeee, I'm sure glad the Republicans have our best interest in mind!!!!</Msg><Username>shawn4golf</Username><Timestamp>1348149722162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:02:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348152493580-25</Id><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report September 20, 2012</Title><Msg>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report September 20, 2012 Released: September 20, 2012 at 10:30 a.m. (eastern time) for the Week Ending September 14, 2012 Notes and Definitions Beginning with the report period for the week ending March 16, 2012, EIA is including salt dome and nonsalt facility subtotals for the Producing Region in the Summary section. The sum of the components may not equal the total for the Producing Region, because of independent rounding. Summary Working gas in storage was 3,496 Bcf as of Friday, September 14, 2012, according to EIA estimates. This represents a net increase of 67 Bcf from the previous week. Stocks were 320 Bcf higher than last year at this time and 278 Bcf above the 5-year average of 3,218 Bcf. In the East Region, stocks were 76 Bcf above the 5-year average following net injections of 44 Bcf. Stocks in the Producing Region were 150 Bcf above the 5-year average of 974 Bcf after a net injection of 20 Bcf. Stocks in the West Region were 52 Bcf above the 5-year average after a net addition of 3 Bcf. At 3,496 Bcf, total working gas is above the 5-year historical range. Working gas stocks in the Producing Region, for the week ending September 14, 2012, totaled 1,124 Bcf, with 217 Bcf in salt cavern facilities and 907 Bcf in nonsalt cavern facilities. Working gas stocks increased 10 Bcf in the salt cavern facilities and increased 10 Bcf in the nonsalt cavern facilities since September 7. An historical series of the salt and nonsalt subtotals of the Producing Region is available for download at eia --------------------------------- Energy Futures Prices Below you may find all the futures prices &amp; quotes for: Crude Oil, Heating Oil, Gasoline RBOB, Natural Gas, ICE Brent Crude Oil, Ethanol (E) and more. Real Time Streaming Futures Quotes (CFDs) forexpros URLs provided at talkstock &amp; stockhouse</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348152493580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348154871463-26</Id><Title>XOM in Bakken; good for Heckmann HEK</Title><Msg>fracking is here to stay</Msg><Username>atxdellionaire</Username><Timestamp>1348154871463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348156917281-27</Id><Topic><Title>LOOK !!!!! HITLER GAIN HIS POWER BY STARTING WITH THE SUPPORT OF THE LABOR PARTY !!!!! SOUNDS FAMILIAR</Title><Username>helpusa730</Username><Timestamp>1348139287767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:08:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think about your kids and grand kids if obama is re-elected it might be too late. there is no possible way the budget can be balanced. obama is leading us into bankruptcy.... the redistribution that obama is in favor of is nothing more than socialism....wake up america before its too late....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1348156917281</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348157481880-28</Id><Topic><Title>LOOK !!!!! HITLER GAIN HIS POWER BY STARTING WITH THE SUPPORT OF THE LABOR PARTY !!!!! SOUNDS FAMILIAR</Title><Username>helpusa730</Username><Timestamp>1348139287767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:08:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right about one thing. It is to late to right the ship. If you think Romney will be your savior, you're mistaken about that also. The Gobernut on Jan. 1st of 2013 is by law to cut 8% across the board on all Gobernut costs including the Military. I will bet you $100. that the law will be changed by that date or completely ignored by either candadate that is elected. The President of the United States is nothing more then a figure head and mouth piece for the ruling elite. If you don't know who they are, then you are amoung the 99%ers who are clueless to the real leaders of the, "New World Order", and their agenda!</Msg><Username>shawn4golf</Username><Timestamp>1348157481880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 12:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348162673929-29</Id><Topic><Title>PLEASE GIVE OS A REAL AMERICAN PRESIDENT ! NOT A MUSLIM PRESIDENT ! LOOK WHAT HAS HAPPEN TO THE USA ! OBAMA LOVE'S HIS MUSLIM LIFE MORE THAN HE DOES AMERICA !!</Title><Username>americagreatest</Username><Timestamp>1348052746993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 07:05:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe if we are led into Socialism, we will have health care, better education, a higher standard of living,. etc. like they do in the Scandanavian countries, Canada and the rest of the world which has surpassed us.</Msg><Username>co1trane</Username><Timestamp>1348162673929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348163091515-30</Id><Topic><Title>split......</Title><Username>benttaildog</Username><Timestamp>970444676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2000-10-01 19:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two fives do equal 10, you are correct. But two dividends is the key and XOM has a history of keeping the dividend the same after splitting so in effect doubling the payout. My parents bought 100 shares back in the 60's and are now getting over $7,000/year in dividends from over 3,000 shares. So if you're in it for the long haul if does make a huge difference.</Msg><Username>circumlocutionator</Username><Timestamp>1348163091515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:44:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348163830859-31</Id><Topic><Title>Taxpayers to Recover a Mere $24 Million from Solyndra; Networks Ignore</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348142386770</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 07:59:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most media reports exactly nothing except slant which is against their stated objectives and obligations.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1348163830859</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348164619640-32</Id><Title>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending September 19, 2012</Title><Msg>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending September 19, 2012 Release Date: September 20, 2012 Pennsylvania’s natural gas production has risen steadily in 2012 despite a significant reduction in the number of new natural gas wells being drilled by operators.The August 23 Natural Gas Weekly Update examined the slowing pace of natural gas drilling in Pennsylvania, noting that the number of new natural gas wells started per day in 2012 has declined sharply in recent months. The state’s natural gas production, however, continues to increase despite the reduction in new well starts. According to BENTEK Energy LLC (Bentek), Pennsylvania’s natural gas production has increased every month in 2012, rising from an average of about 4.4 billion cubic feet (Bcf) per day in January to approximately 5.9 Bcf per day in August. As with production increases in recent years, the rising 2012 volumes are associated predominantly with horizontal drilling programs in sections of the Marcellus and other shale formations. The state’s increasing natural gas production in 2012 is largely a function of a robust inventory of producing wells, particularly the relatively highly-productive horizontal wells drilled and completed during the past three to four years. The drainage area of wells – and therefore their productive potential – increases significantly by switching drilling orientation from vertical to horizontal, and expands even further with longer horizontal laterals. Underscoring the likelihood of continued natural gas production increases in Pennsylvania is the state’s large backlog of already drilled but not yet producing natural gas wells, as well as the impending completion of pipeline projects necessary to market the natural gas. Overview: (For the Week Ending Wednesday, September 12, 2012)•Natural gas prices increased for the report week (Wednesday to Wednesday) at many of the country’s trading locations, with an exception at Transco Zone 6-NY, which registered a decrease of 3 cents. The Henry Hub price closed at $2.96 per million British thermal units (MMBtu), up 9 cents for the week. •The natural gas futures market trended steadily higher over the week. At the New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), the October 2012 natural gas contract gained nearly 27 cents per MMBtu to close at $3.063 per MMBtu yesterday. •Working natural gas in storage rose last week to 3,429 billion cubic feet (Bcf) as of Friday, September 7, according to the U.S. Energy Information Administration’s (EIA) Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report (WNGSR). An implied storage build of 27 Bcf for the week positioned storage volumes 342 Bcf above year-ago levels. •The natural gas rotary rig count, as reported by Baker Hughes Incorporated on September 7, declined by 21 to 452 active units. Meanwhile, oil-directed rigs declined by 10 to 1,409 units. more summary data Prices: Natural gas prices increased over the report week at most spot market locations. For example, at the Sumas, Henry Hub, SoCal, Chicago, and Algonquin Citigate trading points, spot prices increased between 9 cents and 16 cents for the week. The largest price increase occurred at the Algonquin Citygate trading point (serving Boston), which increased by 16 cents (4.5 percent) from $3.55 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.71 per MMBtu yesterday. The NYMEX October 2012 futures contract rose by 9.6 percent from $2.795 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.063 per MMBtu yesterday. The 12-Month Strip (average of October 2012 to September 2013 contracts) increased by 6.7 percent over the same period, from $3.290 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.510 per MMBtu yesterday. Total consumption for the report week registered an overall decrease, driven by a significant decrease in the power sector. According to estimates from Bentek, domestic natural gas consumption declined by 5.0 percent from last week, driven by decreases of 14.6 percent in the power sector due to cooler weather. Consumption in the industrial and residential/ commercial sectors increased by 1.6 percent and 17.6 percent, respectively. Total supply for the week increased by 2.3 percent, driven by an increase in domestic production. According to Bentek estimates, domestic weekly dry gas production was 3.1 percent higher than the previous week and 2.2 percent above the same time last year. Imports from Canada decreased by 6.4 percent to 5.3 Bcf. Liquefied natural gas (LNG) sendout dropped sharply, down 11.1 percent from last week to 0.2 Bcf; sendout volumes remain well below (47.8 percent) year-ago levels. more price data Storage Working natural gas in storage increased to 3,429 Bcf as of Friday, September 7, according to EIA’s WNGSR. This represents an implied net injection of 27 Bcf from the previous week. This week’s injection was 45 Bcf below the 5-year (2007-2011) average injection of 72 Bcf, and 53 Bcf below last year’s injection of 80 Bcf. Inventories are currently 342 Bcf (11.1 percent) greater than last year at this time and 284 Bcf (9.0 percent) greater than the 5-year average. Two of the three storage regions posted increases this week. Inventories in the East and West regions increased by 38 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 51 Bcf) and 2 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 6 Bcf), respectively. The Producing region posted a decrease of 13 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 14 Bcf). In the Producing Region, working natural gas inventories decreased 14 Bcf (6.3 percent) in salt cavern facilities and remained at the previous week’s level in nonsalt cavern facilities. Temperatures during the storage report week were 5.1 degrees warmer than the 30-year normal temperature and 4.0 degrees warmer than the same period last year. Temperatures in the lower 48 States averaged 76.1 degrees, compared to 72.1 last year and the 30-year normal of 71.0 degrees. During the week all regions were warmer than normal, particularly the East North Central and West North Central Census divisions in the Midwest, which, respectively, averaged 7.7 and 7.1 degrees warmer than the 30-year normal. eia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348164619640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348164745080-33</Id><Title>Weekly Coal Production Data for week ended September 15, 2012</Title><Msg>Weekly Coal Production Data for week ended September 15, 2012 Release Date: September 20, 2012 | Next Release: September 27, 2012 For the week ended September 15, 2012: •U.S. coal production totaled approximately 20.2 million short tons (mmst) •This production estimate is 1.4 percent higher than last week's estimate and 6.8 percent lower than the production estimate in the comparable week in 2011 •Coal production east of the Mississippi River totaled 8.2 mmst •Coal production west of the Mississippi River totaled 12.0 mmst •U.S. year-to-date coal production totaled 726.5 mmst, 5.1 percent lower than the comparable year-to-date coal production in 2011 •All of 2011 production has been revised to match the Mine Safety and Health Administration (MSHA) final 2011 production. Second quarter 2012 production has been revised to match MSHA production. These changes are present in the Revisions/Archives section, and are also reflected in the "Current Weekly Estimates" and "Current Monthly Estimates" tables. These changes are not reflected in the two Original Estimates tables. eia Current Weekly Estimates eia URLs at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348164745080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348165367205-34</Id><Topic><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending September 14, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348065332804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:35:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production 9/14/2012 Ethanol - Production jumps, Stocks rise, Demand surges as a percent of gasoline demand from 9.38% to 9.66% ethanolrfa ------------------------------------- E85 Prices at the pump e85prices ------------------------------------- Gas Buddy gasbuddy</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348165367205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348165694772-35</Id><Topic><Title>split......</Title><Username>benttaildog</Username><Timestamp>970444676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2000-10-01 19:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>splits worked pretty good for Dell in the 90's</Msg><Username>atxdellionaire</Username><Timestamp>1348165694772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348167064413-36</Id><Topic><Title>Colossal Advancement for Exxon Mobil Corporation**MUST SEE**</Title><Username>donald.phillips23</Username><Timestamp>1348153268828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 11:01:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks good</Msg><Username>patrickowens182</Username><Timestamp>1348167064413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 14:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348169585616-37</Id><Title>Chicago could see 40 F night this sunday</Title><Msg>That is cold for Sept.</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1348169585616</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348169691261-38</Id><Topic><Title>split......</Title><Username>benttaildog</Username><Timestamp>970444676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2000-10-01 19:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's completely false. Please provide ONE example of when XOM has done that.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348169691261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348169852992-39</Id><Topic><Title>split......</Title><Username>benttaildog</Username><Timestamp>970444676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2000-10-01 19:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most academic research has shown that the price increase tends to occur BEFORE a split, because buyers are optimistic about the company's prospects, and that there is no correlation to price increases after the split.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348169852992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348171380702-40</Id><Topic><Title>split......</Title><Username>benttaildog</Username><Timestamp>970444676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2000-10-01 19:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can anyone gives my post a thumbs down? It's fact. 100 shares splits to 200 splits to 400 split to 800 splits to 1600 splits to 3200. 3200 X $2.28 = $7296. What's to argue?</Msg><Username>circumlocutionator</Username><Timestamp>1348171380702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348177091783-41</Id><Title>The Presidential Race is Over</Title><Msg>If is Mormonism wasn't enough, Romney at the Boca Raton fund-raiser provided a treasure trove of stupid answers.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348177091783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348177777393-42</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Is So Unappealing They're Hiding Him</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348144879873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is true. The racists will tell you Obama is a worse candidate, but they have their eyes closed....they don't see Obama....they refuse to acknowledge him and his successes. You only have to Eastwood's presentation to know how they attack him by addressing an empty chair.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348177777393</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348178852886-43</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Is So Unappealing They're Hiding Him</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348144879873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rmoney is a guy who couldn't even attend the Olympic games without insulting the host country. He couldn't attend a NASCAR race without insulting fans. He joked that he wishes he were Latino so he could win more votes. He couldn't even bother himself to thank American troops during his acceptance speech at the Republican National Convention. And Rmoney's going to bring Democrats and Republicans together? It's time to get real.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1348178852886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:07:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348179357452-44</Id><Topic><Title>split......</Title><Username>benttaildog</Username><Timestamp>970444676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2000-10-01 19:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Splits are great, they give people on Internet forums something to rant and rave about. That and the psychological effect of having a higher number of shares. Do it! Split it now!!</Msg><Username>chance_pocketwatch</Username><Timestamp>1348179357452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348179639668-45</Id><Topic><Title>split......</Title><Username>benttaildog</Username><Timestamp>970444676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2000-10-01 19:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frankly, I'd rather have a dividend increase any day. It's not like they don't have the cash to give us a little more. Do it! Do it now!!</Msg><Username>chance_pocketwatch</Username><Timestamp>1348179639668</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348179671040-46</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like DC Schools</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348094454555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:40:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama won't release his college transcripts since he applied as a foriegn student to get the free money provided to foreign students of "poor" parents. Now i'm not saying he was not born in the US, since i think he was born in Hawaii. But I do believe he lied on his college transcripts to get the aid. I also believe that Obama's grades are OK but not great. Obama speaks well but is lazy and has not learned the details on much - he has very smart people on his staff who condense the information and tell him what to say on his teleprompter.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348179671040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 18:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348183043433-47</Id><Title>Tropical Storm 18W (Jelawat) Warning #02 - JTWC Joint Typhoon Warning Center</Title><Msg>Tropical Storm 18W (Jelawat) Warning #02 - JTWC Joint Typhoon Warning Center I've provided the URLs at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348183043433</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348183726693-48</Id><Title>Kansas E15 Stations Increases to 7</Title><Msg>Kansas E15 Stations Increases to 7 Posted by Joanna Schroeder – September 20th, 2012 There are now seven retail stations in Kansas that offer E15 (15 percent ethanol and 85 percent gasoline). Several of the new stations are located in Olathe, Kansas, the first in a major metropolitan area. More stations are expected to open in the state within the next few weeks. The new E15 stations are: 397 S. Parker St. (Intersection of K-7 &amp; Santa Fe) Olathe, KS 15310 S. Highway 169 (Intersection of I-35 &amp; HWY 169) Olathe, KS 1005 N. Pearl Paola, KS 1415 W. 6th St. Lawrence, KS 900 S. Iowa Lawrence, KS “When the last hurdle fell, the rollout of E15 picked up steam. Momentum is growing. We are hearing from retailers in Kansas, Illinois, Iowa, South Dakota, Nebraska and other states eager to start offering consumers a new greener, more domestic choice at the pump,” said Robert White, Director of Market Development for the Renewable Fuels Association (RFA). Earlier this week, the first station in Iowa began selling E15 in Marion, Iowa. Those retailers interested in selling E15 should download a free copy of the E15 Retailer Handbook. domesticfuel</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348183726693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348184462132-49</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he can’t remember the national debt</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348102086012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:48:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So it is ok (per him) if the gov't screws Americans, just not China (or other foreign country.) In reality, Obama showed his real ignorance but no one ( that I have heard ) has pointed it out. There is some (small) truth to the idea 'we owe it to ourselves' and that debt is less 'important' or worrisome. But this 'owe to ourselves' debt is NOT the Tbills owned by US citizens. It is the the debt one part of the gov't owns i.e. when the Fed buys Tbills from the Treasury. Someone told Obama 'this debt we owe to ourselves' isn't critical. But either they did not explain what they meant or he did not understand them. He just thought (to himself) since only the rich in the US own bonds only the rich will get hurt and all I (we) are really doing is redistributing from the rich to the poor via gov't debt. Cause that we loan ourselves doesn't matter. Of course this is al #$%$ Many UNrich own gov't debt (either directly or indirectly) whether they know it or not. Plus when you 'screw' those rich you will screw all the debt holders. It is not like the debt comes labled who first bought it. Note that eventually, the part of the gov't that 'loaned' money to the other is going to 'need' it back. ala SS which is now started to draw down its balance. At that time, the debt issuer either has to have the money (we don't and foreseeably won't) OR they have to find someone else to buy it and give the proceeds to the original holder. Right now, a big chunk of the buyers is the Fed. They are in effect creating $'s out of thin air. Sooner or later the market is going to say enough is enough and hyper inflation will kick in as teh US dollar value plumments.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1348184462132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348184979237-50</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like DC Schools</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348094454555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:40:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One day you talk about the Romney's being on foodstamps. The next you claim they are silver spoon devils. Make up your mind. You are just like your Pres. You think you can say what is conveinet now and later no one will remember it so you can say the oppostie when it is then conveninent.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1348184979237</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348185118318-51</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like DC Schools</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348094454555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:40:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney graduated with high or highest honors each time he earned a degree. Two of those degrees came from Havard where Obama also attended. So that would seem to be a comparable . But why do we not know Obama's performance at Havard (or anywhere else)?</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1348185118318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:51:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348185279354-52</Id><Topic><Title>split......</Title><Username>benttaildog</Username><Timestamp>970444676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2000-10-01 19:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, what in the world made you reply to a post from over 12 years ago??? Me thinks someone needs help with the new (and cr@ppy) YHOO message forum formas.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1348185279354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348185530497-53</Id><Title>Panel sets floor votes on climate science, EPA mine veto power - The White House issued a veto threat Wednesday evening</Title><Msg>Panel sets floor votes on climate science, EPA mine veto power By Ben Geman - 09/20/12 08:05 AM ET House lawmakers will battle over climate science when they debate GOP legislation to roll back White House policies that Republicans blame for the coal industry’s woes. Rep. Henry Waxman’s (D-Calif.) amendment to uphold a federal finding on the threat of greenhouse gas emissions is among 13 amendments the House Rules Committee has approved for debate. Other amendments include Rep. David McKinley’s (R-W.Va.) plan to restrict the Environmental Protection Agency’s power to retroactively veto coal mine permits. But the Rules Committee, which sets the terms of engagement for floor battles,[b] is not allowing votes on amendments to extend wind energy tax credits.[/b] [b]Lawmakers will open debate Thursday and final votes are expected Friday.[/b] The underlying bill and full list of amendments slated for debate are here. The underlying GOP bill, which Republicans say is meant to counter a White House "war on coal," would scuttle EPA’s power to regulate greenhouse gases. To get there, it includes language repealing EPA’s 2009 “endangerment finding” that the gases threaten public health and welfare, which provides the legal underpinning for various federal climate regulations. Waxman’s amendment would remove the language that overturns the endangerment finding. That effectively forces a debate on the wisdom of overturning a scientific finding when Republicans are seeking to keep political attention on what they contend are the negative economic effects of EPA rules. In addition to scuttling climate rules, the underlying bill would take aim at other air emissions rules, including air toxics standards for coal-fired power plants; prevent EPA from issuing stringent rules on storage and disposal of coal ash, a waste product from coal-fired power plants; and limit the agency’s Clean Water Act powers, among other provisions. The White House issued a veto threat Wednesday evening. The bill is expected to pass the GOP-led House but is extremely unlikely to surface in the Senate, where Democrats are in charge. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348185530497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 19:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348185893498-54</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s policy on wind energy is a real job-killer</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348079688663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many times have I heard this about cellulosic EtOH? Not there yet, but soon will be up there with fusion power. Forever, 'only X years away, nearly free, limitless and clean.'</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1348185893498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 20:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348191119356-55</Id><Topic><Title>Romney’s policy on wind energy is a real job-killer</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348079688663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Been holding my breath and turned blue a long time ago on fusion, cold or hot, and cheap ethanol. Drop oil prices, the economy comes roaring back and quit needlessly worrying about man-made CO2 and what little mercury there is in coal and the economy gets still better.</Msg><Username>greedyoilybasturds</Username><Timestamp>1348191119356</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348192624018-56</Id><Title>Obamao was warned</Title><Msg>that terrorist attacks were likely against our embassies on 9/11 but he was too busy going on Letterman and attending fund raisers. That's why they tried so hard to blame the attack on 'spontaneous' reactions to a film no one has seen. It is the Obamao administration that has made a big deal out of the movie and attracted even more attention to an unknown piece of dreck.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348192624018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:57:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348192748436-57</Id><Title>Obamao apologizes again</Title><Msg>spending $70,000 or more to buy TV ads in Pakistan apologizing for an unknown film they claim to have nothing to do with....</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348192748436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348195239911-58</Id><Topic><Title>The Presidential Race is Over</Title><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348177091783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:38:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. President Obama is in a better position to win November's election than any candidate since Bill Clinton in 1996. Idiots will be expecting the 'Bradley Effect'......again.</Msg><Username>cries_foul</Username><Timestamp>1348195239911</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348195374768-59</Id><Topic><Title>The Presidential Race is Over</Title><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348177091783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:38:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The futility now of anti-Obama lies is both amusing and energizing.</Msg><Username>casey_iii</Username><Timestamp>1348195374768</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348195580231-60</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Is So Unappealing They're Hiding Him</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348144879873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Gaffster is Mitt Does the presentation under Republicanism of Bush, Palin and Romney (not an exhaustive list my any means) give ptoof that rightwingers are idiots?</Msg><Username>casey_iii</Username><Timestamp>1348195580231</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:46:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348196053300-61</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Is So Unappealing They're Hiding Him</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348144879873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 08:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No - but your post demonstrates that you are an idiot.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348196053300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:54:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348196306931-62</Id><Topic><Title>Obamao was warned</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348192624018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 21:57:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Miscues Before Libya Assault Limited Security in Benghazi, Secrecy Over Safe House, Contributed to Tragedy The deadly assault on a U.S. diplomatic mission in Libya on Sept. 11 was preceded by a succession of security lapses and misjudgments, compounded by fog-of-battle decisions, that raise questions about whether the scope of the tragedy could have been contained. Read More U.S. officials issued alerts and ordered security precautions in neighboring Egypt ahead of protests and violence on Sept. 11, but largely overlooked the possibility of trouble at other diplomatic postings in the region. The State Department chose to maintain only limited security in Benghazi, Libya, despite months of sporadic attacks there on U.S. and other Western missions. And while the U.S. said it would ask Libya to boost security there, it did so just once, for a one-week period in June, according to Libyan officials. The U.S. didn't seriously consider sending in the military during the attack. It summoned rapid-response teams of Marines only after the U.S. ambassador was dead. State Department officials said they doubted the Pentagon could have mobilized a rescue force quickly enough to make a difference during the fighting. The Pentagon waited for guidance from State, which is responsible for diplomatic security, a senior military official said. How the Attack Unfolded Adding a new dimension to the chain of events, the siege also engulfed what officials now describe as a secret safe house used by American officials and security personnel involved in sensitive government programs after last year's Libyan revolution. Even when that building, also known as the "annex," came under attack, U.S. officials were reluctant to divulge its existence, and the secrecy complicated the Libyan response and the eventual American evacuation, according to Libyan security officials. The Obama administration has defended levels of security in place. Though intelligence officials are investigating indications al Qaeda's North African affiliate had connections with militants who mounted the attack, U.S. officials say the evidence still indicates it was a spontaneous response to protests in Cairo against an anti-Islamic video. But a detailed review based on interviews with more than a dozen U.S. and Libyan officials shows months of ominous signals suggesting the need for better security, along with missed chances for delivering it. President Barack Obama, in his re-election campaign, gets high marks from voters on national security, but has drawn Republican criticism over his handling of the anti-American protests. After a classified briefing to lawmakers by Secretary of State Hillary Clinton Thursday, Sen. Susan Collins (R., Maine) called the security "woefully inadequate, given the security-threat environment." The State Department has convened an Accountability Review Board to investigate the attack, something it is required to do after such an incident. U.S. officials still are struggling to piece together details of the attack. For more than a week after U.S. Ambassador Christopher Stevens was killed, the State Department couldn't say why he was in Benghazi. On Thursday, officials said they believed he was there to attend the launch of a joint U.S.-Libyan cultural and educational program. Mr. Stevens and Sean Smith, an information officer, were killed at the consulate, in the first wave of the attack. Former Navy SEALs Glen Doherty and Tyrone Woods died later, at the sensitive safe house or annex a kilometer away. It remains unclear to U.S. and Libyan officials whether the militants knew of that facility or just followed a U.S. convoy to it after the consulate attack. The apparent lapses extended to firefighting equipment. Rescue attempts at the main building were thwarted in part by the absence of smoke-protection masks and fire extinguishers, said Libyan guards. Senior State Department officials said these wouldn't have provided sufficient protection against the diesel-fueled inferno. State Department officials said security for the consulate was frequently reviewed and was deemed sufficient to counter what U.S. officials considered to be the most likely threat at the time: a limited hit-and-run attack with rocket-propelled grenades or improvised explosive devices, or IEDs. Map: Middle East Unrest There was a string of attacks in Benghazi in the months before Sept. 11, including a June 6 IED explosion outside the consulate compound. "These types of incidents were the ones that were our principal concerns," a senior State Department official said. more in the WSJ article.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348196306931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 22:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348196435509-63</Id><Title>The Post-American Middle East</Title><Msg>The only tide that is 'receding' is U.S. influence. Another day, another installment in what President Obama likes to call the "receding" tide of war. On Wednesday, John Kerry threatened to cut U.S. aid to Baghdad unless the Iraqi government blocks overflights of Iranian planes suspected of ferrying military supplies to Damascus. But Baghdad isn't budging. Welcome to the post-American Middle East, Senator. "If so many people have entreated the [Iraqi] government to stop and that doesn't seem to be having an impact," said the Chairman of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee at a confirmation hearing for the new U.S. Ambassador to Iraq, then it "seems to send a signal to me maybe we should make some of our assistance or some of our support contingent on some kind of appropriate response." The nominee, current Baghdad chargé d'affaires Robert Beecroft, agreed, saying he has "made it very clear that we find this unacceptable." "Unacceptable" is a word the Administration often uses about behavior it doesn't like but isn't prepared to do much to stop: Think massacres in Syria, warfare in Sudan, mob violence against our embassies—or a nuclear Iran. Now add to the list the nonfeasance of an Iraqi government that calculates it has more to lose from confronting the mullahs than it does from rejecting entreaties from erstwhile friends in Washington. That's not to say that Iraqi Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki is right to let Iran use its airspace to help Syrian dictator Bashar al-Assad remain in power—as Tehran now openly boasts it is doing. It's no secret that Mr. Maliki detests the regime in Tehran, which did so much to foment the insurgency in Iraq in his first years in office. Nor does Mr. Maliki love the Assad regime, which funneled so many jihadists to Iraq and gave safe haven to so many of Saddam's exiled lieutenants. But Iraq will always have Iran and Syria as its neighbors, and it needs to choose its squabbles carefully. Nor could Iraq do much to stop the Iranian overflights even if it chose to. Iraqi airspace has been essentially undefended since the U.S. withdrew its remaining forces last year. In December the Iraqi government made initial payments for two squadrons of F-16s, but delivery isn't expected until 2014. What passes for an Iraqi air force today consists of a hodgepodge of Cessnas, Hueys, plus a few transport planes and helicopters. The Iraqi Prime Minister must also wonder why Mr. Kerry—who until last year was Assad's best friend in Washington, or second best after Nancy Pelosi—should now strike such an indignant pose about the overflights. This is from an ally of an Administration that has consistently refused to intercede in Syria in any serious way beyond symbolic and fruitless diplomacy at the U.N. An America that prefers to lead from behind can't ask other countries to take risks we aren't prepared to run ourselves. All the more so following America's complete pullout from Iraq, when the Administration could have negotiated to maintain a meaningful residual U.S. force. Gratitude is not a powerful operating force in the foreign policy of most states, including Iraq. Joe Biden, the President's point man for Iraq, now gets only the back of Mr. Maliki's hand without U.S. troops as his influence-multiplier. The larger lesson is that withdrawal from Iraq was not the no-cost triumph the President keeps telling American voters it is. The Iranian overflights—of which there have been more than 100 so far—would not happen if the U.S. still had an airbase in Iraq to secure the country's airspace. And Mr. Maliki would likely be more confident in his dealing with Iran if he had a division's worth of American troops to serve as a deterrent to Iranian incursion. As for U.S. aid, the $1 billion is not all that meaningful for a government flush with oil revenues. What goes in Iraq goes as well in the broader Middle East, from Tunisia to Afghanistan. The Administration has repeatedly made it clear that it wants to downsize its commitments to the region, as part of its "pivot" to Asia. But now it wonders why our entreaties in Baghdad (and Cairo) keep falling on deaf ears. Or why jihadists would plan to murder a U.S. Ambassador on the anniversary of 9/11 in Libya, a country we helped to liberate but have since ignored. Having first blamed the attack on the "spontaneous" reaction to a YouTube film, even the Administration has now had to admit it was a terrorist attack. One question Congress should ask is why the White House didn't act to protect or rescue the Ambassador when news reports now say it was warned that an attack could happen. President Obama keeps using his campaign catchphrase that the "tide of war is receding," but the real receding tide is in U.S. power and influence. Our growing irrelevance to the region comes with costs that are growing and that are likely to draw us back in later at a much higher price.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348196435509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 23:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>