<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348913539430-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Supporters' Dirty Tricks to Win the Catholic Vote</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348890115907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:41:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobumba is the devil and so are the dumbocraps.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348913539430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 06:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348913585195-2</Id><Topic><Title>Phantom Savings Obama’s debt-reduction plan is filled with gimmicks</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348889773722</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His whole life has been a gimmick.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348913585195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 06:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348913628136-3</Id><Topic><Title>How to Buy an Election : Just ask the Democrats</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348889367331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:29:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any thing dirty just ask the dumbocraps.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348913628136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 06:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348913685464-4</Id><Topic><Title>Dems Apparently Blind to Bad Economic News</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348889293330</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:28:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They could care less. The new communists is what these dumbocraps are.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348913685464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 06:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348913909221-5</Id><Topic><Title>Another Example Of Trigger Happy #$%$ With Guns</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348853740213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Law abiding citizens are not protected so if one person had the guts to stop this nut job this would not have happened.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348913909221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 06:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348928596337-6</Id><Title>Enbridge rejects suggestion North Gateway pipeline not needed until 2020</Title><Msg>Enbridge rejects suggestion North Gateway pipeline not needed until 2020 By Sheila Pratt, Edmonton Journal September 28, 2012 EDMONTON - Enbridge Inc. rejects a report that concludes there is enough pipeline capacity to handle increased oilsand production until 2020, a federal hearing heard Friday. In the final day of hearings in Edmonton into the proposed $6-billion Northern Gateway project, Enbridge lawyer Jack Nufeld squared off with Thomas Gunton, former deputy minister in the B.C. government and now director of resource and environmental planning at University of British Columbia. Gunton concluded in his report for the Haisla Nation that the project won’t be needed until 2020 because of other major pipeline projects already in the works, including Enbridge’s Alberta Clipper that will take an additional 350,000 — and up to to 800,000 — barrels per day to the U.S. Building Northern Gateway in the next couple of years to carry 525,000 barrels of bitumen to the West Coast for shipment to Asia would create excess pipeline capacity for exports that is costly to the shippers who use the pipeline and is not in the public interest, said Gunton. Pipelines involve “very high fixed costs” and the cost to shippers would be high if the line was not fully utilized. That in turn could affect profits and revenues to governments, he said. “So there is a concern we don’t overbuild,” said Gunton, who noted that Enbridge voiced the same concerns about the high costs — $348 million — of overcapacity at public hearings into the proposed Keystone pipeline from Canada to the U.S. gulf coast. Nufeld said no oil company looking to use Northern Gateway has come to the panel with concerns about excess pipeline capacity. Also, any potential cost from over- building has to be balanced with benefits that come from opening new markets, he said. That includes billions of dollars for oil producers from increased oil prices and revenues for governments over the 30 year life of the project. Nufeld also noted that the growing market for bitumen is in Asia rather than the U.S, where demand for heavy crude will decline, according to forecasts from the Canadian Association of Petroleum Producers. For that reason, Northern Gateway is needed to open new markets and avoid a slowdown of expansion in the oilsands and to ensure there no shut- in bitumen, the panel heard. Nufeld also noted that the National Energy Board recognizes the importance of competition among pipeline companies in considering the public interest aspect of the Northern Gateway. Gunton also said he has “strong reservations”about the company’s cost- benefit analysis which is based on a two-to three dollar price increase on a barrel of oil sent to Asia until 2048. “You should have strong reservations about that forecast over a long period of time,’ he told the Joint Review Panel, consisting of the National Energy Board and the Canadian Environmental Assessment Agency. In response to questions, Gunton told the panel he personally supports plans for a liquid natural gas terminal in Kitimat, to be constructed about 2.5 kilometres from the proposed terminus of the Northern Gateway pipeline and the proposed marine terminal for oil tankers. The Haisla Nation supports the LNG terminal and the pipeline from northeast B.C. but it is opposed to the Northern Gateway fearing a spill of bitumen on the fragile coast would be too damaging. The pipeline hearings resume in Prince George, B.C. in October and move to Prince Rupert in late November. edmontonjournal</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348928596337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348948369475-7</Id><Topic><Title>Another Example Of Trigger Happy #$%$ With Guns</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348853740213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt will take your guns like he did in Massachusetts.</Msg><Username>besttoyou1</Username><Timestamp>1348948369475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 15:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348948588619-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why XOM over $90 with yield of 2.5% &amp; shell (RDS-B) at $71 with yield of 4.8% ??? explain that??</Title><Username>jpmlondonwhale</Username><Timestamp>1348862089583</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:54:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOT $50.00 at 4.6%.</Msg><Username>besttoyou1</Username><Timestamp>1348948588619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 15:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348960574274-9</Id><Title>Obama cheats again</Title><Msg>So what's new--- According to the WARN Act, employers must provide 60 days notice to workers, labor union reps, local governments, etc., in advance of plant closings and mass layoffs that fall within the parameters of the Act. Defense contractor layoffs due to sequestration cuts (that Obama is pictured above announcing in January of this year) are looming January 2, 2013. This means that federal law will require those companies to issue thousands of “you’re out of a job” notices mere days before the November election. If you’re the Obama administration this makes you more nervous than watching Joe Biden start to talk about Dunkin’ Donuts. What to do? Simple — ask the contractors to ignore the law and promise them that taxpayers will cover possible fines and extra costs associated with any subsequent non-compliance judgments: The Obama administration issued new guidance intended for defense contractors Friday afternoon, reiterating the administration’s position that the companies should not be issuing layoff notices over sequestration. The Labor Department issued guidance in July saying it would be “inappropriate” for contractors to issue notices of potential layoffs tied to sequestration cuts. But a few contractors, most notably Lockheed Martin, said they still were considering whether to issue the notices — which would be sent out just days before the November election. But the Friday guidance from the Office of Management and Budget raised the stakes in the dispute, telling contractors that they would be compensated for legal costs if layoffs occur due to contract cancellations under sequestration — but only if the contractors follow the Labor guidance. The guidance said that if plant closings or mass layoffs occur under sequestration, then “employee compensation costs for [Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification] WARN act liability as determined by a court” would be paid for covered by the contracting federal agency. Read the memo for yourself (PDF). The federal government is offering to pay companies to violate federal law so as to not spoil one man’s re-election by exposing him to the fallout from the implementation of his own plan, and it’s all right there in an official memo for all to see (transparency promise: delivered). Republicans so far have responded with the obligatory “strongly worded statements”: Senate Republicans, who accused the White House of trying to hide job losses after the first guidance, said Friday that the new OMB statement “puts politics ahead of American workers.” “The Obama Administration is cynically trying to skirt the WARN Act to keep the American people in the dark about this looming national security and fiscal crisis,” Sens. John McCain (R-Ariz.), Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.) and Kelly Ayotte (R-N.H.) said in a statement. “The president should insist that companies act in accordance with the clearly stated law and move forward with the layoff notices.” Politics ahead of American workers? It puts politics ahead of the law. And if the administration is as certain as they want to appear that these contractors are the few exceptions outlined in the WARN Act, then why does whoever wrote the memo seem resigned to the fact that a court would rule otherwise? Specifically, if (1) sequestration occurs and an agency terminates or modifies a contract that necessitates that the contractor order a plant closing or mass layoff of a type subject to WARN Act requirements, and (2) that contractor has followed a course of action consistent with DOL guidance; then any resulting employee·compensation costs for WARN Act liability as determined by a court, as well as attorneys’ fees and other litigation costs (irrespective of litigation outcome), would qualify as allowable costs and be covered by the contracting agency, if otherwise reasonable and allocable. It’s been asked: This is a big deal. So why isn’t it on the front page of every major newspaper in America? It’s a sad state of affairs because it never even occurs to me to ask that question anymore. Besides, major newspapers these days have more important stories to put on the front page this year.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348960574274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348966368145-10</Id><Title>Lying Headlines</Title><Msg>"Obama campaign suing to restrict the voting rights of military in Ohio" Really?...No. Its a lie, like usual. In fact, the Obama campaign was suing to block an Ohio law which restricts a very successful early voting program in the state. The President’s campaign was trying to keep expanded voting rights in place for everyone, military included. So, why am I still so disturbed?</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1348966368145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:52:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348967366456-11</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Headlines</Title><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1348966368145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:52:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their lies are relentless. Don't they know that the "WMD" lie won't be forgotten for more than a decade?</Msg><Username>casey_iii</Username><Timestamp>1348967366456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348968228717-12</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Headlines</Title><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1348966368145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:52:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will not hear the NY Times or MSNBC talk to question his fellow soldiers.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1348968228717</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348969279044-13</Id><Title>With Commanders in Chiefs like Bush and Obama</Title><Msg>White folks will be unwilling to disarm when it is the Federal Government's policy to import hundreds of thousands of violent gangsters and hundreds of thousands of tons of illegal drugs from the world's largest narco-terrorist state, Mexico. Republican congressmen white washed "Fast and Furious" as that black operation dated back to 2005. Government housing in most major cities is teen age baby factories grinding out future warriors. Cops are afraid to get out of their cars at night in huge sections of most major cities and Hillary and Mitt will attempt to use the United Nations resolutions to disarm Americans. Trust a government that exports millions of jobs to communist China? Not common sense middle America.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1348969279044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348973082797-14</Id><Title>"My job is not to worry about those (47% of Americans) people"</Title><Msg>"My job is not to worry about those (47% of Americans) people" Mitt Romney, May 17, 2012</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1348973082797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348973503056-15</Id><Topic><Title>"My job is not to worry about those (47% of Americans) people"</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1348973082797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:44:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would it be fair to assume that the videographer was not one of the wealthy donors who'd paid $50,000 to eat dinner with Mitt Romney?</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348973503056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348977213419-16</Id><Topic><Title>"My job is not to worry about those (47% of Americans) people"</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1348973082797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:44:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how much does it cost to eat pizza with herman cain ??</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1348977213419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 23:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>