<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-12"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350014519805-1</Id><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Msg>Biden mopped the floor with that fascist Ayn Rand following puke.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350014672657-2</Id><Topic><Title>Where's your money, Romney believers ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1349398373610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:52:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The great lib tactic - accuse others of what you are yourself. Why don't you point out ONE racist post I have made? Oops - you can't - same empty coward as always, like all bullies at heart.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350014672657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350014706137-3</Id><Topic><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL!! And other fantasies by walhe-he-he Welfare. Vice President Ryan.Or - The Romney-Ryan administration.Either way...has a nice ring to it.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350014706137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350015368046-4</Id><Topic><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops - caught in another lie, wahleee boy "An instant poll taken by CNN after Thursday's vice presidential debate found that voters thought Republican candidate Paul Ryan beat Vice President Joe Biden, by a 48-44 margin."</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350015368046</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350015374316-5</Id><Topic><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dream on you fascist fool. The only Vice President on that stage was Joe Biden. And that's the way is gonna stay.. Paul Ryan is out to kill Medicare, Social Security and US Soldiers. On Nov 7th the filth you align with will begin impeachment proceedings because they hate this country's middle class and fear anyone that actually stands to help them. Obama will still be president and the rats on the right will kick and scream like the flailing mental patients they and you are.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350015374316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350015548167-6</Id><Topic><Title>ingernal is so stupid...............</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1349996844904</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:07:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump....</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350015548167</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350018696799-7</Id><Topic><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAHAHAHAHA!!! Joey "Hair Plug" Biden and his repertoire of funny faces! Yeah,he was most impressive. LOL!!!!!!</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350018696799</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 01:11:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350019592144-8</Id><Topic><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On the contrary.YOU'RE the fascist.A lover of all dictators.Assad,Ghadaffi,the freaks in Iran and ALLLLL their fascist buddies.If a country is democratic or even worse, a FRIEND of the US - you hate 'em. HAMAS - you LOVE 'em! Sharia law and all that....yum,yum says Wah-Wah Wahlee Welfare! Assad mass murdering his own people for Iran? Wasteland Wahlee says "NATO keep your hands off" Ghadaffi?.....same thing..........always supporting the fascists.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350019592144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 01:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350022182363-9</Id><Title>HYDRAULIC FRACTURING: Drillers suspicious of EPA's new frack notification</Title><Msg>HYDRAULIC FRACTURING: Drillers suspicious of EPA's new frack notification Mike Soraghan, E&amp;E reporter EnergyWire: Tuesday, October 9, 2012 Oil and gas companies will soon have to start telling U.S. EPA before they "frack" wells, a development that has caught many in the industry off-guard and rekindled some drillers' most potent fears about federal intrusion. The notification requirement is a little-known aspect of air rules for hydraulic fracturing finalized earlier this year by the agency (Greenwire, April 20). The hard-fought and better-known aspects of the rule don't kick in until January 2015. But the email notice requirement starts Monday. The confusion has upset some in the drilling industry, where EPA is regarded with great suspicion. "I've heard people say it's the federal government trying to get their hooks into hydraulic fracturing any way they can," said Gifford Briggs, vice president of the Louisiana Oil &amp; Gas Association. "This shows how important November 6 is." Nov. 6 is the date of the presidential election. The industry tilts heavily Republican. EPA's Region 6, which includes Texas and bordering states, sent a letter dated Sept. 28, informing recipients of the email address to use to send the notification. But Briggs said yesterday that his group didn't learn of the notification requirement until Friday, as the long Columbus Day weekend was about to begin. Now, the group says it has a shortened work week during which it must figure out the details of the new requirement. "Apparently, they went through rulemaking, and it was something everybody missed," Briggs said. After EnergyWire inquired about the notification requirement, an EPA spokeswoman sent a fact sheet about the air rules that includes details about the notification requirement. But the fact sheet does not include the date the notification requirement goes into effect. It does, though, include the 2015 implementation date for other provisions of the rules. It states that drillers should include geographic coordinates of the well being fracked. Briggs noted that drillers do not need to send other information, such as the depth of the well, or the contractor that did the fracking. The letter sent from Region 6 says that eventually, drillers will be able to notify state agencies rather than EPA in advance of fracking, tracking with many EPA programs in which the agency delegates its authority to the states. But until EPA grants that authority, drillers will have to deal with the federal government. Briggs said his members and state officials are trying to figure out whether the authority can be granted to state oil and gas officials, or the state's environmental agency. "If the goal here was to put in place a workable system that gives operators a genuine opportunity to fully comply with what are obviously some pretty complicated rules, this wouldn't be the process you'd choose," said Chris Tucker of Energy in Depth, a public relations campaign of industry groups, primarily the Independent Petroleum Association of America. Industry's dislike of EPA was reflected in its lobbying efforts to exempt hydraulic fracturing from the permitting requirements of the Safe Drinking Water Act, which is run by EPA. That effort bore fruit in the 2005 energy bill. Industry critics now refer to the exemption as the "Halliburton loophole." While EPA regulates some aspects of drilling and can step in under SDWA when a driller has polluted drinking water, industry has managed to keep the agency from having any involvement in the permitting of oil and gas wells. Such permitting is usually done by state agencies that are charged with regulating oil and gas in addition to promoting drilling. "This is as close as they've ever gotten to regulating hydraulic fracturing," Briggs said. "Why does EPA need to be involved when it's regulated by the state already?" Fracking, short for hydraulic fracturing, is a segment of the drilling process in which crews blast millions of gallons of chemical-laced water deep underground at high pressure to break apart rock formations and release gas. Some, particularly drilling critics, use the term "fracking" for all aspects of the drilling process. The air rules, formally known as New Source Performance Standards for volatile organic compounds (VOCs), were finalized April 17. They are best known for requiring "green completions," in which drillers capture the methane and VOCs normally emitted during fracturing. EPA had also originally proposed requiring notification of fracturing 30 days in advance, but that was dropped in favor of the electronic, two-day notification. The most vigorous debates about the rules involved not the notification requirement but the "green completions" rules, which EPA delayed by more than two years to 2015. EPA critics also have accused the agency of using VOC rules as a way to regulate methane emissions. eenews</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350022182363</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 02:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350035313347-10</Id><Topic><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahlleeee how can you be so f--ked up, clearly Ryan beat the clown to death.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350035313347</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 05:48:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350035372647-11</Id><Topic><Title>ingernal is so stupid...............</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1349996844904</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:07:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxipad you are a poor excuse of a man you commie POS and you are leaving soon.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350035372647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 05:49:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350035490403-12</Id><Title>dumb and dumber</Title><Msg>nobama and biten Biden is a clown, old fool, smiling idiot, liar and a communist.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1350035490403</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 05:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350036449467-13</Id><Title>maxipad and wahleee</Title><Msg>dumb and dumber. 2 stooges and commie clowns.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350036449467</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 06:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350044418933-14</Id><Title>Biden : "who do you believe" malarky</Title><Msg>This from a guy who promised that unelployment would not go above 5.6% if the stimulus were passed. Obama and Biden promised that they would lower health care insurance by $2500 and instead they're $3000 higher. Obama &amp; Biden promised to cut the deficit in half. Instead, they added almost 6 Trillion dollars to our debt. So, who are you going to believe? NOT BIDEN!!!! He's full of his own "malarky"</Msg><Username>yankeeddandy</Username><Timestamp>1350044418933</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 08:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350046278894-15</Id><Topic><Title>Biden : "who do you believe" malarky</Title><Username>yankeeddandy</Username><Timestamp>1350044418933</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 08:20:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The job that biten is qualified for is a used car salesman in the ghetto.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350046278894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 08:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350047960893-16</Id><Title>This Week In Petroleum October 11, 2012</Title><Msg>This Week In Petroleum October 11, 2012 Next Release: October 17, 2012 Heating Oil Markets Are Tight As Winter Approaches In petroleum markets, October is typically the time when attention shifts from transportation fuels to heating fuels. Strong global distillate demand and refinery outages have supported prompt distillate prices relative to those in the future. In its October 2012 Short-Term Energy and Winter Fuels Outlook the U.S. Energy Information Administration (EIA) is projecting that retail heating oil prices will average $3.80 per gallon this winter (October-March), which would be $0.07 per gallon above last winter's average of $3.73 per gallon, and the highest on record. Historically, heading into winter, heating oil prices for future delivery are higher than those for current delivery, encouraging inventory builds. However, this year, prices for future delivery are below current prices, so there is little if any incentive to buy product now and store it for sale later in the winter. As the northern hemisphere prepares for winter, the demand for distillate fuels is typically strong as consumers fill tanks in preparation for the heating season. This year, as has been the case for the last several years, the seasonal increase in demand is occurring against a backdrop of tight global distillate markets in which supply and demand centers are geographically mismatched. Europe and Latin America produce less distillate fuels than they consume and have been relying on supply from the United States, mostly exports from the U.S. Gulf Coast. This trade has been mutually beneficial because it has provided U.S. refiners with an attractive market that has encouraged high refinery utilization, which also has supported the production of additional gasoline. The tightness in global distillate markets is reflected in both the futures market prices and inventory levels in the United States. While U.S. distillate production is high, the global supply-demand balance for distillate fuels has created a price structure that has not encouraged inventory builds. In recent weeks, prompt prices for distillate fuel have risen compared to prices for fuel delivered in future months. For the week ending October 5, distillate inventories in the U.S. Northeast (PADDs 1A and 1B) were 28.3 million barrels, about 21.5 million barrels (43 percent) below their five-year average level (Figure 1). Distillate inventories have historically been used to meet normal winter heating demand but are also an important source of supply when demand surges as a result of unexpected or extreme cold spells. The low distillate inventories could contribute to heating oil price volatility this winter. In addition, outages at several major refineries, notably Petroleos de Venezuela's Amuay Refinery, Shell Oil's Pernis Refinery in the Netherlands, and Irving Oil's Saint John Refinery in Canada, have added to the fundamental market pressures in the Atlantic Basin. Market tightness could be exacerbated by a regulatory change in New York state, which starting this heating season limits the sulfur content of home heating oil to 15 parts per million (ppm), matching the sulfur content limit for ultra-low sulfur diesel fuel (ULSD). This change results in an estimated additional 70,000 barrels per day (bbl/d) of ULSD demand on an annual basis, but in times of peak demand - such as during sustained cold temperatures - could be as high as 170,000 bbl/d (See EIA Northeast Refinery Study). The specification change also eliminates an equivalent amount of demand for high-sulfur heating oil, which is the specification currently used in other northeastern states. This demand shift could be significant because ULSD is less available globally than is high-sulfur distillate fuel and the major production center for ULSD is on the U.S. Gulf Coast. Some factors could work to bring supplies to the Northeast as winter approaches. One is the late-September restart of Delta Air Lines' (Monroe Energy LLC) 185,000-bbl/d Trainer Refinery near Philadelphia, which had been idle for the past year. Some additional production could become available if other Northeast refineries increase runs in response to the current strong distillate margins. Additionally, the U.S. East Coast exported an average of 135,000 bbl/d of distillate fuel in 2012 through July. However, prices in the Northeast have recently risen compared with European markets. Heating oil in New York Harbor typically sells at a discount to similar fuel in northwest Europe, which prompts flows of distillate from the East Coast to Europe. But in recent weeks, that spread has flipped and New York Harbor distillate is selling at a small premium to European distillate. This change in price spreads could help keep some distillate in the domestic market. More supplies could also result from Colonial Pipeline's completion of a recent 55,000-bbl/d capacity expansion of a dedicated distillate pipeline from Houston, Texas, to Greensboro, North Carolina. Colonial is also expanding capacity by an additional 60,000-bbl/d from Greensboro to Linden, New Jersey, and that capacity could come online as early as the first quarter of 2013. Besides factors unique to the distillate market, crude oil prices are a major determinant of heating oil prices. Brent spot prices are expected to average about $108 per barrel this winter, about 6 percent lower than last winter. Weather will be the major factor affecting demand, and, thus, could also cause prices to vary significantly from the EIA forecast. Although the residential market share for heating oil has been declining as more consumers favor other primary heating fuels, consumption can still vary greatly based on weather. This year, winter temperatures are expected to return closer to normal levels after last year's very mild weather. Based on the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) weather forecast, EIA projects population-weighted U.S. heating degree days will be about 18 percent higher than last winter, which was the fourth warmest winter on record and the warmest since 1999-2000, but about 2 percent lower than the 30-year (1971-2000) average. Heating degree day projections vary between different regions. For example, heating degree days in the Northeast, which includes about 80 percent of all households that use heating oil as their primary heating fuel, are projected to be about 20 percent higher than last winter. However, any variation in actual weather from the forecast could cause demand to vary. Gasoline and diesel fuel prices both increase The U.S. average retail price of regular gasoline increased five cents last week to $3.85 per gallon, 43 cents per gallon higher than last year at this time. Prices decreased in all regions of the Nation except the West Coast, where the price was up 33 cents to $4.41 per gallon. This is the largest one week increase in the West Coast gasoline price since EIA began collecting data. The Gulf Coast and Rocky Mountain prices each decreased two cents, to $3.54 per gallon and $3.75 per gallon, respectively. The Midwest price was down a penny to $3.77 per gallon, while the price on the East Coast is $3.80 per gallon, down less than a penny from last week. The national average diesel fuel price increased a penny and a half to $4.09 per gallon, 37 cents per gallon higher than last year at this time. The largest increase came in the Midwest, where the price increased three cents to $4.04 per gallon. The East Coast price increased two cents to $4.10 per gallon, while the price on the Gulf Coast did not change from last week and remains at $4.00 per gallon. West of the Rockies, the Rocky Mountain price is a penny less than last week at $4.19 per gallon, and the West Coast price is up two cents to $4.32 per gallon. Propane Stocks Continue to Increase Total U.S. inventories of propane showed another build last week, adding 0.3 million barrels to end at 75.9 million barrels. Most of the gain occurred in the Gulf Coast region, which added 0.7 million barrels of new propane stocks. East Coast stocks were 0.1 million barrels higher and the Rocky Mountain/West Coast regional inventories were up slightly. Midwest regional stocks fell 0.5 million barrels. Propylene non-fuel-use inventories represented 5.8 percent of total propane inventories. Residential heating oil prices increased Residential heating oil prices increased during the period ending October 8, 2012. The average residential heating oil price rose by almost $0.02 per gallon last week to reach $3.98 per gallon, an increase of $0.29 per gallon from the same time last year. Wholesale heating oil prices increased by $0.01 last week to reach $3.28 per gallon; nearly $0.32 per gallon more than last year at this time. The average residential propane price increased last week, by almost $0.02 per gallon, to reach a price just under $2.38 per gallon. This is a drop of $0.40 per gallon compared to the $2.78 per gallon average from the same period last year. Wholesale propane prices increased by more than $0.03 per gallon, rising from just under $0.94 per gallon a week ago to $0.97 per gallon for the week ending October 8, 2012. This was a decrease of $0.55 per gallon when compared to the October 10, 2011 price of $1.52 per gallon. eia URL provided at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350047960893</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350048324602-17</Id><Title>HYDRAULIC FRACTURING: Drillers suspicious of EPA's new frack notification</Title><Msg>HYDRAULIC FRACTURING: Drillers suspicious of EPA's new frack notification Mike Soraghan, E&amp;E reporter EnergyWire: Tuesday, October 9, 2012 Oil and gas companies will soon have to start telling U.S. EPA before they "frack" wells, a development that has caught many in the industry off-guard and rekindled some drillers' most potent fears about federal intrusion. The notification requirement is a little-known aspect of air rules for hydraulic fracturing finalized earlier this year by the agency (Greenwire, April 20). The hard-fought and better-known aspects of the rule don't kick in until January 2015. But the email notice requirement starts Monday. The confusion has upset some in the drilling industry, where EPA is regarded with great suspicion. "I've heard people say it's the federal government trying to get their hooks into hydraulic fracturing any way they can," said Gifford Briggs, vice president of the Louisiana Oil &amp; Gas Association. "This shows how important November 6 is." Nov. 6 is the date of the presidential election. The industry tilts heavily Republican. EPA's Region 6, which includes Texas and bordering states, sent a letter dated Sept. 28, informing recipients of the email address to use to send the notification. But Briggs said yesterday that his group didn't learn of the notification requirement until Friday, as the long Columbus Day weekend was about to begin. Now, the group says it has a shortened work week during which it must figure out the details of the new requirement. "Apparently, they went through rulemaking, and it was something everybody missed," Briggs said. After EnergyWire inquired about the notification requirement, an EPA spokeswoman sent a fact sheet about the air rules that includes details about the notification requirement. But the fact sheet does not include the date the notification requirement goes into effect. It does, though, include the 2015 implementation date for other provisions of the rules. It states that drillers should include geographic coordinates of the well being fracked. Briggs noted that drillers do not need to send other information, such as the depth of the well, or the contractor that did the fracking. The letter sent from Region 6 says that eventually, drillers will be able to notify state agencies rather than EPA in advance of fracking, tracking with many EPA programs in which the agency delegates its authority to the states. But until EPA grants that authority, drillers will have to deal with the federal government. Briggs said his members and state officials are trying to figure out whether the authority can be granted to state oil and gas officials, or the state's environmental agency. "If the goal here was to put in place a workable system that gives operators a genuine opportunity to fully comply with what are obviously some pretty complicated rules, this wouldn't be the process you'd choose," said Chris Tucker of Energy in Depth, a public relations campaign of industry groups, primarily the Independent Petroleum Association of America. Industry's dislike of EPA was reflected in its lobbying efforts to exempt hydraulic fracturing from the permitting requirements of the Safe Drinking Water Act, which is run by EPA. That effort bore fruit in the 2005 energy bill. Industry critics now refer to the exemption as the "Halliburton loophole." While EPA regulates some aspects of drilling and can step in under SDWA when a driller has polluted drinking water, industry has managed to keep the agency from having any involvement in the permitting of oil and gas wells. Such permitting is usually done by state agencies that are charged with regulating oil and gas in addition to promoting drilling. "This is as close as they've ever gotten to regulating hydraulic fracturing," Briggs said. "Why does EPA need to be involved when it's regulated by the state already?" Fracking, short for hydraulic fracturing, is a segment of the drilling process in which crews blast millions of gallons of chemical-laced water deep underground at high pressure to break apart rock formations and release gas. Some, particularly drilling critics, use the term "fracking" for all aspects of the drilling process. The air rules, formally known as New Source Performance Standards for volatile organic compounds (VOCs), were finalized April 17. They are best known for requiring "green completions," in which drillers capture the methane and VOCs normally emitted during fracturing. EPA had also originally proposed requiring notification of fracturing 30 days in advance, but that was dropped in favor of the electronic, two-day notification. The most vigorous debates about the rules involved not the notification requirement but the "green completions" rules, which EPA delayed by more than two years to 2015. EPA critics also have accused the agency of using VOC rules as a way to regulate methane emissions. eenews</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350048324602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350048532084-18</Id><Topic><Title>HYDRAULIC FRACTURING: Drillers suspicious of EPA's new frack notification</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350048324602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously there'll be EPA surviellance which should have been implemented years ago. Helicopters, aircraft, drones?, satellites? ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350048532084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350048875364-19</Id><Topic><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah yes more right wing lies.. Keep lying to yourself you fool, it must make it easier for you being the coward you are. Here's a blurp in review of the thrashing Bidan gave Lyin Ryan. Whether you loved or hated his performance — a decision that seemed to split (surprise!) along partisan lines — it was Biden who dominated the conversation during and after Thursday's vice-presidential debate, with his animated facial reactions to almost anything his opponent, Paul Ryan, uttered. The vice president also came up with the two catchiest phrases of the night — "bunch of malarkey" and "bunch of stuff" — both of them employed (and tweeted, and retweeted) to paint his Republican opponent as untruthful.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350048875364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350049437356-20</Id><Title>As*les .. pump XOM to infinity?</Title><Msg>Oil crooks are so rich</Msg><Username>behindtruth2003</Username><Timestamp>1350049437356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350049512029-21</Id><Topic><Title>Survey: Adult film industry favors Obama</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349975000571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The adult film industry is owned and controlled by j's. Of course a majority are going to support any Democrat</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1350049512029</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350054002331-22</Id><Title>F* you oil crooks!!!!</Title><Msg>You robbed the world</Msg><Username>oih_2007</Username><Timestamp>1350054002331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350054461547-23</Id><Topic><Title>XOM is too superior to skip right now. Examine why!</Title><Username>jonathoncollins47</Username><Timestamp>1349959331474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 08:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow unreal action we going down big time,cash out and cash in</Msg><Username>bueno.ethridge</Username><Timestamp>1350054461547</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350056437080-24</Id><Title>Time to step in and buy here.</Title><Msg>there's upside</Msg><Username>causinginflation</Username><Timestamp>1350056437080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350058009566-25</Id><Title>Cup / handle</Title><Msg>Excellent cup/handle chart. EBIX. Perfect timing.</Msg><Username>janiegarcia956</Username><Timestamp>1350058009566</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350058775650-26</Id><Topic><Title>ROBME SAID HE WILL "BUILT MORE NAVAL SHIPS AND SUBMARINES" !! BUT CUT BIG BIRD ??</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1349759359201</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 01:09:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAHAHAHAHA! So unless "authorized" in a 200 year old document, we can't spend money on it? What does the constitution say about our Air Force? (snicker!)</Msg><Username>hello2bushdepression</Username><Timestamp>1350058775650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350058852890-27</Id><Title>GOPtard says public TV "not authorized" in the constitution!</Title><Msg>There is no doubt, the GOP is the party of idiots.</Msg><Username>hello2bushdepression</Username><Timestamp>1350058852890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:20:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350058932846-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Backs Renewable Fuel Standard</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349961972068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:26:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Until he changes his mind tomorrow!</Msg><Username>hello2bushdepression</Username><Timestamp>1350058932846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:22:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350059205657-29</Id><Title>WOW, are you rubes going to fall for the same old promises Bush made?</Title><Msg>shortly before he DOUBLED the NATIONAL DEBT?</Msg><Username>hello2bushdepression</Username><Timestamp>1350059205657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350059840865-30</Id><Title>Surprise Jack Welch Missed Shows Better U.S. Growth: Economy</Title><Msg>Surprise Jack Welch Missed Shows Better U.S. Growth: Economy By Shobhana Chandra and Mike Dorning - Oct 12, 2012 9:46 AM CT Bloomberg: It isn’t only the federal government’s Bureau of Labor Statistics that is issuing surprisingly good news about the U.S. economy these days. If former General Electric Co. Chief Executive Officer Jack Welch’s charges of a political fix to manipulate economic data ahead of the presidential election are true, there must be a vast econometric conspiracy embracing auto dealers, real estate agents, the Federal Reserve and corporate America’s 96-year-old Conference Board. The economy is improving more than professional forecasters anticipated, particularly in data on employment and housing, according to the Bloomberg Economic Surprise Index, which compares 38 indicators with analysts’ predictions. The index, based on gauges compiled by private businesses and trade groups in addition to government, confirms U.S. growth is generating jobs in the face of a global slowdown and looming federal spending cuts and tax increases known as the fiscal cliff.</Msg><Username>captain_tweezers</Username><Timestamp>1350059840865</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350060221149-31</Id><Title>Joe Terranova is buying XOM, CVX on cnbc now.</Title><Msg>.........</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1350060221149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350062029287-32</Id><Topic><Title>WOW, are you rubes going to fall for the same old promises Bush made?</Title><Username>hello2bushdepression</Username><Timestamp>1350059205657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:26:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a f--kin #$%$ or blind?</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350062029287</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350062079184-33</Id><Topic><Title>GOPtard says public TV "not authorized" in the constitution!</Title><Username>hello2bushdepression</Username><Timestamp>1350058852890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:20:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you are a rat commie traitor to your country.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350062079184</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:14:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350062121251-34</Id><Topic><Title>F* you oil crooks!!!!</Title><Username>oih_2007</Username><Timestamp>1350054002331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:00:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go ride a horse F.Face.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350062121251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350062231509-35</Id><Topic><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan let the old fool clown run his mouth in front of america. The young stud set the old fool up. And just like dopey maxipad and wahleee biten ran with nit.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350062231509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350063689291-36</Id><Topic><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just laughed out loud at you. You're an idiot..</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350063689291</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350064943307-37</Id><Topic><Title>XOM is too superior to skip right now. Examine why!</Title><Username>jonathoncollins47</Username><Timestamp>1349959331474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 08:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you read this youd be safe</Msg><Username>townsend.babcock</Username><Timestamp>1350064943307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350066144056-38</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u got that right</Msg><Username>townsend.babcock</Username><Timestamp>1350066144056</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350067298678-39</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>exciting</Msg><Username>travisgutierrez91</Username><Timestamp>1350067298678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350069051558-40</Id><Topic><Title>XOM price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>joehammond14</Username><Timestamp>1349444388478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>changed my opinion on it for sure</Msg><Username>gebotynes</Username><Timestamp>1350069051558</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350072199445-41</Id><Title>Iraq Iran Syria alliance not a surprise to US officials</Title><Msg>Even though they are privately irritated ultimately the entire Middle East understands we want to put them under Netty's control.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1350072199445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 16:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350073376368-42</Id><Topic><Title>Iraq Iran Syria alliance not a surprise to US officials</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1350072199445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 16:03:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But stupid joe biten says------</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350073376368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 16:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350073511370-43</Id><Topic><Title>Punk Ryan Put In His Place</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350014519805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:01:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nov 7 I am kicking wahlees #$%$ out of america and then its maxidopy's #$%$.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350073511370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 16:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350076331023-44</Id><Topic><Title>I Think Wahleee's Numerous Loonie Posts Today Are Indicative</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1349809879821</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wahleeee and Biden are one in the same angry old white men libs with mental disorders. Biden sounded and looked alot like Wahleee's loonie tune posts.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350076331023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 17:12:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350084274974-45</Id><Title>Benghazi Blues PT III What did Obama know and.....</Title><Msg>when did he know it????? NOBODY at State or CIA who was anywhere near the Benghazi attack said it was preceded by a demonstration.Only when it reached Washington did the phantom demonstration suddenly appear......but not really,as we now know. This is playing out like Aznar and the Al-Quaeda Madrid bombing a/k/a the spanish "9/11" - In the midst of a parliamentary election Aznar at first denied it was an Al-Quaeda attack. But once the truth emerged his party was roundly defeated in the election.The White House concocted the demonstration story for the same reason. And now,in the words of his philosophical father Jeremiah Wright, "The chickens are coming home to roost"!!</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350084274974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:24:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350088308769-46</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Blues PT III What did Obama know and.....</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1350084274974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are governed by pathological liars. No question about that. What is in question is: WHY? Why would Harry not pass a budget? Why would Nancy want to pass the healthcare/not bill to find out what is in it? Who is pulling obama's strings? If you belive clinton, you are smoking way too much. Wake-up America. If you don't, you won't have the freedom to be a idiot anymore. Hide and watch!</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1350088308769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 20:31:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350098398096-47</Id><Topic><Title>Well what happens when u create over 5 MILLION JOBS ?? 7.8 % Unemployment it will continue going down!!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1349756639934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 00:23:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're still lying. Does anyone believe you any more? Probably not even your mother.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350098398096</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 23:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>