<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-16"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355634247453-1</Id><Title>gop congress--2004--w Bush--BLOOD ON HANDS</Title><Msg>never forget the gop congress and the w bush that WOULD NOT BAN ASSAULT WEAPONS. Read what Sarah Brady(wife of Jim Brady) thinks of the "w". NEVER FORGET the people that defend and support the w and his gop brand of politics. 20 children DEAD because of sarah palin--ted nugent--charlie hesston/et al. These people will answer someday for their actions. So will the whitetrash on this board such as infern ,invest, 4skin,the refsteves, and the like that defend the "w". May God have mercy on your souls and forgive you for your chosen ignorance</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1355634247453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 00:04:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355640944232-2</Id><Topic><Title>gop congress--2004--w Bush--BLOOD ON HANDS</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1355634247453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 00:04:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans love death.</Msg><Username>casey_iii</Username><Timestamp>1355640944232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 01:55:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355657349957-3</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Clinton Known Drunk</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355597574847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! Figured I would get a rise out of Wahleee and Maxwizard. I agree that Hillary Clinton could very well be our next President, if the US is still a country 4 years from now. If the half black neo-Marxist Obama doesn't finish off the country within the next 4 years, the drunk femaNazi neo-Marxist Clinton will finish the job, and the low IQ Demoncrap sheeple will continue to chant "workers rights", "hooray for unions", "get the rich", "4 more years" as the good ship USA sinks into the abyss of finanacial failure.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355657349957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 06:29:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355662046305-4</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Clinton Known Drunk</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355597574847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maxipad you are the #$%$ c--t.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1355662046305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 07:47:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355666029062-5</Id><Title>Obama panic Attack</Title><Msg>He says he has bigger fish to fry than gun control and the legalization of pot issues. That is correst. He is worried that White Male Americans, who run this country, are getting ready to shut down spending, shut down hiring, and go into hibernation for about 4 years. That would make him a Depression Era President. He'd better be nice to us.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1355666029062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 08:53:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355669585784-6</Id><Title>Largest “Stomach” In The U.S.A. Digests Food Waste, Spits Out Biogas Fuel For Trucks</Title><Msg>Largest “Stomach” In The U.S.A. Digests Food Waste, Spits Out Biogas Fuel For Trucks December 15, 2012 Tina Casey The company CleanWorld has just started up what could be described as a gigantic man-made digestive system at a garbage transfer station in Sacramento, California. When it’s fully expanded, the Sacramento Biodigester will be the largest facility of its kind in the U.S., capable of gobbling up about 100 tons of food waste per day and converting it into enough natural gas fuel to replace 1 million gallons of conventional diesel fuel per year — and that’s just for starters. The Skinny on the Sacramento Biodigester The new digester basically employs the</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355669585784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 09:53:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355670114904-7</Id><Title>Northern Gateway pipeline proposal heading toward showdown over First ...</Title><Msg>Northern Gateway pipeline proposal heading toward showdown over First ... Vancouver Sun - ‎Dec 14, 2012‎ PRINCE RUPERT, B.C. - There have been times over the past few days at the review hearings into the proposed Northern Gateway pipeline when the testy exchanges between Enbridge experts and First Nations lawyers have bordered on verbal warfare...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355670114904</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 10:01:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355670521050-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama panic Attack</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1355666029062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 08:53:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound frustrated and deprived. Maybe a mistress would help. You know in France if you are male and powerful they think you are #$%$ if you don't have a mistress. Those 20 beautiful little children mowed down because guns are as easy to buy in America as condoms need to be replaced too. Get at it...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355670521050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 10:08:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355671596814-9</Id><Title>Boehner caves on principle on taxes</Title><Msg>Now that he has decided that $1,000,000 is the line at which income becomes high enough to tax to get revenue, let him come up with a tax rate that meets the revenue targets. If he wants to preserve tax break for this or that corporate lobby let him make up the difference on the 1,000,000+ bracket. 39.6% is nowhere near high enough. 45% or so might be a good start...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355671596814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 10:26:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355672316469-10</Id><Topic><Title>Sending F-16 to Egypt is such a good thing</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1355621966969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:39:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm tired of hearing about middle east issues... Perhaps a new policy might help: Let the Arabs and Jews buy as many armaments as they want from America's vast mothballed cold war storage pile. Cold hard cash that is how you pay.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355672316469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 10:38:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355674752520-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama panic Attack</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1355666029062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 08:53:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ greed the brains are going to shut the country down for the next 4 years. Guess what you #$%$ #$%$ no one is going to sit by and let your grubby little paws pick their pocket. Big lesson coming for your dumb #$%$ #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1355674752520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 11:19:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355674818524-12</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Clinton Known Drunk</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355597574847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will be hungry soon you lobotomy case.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1355674818524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 11:20:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355675318396-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama panic Attack</Title><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1355666029062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 08:53:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You might want to tweak your technique a bit Mr. Ref. Remember that each female is different, and to be a good lady's man you need to keep in touch with your feminine side...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355675318396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 11:28:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355680626835-14</Id><Topic><Title>gop congress--2004--w Bush--BLOOD ON HANDS</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1355634247453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 00:04:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No rise in mass killings And yet those who study mass shootings say they are not becoming more common. "There is no pattern, there is no increase," says criminologist James Allen Fox of Boston's Northeastern University, who has been studying the subject since the 1980s, spurred by a rash of mass shootings in post offices. The random mass shootings that get the most media attention are the rarest, Fox says. Most people who die of bullet wounds knew the identity of their killer. Society moves on, he says, because of our ability to distance ourselves from the horror of the day, and because people believe that these tragedies are "one of the unfortunate prices we pay for our freedoms." Grant Duwe, a criminologist with the Minnesota Department of Corrections who has written a history of mass murders in America, said that while mass shootings rose between the 1960s and the 1990s, they actually dropped in the 2000s. And mass killings actually reached their peak in 1929, according to his data. He estimates that there were 32 in the 1980s, 42 in the 1990s and 26 in the first decade of the century. Chances of being killed in a mass shooting, he says, are probably no greater than being struck by lightning.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1355680626835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 12:57:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355681466893-15</Id><Topic><Title>gop congress--2004--w Bush--BLOOD ON HANDS</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1355634247453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 00:04:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Chances of being killed in a mass shooting, he says, are probably no greater than being struck by lightning." It would be much simpler to just dispense with all appeals in criminal cases and put the convict to death - and cheaper too. The chances of executing an innocent would be statistically low, but that is not acceptable. Your principles are flawed and contemptible... This how a civilized society, like Germany, handles things: you have to have a firearms ownership license (Waffenbesitzkarte) to buy each gun. To get one you must meet the following criteria: § 4 WaffG - age of majority § 5 WaffG - trustworthiness § 6 WaffG - personal adequacy § 7 WaffG - expert knowledge § 8 WaffG - necessity In a barbaric society you just show up with a suitcase of money at a gunshop or show and can leave like Rambo...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355681466893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 13:11:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355686594994-16</Id><Title>The Philosophy of Right</Title><Msg>More remedial instruction for the confused libertarians: Read Natural Law of the Sciences of State in outline, Elements of the Philosophy of Right, Hegel, 1820. The book is a textbook of lectures given by Hegel as University Professor instructing the ruling class of Germany in good methods of governance. Most of his ideas were not original to him but just a distillation of Prussian methods of governance. In Hegel's words: "(you are) the universal class...the class in which the consciousness of Right and the undeveloped intelligence of the mass of the people is found." The students were the nobles, the princes, and the sons of wealthy businessmen across Germany, not a second rate rabble. Modern Progressives and "technocrats" aspire to such as well, as well they should. Such philosophy indicates a very large role for government in a RIGHT WING society...40-50% of society dominated by government and "technocrats" for well over a century is a matter of course. It was not for nothing that Americans opened all German intellectual property rights to pillage by American corporations just after World War II, thus allowing them to extract technology worth at least $10 billion (7 or 8% of the value of all American stocks at the time), and thousands of German scientists to fill the yawning gap of technical knowledge in America at the time. If limited government matched the German big government model such transfers would not have been necessary. The Progressives did copy the philosophy outlined by Hegel, and his students' philosophy, as much as they could, but they were fought by the libertarian strain from start to finish...So what was created was a curious hybrid that was smart and advanced in many ways, possessed of immense natural resource, but capable of putting a fool like Coolidge, or W in office. The American Civil War, which boiled down to a class of ideology along such lines of the role of government (and especially states rights), did not eliminate all the libertarian small government view.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355686594994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 14:36:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355689804193-17</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Clinton Known Drunk</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355597574847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is one way to keep Obama from telling her not to testify. Like everything else he just gets to fly around and tell everyone "LOOK AT ME" and not things that are important to the working man. Benghazi will go the way of the Mexico guns and dead Americans, under the sheets.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1355689804193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 15:30:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355692552683-18</Id><Title>Obama continues Bush policies with blood on his hands</Title><Msg>No wonder the middle east can't make peace.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1355692552683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 16:15:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355709873305-19</Id><Topic><Title>gop congress--2004--w Bush--BLOOD ON HANDS</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1355634247453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 00:04:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And a perfect example of your parents failure. Not once does infernal grasp that the post is about ASSAULT WEAPONS. So ignorant in your beliefs that you can't read or comprehend.So you are a reflection of your family as Hatfields begat Hatfields; while it is sad what a failure your parents obviously are; the sadness is that filth like you will spawn more ignorant hillbilly trash. Just sad from every level. But if there is EVER ANY DOUBT where support for a bush or a palin comes from--you are the perfect example of what rove/fox news exploits</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1355709873305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 21:04:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355717487402-20</Id><Title>Clintons are at it again:</Title><Msg>Hillary fakes a concussion as the time for her to testify about Obama's (and her own) big lie about the video and Benghazi nears. If required by law to testify she can complain that her memory was affected by the concussion. Will Obama get away with this? Does anyone actually believe this?</Msg><Username>carrieanneamerica</Username><Timestamp>1355717487402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 23:11:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355719182935-21</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Clinton Known Drunk</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355597574847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will she really get a pass on this? She told the HERO SEAL'S father that she would make sure the video-maker who had NOTHING TO DO WITH THE TERROR ATTACK AND MURDERS, was arrested, and SHE SUPPORTED THE DISGUSTING LIE about the September 11th ISLAMIST TERRORIST ATTACK in Libya. HILLARY DOES NOT WANT TO RISK LYING UNDER OATH because she remembers what happened to Bill. Obama and Hillary are very bad people with no ethics, honesty, or integrity (among other shortcomings).</Msg><Username>carrieanneamerica</Username><Timestamp>1355719182935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-16 23:39:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>