<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-01"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351743103398-1</Id><Title>Rep. Waxman seeks lame-duck hearing on Sandy, climate change links</Title><Msg>Rep. Waxman seeks lame-duck hearing on Sandy, climate change links By Ben Geman - 10/31/12 04:34 PM ET The top Democrat on the House Energy and Commerce Committee is urging Republicans to hold a hearing in the lame-duck session on links between climate change and Hurricane Sandy. Rep. Henry Waxman’s (D-Calif.) letter to the committee's chairman, Rep. Fred Upton (R-Mich.), makes Waxman the latest of several Democrats to cite the massive storm when calling for tougher action to battle global warming. Wednesday’s letter argues that regardless of what happens at the ballot box in November, “the election should be a time to return to fact-based policymaking.” “Hurricane Sandy is exactly the type of extreme weather event that climate scientists have said will become more frequent and more severe if we fail to reduce our carbon pollution. That is why we are writing to request that you hold a hearing on the storm and its relation to climate change in the lame-duck session,” Waxman and Rep. Bobby Rush (D-Ill.), a top lieutenant on the committee, wrote. The letter is the latest in a series of requests from Waxman to hold a hearing on climate science, but Upton has not agreed. Upton’s office did not respond to a request for comment Wednesday. Waxman, when he chaired the Energy Committee, co-authored the big emissions-capping bill that narrowly passed the House in 2009, though it didn’t advance in the Senate. Experts urge caution in singling out climate change as the culprit when major storms occur. But scientists say warming oceans and greater atmospheric moisture are adding to the intensity of storms while rising sea levels are making coastal impacts worse. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351743103398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 00:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351747503785-2</Id><Title>$1.97 eps, 112.45 Revs,</Title><Msg>I predict, stock goes up to 92.50</Msg><Username>greenlight_cap</Username><Timestamp>1351747503785</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 01:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351764901355-3</Id><Title>Hurrican Sandy Not Caused by Man Made Global Warming</Title><Msg>say scientist. But Demoncrap politicians keep selling the Snake Oil to the low IQ enviroweenie sheeple. "New York Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo and Mayor Mike Bloomberg told the country in no uncertain terms on Tuesday that devastating superstorm Sandy was clear proof of climate change. 'Anyone who says there's not a dramatic change in weather patterns, I think is denying reality,” Cuomo said in a press conference. "What is clear is that the storms that we've experienced in the last year or so, around this country and around the world, are much more severe than before," Bloomberg agreed. But scientists say the evidence is far less concrete than the politicians appear to believe. Martin Hoerling, a meteorologist with the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), said Sandy wasn’t boosted by global warming -- the storm merely revealed natural forces at work."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351764901355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 06:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351772984137-4</Id><Topic><Title>Composite Indicators Signal</Title><Username>geniesulsgcz</Username><Timestamp>1300639590000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-03-20 12:46:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already a member since 2006, you really know how to pick them.</Msg><Username>lillyantony70</Username><Timestamp>1351772984137</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351773851446-5</Id><Topic><Title>+10.3%</Title><Username>adinaborden076</Username><Timestamp>1299432397000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-03-06 12:26:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this with us.</Msg><Username>lillyantony70</Username><Timestamp>1351773851446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351774022096-6</Id><Topic><Title>Hurrican Sandy Not Caused by Man Made Global Warming</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351764901355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 06:15:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont know how much one can conclude from one storm, but worse storms could come with global warming. Agree global warming is happening, not so sure just how much is the result of man activities. Not sure anything of significance can be done by changing mans activities. We could spend huge amounts of money and make big sacrifice only to find no significant improvement. This takes a lot more study before coslty actions are taken. jmho</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1351774022096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 08:47:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351774816822-7</Id><Title>XOM Owes Shareholders Dividend Increase</Title><Msg>With announcement of new net profits for last quarter over $9 Billion AGAIN , it appears that XOM management needs to step up the quarterly dividends on common shares. With twice the market value of CVX, Exxon has a 21 percent payout in the amount of 57 cents per quarter for 2.28 percent while CVX with half the market cap has a 25 percent payout in the amount of 90 cents quarterly for 3.6 percent. Shareholders would appreciate a significant dividend increase and XOM would not miss a step in its total corporate program.</Msg><Username>trapper702002</Username><Timestamp>1351774816822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351775162989-8</Id><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Announces Estimated Third Quarter 2012 Results</Title><Msg>Exxon Mobil Corporation Announces Estimated Third Quarter 2012 Results Thursday, November 1, 2012 9:01 am EDT IRVING, Texas--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- Exxon Mobil Corporation (NYSE:XOM): exxonmobil</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351775162989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:06:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351775981113-9</Id><Title>Exxon Profit Declines as Slowing Demand Growth Cuts Price</Title><Msg>Exxon Profit Declines as Slowing Demand Growth Cuts Price By Joe Carroll - Nov 1, 2012 6:04 AM MT. Exxon Mobil Corp. (XOM), the world’s largest energy company by market value, said third-quarter profit dropped amid slowing growth in worldwide oil demand and a North American natural gas glut that lowered prices. Net income was $9.57 billion, or $2.09 a share, compared with $10.3 billion, or $2.13, a year earlier, Irving, Texas- based Exxon said in a statement today. Profit was 13 cents more than the $1.96 average of 19 analysts’ estimates compiled by Bloomberg. Exxon Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Rex Tillerson budgeted about $100 million a day this year to find oilfields, build gas-export terminals and upgrade refineries and chemical plants. The company agreed to almost $5 billion in acquisitions in the past six weeks to reverse the longest stretch of quarterly production declines in 13 years. Brent oil futures, the benchmark for two-thirds of the world’s crude, fell 2.4 percent during the quarter to an average of $109.42 a barrel as global demand failed to keep pace with growing supply. Exxon, the biggest U.S. natural gas producer, also was stung by a 29 percent plunge in gas prices to an average of $2.893 per million British thermal units during the quarter. Tillerson said in June that gas producers have been “losing our shirts” as drilling innovations allowed explorers to penetrate North American shale formations, leading to a supply glut. The earnings statement was released before the opening of regular U.S. stock trading. Exxon rose 0.6 percent yesterday to $91.17 in New York. Exxon has risen 7.6 percent this year, outperforming the 3.7 percent gain by the Standard &amp; Poor’s 500 Energy Index. The shares have 13 buy recommendations from analysts, 15 holds and zero sell ratings. Supply Surge Global crude production increased by 2.16 million barrels a day during the third quarter from a year earlier, overwhelming demand that grew by just 540,000 barrels, according to an Oct. 12 report by the International Energy Agency. Rising oil usage in major economies such as China, Japan, India and Russia was insufficient to offset falling demand in the U.S., the world’s largest crude market. Exxon agreed on Sept. 20 to pay about $2 billion in cash and assets for Denbury Resources Inc. (DNR)’s drilling rights to 196,000 net acres in the Bakken Shale formation beneath North Dakota and Montana. The transaction will boost Exxon’s holdings in the region by about 50 percent, the company said at the time. Last month, Exxon added more shale acreage to its portfolio with a C$2.86 billion ($2.86 billion) agreement to purchase Celtic Exploration Ltd. (CLT) The acquisition, Exxon’s largest since the $35 billion takeover of XTO Energy in June 2010, will provide access to the Montney and Duvernay formations in western Canada. bloomberg</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351775981113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351776147261-10</Id><Title>$2.09 EPS, Nice beat!</Title><Msg>................</Msg><Username>greenlight_cap</Username><Timestamp>1351776147261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:22:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351776675591-11</Id><Title>Republicans In Perfect Position To Steal Election</Title><Msg>The internet has been abuzz since the British website UK Progressive released a report on how a retired NSA analyst Michael Duniho had gone over the Arizona GOP Primary Results from earlier this year and discovered widespread GOP election fraud through what can be called an electronic fingerprint. He found that when you break down the primary results in to their component precincts, and then compare the percentage of each candidate and how much they gained per precinct, a pattern appeared: This is statistically improbable to occur even in one election. What he discovered is that this is not a one time fluke at all. Instead, he found the tell-tale signature of electronic manipulation. He took this data, and compared it to other Arizona elections. He found the same signature, signaling a shifting of votes away from multiple candidates and towards one particular candidate, a Republican candidate, or in this case, the Republican leadership’s preferred candidate. Using this model, and comparing it, you find this same pattern happening in other elections. In this paper from Francois Choquette and James Johnson, they find the same patterns in other races, such as the special election to replace former Congresswoman Gabby Giffords: When these reports first came out, we went over the numbers instead of just rushing in with the story. The numbers are clear as day. The fix is in all across the country, and it is restricted to states run by Republicans. This kind of manipulation can only be done subtly: votes are not shifted more than 10%. The reason why the fraud is so easy to spot when you examine the primaries is because the tampering was not restricted to stealing votes from one specific competitor, but from several, which increased the rate of shift as the voting population increased. The large Republican primary base becomes the scam’s undoing. The computerized manipulation algorithm leaves a fingerprint easy to identify; all such things do…and now we know what to look for. To show how the manipulation works, here is a sample of the Ohio primary breakdown: In Mercer County, a total of 383 people voted in the Republican primary. Of those, 42% voted for Santorum, while 30% voted for Romney. In Highland County, 5,590 people voted, 39% for Santorum and 31% for Romney. Now examine the results from larger Ashtabula County, with its 8,932 voter turnout: it shows that Santorum suddenly dropped to 35% while Romney’s votes climbed to 33%. In the largest, Montgomery County, with its 56,283 voter turnout, Romney’s vote tally suddenly zoomed up to 38%, and Santorum’s tally dropped to a distant 31%. These results have been verified by cross-checking with the election results numbers posted on the Ohio Secretary of State‘s website. For the above charts, Choquette and Johnson also used Wisconsin‘s election results information by precinct, district and ward.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351776675591</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351778278011-12</Id><Title>Romney Relief Rally Staged. How Filthy Is This Weasel?</Title><Msg>The Romney campaign bought $5,000 worth of products to hand to their racist and religiously infected minions so they could GIVE IT BACK to "Mitt". And have a nice little picture taken with Mitt so that phoney could appear like he actually cared.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351778278011</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351781176300-13</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Owes Shareholders Dividend Increase</Title><Username>trapper702002</Username><Timestamp>1351774816822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Logically and in order to maximize profits they should increase the dividend ergo to make the stock more attractive. However, in the short run the owners of this company prefer to buy back their own stock, creating an invisible bonus.. At the time of the last dividend increase the company satisfied both views. I hope they compromise a little again.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1351781176300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:46:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351781188481-14</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Owes Shareholders Dividend Increase</Title><Username>trapper702002</Username><Timestamp>1351774816822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd rather they keep buying back 50 million shares a year.</Msg><Username>eric_von_zipper</Username><Timestamp>1351781188481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351781340781-15</Id><Topic><Title>Hurrican Sandy Not Caused by Man Made Global Warming</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351764901355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 06:15:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry guys, tell me about Al Gore and the internet all you want but scientists have measured global warming and the evidence that it is man made is just too big.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1351781340781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 10:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351784225899-16</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Relief Rally Staged. How Filthy Is This Weasel?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351778278011</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:57:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You provide this board with a perfect exapmle of dull. Thank you for what you do.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1351784225899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351784538515-17</Id><Topic><Title>Hurrican Sandy Not Caused by Man Made Global Warming</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351764901355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 06:15:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is absolutely no scientific evidence that man significantly impacts the climate. If there is such evidence, please make it available for all to see. And I'm talking about real, direct measurements--not unvalidated computer models with fudge factors adjusted to give the PC answer. By the way, Curiosity, our robot on Mars reported its first findings last week. Measurements showed that the surface temperature on Mars has increased the past two decades--"a warming trend" is underway. And Curiosity did not report sitings of any SUVs.</Msg><Username>eddiemaybe</Username><Timestamp>1351784538515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 11:42:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351785607548-18</Id><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending October 26, 2012</Title><Msg>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending October 26, 2012 U.S. crude oil refinery inputs averaged about 14.9 million barrels per day during the week ending October 26, 48 thousand barrels per day above the previous week’s average. Refineries operated at 87.7 percent of their operable capacity last week. Gasoline production increased last week, averaging 9.2 million barrels per day. Distillate fuel production increased last week, averaging 4.5 million barrels per day. U.S. crude oil imports averaged over 7.9 million barrels per day last week, down by 901 thousand barrels per day from the previous week. Over the last four weeks, crude oil imports have averaged over 8.3 million barrels per day, 506 thousand barrels per day below the same four-week period last year. Total motor gasoline imports (including both finished gasoline and gasoline blending components) last week averaged 616 thousand barrels per day. Distillate fuel imports averaged 32 thousand barrels per day last week. U.S. commercial crude oil inventories (excluding those in the Strategic Petroleum Reserve) decreased by 2.0 million barrels from the previous week. At 373.1 million barrels, U.S. crude oil inventories are above the upper limit of the average range for this time of year. Total motor gasoline inventories increased by 0.9 million barrels last week and are in the lower half of the average range. Both finished gasoline inventories, and blending components inventories increased last week. Distillate fuel inventories decreased by 0.1 million barrels last week and are below the lower limit of the average range for this time of year. Propane/propylene inventories decreased by 0.5 million barrels last week, but remained above the upper limit of the average range. Total commercial petroleum inventories decreased by 0.1 million barrels last week. Total products supplied over the last four-week period have averaged over 18.9 million barrels per day, up by 1.5 percent from the same period last year. Over the last four weeks, motor gasoline product supplied has averaged about 8.7 million barrels per day, up by 0.1 percent from the same period last year. Distillate fuel product supplied has averaged 3.7 million barrels per day over the last four weeks, down by 12.5 percent from the same period last year. Jet fuel product supplied is 3.2 percent higher over the last four weeks compared to the same four-week period last year. eia Data Overview (Combined Table 1 and Table 9) eia ------------------------------ BLOOMBERG DOLLAR INDEX SPOT bloomberg ------------------------------ Energy Futures Prices Below you may find all the futures prices &amp; quotes for: Crude Oil, Heating Oil, Gasoline RBOB, Natural Gas, ICE Brent Crude Oil, Ethanol (E) and more. Real Time Streaming Futures Quotes (CFDs) forexpros ------------------------------ Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report November 1, 2012 Released: November 1, 2012 at 10:30 a.m. (eastern time) for the Week Ending October 26, 2012. Next Release: November 8, 2012 Notes and Definitions Beginning with the report period for the week ending March 16, 2012, EIA is including salt dome and nonsalt facility subtotals for the Producing Region in the Summary section. The sum of the components may not equal the total for the Producing Region, because of independent rounding. Summary Working gas in storage was 3,908 Bcf as of Friday, October 26, 2012, according to EIA estimates. This represents a net increase of 65 Bcf from the previous week. Stocks were 136 Bcf higher than last year at this time and 259 Bcf above the 5-year average of 3,649 Bcf. In the East Region, stocks were 49 Bcf above the 5-year average following net injections of 34 Bcf. Stocks in the Producing Region were 159 Bcf above the 5-year average of 1,118 Bcf after a net injection of 23 Bcf. Stocks in the West Region were 51 Bcf above the 5-year average after a net addition of 8 Bcf. At 3,908 Bcf, total working gas is above the 5-year historical range. Working gas stocks in the Producing Region, for the week ending October 26, 2012, totaled 1,277 Bcf, with 300 Bcf in salt cavern facilities and 978 Bcf in nonsalt cavern facilities. Working gas stocks increased 14 Bcf in the salt cavern facilities and increased 10 Bcf in the nonsalt cavern facilities since October 19. An historical series of the salt and nonsalt subtotals of the Producing Region is available for download at eia ------------------------------ Weekly Coal Production Data for week ended: October 27, 2012 | Release Date: November 01, 2012 | Next Release: November 08, 2012 For the week ended October 27, 2012: •U.S. coal production totaled approximately 19.6 million short tons (mmst) •This production estimate is 2.1 percent higher than last week's estimate and 11.2 percent lower than the production estimate in the comparable week in 2011 •Coal production east of the Mississippi River totaled 8.3 mmst •Coal production west of the Mississippi River totaled 11.3 mmst •U.S. year-to-date coal production totaled 841.8 mmst, 6.1 percent lower than the comparable year-to-date coal production in 2011 •As of the week ending September 15, 2012, all of 2011 production has been revised to match the Mine Safety and Health Administration (MSHA) final 2011 production and second quarter 2012 production has been revised to match MSHA production. These changes are present in the Revisions/Archives section, and are also reflected in the "Current Weekly Estimates" and "Current Monthly Estimates" tables in the year-to-date and 52 weeks ended totals. These changes are not reflected in the two Original Estimates tables. eia Weekly U.S. Coal Production eia ------------------------------- Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production Usually updated late in the day on Thursday ethanolrfa URLs at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351785607548</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351785647009-19</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Said Gut FEMA Last Year NOW He Says Something Completely Different</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351710839298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The gut is a complete sham. He's just dying to slash the throats of hard working Americans so his wealthy buddies can have it all. WAHLIEEEEEEEE......EVERY BOARD SEEMS TO HAVE AN IDIOT....CONGRATULATIIONS, YOU WIN FIRST PLACE....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1351785647009</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351786089121-20</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Said Gut FEMA Last Year NOW He Says Something Completely Different</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351710839298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should be gutted, wahleee, you dick suckin queer. Better yet, string you from a tree branch upside down and fill you up with sand!</Msg><Username>ihategooks</Username><Timestamp>1351786089121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:08:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351786937292-21</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Owes Shareholders Dividend Increase</Title><Username>trapper702002</Username><Timestamp>1351774816822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zipper: Help enlighten this aging long time investor on the significant benefits of buybacks over dividends to shareholder. Seem to me that buybacks is a cheap and covert way for corporate management to use a significant number of these buyback shares for compensation/perks to management and pet projects without suitable transparency to the investors on how the buyback shares are used. It would be great if the buyback shares were used for reducing a similar number of outstanding corporate shares, but the numbers never seem to validate that assumption. XOM has a lot of supporters and I have long owned the stock,but I have long had questions about how such a successful corporation has pver paid management and been so tight in rewarding the shareholders.</Msg><Username>trapper702002</Username><Timestamp>1351786937292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351787788053-22</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Owes Shareholders Dividend Increase</Title><Username>trapper702002</Username><Timestamp>1351774816822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There you have the problem summarized in one word. Transparency. These directors et al. are sitting on stock options many years old and now due.But I'm sure there are enough profits to let them satisfy their acquisitive propensities and strengthen the stock by another dividend increase.Today greed is the new normal given and we have to add it into any of our financial equations.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1351787788053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351792087228-23</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Owes Shareholders Dividend Increase</Title><Username>trapper702002</Username><Timestamp>1351774816822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>trapper........ my advice to you, buy CVX, buy COP and dump XOM. There you have it. Lots more divvies and you never have to complain about XOM's payout.</Msg><Username>stoxx_detective</Username><Timestamp>1351792087228</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351792278912-24</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Owes Shareholders Dividend Increase</Title><Username>trapper702002</Username><Timestamp>1351774816822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I look at it simply. Buybacks increase my ownership in the company and raise the EPS that values the stock; dividends reduce my stake AND makes me pay, currently, 20% federal/ state/ local, for the privilege of losing my position.</Msg><Username>eric_von_zipper</Username><Timestamp>1351792278912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351793401747-25</Id><Title>Positive point</Title><Msg>The buy rating at 9trading website for XOM shows positive signs of buying and the short term target is 118.6.</Msg><Username>gsunwab</Username><Timestamp>1351793401747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:10:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351793835423-26</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Owes Shareholders Dividend Increase</Title><Username>trapper702002</Username><Timestamp>1351774816822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the zipper is correct except for shares bought--I believe that number to be for the qtr/thus for the yr would be in the 200 million area?? As for a divvy increase--if you look at your history/that is in the June/summer timeframe and pretty sure there is a increase most EVERY year.</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1351793835423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351794897372-27</Id><Title>Ethanol urged to ease Sandy's gas squeeze</Title><Msg>Ethanol urged to ease Sandy's gas squeeze Published: Nov. 1, 2012 at 1:37 PM WASHINGTON, Nov. 1 (UPI) -- The U.S. ethanol industry urged President Obama to allow the use of more of the corn-based additive to stretch gasoline supplies in the Northeast. The Iowa Renewable Fuels Association said it sent a letter to the White House calling for a temporary lifting of federal ethanol limits to allow gasoline to contain a higher percentage of ethanol. Most Northeastern states have a 10-percent limit on ethanol in gasoline; however, the association contended that with refinery production still limited following Hurricane Sandy, now would be a good time to allow the sale of so-called E15 and E20 gasoline, which contains 15 and 20-percent ethanol, respectively. The proposal was floated a day after the Obama administration announced a waiver of the requirements for the sale of cleaner-burning reformulated gasoline to allow the use of conventional gasoline in affected areas where supplies were tight. The association said in a written statement the industry had plenty of ethanol available to meet increased demand. "Hundreds of millions of gallons of ethanol are in storage and dozens of ethanol plants are running at reduced rates or have been idled," IRFA Executive Director Monte Shaw said. "By removing the restrictions to higher ethanol blends on a temporary basis consumers win, clean air wins and American energy security wins." upi</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351794897372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351796181190-28</Id><Title>I'd be a seller here! Poor earnings and due for a correction,</Title><Msg>CVX PULLED BACK ALMOST 10%</Msg><Username>riskreversal777</Username><Timestamp>1351796181190</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351796796399-29</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Owes Shareholders Dividend Increase</Title><Username>trapper702002</Username><Timestamp>1351774816822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please point out what options remain to be exercised by XOM executives, excluding outside Directors and employees who were part of recent acquisitions.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351796796399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351799527018-30</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Relief Rally Staged. How Filthy Is This Weasel?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351778278011</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:57:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So lets have your source to refute this. You know it's true and you know that the Republicans could care less about social infrastructure. This filthy Romney wants to "Privatize" disaster relief. And your party hates working Americans too. Proof of that? Why do you all scream for lower wages while supporting #$%$ like Romney that have a history a BUSINESS HISTORY of offshoring jobs. GFY you filthy corporate fascist.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351799527018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351799585895-31</Id><Title>Wind Farm Operating Costs Fall 38% in Four Years, BNEF Says</Title><Msg>Wind Farm Operating Costs Fall 38% in Four Years, BNEF Says By Louise Downing - Nov 1, 2012 10:28 AM MT. 0 Comments The cost of running and maintaining wind farms has fallen 38 percent in four years as competition among contractors increased and turbine performance improved, bringing closer the day that the technology matches fossil fuel. The average price of operation and maintenance contracts for onshore farms this year slid to 19,200 euros ($25,000) a megawatt from 30,900 euros in 2008, Bloomberg New Energy Finance said today. It took data from 38 developers and service providers in more than 24 markets for its first O&amp;M Price Index. “Wind power has done much to improve its competitiveness against gas-fired and coal-fired generation in recent years via lower-cost, more technically advanced turbines and more sophisticated siting and management,” Michael Liebreich, chief executive officer of London-based BNEF, said in the statement. The figures help inform debate in the U.S. and Britain, where governments are considering how much to subsidize renewable energy. BNEF’s findings show manufacturers led by as Vestas Wind Systems A/S (VWS) are bringing down prices, making the machines more profitable for power providers to run. Britain is cutting subsidies for onshore wind by 10 percent as Prime Minister David Cameron’s government discusses halting subsidies once the current renewable energy targets are met. In the U.S., President Barack Obama’s administration is pushing Congress to renew tax credits favoring wind in the face of opposition from Republican lawmakers. Subsidy Dependence Without the U.S. credit, the market for wind towers may fall to $100 million to $500 million next year from $2 billion to $2.5 billion at present, BNEF said on July 31. Declining costs for servicing wind farms are positive for developers of projects, which are suffering from subsidy cuts across Europe and the U.S. Service agreements are also an important additional revenue stream for turbine makers such as Vestas, the world’s largest turbine-maker. Developers expect O&amp;M pricing to be “fairly stable” to at least 2015 and view turbine makers Enercon GmbH, Siemens AG (SIE) and Vestas as the best service providers, according to BNEF. Enercon’s full-service contracts were nearly 20 percent cheaper than the average from 2008 to 2012. bloomberg</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351799585895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:53:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351799962664-32</Id><Topic><Title>Hurrican Sandy Not Caused by Man Made Global Warming</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351764901355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 06:15:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All that $$ the Oil Companies throw out there to propagandize fools like you is paying off. They should make big oil and coal insure the losses.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351799962664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 15:59:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351800248491-33</Id><Title>Geraldo Breaks, In The Face Of Reality Admits Foxnews Lying About Benghazi</Title><Msg>Geraldo Rivera slammed the politicization of the attack in Benghazi, firing off a series of tweets while hunkered down at home in Edgewater, N.J., during Hurricane Sandy. Rivera, the Fox News contributor and "Geraldo at Large" host, criticized the controversy being pushed by some conservatives. It's "clear no C130 gunships were available," Rivera tweeted. "Criticize coverup [but] saying White House watched [and] did nothing to help is a lie." Rivera called the "GOP bloodlust" surrounding the Obama administration's handling of Libya "insincere," "desperate" and reminiscent of the political firestorm surrounding the "Fast and Furious" gun-walking scandal that rocked the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives in 2011. The "real" question regarding Benghazi, Rivera tweeted, is this: "Did Obama spin to retain Bin Laden killer mystique?" To suggest the four U.S. consulate workers killed in Benghazi "could have been saved," Rivera added, is a "cruel myth." "Life is not an action movie," he tweeted. As Mediaite pointed out, Rivera did not mention Fox News—which has aired much of the "GOP bloodlust" over Benghazi—in his criticism of the criticism. ...</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351800248491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351800892885-34</Id><Topic><Title>Geraldo Breaks, In The Face Of Reality Admits Foxnews Lying About Benghazi</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351800248491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No surprise. FoxNOISE is pure propaganda --- slander sheet against any democrat and a love letter to right wing lugnuts that think like the Taliban</Msg><Username>manwhoneversaysdie</Username><Timestamp>1351800892885</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351801084102-35</Id><Topic><Title>Geraldo Breaks, In The Face Of Reality Admits Foxnews Lying About Benghazi</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351800248491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Obamao asked the Seals for help, they went and killed Bin Laden. When the Seals asked Obamao for help, he said: go die (along with my Ambassador), I need to get to Vegas to party and raise money with my celebrity friends.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351801084102</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351801221976-36</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Relief Rally Staged. How Filthy Is This Weasel?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351778278011</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:57:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As always, Mr brain death curses when he can't back up his fallacious lemming propaganda.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351801221976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351802641176-37</Id><Title>Republicans Caught Lying... Again</Title><Msg>The New York Times reported on Thursday that Senate Republicans applied pressure to the nonpartisan Congressional Research Service (CRS) in September, successfully persuading it to withdraw a report finding that lowering marginal tax rates for the wealthiest Americans had no effect on economic growth or job creation. "The pressure applied to the research service comes amid a broader Republican effort to raise questions about research and statistics that were once trusted as nonpartisan and apolitical," the Times reported.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351802641176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351802757425-38</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Relief Rally Staged. How Filthy Is This Weasel?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351778278011</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 09:57:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still nothing of substance from you?</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351802757425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:45:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351803296179-39</Id><Topic><Title>Geraldo Breaks, In The Face Of Reality Admits Foxnews Lying About Benghazi</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351800248491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never get the inferno to explain WHY he has no outrage on marine barracks bombing under reagan/gipper admins ?? I wonder where was the call for war--I wonder where was his call for justice--I wonder?? oh that was USA lives LOST under GOP admins--that is ok some set of principles you and the "w' supporters have--actually an empty set--politics only</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1351803296179</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351804260536-40</Id><Topic><Title>Geraldo Breaks, In The Face Of Reality Admits Foxnews Lying About Benghazi</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351800248491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Reagan running for President? I must have missed that. But, I guess you've been told to use any 'diversion to try to deflect discussion of Obamao's record.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351804260536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351804688205-41</Id><Topic><Title>Geraldo Breaks, In The Face Of Reality Admits Foxnews Lying About Benghazi</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351800248491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1 thing you missed for sure--answering that question</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1351804688205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 17:18:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351807999269-42</Id><Title>Ohio Democrat backs Romney</Title><Msg>Former Ohio Democratic congressman James Stanton, who served in Congress from 1971 to 1977, has endorsed Mitt Romney in a Cleveland Plain Dealer column. “I supported Barack Obama in 2008 because I liked what he had to say. But after four years of painful unemployment and $5 trillion in new debt under President Obama, it’s clear to me that he just hasn’t gotten the job done,” he wrote. “I am endorsing Gov. Mitt Romney because I believe it’s time for new leadership.”</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351807999269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351808165538-43</Id><Topic><Title>Geraldo Breaks, In The Face Of Reality Admits Foxnews Lying About Benghazi</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351800248491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What Reagan did or did not do has absolutely nothing to do with this election wahleee boy. I am sure however that you are studiously following your instructions to try and talk about anything other than Obamao's total failure as President.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351808165538</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351810132045-44</Id><Topic><Title>Geraldo Breaks, In The Face Of Reality Admits Foxnews Lying About Benghazi</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351800248491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't Stop Be- Lie-ving! Your be-lie-fs are all levraged on lies....</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351810132045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 18:48:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351811246534-45</Id><Topic><Title>Geraldo Breaks, In The Face Of Reality Admits Foxnews Lying About Benghazi</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351800248491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who said anything about Reagan? You're a delusional old man. Either that or your projecting the same spin and lies that corporate spokesperson Reagan shoved down Americans throats. That is until we vomited up a $16 Trillion deficit. Reagonmics was a lie, Romneyomics will end the American middle class and that fascist maggot Paul Ryan will find his Ayn Rand filled head on a pole..</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351811246534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:07:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351813414500-46</Id><Topic><Title>How long before infernal and invest croak ???????????</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1351812178848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh don't worry Max, Medicare will keep em alive for a long long time. And you can be sure they'll be a cashin that SS check until that day comes. They're typical right wing hypocritical liars.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351813414500</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351822281823-47</Id><Title>Bloomberg Backs Obama, Citing Fallout From Storm - saying climate change was “a threat to our children’s future, and we owe it to them to do something about it.”</Title><Msg>Bloomberg Backs Obama, Citing Fallout From Storm By RAYMOND HERNANDEZ Published: November 1, 2012 881 Comments In a surprise announcement, Mayor Michael R. Bloomberg said Thursday that Hurricane Sandy had reshaped his thinking about the presidential campaign and that as a result, he was endorsing President Obama. Mr. Bloomberg, a political independent in his third term leading New York City, has been sharply critical of Mr. Obama, a Democrat, and Mitt Romney, the president’s Republican rival, saying that both men had failed to candidly confront the problems afflicting the nation. But he said he had decided over the past several days that Mr. Obama was the better candidate to tackle the global climate change that he believes might have contributed to the violent storm, which took the lives of at least 38 New Yorkers and caused billions of dollars in damage. “The devastation that Hurricane Sandy brought to New York City and much of the Northeast — in lost lives, lost homes and lost business — brought the stakes of next Tuesday’s presidential election into sharp relief,” Mr. Bloomberg wrote in an editorial for Bloomberg View. “Our climate is changing,” he wrote. “And while the increase in extreme weather we have experienced in New York City and around the world may or may not be the result of it, the risk that it may be — given the devastation it is wreaking — should be enough to compel all elected leaders to take immediate action.” Mr. Bloomberg’s endorsement is another indication that Hurricane Sandy has influenced the presidential campaign. The storm and the destruction it left in its wake have dominated news coverage, transfixing the nation and prompting the candidates to halt their campaigning briefly. The announcement is also the latest in a series of steps Mr. Bloomberg has taken in a bid to assert his influence nationally as his final term as mayor enters its twilight — and after he appears to have abandoned his own hopes of one day becoming president. Last month, the mayor said that he was creating his own “super PAC” to support candidates from either party, as well as independents, who he believes are devoted to his brand of nonideological problem solving, and he has increasingly used his personal wealth and the bully pulpit of his office in an effort to persuade elected officials to support same-sex marriage, gun control and education reform. The impact of Mr. Bloomberg’s endorsement is unclear; his city and his state are overwhelmingly Democratic, and although he is a well-known and long-serving public official who frequently appears in the national media, his influence is difficult to measure: an ABC News/Washington Post poll conducted in December found 30 percent of Americans had a favorable view of Mr. Bloomberg, 26 percent had an unfavorable view, and many — 44 percent — had no opinion of him one way or the other. Both the Obama and Romney campaigns had aggressively sought the mayor’s endorsement, in large part because they believed he could influence independent voters around the country. Mr. Bloomberg had recently signaled he would not make an endorsement, telling reporters several weeks ago that he had decided whom he would vote for, but that he was not sure he would share that decision with the public. John Weaver, a prominent Republican political strategist, said the timing of the mayor’s endorsement was notable. “His announcement is sandwiched between this horrific calamity and the presidential election,” he noted. “So the timing could not have been more significant for him and his views.” Steve McMahon, a veteran Democratic strategist, said he believed that now that Mr. Bloomberg had come to terms with not running for the presidency, he was interested in cementing his political legacy. “Many politicians reach the point in their careers where they have built up considerable political equity and the only question is how they use it to make a difference,” he said. “In endorsing President Obama, the mayor seems to have decided to use some of his equity.” Even before the hurricane struck, Mr. Bloomberg had been concerned about climate change. He is the chairman of an organization called C40, a network of cities seeking to reduce greenhouse-gas emissions. Yet until the storm, climate change had not been much of an issue in the presidential campaign. The topic did not come up during the three presidential debates, and the candidates have not provided detailed legislative or regulatory plans outlining their stances on the issue. Since the hurricane, a number of elected officials have come forward, chiefly in New York, to say that they have concluded the planet is undergoing climate change, that huge storms are no longer freak occurrences but expectable reality, and that public policy must begin to prepare for the impact. Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo of New York said Tuesday, “Anyone who says there is not a dramatic change in weather patterns I think is denying reality.” Senator Charles E. Schumer, Democrat of New York, said Wednesday, “We’re going to pay a price for the change in climate.” And Representative Jerrold Nadler, Democrat of Manhattan, echoed the consensus of local officials on Thursday, saying simply, “There will be a storm of this magnitude again.” Mr. Bloomberg did not endorse a presidential candidate in 2008, when Mr. Obama ran against Senator John McCain, Republican of Arizona, and until Thursday, he had steadfastly withheld his support from both presidential candidates this year, largely because he had grown frustrated with the tone and substance of the presidential campaign. He recently derided as “gibberish” the answers that Mr. Obama and Mr. Romney gave during a debate to a question about an assault-weapons ban. He has expressed disappointment with Mr. Obama’s performance over the past few years and concern about what he has described as the shifts in Mr. Romney’s views over time. Even in his endorsement, the mayor continued to express criticism of the president. He said Mr. Obama had fallen short of his 2008 campaign promise to be a problem solver and consensus builder, noting that Mr. Obama had “devoted little time” to creating a coalition of centrists in Washington who could find common ground on important issues like illegal guns, immigration, tax reform and deficit reduction. “Rather than uniting the country around a message of shared sacrifice,” Mr. Bloomberg said of Mr. Obama, “he engaged in partisan attacks and has embraced a divisive populist agenda focused more on redistributing income than creating it.” In making his endorsement, Mr. Bloomberg listed the various steps that Mr. Obama had taken over the last four years to confront the issue of climate change, including pushing regulations that seek to curtail emissions from cars and power plants. But the mayor cited other reasons for endorsing Mr. Obama, including the president’s support for abortion rights and for same-sex marriage, two high-priority issues for the mayor. At the same time, Mr. Bloomberg said he might have endorsed Mr. Romney, a former Massachusetts governor, except for the fact that the Republican had abandoned positions that he once publicly held. “In the past he has taken sensible positions on immigration, illegal guns, abortion rights and health care — but he has reversed course on all of them, and is even running against the very health care model he signed into law in Massachusetts,” the mayor said of Mr. Romney. In a statement, Mr. Obama said he was “honored to have Mayor Bloomberg’s endorsement.” The president acknowledged Mr. Bloomberg’s chief concern, saying climate change was “a threat to our children’s future, and we owe it to them to do something about it.” And alluding to the damage from the hurricane, Mr. Obama said: “He has my continued commitment that this country will stand by New York in its time of need. And New Yorkers have my word that we will recover, we will rebuild, and we will come back stronger.” Coming on the heels of Gov. Chris Christie’s public embrace of Mr. Obama, the endorsement by Mr. Bloomberg left aides to Mr. Romney a bit flustered, and they privately dismissed its importance. nytimes</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351822281823</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351824066795-48</Id><Topic><Title>How long before infernal and invest croak ???????????</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1351812178848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I keep asking you to provide one example of hatred and/or bigotry in my posts. A real lawyer wouldn't make such a claim without evidence. Since you regularly do, either you are not a real lawyer or you are a pretty poor one. Makes one wonder about your claimed background as a Navy Seal as well, doesn't it? Your delusions have really overtaken you.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351824066795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351824215494-49</Id><Topic><Title>Geraldo Breaks, In The Face Of Reality Admits Foxnews Lying About Benghazi</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1351800248491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you read the posts in the chain, including your own under your aliases? Or have you lost that ability as well? Oh well, brain death does that.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351824215494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351825129630-50</Id><Title>President Obama in Green Bay, Wisconsin - Full Speech 11/1/2012</Title><Msg>President Obama in Green Bay, Wisconsin - Full Speech 11/1/2012 BarackObama·2,919 videos 301 views Published on Nov 1, 2012 Gotta vote? Go here: Today, at a grassroots event in Green Bay, Wisconsin, President Obama laid out the closing argument he will make to the American people in the final days of the election. The President is fighting for the same things he's always believed and run on -- that this country cannot succeed without a growing, thriving middle class. In the decade before President Obama took office, middle-class security was undercut by the same top-down, failed economic policies that Mitt Romney is now promoting. While Romney thinks that means 'change,' the President will continue to move our country forward to real change that boosts the middle class and creates a stronger future for all Americans. youtube url at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1351825129630</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 22:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351828391134-51</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncrap Voter Fraud in Ohio</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1351424350687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 07:39:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I spell it "maxwizard."</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1351828391134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>