<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344485858000-1</Id><Topic><Title>July 2012 HOTTEST MONTH EVER!!!!</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1344449158000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 14:05:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its amateur climatology time again is it? 3 factors stand out. 1. The scientific understanding of climate change has become sufficiently clear to justify nations taking prompt action. 2. Political assaults on climate change scientists. 3. The face of Lord Monkton. http://cafewhispers.files.wordpress.com/2011/05/monkton.jpg</Msg><Username>luke_oflaherty</Username><Timestamp>1344485858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 00:17:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344489851000-2</Id><Title>This Week In Petroleum August 8, 2012</Title><Msg>This Week In Petroleum August 8, 2012 Corn Ethanol Issues Not Expected to Significantly Impact Gasoline Prices in 2012 In recent weeks, drought conditions have lowered the outlook for this year's corn harvest across the Midwest and raised concerns over the higher costs of fuel ethanol and satisfying the blending mandates of the Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS). Ethanol production fell from 920,000 barrels per day (bbl/d) for the week ending June 8, 2012 to 817,000 bbl/d (an annualized rate of about 12.6 billion gallons) for the week ending August 3, 2012. The U.S. Energy Information Administration (EIA), in the August 2012 Short-Term Energy Outlook (STEO) released yesterday, reduced its ethanol production forecast for the second half of 2012 by 70,000 bbl/d to 830,000 bbl/d, below the annual rate of 13.2 billion gallons of renewable fuels that the RFS allows to be met with corn-derived ethanol during 2012. EIA does not expect the current situation in corn markets to have a significant effect on the pump price of gasoline. Given the year-to-date ethanol supply and the availability of banked renewable identification number (RIN) credits, the current relationship between the prices of ethanol and petroleum-based gasoline components, and the relatively modest share of ethanol in the overall gasoline pool, we expect gasoline prices will continue to be driven by crude oil prices and refining margins. The impact of the forecasted decline in domestic ethanol production should be primarily reflected in reduced ethanol exports. So far, 2012 has proven to be a challenging year for the ethanol industry. Falling gasoline consumption and a nearly saturated ethanol blending market led to domestic ethanol supplies exceeding U.S. demand during the first half of 2012. The abundance of ethanol in the domestic market has resulted in low ethanol margins for most of 2012, causing the idling of some ethanol plants pending more favorable market conditions and the continued export of excess ethanol volumes. Ethanol crush spreads, which measure the difference between the wholesale prices of ethanol and corn, have been negative for most of 2012, falling from over $0.50 per gallon in late 2011 to almost -$0.40 per gallon in recent weeks (Figure 1). After selling at or above Reformulated Blendstock for Oxygenate Blending (RBOB) gasoline spot prices over much of the second half of 2011, ethanol prices fell below RBOB spot prices in late 2011 as the blender's tax credit neared its expiration date (Figure 2). Through early 2012, ethanol's discount to gasoline grew, reaching almost $1 per gallon in April as ethanol prices remained flat while gasoline prices increased driven by higher crude oil costs. http://www.eia.gov/oog/info/twip/twip.asp</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344489851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 01:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344489871000-3</Id><Topic><Title>This Week In Petroleum August 8, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344489851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 01:24:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ethanol is consumed primarily as a gasoline blendstock at 10 percent by volume of finished gasoline, which is often referred to as E10. Every $1-per-gallon change in the price discount or premium of ethanol relative to gasoline results in a potential pass-through of around $0.10 per gallon in retail E10 gasoline. Beginning in late June 2012, when the extended Midwestern drought led the U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) to significantly reduce the corn production estimates in its World Agriculture Supply and Demand Estimates (WASDE) report, ethanol prices rapidly increased after several months of relative stability. Ethanol spot prices rose from around $2.10 per gallon in late June to reach a year-to-date high of $2.70 per gallon on July 25. As discussed above, if that 60-cent increase were all passed through to consumers, it would raise retail E10 gasoline prices by $0.06 per gallon, but there is little evidence this has occurred. Over this same period, the spot price of Brent crude oil increased about $13 per barrel ($0.31 per gallon), while the spot price of Gulf Coast conventional gasoline rose more than $0.20 per gallon and New York Harbor spot RBOB rose about $0.16 per gallon over a similar period. Even after the recent sharp increase in ethanol prices, it was still selling at around a $0.20-per-gallon discount to RBOB in New York Harbor at the end of July. The national average retail gasoline price only increased about $0.15 per gallon during the month of July, indicating no discernible pass-through pressure on retail prices beyond those of crude oil and wholesale gasoline. Banked RFS RIN credits provide an additional cushion that limits the effect of higher ethanol prices on retail gasoline prices. There are an estimated 2.5 billion gallons of banked RIN credits available for compliance this year due to production beyond the mandated level in previous years. The availability of banked RINs should ameliorate tightness in the market for the remainder of the year in the event physical ethanol volumes fall short of the 2012 RFS mandate.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344489871000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 01:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344489880000-4</Id><Topic><Title>This Week In Petroleum August 8, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344489851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 01:24:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gasoline and diesel fuel prices continue to increase The U.S. average retail price of regular gasoline increased 14 cents this week to $3.65 per gallon, three cents per gallon lower than last year at this time. This is the largest one-week increase in the U.S. average price since March 7, 2011. Prices increased in all regions except the Rocky Mountains, where the price decreased less than a penny to remain at $3.46 per gallon. The Rocky Mountain price has decreased for 16 consecutive weeks. The largest increase came in the Midwest, where the price increased 26 cents to $3.77 per gallon. This is the third largest increase in the Midwest price since EIA began collecting these prices in 1992. The East and Gulf Coast prices were both up 10 cents, to $3.60 per gallon and $3.41 per gallon, respectively. Rounding out the regions, the West Coast price is now $3.76 per gallon, up five cents from last week. The national average diesel fuel price increased five cents to $3.85 per gallon, five cents per gallon lower than last year at this time. Prices increased in all regions of the Nation, with the largest increase coming in the Rocky Mountain region, where the average price is $3.81 per gallon, an increase of eight cents from last week. The Midwest price increased seven cents to $3.85 per gallon. The Gulf and West Coast price are both up six cents from last week to $3.75 per gallon and $3.96 per gallon, respectively. The smallest increase came on the East Coast, where the price is up three cents to $3.87 per gallon. Propane inventories show another rise Last week, total U.S. inventories of propane continued their seasonal growth, adding 0.6 million barrels to end at 68.1 million barrels, 18.5 million barrels (37 percent) higher than a year ago. The majority of new inventories appeared in the Gulf Coast region, which added 0.9 million barrels of new propane stocks. Meanwhile, Midwest regional stocks fell 0.2 million barrels and the East Coast and Rocky Mountain/West Coast regions each dropped by 0.1 million barrels. Propylene non-fuel-use inventories represented 7.3 percent of total propane inventories.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344489880000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 01:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344492854000-5</Id><Title>Madonna schilling for William Kristol</Title><Msg>As Putin attempts to reign in the Zio Oligarchs that scarfed up Mother Russia's oil and other natural resources under Yeltsin, Hollywood has unleashed Madonna in a desperate PR blitz to preserve zio dominance over the vast mineral and oil wealth. As the NBA call girl critiques Putin for returning to the citizens of the world's once largest Christian empire the resources confiscated by the banker backed Bolsheviks, the decrepid slut appears to be doing more harm than good.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1344492854000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 02:14:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344517878000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Reid hopeful for climate bill if Dems hold Senate</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344467402000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 19:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reid can't even pass a budget bill. He is part of our "national confusion". We the people have jokers to our left and jokers to our right and we are stuck in the middle of graft and special interest on either side. We got to this point because Washington DC, including all three branches of government, is engaged in a continuous re-election mode. Even the Supreme Court is caught-up in our dysfunctional political system and, this is our reward for our apathy. None of them understands the meaning of the word service. Their convoluted policies have created a polorized electorate which makes it impossible to make the "right" decision in the voting booth because, we are left with a choice between wrong and wrong. The best America can hope for is the wisdom to manage inefficiency. Conservatives (myself included) would like to see {order] based on individual effort. We are not "selfish" or greedy beyond normal human tendency. We care about the welfare of every citizen and the environment as well. We understand that individual success does not mean that we pay for those who will not work and have become professional takers. Those who cannot work are a different story. They have always been cared for and, that is the fitting thing to do. It's hard for me to understand what liberals want and, how they will recognize "it" when they get there. Are you "there" when everything is free? Are you "there" when we the people are completly subservient to government. When are you "there". If any liberal has the intellectual ability and the inclination to describe your vision of utopia, you will find me genuinely interested. I don't want to argue with you. I just want to know how you define success/happiness, regardless of your definition of either.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1344517878000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344519815000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo - The Golden Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>vazquezroman348</Username><Timestamp>1344518197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have heard it said that "Shares eventually find their rightful owners" let’s see how many the WS Crooks shake out today.</Msg><Username>espinozanicholson562</Username><Timestamp>1344519815000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344521619000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Calling All Longs!!</Title><Username>namerdia26</Username><Timestamp>1344519067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post of the day! Thanks</Msg><Username>menancydav59</Username><Timestamp>1344521619000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344521741000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo - The Golden Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>vazquezroman348</Username><Timestamp>1344518197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for your insightful view, as usual. A lot of people on this board claiming to be long, but very short-sighted</Msg><Username>kirkmorrow666</Username><Timestamp>1344521741000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344521769000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Calling All Longs!!</Title><Username>namerdia26</Username><Timestamp>1344519067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Logical Thinking</Msg><Username>menancydav59</Username><Timestamp>1344521769000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344522639000-11</Id><Title>FRAUD ALERT! XOM IS noT UP .53, Puts getting crushed, It's an ERROR,</Title><Msg>It was down and PUT OPTIONS WERE DOWN</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1344522639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344522743000-12</Id><Title>THIS CLOSES AT 88.30 OR SO. TOTAL FRAUD!!!!!!</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1344522743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:32:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344522765000-13</Id><Title>IT'S NOT UP!!!!!! IT WAS DOWN .70</Title><Msg>..............</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1344522765000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:32:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344523038000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo - The Golden Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>vazquezroman348</Username><Timestamp>1344518197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your attempt is good but now online trading system has been introduced and became popular by making everybody easy to deal with stock exchange. You should attach the system of such trading to increase your article's quality. Though, regarding share market is really good. Thank you so much for posting such valuable information for us. Hope you continue to do so.</Msg><Username>floydosborne900</Username><Timestamp>1344523038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344523578000-15</Id><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report August 9, 2012</Title><Msg>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report August 9, 2012 August 9, 2012 at 10:30 a.m. (eastern time) for the Week Ending August 3, 2012. Notes and Definitions Beginning with the report period for the week ending March 16, 2012, EIA is including salt dome and nonsalt-dome subtotals for the Producing Region in the Summary section. The sum of the components may not equal the total for the Producing Region, because of independent rounding. Summary Working gas in storage was 3,241 Bcf as of Friday, August 3, 2012, according to EIA estimates. This represents a net increase of 24 Bcf from the previous week. Stocks were 465 Bcf higher than last year at this time and 386 Bcf above the 5-year average of 2,855 Bcf. In the East Region, stocks were 134 Bcf above the 5-year average following net injections of 30 Bcf. Stocks in the Producing Region were 171 Bcf above the 5-year average of 937 Bcf after a net withdrawal of 5 Bcf. Stocks in the West Region were 81 Bcf above the 5-year average after a net drawdown of 1 Bcf. At 3,241 Bcf, total working gas is above the 5-year historical range. Working gas stocks in the Producing Region, for the week ending August 03, 2012, totaled 1,108 Bcf, with 226 Bcf in salt cavern facilities and 881 Bcf in nonsalt cavern facilities. Working gas stocks decreased 8 Bcf in the salt cavern facilities and increased 1 Bcf in the nonsalt cavern facilities since July 27. An historical series of the salt and nonsalt subtotals of the Producing Region is available for download at: http://ir.eia.gov/ngs/ngs.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344523578000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:46:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344523654000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report August 9, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344523578000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:46:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Energy Futures Prices Below you may find all the futures prices &amp; quotes for: Crude Oil, Heating Oil, Gasoline RBOB, Natural Gas, ICE Brent Crude Oil, Ethanol (E) and more. Real Time Streaming Futures Quotes (CFDs) http://www.forexpros.com/commodities/energies</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344523654000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344526809000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo - The Golden Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>vazquezroman348</Username><Timestamp>1344518197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh, i didn't take the short on that one, i just wanted to exit longs, now i see what you mean</Msg><Username>cliffthomas60</Username><Timestamp>1344526809000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 11:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344528150000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo - The Golden Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>vazquezroman348</Username><Timestamp>1344518197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone capable of buying 100k or more shares of probably wouldn't want to show off like you. Your point is well taken though.</Msg><Username>campbell_gonzalo</Username><Timestamp>1344528150000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 12:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344531184000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo - The Golden Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>vazquezroman348</Username><Timestamp>1344518197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just did with my 102k shares. great advice, thanks</Msg><Username>morenoezra977</Username><Timestamp>1344531184000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 12:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344534437000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending August 3, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344448791000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 13:59:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production http://ethanolrfa.org/pages/weekly-ethanol-feed-production Ethanol production rises, stocks fall and demand rises for the week August 3, 2012</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344534437000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 13:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344535569000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo - The Golden Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>vazquezroman348</Username><Timestamp>1344518197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when i came to know about the feture returns of the share's policy,i bacame more interested to invest my money on this.thanks for letting me know.have a good time ahead.</Msg><Username>danielbarber706</Username><Timestamp>1344535569000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 14:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344539893000-22</Id><Title>MARKET MAKER FRAUD, THIS CLOSED AT $88.33</Title><Msg>IT IS NOT UP .60</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1344539893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 15:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344539945000-23</Id><Title>MY AUGUST 87.5 PUT should be UP! IT'S DOWN .34</Title><Msg>DUE TO THIS ERROR</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1344539945000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 15:19:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344541420000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo - The Golden Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>vazquezroman348</Username><Timestamp>1344518197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what makes you think it will double?</Msg><Username>ramseywolfe535</Username><Timestamp>1344541420000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 15:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344542457000-25</Id><Title>I sraeli contributions to 2012 Summer Olympic Games</Title><Msg>Complaints of antisemitisim for no moment of silence: 6,422 Stolen towels from Olympic village: 584 Wigger I sraeli with star of David shaved on the side of his head: 1 Olympic Medals won: 0</Msg><Username>sal_bando_50</Username><Timestamp>1344542457000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 16:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344543228000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report August 9, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344523578000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:46:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending August 8, 2012 Release Date: August 9, 2012 In the News: Infrastructure constraints in the Northeast, particularly in Northern Pennsylvania, have led Marcellus prices to diverge from the Henry Hub since May 2012. Additionally, BENTEK Energy LLC (Bentek) reported that infrastructure constraints have led Northeast Pennsylvania production to flatten in recent weeks. Bentek estimates that more than 1,000 wells have been drilled but are not yet producing because of insufficient pipeline capacity. Several infrastructure projects have been proposed recently to help ease constraints in the region: •Earlier this month, Williams Partners LP (Williams) announced plans for a major infrastructure expansion in Pennsylvania that would expand capacity on its existing Transcontinental Pipeline’s Leidy Line by 800 million British thermal units (MMBtu) per day by late 2015. Williams, which received interest for the expansion from shippers in a recent non-binding open season, will begin the pre-filing process with the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission in early 2013. The expansion would serve the needs of gas distributors and power generators on the East Coast. •Tennessee Gas Pipeline recently announced a binding open season (when the pipeline obtains firm commitments for capacity from shippers) for its proposed Rose Lake Expansion Project, located in its Zone 4 area in Pennsylvania. •The project will add 230 million cubic feet per day of capacity. The entire system, which has about 13,900 miles of pipelines from the Gulf Coast, has existing capacity of 6.9 billion cubic feet (Bcf) per day. Overview: (For the Week Ending Wednesday, August 1, 2012)•Natural gas prices declined for the report week (Wednesday to Wednesday) at many of the country’s trading locations, although a few points in the Northeast defied the trend. Algonquin Citygate (for delivery to Boston) began the week at $3.97 per MMBtu and rose to $4.24 per MMBtu yesterday, while the Henry Hub price closed at $2.96 per MMBtu, down 24 cents for the week. •The natural gas futures market sank a bit week-over-week. At the New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), the September 2012 natural gas contract fell 23.8 cents per MMBtu to close at $2.933 per MMBtu yesterday. •Working natural gas in storage rose last week to 3,241 Bcf as of Friday, August 3, according to the U.S. Energy Information Administration’s (EIA) Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report (WNGSR). An implied storage build of 24 Bcf for the week moved storage levels 465 Bcf above year-ago levels. •The Baker Hughes Incorporated natural gas rotary rig count declined by 7 to 498 active units on the week ending August 3. The oil-directed rig count increased by 13 to 1,429 units. more summary data Prices: Natural gas prices fell across most spot market locations, with the exception of certain Northeast and Marcellus pricing points. Spot prices fell by about 10 to 25 cents per MMBtu across most trading points for the week. Marcellus price points saw large price drops early in the week that had mostly rebounded by yesterday. Tennessee Zone 4 Marcellus increased by 19.2 percent week-on-week, beginning the week at $1.82 per MMBtu last Wednesday, falling to $1.40 per MMBtu on Friday, and jumping back up to conclude the week at $2.17 per MMBtu. Tennessee Zone 5 Line 300, which also serves the Marcellus region, ended the week down 2.1 percent, although it showed a similar pattern, moving from $2.34 per MMBtu last Wednesday, falling to $1.45 per MMBtu on Friday, and landing at $2.29 per MMBtu yesterday. The overall low prices in the Marcellus region are attributed largely to pipeline constraints. The Northeast saw warmer-than-normal weather, pushing the Algonquin Citygate (for delivery into Boston) price up 6.8 percent to finish the week at $4.24 per MMBtu. http://www.eia.gov/naturalgas/weekly/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344543228000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 16:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344543240000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report August 9, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344523578000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:46:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The NYMEX September 2012 futures contract fell by 7.5 percent from $3.171 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $2.933 per MMBtu yesterday. The settlement price dropped week-on-week after rising consistently throughout June and July. It fell to a low of $2.877 per MMBtu last Friday, and gained slightly thereafter. The 12-Month Strip (average of August 2012 to July 2013 contracts) fell by 2.9 percent, starting at $3.539 per MMBtu last Wednesday, dipping to $3.296 per MMBtu on Friday, and rebounding to $3.436 per MMBtu yesterday. Total consumption for the report week showed an overall increase, driven by an uptick in natural gas consumed for power generation. According to Bentek estimates, natural gas consumption in the residential/commercial sectors fell by 1.5 percent, but was more than offset by an increase in consumption in the power and industrial sectors, which grew by 1.0 and 1.5 percent, respectively. Higher demand for electricity due to warmer temperatures in the Northeast outweighed a drop in demand in the Southeast stemming from cooler temperatures. Supply fell by 0.3 percent week-on-week, driven by lower dry gas production. Bentek estimates a 0.4 percent drop in dry production for the report week, although it is nonetheless 2.2 percent higher than the same week last year. Imports from Canada increased by 1.3 percent, having little impact on the overall supply change. Similarly, liquefied natural gas (LNG) sendout had little effect on the overall change in supply. Despite increasing by 6.5 percent for the report week, LNG accounts for only a small fraction of overall supply and is now 42.3 percent below 2011 levels for the corresponding week. more price data Storage Working natural gas in storage increased to 3,241 Bcf as of Friday, August 3, according to EIA’s WNGSR. This represents an implied net injection of 24 Bcf from the previous week. This week’s injection was 21 Bcf below the 5-year (2007-2011) average injection of 45 Bcf, and 7 Bcf below last year’s injection of 31 Bcf. Since April 27, injections of working natural gas into underground storage have fallen short of both year-ago levels and the 5-year average, although stocks remain well above historical levels. Inventories are currently 465 Bcf (16.8 percent) greater than last year at this time and 386 Bcf (13.5 percent) greater than the 5-year average. Only one of the three storage regions posted an increase this week. Inventories in the East region increased by 30 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 44 Bcf). The West and Producing regions posted decreases of 1 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 5 Bcf) and 5 Bcf (the 5-year average net withdrawal is 4 Bcf), respectively. In the Producing Region, working natural gas inventories decreased 8 Bcf (3.4 percent) in salt cavern facilities and increased 1 Bcf (0.1 percent) in nonsalt cavern facilities. Temperatures during the storage report week were 2.0 degrees warmer than the 30-year normal temperature and 2.0 degrees cooler than the same period last year. Temperatures in the Lower 48 States averaged 77.4 degrees, compared to 79.4 last year and the 30-year normal of 75.4. During the week all regions were warmer than normal, particularly the West South Central and West North Central divisions, which, respectively, averaged 4.1 and 3.9 degrees warmer than the 30-year normal.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344543240000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 16:14:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344543949000-28</Id><Topic><Title>despicable</Title><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344475317000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 21:21:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only if those households each average less than $9,000.j BTW, not only do those rich pay more in absolute terms than you, they on avergae pay more in % terms as well.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1344543949000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 16:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344543959000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Reid hopeful for climate bill if Dems hold Senate</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344467402000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 19:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good info. More reasons to vote the Democraps out of power.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1344543959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 16:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344548962000-30</Id><Topic><Title>MY AUGUST 87.5 PUT should be UP! IT'S DOWN .34</Title><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1344539945000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 15:19:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chairman is this your first day in the stock market?</Msg><Username>thorbo52</Username><Timestamp>1344548962000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 17:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344561334000-31</Id><Title>5 months of a "wobbling" MKT? Prepare to DIVE deep!</Title><Msg>GET SHORT NOW boys..................</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1344561334000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344569116000-32</Id><Topic><Title>despicable</Title><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344475317000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 21:21:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: despicable 9-Aug-12 04:25 pm only if those households each average less than $9,000.j BTW, not only do those rich pay more in absolute terms than you, they on avergae pay more in % terms as well. Split hairs if you like you got the point about the Walton Family. As far as the percentage terms, if my family earns $47,000 anually and pay 25% income tax then my family can`t eat. If I have Twenty Billion Dollars and earn another Two Billion Anually and am taxed at 35% then I can only afford Two New Jets One Mansion in Switzerland and may have to down size my Custom Yacht from 230 feet to 210 feet.Besides the Majority of income these Billionaires recieve are in the form of dividends and only taxed at 15%.</Msg><Username>bhenning32</Username><Timestamp>1344569116000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 23:25:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344570530000-33</Id><Topic><Title>despicable</Title><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344475317000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 21:21:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have to excuse 4skin--he wasn't trying to argue its just he is so stupid he thought you were ref. the goodnight John boy "waltons" he knew the poor family farmers on TV were taxed plenty</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1344570530000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 23:48:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>