<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354513330570-1</Id><Topic><Title>RewindStevens</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354473581524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:39:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rhodesbob used up his Medicare and he is most likely dead. One less filthy right winger in a dying party of liars. Whoooopie! Invest why do you say the Democrats "owned the economy" since 2007? Is this because they held the House then? Well what responsibility does the Republican filth have seeing they've held the House since 2010? Probably none to you because you're a blind fool. Invester the molester, taking his free healthcare from Medicare instead of selling everything like he wants everyone else to do. Another filthy liar of the hypocritical right.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1354513330570</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 00:42:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354518486472-2</Id><Title>Inhofe: Some Dems won’t ‘fall on the sword of Obama’ to defend EPA rules</Title><Msg>Inhofe: Some Dems won’t ‘fall on the sword of Obama’ to defend EPA rules By Ben Geman - 12/02/12 02:47 PM ET Sen. James Inhofe (R-Okla.) believes all is not lost in his push to thwart Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) regulations despite President Obama’s victory and Democrats’ continued control of the Senate. Inhofe, one of Capitol Hill’s most persistent critics of EPA regulations on carbon dioxide and other pollutants, said in an interview broadcast Sunday that new political opportunities await EPA foes. “There are a lot of Democrats who are coming up for re-election in 2014 who are not going to want to fall on the sword of Obama on this overregulation once the people at home know what it is costing them,” he said on Platts Energy Week TV. Inhofe said “we’ve got a rough two years” ahead, but added that he will continue trying to turn back EPA rules, including with Congressional Review Act (CRA) resolutions. The mid-1990s law, which was part of then-Speaker Newt Gingrich’s (R-Ga.) “Contract with America,” gives Congress an opening to overturn federal agency regulations. Resolutions under the act are immune from Senate filibuster. However, it has been used successfully just once, and new efforts would face big Senate obstacles (not to mention likely veto threats). Recent attempts to use the CRA to target EPA rules have fallen short in the Senate. Sen. Rand Paul’s (R-Ky.) attempt to turn back rules on smog and particulate-forming pollution from power plants stalled in late 2011. Inhofe’s separate measure to block rules on power plant emissions of mercury and other toxics fell short in June. But new battles await. The courts may force EPA to rewrite the Cross-State Air Pollution Rule that Paul tried to thwart, while EPA has yet to finalize carbon emissions standards for new power plants and other rules in the offing. Inhofe is the ranking Republican on the Environment and Public Works Committee but must leave that post in the next Congress. He will remain on the committee and says his focus won’t change. “I will continue to do the things that I have been doing actively on the committee, most having to do with overregulation and energy,” he said. Inhofe and other critics of EPA rules allege they will hurt the economy by making coal less viable as a power source, forcing closure of plants and mines and costing jobs. But EPA defenders say the coal-fired power industry’s woes don’t stem from EPA rules, and instead point to the natural gas production boom that has driven down costs for the fuel source that competes with coal. EPA defenders say Inhofe and other Republicans are seeking to gut vital public-health protections that are estimated to prevent large numbers of heart attacks, childhood asthma cases and other respiratory ailments. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/270491-sen-inhofe-on-epa-some-dems-wont-fall-on-the-sword-of-obama</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354518486472</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 02:08:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354524285763-3</Id><Topic><Title>The most incompetent government money can buy</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354509640595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:40:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354524285763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 03:44:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354542072476-4</Id><Topic><Title>Shorted More Here</Title><Username>socorrowarne566</Username><Timestamp>1330825565000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-03-03 20:46:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow!!!</Msg><Username>youngjim277</Username><Timestamp>1354542072476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 08:41:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354542440519-5</Id><Topic><Title>The most incompetent government money can buy</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354509640595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:40:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, while the USA burns we should just go play golf?</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1354542440519</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 08:47:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354544981561-6</Id><Topic><Title>The most incompetent government money can buy</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354509640595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:40:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"*highest gun ownership rate" Um, that's a positive not a negative!</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1354544981561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 09:29:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354547555869-7</Id><Topic><Title>The most incompetent government money can buy</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354509640595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:40:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"*highest gun ownership rate" ---Um, that's a positive not a negative! Yes, I'm sure you would think so. The society wastes money on the guns, the police waste still more money fighting gun crime, the hospitals expend still more resources dealing with the consequences, and the whole thing shows up in GDP as more spending, and you think you are getting richer, when, in fact, you are getting poorer. Why don't you run out and shoot out all the windows in every city while you are at it, and then you can spend even more money fixing them. A good stimulus idea, I'm sure. Very American. The situation is exactly analogous to the $900 billion a year you squander on the military. People are entitled to their entertainments, but really, $900 billion? Sure, sure, you get to spend lots more on welfare and medical care for soldiers with so much warring, and the toxic pollutants the military spreads across the land allow you to spend still more money on health care. You create 10 enemies for every one you kill off so its a renewable resource of "waste/GDP" Great stimulus! Very American. Just stupid. Keep it up...</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354547555869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:12:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354547621293-8</Id><Topic><Title>The most incompetent government money can buy</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354509640595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:40:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"*highest gun ownership rate" ---Um, that's a positive not a negative! Yes, I'm sure you would think so. The society wastes money on the guns, the police waste still more money fighting gun crime, the hospitals expend still more resources dealing with the consequences, and the whole thing shows up in GDP as more spending, and you think you are getting richer, when, in fact, you are getting poorer. Why don't you run out and shoot out all the windows in every city while you are at it, and then you can spend even more money fixing them. A good stimulus idea, I'm sure. Very American.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354547621293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:13:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354548151590-9</Id><Topic><Title>The most incompetent government money can buy</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354509640595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:40:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, while the USA burns we should just go play golf? Vote out who caused it: The Republican Party? The USA was the richest country in the world before the election of Ronald Reagan. It no longer is per person, closer to half as much now and falling yearly in the rankings. GDP is still high but is indiscriminate about what it calls "income"- break a window and fix it and that's GPD; spend $200,000 on health care on a wounded soldier and that's GDP; and spend $200,000 educating a PhD in Engineering or Chemistry and that's GDP....</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354548151590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:22:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354549743423-10</Id><Title>ONE TRILLION OF DEFENSE CUTS GO OVER THE CLIFF !! YES !!!</Title><Msg>Cut spending in Military we need smart lean Military.</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1354549743423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:49:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354550184414-11</Id><Topic><Title>RewindStevens</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354473581524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:39:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"experience destitution...." About the most ignore rant I've seen on this board in a while. Your position has no support at all. --The USA as a whole is poorer than developed countries with bigger governments. --The parts of the USA with smaller government are poorer than the urban states with bigger government. --The USA's wealth ranking has been consistently falling relative to Germany, Austria, Denmark, Switzerland, France, the Netherlands, Belgium, Japan, etc...since it embraced your small government vision 3 decades ago. --China is on the rise now too thanks to a system of state capitalism that is far superior to the American model. It is worth noting that China has been unable to compete against the likes of Germany, Austria, and the Netherlands. The American is like the student who doesn't prepare for the test, fails, and wonder why - worse still he gets his parent to complain about the test being unfair. It's time you shaped up sport. You are losing. Oh, sure, sure the USSR failed. That is communist, not mixed capitalist, and the difference is not trivial, plus the USSR spent about 20% of its GDP on the military something that USA seems hell bent on rivaling.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354550184414</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:56:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354552090729-12</Id><Topic><Title>RewindStevens</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354473581524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:39:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roman, Try a stronger laxative1</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1354552090729</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:28:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354552835436-13</Id><Title>Fiscal Cliff analogies</Title><Msg>If you've ever been divorced (twice), you probably know what a Fiscal cliff is. If you owned a bunch of stock or had a retirement plan w/ Enron,you probably know what a fiscal cliff is If you ever bought a Boat longer than 30 foot, you probably know what a temporary fiscal cliff is If you are nearing retirement with two kids still in College, you defintely know whar a fiscal cliff is. I'm just making these up as I go along. Add as you see fit.</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354552835436</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:40:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354553258582-14</Id><Topic><Title>RewindStevens</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354473581524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:39:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A reply worthy of the steves, raul, or inferno... - Irrelevant and brief.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354553258582</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 11:47:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354554341988-15</Id><Topic><Title>ONE TRILLION OF DEFENSE CUTS GO OVER THE CLIFF !! YES !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1354549743423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:49:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask for $3 trillion, settle on $1 trillion... The R&amp;D and defense labs should be sparred the ax, but the personnel budget is far too high, and he logistical capability (offensive war fighting ability) needs to be reduced. There are far too many generals, and other officers collecting salaries and benefits (and mistresses)... They could disband half the army, and mothball half the aircraft carriers and ballistic missile subs and it would still be too big.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354554341988</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 12:05:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354554741493-16</Id><Topic><Title>ONE TRILLION OF DEFENSE CUTS GO OVER THE CLIFF !! YES !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1354549743423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:49:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but the GOP wants more horses and bayonets 15 military installations in ITALY still leftover from WWII--what nonsense the teabags run around wanting the federal reserve AUDIT AUDIT THE PENTAGON--N O W</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1354554741493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 12:12:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354554859869-17</Id><Topic><Title>The most incompetent government money can buy</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354509640595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 23:40:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not a Reagan fan but make the BEST gun so everyone wants to buy the one you make. Work the problem like health care. If you have a broken bone think about all the different people you pay when your own Dr. could say " it's broken" not go see all these other Dr's to see what they say and then come back.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1354554859869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 12:14:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354555987823-18</Id><Topic><Title>ONE TRILLION OF DEFENSE CUTS GO OVER THE CLIFF !! YES !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1354549743423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:49:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How would you like $65 M to think up a new air craft even if it never gets built. Look how the Pentagon pays for something new.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1354555987823</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 12:33:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354556318152-19</Id><Title>THE BIG FREAKIN CHA CHING IS ABOUT TO COME!!!!!!!!!! LOOK OUT BELOW!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>OMG</Msg><Username>ushouldsay</Username><Timestamp>1354556318152</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 12:38:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354559167751-20</Id><Title>House members warn CARDON TAX would increase unemployment rate</Title><Msg>House members warn carbon tax would increase unemployment rate By Pete Kasperowicz - 12/03/12 11:34 AM ET A group of Republicans and Democrats in the House has proposed a resolution saying Congress opposes any effort by the federal government to set up a carbon tax on gasoline, coal or natural gas, arguing it would only lead to increased joblessness. The resolution, from Rep. David McKinley (R-W.Va.), states that a carbon tax on gasoline would have a "dramatic, immediate impact on transportation costs, with the greatest impact being felt by low-income Americans and their families." It also says that the price of electricity derived from coal and natural gas would increase if a carbon tax were applied to those fuels. "[W]ith continuing high national joblessness and an unemployment rate exceeding 7.8 percent every month since February 2009, a carbon tax will drive the unemployment rate even higher," the resolution states. It argues further that a carbon tax would have an "uneven effect" across the country, as it would hit some areas harder than others. And, it says imposing a carbon tax in the United States would do nothing to stop carbon emissions in China, India and other large carbon-emitting nations. McKinley's resolution, H.Con.Res. 142, is co-sponsored by five Republicans and three Democrats: Reps. Joe Barton (R-Texas), Tim Holden (D-Pa.), Bill Johnson (R-Ohio), Collin Peterson (D-Minn.), Nick Rahall (D-W.Va.), John Shimkus (R-Ill.), Fred Upton (R-Mich.) and Ed Whitfield (R-Ky.). thehillDOTcom/blogs/floor-action/house/270579-house-members-warn-carbon-tax-would-increase-unemployment-rate</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354559167751</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 13:26:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354559800504-21</Id><Title>Fossil fuel subsidies in focus at climate talks</Title><Msg>Fossil fuel subsidies in focus at climate talks By By Karl Ritter on December 03, 2012 DOHA, Qatar (AP) — Hassan al-Kubaisi considers it a gift from above that drivers in oil- and gas-rich Qatar only have to pay $1 per gallon at the pump. "Thank God that our country is an oil producer and the price of gasoline is one of the lowest," al-Kubaisi said, filling up his Toyota Land Cruiser at a gas station in Doha. "God has given us a blessing." To those looking for a global response to climate change, it's more like a curse. Qatar — the host of U.N. climate talks that entered their final week Monday — is among dozens of countries that keep gas prices artificially low through subsidies that exceeded $500 billion globally last year. Renewable energy worldwide received six times less support — an imbalance that is just starting to earn attention in the divisive negotiations on curbing the carbon emissions blamed for heating the planet. "We need to stop funding the problem, and start funding the solution," said Steve Kretzmann, of Oil Change International, an advocacy group for clean energy. His group presented research Monday showing that in addition to the fuel subsidies in developing countries, rich nations in 2011 gave more than $58 billion in tax breaks and other production subsidies to the fossil fuel industry. The U.S. figure was $13 billion. The Paris-based Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development has calculated that removing fossil fuel subsidies could reduce carbon emissions by more than 10 percent by 2050. Yet the argument is just recently gaining traction in climate negotiations, which in two decades have failed to halt the rising temperatures that are melting Arctic ice, raising sea levels and shifting weather patterns with impacts on droughts and floods. In Doha, the talks have been slowed by wrangling over financial aid to help poor countries cope with global warming and how to divide carbon emissions rights until 2020 when a new planned climate treaty is supposed to enter force. Calls are now intensifying to include fossil fuel subsidies as a key part of the discussion. "I think it is manifestly clear ... that this is a massive missing piece of the climate change jigsaw puzzle," said Tim Groser, New Zealand's minister for climate change. He is spearheading an initiative backed by Scandinavian countries and some developing countries to put fuel subsidies on the agenda in various forums, citing the U.N. talks as a "natural home" for the debate. The G-20 called for their elimination in 2009, and the issue also came up at the U.N. earth summit in Rio de Janeiro earlier this year. Frustrated that not much has happened since, European Union climate commissioner Connie Hedegaard said Monday she planned to raise the issue with environment ministers on the sidelines of the talks in Doha. Many developing countries are positive toward phasing out fossil fuel subsidies, not just to protect the climate but to balance budgets. Subsidies introduced as a form of welfare benefit decades ago have become an increasing burden to many countries as oil prices soar. "We are reviewing the subsidy periodically in the context of the total economy for Qatar," the tiny Persian gulf country's energy minister, Mohammed bin Saleh al-Sada, told reporters Monday. Qatar's National Development Strategy 2011-2016 states it more bluntly, saying fuel subsides are "at odds with the aspirations" and sustainability objectives of the wealthy emirate. The problem is that getting rid of them comes with a heavy political price. When Jordan raised fuel prices last month, angry crowds poured into the streets, torching police cars, government offices and private banks in the most sustained protests to hit the country since the start of the Arab unrest. One person was killed and 75 others were injured in the violence. Nigeria, Indonesia, India and Sudan have also seen violent protests this year as governments tried to bring fuel prices closer to market rates. Iran has used a phased approach to lift fuel subsidies over the past several years, but its pump prices remain among the cheapest in the world. "People perceive it as something that the government is taking away from them," said Kretzmann. "The trick is we need to do it in a way that doesn't harm the poor." The International Energy Agency found in 2010 that fuel subsidies are not an effective measure against poverty because only 8 percent of such subsidies reached the bottom 20 percent of income earners. The IEA, which only looked at consumption subsidies, this year said they "remain most prevalent in the Middle East and North Africa, where momentum toward their reform appears to have been lost." In the U.S., environmental groups say fossil fuel subsidies include tax breaks, the foreign tax credit and the credit for production of nonconventional fuels. Industry groups, like the Independent Petroleum Association of America, are against removing such support, saying that would harm smaller companies, rather than the big oil giants. In Doha, Mohammed Adow, a climate activist with Christian Aid, called all fuel subsidies "reckless and dangerous," but described removing subsidies on the production side as "low-hanging fruit" for governments if they are serious about dealing with climate change. "It's going to oil and coal companies that don't need it in the first place," he said. businessweekDOTcom/ap/2012-12-03/us-envoy-hits-chinas-stand-in-un-climate-talks</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354559800504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 13:36:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354564642043-22</Id><Topic><Title>RewindStevens</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354473581524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:39:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, straight to the point because, you are backed-up to your eyeballs.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1354564642043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 14:57:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354564931961-23</Id><Title>here it is</Title><Msg>LOS ANGELES, CA--(Marketwire - Nov 29, 2012) - All American Pet Company, Inc. ( OTCQB : AAPT ) -- All American Pet Brands is ready this holiday season to meet the needs of the 60,000 retail stores that have approved "America's wellness company" -- with the first of its kind NUTRABAR.</Msg><Username>maxeileen</Username><Timestamp>1354564931961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 15:02:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354565184919-24</Id><Topic><Title>THE BIG FREAKIN CHA CHING IS ABOUT TO COME!!!!!!!!!! LOOK OUT BELOW!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ushouldsay</Username><Timestamp>1354556318152</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 12:38:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock finishing up fourth straight year of under- performing every major average. Stock seems to underperform Dow/S&amp;P about 90% of days for years. Since 2008 stock has returned zero counting dividends. This is the worst managed oil company there is-earnings misses every quarter, production shortfalls quarter after quarter, topped off by the XTO debacle. The Tillerson wrecking crew has destroyed probably $100 billion in shareholder wealth. Pathetic, I wouldn't let this crew run a lemonade stand. .</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1354565184919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 15:06:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354568259715-25</Id><Topic><Title>RewindStevens</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354473581524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:39:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You cannot even keep track of what is the point - the fraud and failure which is your brand of governance. Naturally you do not consider it a fraud, and your merry band of imbeciles in Congress certainly don't either. That is good - at least they are giving battle now, holding to their principle. Why don't you join them in the Thermopylae Pass (look it up) and see if you can hold back the armies of darkness (as you see them)... For some light reading look up Peter Morici's column today, that is if you can get your mind out off the topic of feces, and fascist marching themes, and military pomposity (which contradicts all the small government tripe you support by the way)... The column doesn't leave much hope for your vision of the USA. He does try to be dry and non-dramatic, of course...</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354568259715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 15:57:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354572188720-26</Id><Topic><Title>ONE TRILLION OF DEFENSE CUTS GO OVER THE CLIFF !! YES !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1354549743423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:49:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ #$%$ @›$$hole.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354572188720</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 17:03:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354581251997-27</Id><Topic><Title>RewindStevens</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354473581524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-02 13:39:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually roman, I don't have to look "it" up. You remind me of of one who has the character references of Ephialtes. I do agree with you that we are governed by imbeciles. But, they are NOT standing by their principals, rather their politics. The "empty suit" is not going to give up on his radical playbook and, the complicit senate, as well as the intellectually vacant press, is demanding the unachievable goal of loser takes all. Simply put: Won't Work! If you are determined to rely on history for making your case, you might research the history of socialism. Try to contrast your discovery to the history of the free markets and the freedom provided by democracy. No question: We are not perfect. We have a display of greed exemplified by reid and polosi, among many others. We have the agenda driven stupidity exemplified by the administration. Most of this is because we have a voter community with no skin in the game. Sound familiar? It should. It records the beginnings of tyranny throughout history. May God bless our country and restore in the minds of real men and women why we are here and, how we got here. History worth revisiting.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1354581251997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 19:34:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354582325571-28</Id><Title>OVERNIGHT ENERGY: Greens, key Dem press climate agenda</Title><Msg>OVERNIGHT ENERGY: Greens, key Dem press climate agenda By Zack Colman and Ben Geman - 12/03/12 05:03 PM ET STATE OF PLAY: As international climate talks continue in Doha, Qatar, a pair of Tuesday events will showcase advice from the left for President Obama on a second-term climate agenda. At his first post-election press conference last month, Obama said he wants to address climate, but offered no specifics on his agenda. Rep. Edward Markey (D-Mass.) will discuss the ways Congress and Obama could approach the matter at a Tuesday panel hosted by Climate Desk Live. Environmental Defense Fund Senior Vice President Eric Pooley and Georgetown Climate Center Director Vicki Arroyo also will speak at the event. Separately, the Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) will detail its proposals for cutting carbon dioxide emissions from coal-fired power plants at the National Press Club. NRDC will advocate for a “new federal-state approach,” which it says will cut greenhouse gas emissions and add clean-energy jobs. NRDC Executive Director Peter Lehner will speak at the event. He will be joined by Dallas Burtraw, a senior fellow with think tank Resources for the Future, and Dan Lashof, director of NRDC’s climate and clean air program. Congress has been frozen on global warming since a cap-and-trade bill co-authored by Markey died in the Senate in 2010. But the Obama administration has pushed ahead on the topic. In his first term, Obama rolled out the first-ever emissions limits for new coal-fired power plants and increased vehicle fuel efficiency standards. Green groups, along with congressional Democrats, want the president to continuing using executive powers to curb carbon emissions by regulating, for example, existing coal-fired power plants. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/270655-overnight-energy-greens-key-dem-eye-climate-agenda</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354582325571</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 19:52:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354583229605-29</Id><Title>Next Kyoto Protocol phase in place from start of 2013, predicts UN climate chief &amp; Obama’s climate envoy, agreed that phasing out these subsidies</Title><Msg>Next Kyoto Protocol phase in place from start of 2013, predicts UN climate chief The Irish Times - Tuesday, December 4, 2012 FRANK McDONALD Environment Editor, in Doha UN climate chief Christiana Figueres has confidently predicted that the conference in Doha, Qatar, “will produce a second commitment period for the Kyoto Protocol, as of January 1st, 2013”. Kyoto, the only international legally binding agreement on global warming, is due to expire on December 31st, but the European Union, Australia, Norway and other countries have pledged to renew it even without the participation of Canada, Japan and Russia. EU climate commissioner Connie Hedegaard told a press briefing yesterday that Europe “will make an immediate commitment on the second commitment period in 28 days from now” – in all probability for a further seven years, until 2020. “We have a track record in taking legally binding commitments but also delivering on them. We all know that too few countries will be making that commitment, so we need to focus on what the remaining countries responsible for 85 per cent of global emissions are doing.” Pointing fingers Although Ms Hedegaard said it “won’t bring us a lot further pointing fingers at each other”, she pointedly noted that Europe’s greenhouse gas emissions had fallen by 18 per cent since 1990, while emissions in the US had gone up by 10.8 per cent in the same period. She also noted that China’s emissions had reached 6.6 tonnes per person, compared to the EU’s 7.3 tonnes and the US figure of 17.2 tonnes. “We have a common obligation to try to be more ambitious, because we are moving very, very fast in the wrong direction.” She reiterated that the EU’s offer to increase its level of ambition from 20 per cent to 30 per cent cuts in emissions by 2020 was “conditional on others doing more”. Nonetheless, the EU had cut emissions by 18 per cent and would easily exceed the 20 per cent target. Ms Hedegaard said she expected that other delegations in Doha would use the day-long “ministerial roundtable” tomorrow to say what they were prepared to do in the interim, such as reducing fossil fuel subsidies, which exceeded $500 billion (€383 billion) last year. Todd Stern, President Barack Obama’s climate envoy, agreed that phasing out these subsidies “makes a tremendous amount of sense”. He told the press that only about 20 per cent of the total went to poor people and there were “other ways to take care of them”. Mr Stern said any future agreement on foot of the Durban Platform “has to be applicable to all countries in the world of the 2020s. It needs to be inclusive, drawing in all countries of the world, and needs to be based on real-world considerations, not on ideology.” Ms Figueres said this would entail a “complete transformation of economic structure of the world that can’t happen overnight”. She was concerned that “we’re very far behind where science says we need to be”, but hopeful Doha would be a step in the right direction. irishtimesDOTcom/newspaper/world/2012/1204/1224327438977.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354583229605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 20:07:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354584465277-30</Id><Title>What to expect from Obamao care</Title><Msg>Hospitals are "full to bursting" and bed use is reaching such "dangerous" levels that staff are struggling to maintain the safety and quality of patients' care, claims an authoritative report based on the NHS's own performance data. Bed occupancy rates are often well above 85%, the maximum for patients to be well looked after and not exposed to health risks, according to official statistics collated by healthcare information firm Dr Foster, which the government half owns. The analysis also found that death rates at more than a dozen hospital trusts in England are "worryingly high". At 12 trusts, death rates were higher than expected on two out of four hospital mortality measures. Senior doctors warned that the findings reflected their increasingly frantic efforts to find beds for the growing number of emergency admissions and that repeated breaches of the 85% limit mean that patients – especially the elderly – are being scattered across hospitals. A lack of beds in specialist wards results in patients being sen to wards where staff may not know how to look after them properly. Some operations being cancelled because of this "overspill", hospital doctors' leaders say. The NHS recognises that occupancy rates above 85% make it difficult to give high-quality care, minimise the risk of hospital-acquired infections and avoid busy staff making mistakes with medication. Ministers say hospitals across England do manage to maintain 85% average bed occupancy across the year and the service is flexible enough to cope well with fluctuations in demand. But NHS figures published in the independent health information service Dr Foster's new Hospital Guide, which analyses the performance of every hospital in England in 2011-12, show occupancy was running at 88% in midweek throughout that period and averaged 90% for 11 of the 12 months, excluding the NHS's quiet periods, such as Christmas and new year. The national level was over 85% on 230 of 365 days of last year (62.8%) and over 90% occupied on 19 (5.2%), NHS data given to Dr Foster shows. "The NHS is full," said Roger Taylor, director of research at the firm, which is co-owned by the Department of Health. Up to 29% of beds occupied by people who could have been treated elsewhere and other inefficiencies are costing the NHS billions of pounds a year, Dr Foster estimates. Over half such cases involve patients over 75 years old. In addition, the NHS's Health and Social Care Information Centre says over the whole of 2011-12 many of the 146 hospital trusts it has data for, ran at 90% capacity or higher. "Hospitals are busier than they have ever been and the beds that we have are under significant pressure", said Mike Farrar, chief executive of the NHS Confederation, which represents hospitals. The NHS in England has shed a third of its total stock of beds in the last 25 years, including 4,000 since 2007. Hospitals increasingly declare themselves on "red alert", which means they have very few beds left, or even "black alert", when they have to shut their doors to new admissions and send patients elsewhere, said Dr Andrew Goddard, the director of the medical workforce unit at the Royal College of Physicians, which represents hospital doctors. "If you ask any doctor in this country they would say that the system is straining to burst; particularly in winter, but now it's increasingly happening the rest of the year. Hospitals always seem to be full. There always seem to be problems findings beds for patients." Dr Foster may underestimate the overcrowding, said Goddard. "The situation in the NHS is worse than this report portrays it. Their figures give bed occupancy rates at midnight. But hospitals are actually even busier between noon and the late afternoon, when we are trying to get patients home and deal with the new arrivals." Shunting patients with conditions such as pneumonia on to surgical wards means they may not receive the specialist care they need, and hospitals lose income as procedures are cancelled because there are no beds for patients awaiting surgery, he said. "These things are happening across the country. That's pretty common and it's getting worse and worse". Paul Flynn, chair of the British Medical Association's hospital consultants committee, said: "Most of us would recognise the picture of the NHS being 'full to bursting'. It is running at excessive occupancy for far too much of the year. It used to be that pressures were winter pressures but nobody calls them winter pressures any more because they run for most of the year." In September the Care Quality Commission (CQC), the NHS regulator in England, took legal action against Mid Yorkshire Hospitals NHS Trust when it found that some patients who were not awaiting surgery were being left for as long as four days in the day surgery unit at Pinderfields hospital in Wakefield, where they had no washing facilities, no lighting and no bedside storage because the unit was generally used by those staying for less than a day. Dr Foster's findings pose a challenge to the coalition's attempts to defend its stewardship of the NHS at a time when the service is trying to cope with a £20bn efficiency drive and rising demand for its services. But Jeremy Hunt, the health secretary, insisted that "The NHS is not overcrowded. On average there are around 20,000 of its beds available. Of course this goes up and down, but the NHS has practice and experience in managing peaks of demand, particularly in the winter." Katherine Murphy, chief executive of the Patients Association, said: "These distressing figures reveal bed occupancy rates are at the very limit of what is safe or indeed desirable for patients." Dr Foster's analysis of NHS mortality data shows 12 hospital trusts had worryingly high death rates, according to its measurements, that three had consistently high rates as judged by the Hospital Standardised Mortality Ratio indicator and death rates at weekends were high at five other trusts, possibly because too few staff were on duty.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354584465277</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 20:27:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354585292120-31</Id><Topic><Title>ONE TRILLION OF DEFENSE CUTS GO OVER THE CLIFF !! YES !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1354549743423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 10:49:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The central banking families that own the Federal Reserve demand that the Democrats give them perpetual wars to enslave idiot taxpayers with inextinguishable debt. Audit the Fed, shackle the IRS and the welfare/warfare state goes down the toilet. Bankers love international socialism</Msg><Username>potterkimberly44</Username><Timestamp>1354585292120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 20:41:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>