<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347083365434-1</Id><Title>GOP Rep. Steve King defends biofuels, opposes government intervention</Title><Msg>GOP Rep. Steve King defends biofuels, opposes government intervention By Zack Colman - 09/07/12 01:42 PM ET Rep. Steve King (R-Iowa) said during a Thursday debate that he wants “government to get out of the way” of markets, but then praised the renewable fuels industry — which is propped up by a government mandate — for providing Iowa jobs. King was debating Democrat Christie Vilsack, who is challenging the Republican for his seat, on Iowa radio station WHO 1040. “The prosperity that we have enjoyed is a result of a lot of things; risk-taking capital, trying to get government out of the way, trying to reduce the intrusiveness of the federal government,” King said, according to a clip of the debate provided by Think Progress. He added: “And by the way, the very best thing that has come along for small communities in Iowa, around 950 of them, has been renewable fuels, and I’m fortunate that I’ve been in the middle of that for a long, long time.” King has in the past supported the renewable fuel standard (RFS), which requires refiners to blend 13.2 billion gallons of corn-based ethanol into traditional transportation fuel this year. Iowa produces more corn ethanol than any state in the nation. But Republicans have criticized the RFS as a government mandate that gives a pulse to a technology that could not survive on its own. The Hill, in checking with King’s office to get a clarification on his comments, was told by an aide that he was set to introduce GOP presidential candidate Mitt Romney — who supports the RFS — at an Iowa event. King has disregarded his anti-interventionist stance when it benefits his constituents before. He, like other Iowa Republicans, wants to extend a 2.2 cent per kilowatt-hour tax incentive for wind production that many Republicans oppose. Iowa, as it happens, has about 7,000 workers in the wind sector and...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347083365434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347106898424-2</Id><Title>B.C. lawyer grills Northern Gateway president on Enbridge’s liability</Title><Msg>B.C. lawyer grills Northern Gateway president on Enbridge’s liability Dean Bennett Edmonton — The Canadian Press Published Friday, Sep. 07 2012, 1:35 PM EDT Last updated Friday, Sep. 07 2012, 7:21 PM EDT 26 comments A B.C. government lawyer hammered away at the president of the proposed Northern Gateway pipeline Friday, saying that while the parent company, Enbridge, is promising to clean up oil spills, it has created a corporate structure to limit how much it would have to pay. “From the perspective of British Columbians, this doesn’t look good,” Elisabeth Graff told John Carruthers at federal hearings on the $6-billion line that would ship Alberta crude to B.C.’s coast. Ms. Graff questioned Mr. Carruthers over the decision by Calgary-based Enbridge to hive off the Northern Gateway project as a limited partnership, with Enbridge having a 50 per cent stake and private investors covering off the rest. That, noted Ms. Graff, means Enbridge would only be liable for an equivalent amount of liability in the case of a major catastrophe, such as the $800-million oil spill on an Enbridge pipeline in southern Michigan in 2010. “Are you willing to acknowledge this is a complex organizational structure that limits the liability of a corporate giant that definitely would have sufficient funds?” she asked. “What we’re left with is an entity which you tell us has the financial resources necessary to cover any type of spill, but we’re still doubting whether that is possible.” “No, I just fundamentally can’t accept that,” replied Mr. Carruthers, adding Northern Gateway and its investors would not invest in such a megaproject only to see it sunk by an environmental catastrophe. “Because of the investment, everyone would want to make sure there’s proper funding available in case of a spill,” he said. He said the issue is not the corporate organizational structure but whether a spill will be cleaned up properly and paid for by the operators. That will happen, he said, through adequate insurance and in-house savings. The project is expected to realize an annual net income of more than $300-million. “British Columbians would need to know there’s an effective response to any spill [and] we’re very much aligned with that,” he said. Mr. Carruthers and six Enbridge economists have been taking questions this week from interveners, including the B.C. government, as part of a federal joint panel review of the pipeline. The three-member panel is to make a recommendation to the federal government by the end of next year on whether the pipeline is needed given oil supply and demand, and whether the line can be built and sustained safely. Mr. Carruthers said the decision by Enbridge to hive off Northern Gateway and take on investors is simply sound and commonly accepted business practice. B.C. estimates $81-billion in tax revenue will be accrued by the pipeline over 30 years, with $36-billion going to the federal government, $32-billion to Alberta and just $6-billion to B.C. B.C. Premier Christy Clark has said her government won’t consider signing off on the deal until it gets a better percentage of the profits and it’s satisfied with steps taken to prevent spills and clean them up should they occur. On Thursday, B.C.’s Environment Minister Terry Lake underlined provincial concern by personally attending the hearings. On Friday, Janet Holder, Enbridge’s senior executive in charge of Northern Gateway, attended. Outside the hearing, Ms. Holder told reporters the company has no intention of saddling B.C. citizens with a polluted mess or a large cleanup bill. “We’re doing everything in our power to mitigate against a spill,” Ms. Holder said. “Believe me, Enbridge doesn’t want a spill. It’s not what we’re in the business for. We’re in the business of moving very safely, environmentally sound and in a sustainable way, product from one spot to another.” When the hearings began Friday, there was some question whether Ms. Graff would be allowed to ask any questions at all. Panel chair Sheila Leggett shut down Ms. Graff’s line of questioning Thursday. She said the Edmonton hearings are to focus on finances, and economics and insurance issues would be better heard by an upcoming panel in B.C. that is to hear evidence about pipeline safety and emergency preparedness. However on Friday, Ms. Leggett allowed broad questions on spill liability after Ms. Graff and Enbridge agreed the ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347106898424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 08:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347110458996-3</Id><Topic><Title>SPLIT SEEMS IMMINENT</Title><Username>plantmatter</Username><Timestamp>1347052626730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:17:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are rumors of a second Divy Hikez also,for 2012.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1347110458996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:20:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347110766885-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Magic Number Is 90 As We Near Splitz Announcement!</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1347021096342</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 08:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new tax codes will be My greatest concern.If They boost tax from 15% to 45%,on long term holdings,then I think dumping everything is wise.Buy a new Caddy,invest somewhere with high Div,and leave it to children.They will inherit at stepped up basis.. The $tenchMan.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1347110766885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:26:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347110829065-5</Id><Topic><Title>here we go...</Title><Username>gautreauxclsm0389</Username><Timestamp>1346085987000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>john_peter365</Username><Timestamp>1347110829065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112640883-6</Id><Topic><Title>The Magic Number Is 90 As We Near Splitz Announcement!</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1347021096342</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 08:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you stupid?</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1347112640883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112681181-7</Id><Topic><Title>SPLIT SEEMS IMMINENT</Title><Username>plantmatter</Username><Timestamp>1347052626730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:17:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ #$%$</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1347112681181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:58:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347126212355-8</Id><Title>California’s Solar Energy Passes a Milestone ~ 1GW</Title><Msg>California’s Solar Energy Passes a Milestone September 7, 2012 By Nicholas Brown 1 Comment During a recent heatwave, California reached a solar energy milestone. Its solar power plants hit over 1,000 MW (1 GW) of electricity generation, almost as much as their combined 1,160 MW capacity, which is equal to the power production of two large 500-MW gas-fired power stations. The power plants reached this milestone on several occasions during the heatwave. California solar panels via Shutterstock Despite their large size, solar panels have the potential to utilize the least land of all types of power plants, due to the fact that they can be integrated into almost anything, whether it is on the ground or installed on rooftops which are usually hardly utilized. Electricity demand tends to be higher on sunny days, and this is especially due to the power requirements of air conditioners, standing fans, and evaporative coolers. Generally speaking, the sunnier the weather is, the hotter it becomes (not including those times of day in certain places when it simply becomes “hot” due to high humidity). This is clearly a great match for solar. Heat rises, electricity demand rises, and solar electricity is rising at the same time. This is one reason solar panels are complemented so nicely by air conditioners (or vice versa). Typical coal-fired power plants are not very adjustable because they take a long time to start up and shut down, so it is difficult for them to increase power production in time to meet increased air conditioner power consumption in such heatwaves. Bob Foster, chairman of the...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347126212355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347127402243-9</Id><Title>Spinach power gets a major boost</Title><Msg>Spinach power gets a major boost by David Salisbury | Posted on Tuesday, Sep. 4, 2012 — 11:00 AM Spinach power has just gotten a big boost. An interdisciplinary team of researchers at Vanderbilt University have developed a way to combine the photosynthetic protein that converts light into electrochemical energy in spinach with silicon, the material used in solar cells, in a fashion that produces substantially more electrical current than has been reported by previous “biohybrid” solar cells. The research was reported online on Sep. 4 in the journal Advanced Materials and Vanderbilt has applied for a patent on the combination. “This combination produces current levels almost 1,000 times higher than we were able to achieve by depositing the protein on various types of metals. It also produces a modest increase in voltage,” said David Cliffel, associate professor of chemistry, who collaborated on the project with Kane Jennings, professor of chemical and biomolecular engineering. “If we can continue on our current trajectory of increasing voltage and current levels, we could reach the range of mature solar conversion technologies in three years.” The researchers’ next step is to build a functioning PS1-silicon solar cell using this new design. Jennings has an Environmental Protection Agency award that will allow a group of undergraduate engineering students to build the prototype. The students won the award at the National Sustainable Design Expo in April based on a solar panel that they had created using a two-year old design. With the new design, Jennings estimates that a two-foot panel could put out at least 100 milliamps at one volt – enough to power a number of different types of small electrical devices. Harnessing the power of spinach More than 40 years ago, scientists discovered that one of the proteins involved in photosynthesis, called Photosystem 1 (PS1), continued to function when it was extracted from plants like spinach. Then they determined PS1 converts sunlight into electrical energy with nearly 100 percent efficiency, compared to conversion efficiencies of less than 40 percent achieved by manmade devices. This prompted various research groups around the world to begin trying to use PS1 to create more efficient solar cells. Another potential advantage of these biohybrid cells is that they can be made from cheap and readily available materials, unlike many microelectronic devices that require rare and expensive materials like platinum or indium. Most plants use the same photosynthetic proteins as spinach. In fact, in another research project Jennings is working on a method for extracting PS1 from kudzu. Since the initial discovery, progress has been slow but steady. Researchers have developed ways to extract PS1 efficiently from leaves. They have demonstrated that it can be made into cells that produce electrical current when exposed to sunlight. However, the amount of power that these biohybrid cells can produce per square inch has been substantially below that of commercial photovoltaic cells. Another problem has been longevity. The performance of some early test cells deteriorated after only a few weeks. In 2010, however, the Vanderbilt team kept a PS1 cell working for nine months with no deterioration in performance. “Nature knows how to do this extremely well. In evergreen trees, for example, PS1 lasts for years,” said Cliffel. “We just have to figure out how to do it ourselves.” Secret is “doping” silicon The Vanderbilt researchers report that their PS1/silicon combination produces nearly a milliamp (850 microamps) of current per square centimeter at 0.3 volts. That is nearly two and a half times more current than the best level reported previously from a biohybrid cell. The reason this combo works so well is because the electrical properties of the silicon substrate have been tailored to fit those of the PS1 molecule. This is done by implanting electrically charge atoms in the silicon to alter its electrical properties: a process called “doping.” In this case, the protein worked extremely well with silicon doped with positive charges and worked poorly with negatively doped silicon. To make the device, the researchers extracted PS1 from spinach into an aqueous solution and poured the mixture on the surface of a p-doped silicon wafer. Then they put the wafer in a vacuum chamber in order to evaporate the water away leaving a film of protein. They found that the optimum thickness was about one micron, about 100 PS1 molecules thick. Protein alignment When a PS1 protein exposed to light, it absorbs the energy in the photons and...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347127402243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347149973237-10</Id><Topic><Title>California’s Solar Energy Passes a Milestone ~ 1GW</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1347126212355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:43:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what PERCENTAGE is this of all types of GW production in California. 1%, 10%, 50% ....what is it?</Msg><Username>iggybiggies</Username><Timestamp>1347149973237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>