<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354252178061-1</Id><Topic><Title>How Obamao won</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354246000595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:26:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama won the most highly educated group in America, those with more than an undergraduate degree, by 55% to 42%...</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354252178061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 00:09:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354253120510-2</Id><Title>Free college education</Title><Msg>That would be a good idea. The government should pay off the $1 trillion, or whatever it is, in student loan debt with the sale of 30 year bonds. They could put a $30 billion/year tax on dividends to cover the interest. The government should, of course, provide some guidance to universities about the kind of degrees it would like to promote. If it is paying for everything, things that generate high salaries and payoffs for the state are most key...</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354253120510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 00:25:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354253778474-3</Id><Topic><Title>GM seeks to build excitement for Chevy brand with SS sedan</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354245777421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:22:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the Republicans are driven out of Congress the Democrats should be able to develop a rational strategy for the development of industry &amp; technology. Abolishing the worthless farm subsidy program should be enough to fund it.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354253778474</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 00:36:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354273159952-4</Id><Topic><Title>GM seeks to build excitement for Chevy brand with SS sedan</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354245777421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:22:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and romans mother is a hoe.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354273159952</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 05:59:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354273199579-5</Id><Topic><Title>Free college education</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354253120510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 00:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ or pay for it.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354273199579</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 05:59:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354273267026-6</Id><Topic><Title>How Obamao won</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354246000595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:26:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ #$%$ POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354273267026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 06:01:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354283837146-7</Id><Title>China Forecast To Hit 150 GW Installed Wind Capacity By 2015</Title><Msg>China Forecast To Hit 150 GW Installed Wind Capacity By 2015 China’s wind industry is forecast to reach 150 gigawatts (GW) of installed capacity by 2015 — shattering the central government’s goal of 100 GW by 2015. These findings come from the first installment of GTM Research’s China Wind Market Quarterly, released with market analysts Azure International. The report predicts steady government support and rising demand will keep the country far ahead of the renewable energy economies of America, Europe, and India. While China was not immune to the financial slowdown that has gripped the world in recent years, its clean energy output has boomed in recent years, led by the wind industry. Already the international leader in installed nameplate capacity, China installed 18 GW of new wind capacity – a 40% growth rate from 2011 – to pass 50 GW of grid-connected and more than 70 GW total wind capacity at the end of Q3 2012. New Installations Gusting Forward Wind energy keeps growing in China, at an exponential rate. In 2006, it had roughly 3 GW of installed capacity, good for 4% of the global share. Since then, it has reached approximately 35% of installed global capacity – a 25-fold increase, while the rest of the world only expanded by a factor of 2.6. The nation shows no signs of slowing down the pace, either. China added 2.9 GW new wind capacity in Q3, and is on track to add another 9 GW in Q4 to reach 80 GW total capacity. China consumed 50.4 billion kilowatt-hours (kWh) of wind power in the first six months of 2012, currently supplies a quarter of all wind energy supplied to the grid worldwide, and will soon become the largest wind energy generator of any country in the world. Curtailment’s Strong Headwinds However, wind’s rapid expansion has come with problems. Growth has been concentrated in several northern and western provinces, with Inner Mongolia boasting twice the capacity of the next highest province, Hebei. Like in many parts of the U.S., these regions with massive generation potential are sparsely populated, cannot absorb all the locally generated wind power, and see their wind farms subjected to curtailment when generation outstrips grid needs and transmission capacity. The issue is arguably the highest hurdle for China to clear in realizing its full potential. Curtailment is caused by challenges like limited local demand, undersized transmission infrastructure, inflexible coal-baseload generation, and wind cycles that often run counter to demand. The three highest-generating regions of the country all experienced more than 22 percent of generation curtailed from 2009-2011. And, in 2011, 15 terawatt-hours (TWh) of wind power were curtailed – 17% of all generation and an economic loss of RMB 5 billion (about $802 million). Even though China is planning the world’s most ambitious grid upgrade and Inner Mongolia began a power exchange to replace local coal generation with wind, GTM forecasts curtailment issues are likely to persist. Two Growth Jetstreams: Rising Demand and Constant Government Support Regardless of nagging curtailment issues, China’s wind growth is remarkable, and an output of unique circumstances: skyrocketing demand and consistent (if inefficient) government support at the national and local level. China’s electricity demand has mirrored the country’s economic rise, growing 15 times higher than 1980s levels. The government forecasts demand to rise from 5 trillion kWh in 2012 to over 8 trillion kWh in 2020. Rising power demand means more demand for wind turbines – especially along the densely populated coastal regions, which expect to install 3 GW of offshore wind by 2015. Government policies have been nothing if not ambitious. Wind installation targets have been a part of China’s five-year development plans since 2000, laws mandate the grid must accept all power from renewable generation, feed-in tariffs have been functioning since 2009, businesses receive a 50% discount on the value-added tax of wind-generated electricity, and seven provinces have wind generation targets and local feed-in tariffs. No Windbreakers In Sight Ultimately, while China’s wind energy industry faces notable challenges, GTM’s report finds the sheer volume of projects in the development pipeline and scale of demand means the country will lead the world far into the future. “China’s wind industry retains its leadership position worldwide, whether looking at policy targets, overall installation numbers or innovation,” said Scott Clavenna, CEO of Greentech Media. Image Credits: China wind turbine image via Shutterstock; All charts and graphs courtesy GTM Research Clean Technica ( sDOTtt/1voJI )</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354283837146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 08:57:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354284082883-8</Id><Title>China Forecast To Hit 150 GW Installed Wind Capacity By 2015</Title><Msg>China Forecast To Hit 150 GW Installed Wind Capacity By 2015 China’s wind industry is forecast to reach 150 gigawatts (GW) of installed capacity by 2015 — shattering the central government’s goal of 100 GW by 2015. These findings come from the first installment of GTM Research’s China Wind Market Quarterly, released with market analysts Azure International. The report predicts steady government support and rising demand will keep the country far ahead of the renewable energy economies of America, Europe, and India. While China was not immune to the financial slowdown that has gripped the world in recent years, its clean energy output has boomed in recent years, led by the wind industry. Already the international leader in installed nameplate capacity, China installed 18 GW of new wind capacity – a 40% growth rate from 2011 – to pass 50 GW of grid-connected and more than 70 GW total wind capacity at the end of Q3 2012. New Installations Gusting Forward Wind energy keeps growing in China, at an exponential rate. In 2006, it had roughly 3 GW of installed capacity, good for 4% of the global share. Since then, it has reached approximately 35% of installed global capacity – a 25-fold increase, while the rest of the world only expanded by a factor of 2.6. The nation shows no signs of slowing down the</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354284082883</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:01:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354284795329-9</Id><Topic><Title>XOM can be the next ten bagger!</Title><Username>charlesjackson845</Username><Timestamp>1354277069364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 07:04:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they help you select the right car for you</Msg><Username>smithsteven480</Username><Timestamp>1354284795329</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:13:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354285295531-10</Id><Topic><Title>GM seeks to build excitement for Chevy brand with SS sedan</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354245777421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:22:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rome wasn't built in a day. Things will go much more quickly when the House Republicans are voted out. The more they obstruct the more of them will get voted out. They could shift strategy, reform their radical ways, and then the country could be turned around more quickly...</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354285295531</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 09:21:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354288173463-11</Id><Title>China’s wind industry is forecast to reach 150 gigawatts (GW) of installed capacity by 2015</Title><Msg>China’s wind industry is forecast to reach 150 gigawatts (GW) of installed capacity by 2015</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354288173463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:09:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354289632766-12</Id><Title>Do you still believe in Laissez Fairies?</Title><Msg>The theory is just total garbage and was long since tossed onto the rubbish heap. It ignores the concept of public goods. It ignores the concept of social return. It ignores the concept of externality. It ignores the concept of network effect. It ignores the concept of economies of scale and scope. It ignores the concept of risk. Its most famous and ambitious formulation, the one by Adam Smith, has been proven wrong, mathematically, by Nash. It ignores just about all reality, and substitutes in its place a vision that is most suited to preserving the interests of select few, especially rent seekers, the politically well connected, or those with access to large amounts of resources accumulated by someone else. The Laissez Faire view has now been soundly rejected by the voters in America. There was never a time when it held sway in Europe, except perhaps in the Dark Ages. Roman law and methods of administration, the gift of the ancient world to the modern, leaves scarcely any room for it at all. Even the Patricians of the past knew they could do much better. The world will be a better place when it is swept away for eternity.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354289632766</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:33:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354290413858-13</Id><Topic><Title>Of Course I Coined The Alias "Greedful" Only I Followed That With...</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1354246727488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:38:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another alias greedfuldingaling? Romanis? You're jack off. Go jack off in the corner as you pretend to be some character that you imagine to be. Talk about losers, you're the king of them. And I'm the progressive in your worst nightmares.. One that'll punch you in the face</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1354290413858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:46:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354290930353-14</Id><Topic><Title>Of Course I Coined The Alias "Greedful" Only I Followed That With...</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1354246727488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 22:38:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can play the fascist wahleee boy, for few months, if you like. Think of it as an ironic parody. It will be entertaining. lol</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354290930353</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:55:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354295231953-15</Id><Title>Wealth Tax</Title><Msg>Wealth taxes have a long history. The ancient Romans used them to fund the government, taxing inheritances and real estate, as did the Byzantines, especially after the reforms of Justinian in the 6th century, reforms which preserved 1000 years of administrative and legal practice for another 1000 years. The English state funded itself almost entirely through land taxes, and by the time of the English Civil War, direct taxes on financial assets and monies as well. A more administratively cumbersome system of excises was introduced by the 18th century, however. The Dutch have used wealth taxes to fund their government for over 400 years. The French have used wealth taxes as well. A wealth tax is a highly efficient means of raising revenue for a government, as the mechanism for assessing the value of real estate is ancient, and it is straightforward enough, in the modern world, to have a CPA certify the amount bonds, stocks, and cash in someone's possession at the end of a fiscal year. Considering the amount of wealth in the hands of Americans, especially those with assets of more than $1 million, the amount that could be collected with a wealth tax is staggering. A 2% tax on individual wealth over $1 million would easily bring in $1 trillion in revenue per year. The idea that a country such as the United States, one with so much wealth, could ever go "bankrupt" is just absurd - especially when the wealth is rising daily with government bond sales, all of which take savings to finance, and are wealth... The U.S. Constitution does have archaic language about direct Federal taxes being divided by population among the states. That is easily got round by just making the states assume most of the burden of funding Federal programs, and funding them with wealth taxes collected by the states, or, if some states refuse, lose the federal funding.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354295231953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:07:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354295309923-16</Id><Topic><Title>China’s wind industry is forecast to reach 150 gigawatts (GW) of installed capacity by 2015</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354288173463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 10:09:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Investing in LNG is the same as throwing your money away! It's too late! The market is vanishing forever!</Msg><Username>crystal4u2see</Username><Timestamp>1354295309923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:08:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354296159390-17</Id><Title>US Veterans Fight For Wind Jobs As Tax Credit Hits The Cliff</Title><Msg>US Veterans Fight For Wind Jobs As Tax Credit Hits The Cliff Lean, mean, fighting machine. That is what the US military is known for on the battlefield. Now, military veterans are taking the fight for wind jobs to Washington, DC. Interesting PHOTO, Palm Springs, CA Image Credit: Wind Turbines via Urban Mixer/Flickr-Some Rights Reserved Earlier this week,</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354296159390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:22:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354299177349-18</Id><Title>madmilker</Title><Msg>was here.</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1354299177349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:12:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354299778552-19</Id><Title>DuPont breaks ground at 30 MMgy cellulosic ethanol facility</Title><Msg>DuPont breaks ground at 30 MMgy cellulosic ethanol facility By DuPont | November 30, 2012 PHOTO Once fully operational, the DuPont facility will produce 30 MMgy of cellulosic ethanol. Lincolnway Energy LLC, a 60 MMgy corn-ethanol plant, can be seen in the background, behind the construction site. DuPont. NEVADA, IOWA – DuPont came one step closer to commercializing advanced biofuels by breaking ground on its cellulosic ethanol facility in Nevada, Iowa, on Nov. 30. Expected to be completed in mid-2014, this more than $200 million facility will be among the first and largest commercial-scale cellulosic biorefineries in the world. This new facility is expected to generate 30 MMgy cellulosic biofuel produced from corn stover residues, a non-food feedstock that consists of corn stalks and leaves. This is more capacity than original estimates called for as data derived from our piloting facility in Tennessee has allowed DuPont to further optimize our process and technology. This first commercial facility will require a capital investment of about $7 per gallon of annual capacity. “Nearly a decade ago, DuPont set out to develop innovative technology that would result in low capital and low-cost cellulosic ethanol production,” said James Collins, president, DuPont Industrial Biosciences. “We recognized that science-powered innovation was the catalyst to make cellulosic ethanol a commercial reality and to help reduce global dependence on fossil fuels.” “By leveraging DuPont Pioneer corn production expertise and designing an integrated technology platform, we’ve built an affordable and sustainable entry point into this new industry. We’re committed to continued productivity gains to drive costs down even further for the coming generations of plants, ones based on corn stover as well as other feedstocks,” Collins continued. “And we didn’t get to this point alone. We’ve built an incredible partnership with the state of Iowa, Iowa State University, entrepreneurial growers and a whole host of partners around the country who share our vision of making renewable fuels a commercial reality.” Collins was joined by Iowa Gov. Terry Branstad to celebrate the official beginning of construction on the facility at a ceremony held at the construction site adjacent to grain ethanol facility Lincolnway Energy. “During my previous terms as governor, we were excited to bring ethanol production to the state. After many hard years of work by Iowa growers and technology companies like DuPont, Iowa now leads the country in renewable fuel production,” Branstad said. “This site in Nevada is the next critical step in our cellulosic ethanol journey. We look forward to bringing these advanced technologies online, creating local jobs and helping to deliver clean, sustainable energy.” Agricultural Impact To supply the corn stover for its plant, DuPont will contract with more than 500 local farmers to gather, store and deliver over 375,000 dry tons of stover per year into the Nevada facility. In addition to the estimated 60 full-time plant operations jobs, there will be over 150 individuals involved in the collection, stacking, transportation and storage of the stover feedstock seasonally during each harvest. The stover will be collected from an approximate 30 mile radius around the new facility and harvested off of 190,000 acres. For many corn growers, residue management is a major challenge when maximizing their potential grain yield. Leftover corn stover interferes with planting, delays stand establishment, monopolizes nitrogen in the soil and often harbors damaging insect, pests and pathogens. Some stover from the corn crop is left on the field to protect the soil from erosion. “Many of us who have participated in the stover harvest program with DuPont are already seeing benefits of this alternative residue management strategy including positive effects on grain yields the following year on our fields,” said Jim Hill, a corn grower whose stover will be used to supply DuPont’s biorefinery. “We’re excited to work with DuPont to supply stover to this new biorefinery, partner to discover new markets for our products and co-products and develop new crop production techniques based on the opportunity to manage residues thru partial stover removal.” DuPont will further adapt its cellulosic ethanol technology to additional feedstocks. It is already processing switchgrass in the testing facility it owns jointly with the University of Tennessee near Knoxville, Tenn. Environmental Impact The use of advanced biofuels can result in fewer greenhouse gas emissions. An International Organization for Standardization (ISO) compliant, peer reviewed life cycle assessment of the DuPont biorefinery and supply chain indicates a potential greater than 100 percent reduction in greenhouse gas emissions compared to gasoline. This significant greenhouse gas reduction is enabled by use of cellulosic co-products as a source of renewable energy. The DuPont biorefinery co-product is a material that can displace coal in facilities currently burning this fossil fuel. Regional businesses and academic institutions have already indicated interest in exploring the potential use of the renewable co-products to replace portions of their coal fired operations. “We are excited to explore the various synergies between Lincolnway and DuPont that bring value to both companies. One area is the possibility of using DuPont’s cellulosic ethanol co-product to replace our coal usage,” said Lincolnway Energy Chairman Jeff Taylor. “We strive to continually improve our operations and environmental impact. Replacing our fossil fuels with this renewable cellulosic ethanol co-product to generate heat and power makes great sense. It is generated right next door, would reduce our coal usage and the transportation costs of shipping coal cars almost a thousand miles.” DuPont provided additional details about the project in an interview prior to the groundbreaking. ethanolproducerDOTcom/articles/9337/dupont-breaks-ground-at-30-mmgy-cellulosic-ethanol-facility</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354299778552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:22:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354301200636-20</Id><Topic><Title>DuPont breaks ground at 30 MMgy cellulosic ethanol facility</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354299778552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:22:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Study finds biodiesel from algae, yeast and bacteria can displace both petroleum diesel and soybean biodiesel 23 November 2012 IMAGE Diesel engine torque output as a function of the engine speed (rpm) for the tested fuels. Credit: ACS, Wahlen et al. Click to enlarge. Biodiesel (fatty acid methyl ester) derived from oleaginous microbes—microalgae, yeast, and bacteria—can effectively displace both petroleum diesel and biodiesel produced from plant oils, according to the findings of a new study by a team from Utah State University. The researchers, who reported their results in a paper published in the ACS journal Energy &amp; Fuels, examined the properties, engine performance, and emissions for biodiesel produced from the microalgae Chaetoceros gracilis; the yeast Cryptococcus curvatus; and the bacterium Rhodococcus opacus. While biodiesel derived from plant seed oils has advantages as a replacement for petroleum diesel, there is strong interest in the potential for biodiesel produced from microbial derived oils because of potential use of contaminated water, the diversity of oils that can be produced, use of marginal lands, and potential for higher oil yields per acre. Three different groups of microbes are known to produce high neutral oils including select microalgae, bacteria, and yeast. Here, we have selected a representative from each of these three groups, produced biodiesel, have characterized the properties of the fuels in comparison to biodiesel produced from plant oils. Plant-based oils, commonly used to produce biodiesel (e.g., soybean, canola, and sunflower) are similar to one another in terms of fatty acid composition, containing primarily C16 and C18 fatty acids with varying degrees of unsaturation. Microbial oils, however, can differ substantially and may contain uncommon fatty acids that differ in both chain length and structure. Each of the microbial sources of oil chosen for this study differ in one way or another from soybean oil, a common feedstock for biodiesel production. —Wahlen et al. IMAGE Brake specific fuel consumption (BSFC; Lb/Hp/h or g/MJ) as a function of engine speed (rpm) for the tested fuels. Credit: ACS, Wahlen et al. Click to enlarge. The team determined the key physical properties of each biodiesel and compared them with commercial soybean biodiesel. Each fuel was then used to operate a two-cylinder indirect injection diesel engine attached to an eddy current dynamometer. The horsepower and torque output from the engine under load was reported for each microbial biofuel and compared to outputs obtained with both diesel fuel and soybean biodiesel. Key emissions data were collected for each biofuel without load at a steady 3500 rpm, allowing comparison to emissions from petroleum diesel and soybean biodiesel. They found that the selected physical properties of the three microbial fuels were comparable to soybean biodiesel and are within ASTM (ASTM D6751) specification. In engine testing, diesel #2 delivered the highest power output (8.5 hp) of all fuels. Soybean biodiesel registered a power output of 8.2 hp, 96.5% of the value obtained for diesel #2. Of the microbial fuels tested, bacterial biodiesel had the lowest power output at 7.8 hp, still producing 92% and 95% of the output achieved with diesel #2 and soybean biodiesel, respectively. Power output for the engine operated with both yeast and microalgae biodiesel was similar for each fuel achieving 93% and 96% of outputs for diesel #2 and soybean biodiesel, respectively. The team found less of a difference in observed torque output. Exhaust gas temperatures were highest for diesel #2, followed by soybean, microalgae, yeast, and bacteria (in order of decreasing temperatures). The biofuels showed higher fuel consumption (BSFC) across the rpm range of the test compared to diesel #2, which is consistent with their lower energy content. Very small differences in BSFC between the biodiesel fuels were observed. Hydrocarbon and CO emissions were reduced from diesel #2 levels for all microbial and soybean biodiesel fuels. While NOx emissions are elevated relative to diesel #2 in yeast, bacteria, and soybean biodiesel fuels, microalgae biodiesel fuel generated NOx emissions that were significantly lower, they found. They suggested that the low prevalence of polyunsaturated fatty acids and the predominance of shorter chain length fatty acids present in C. gracilis oil likely contribute to its low NOx emissions. his study demonstrates that microbial-derived biodiesel shows comparable properties in the parameters tested to soybean biodiesel. Future wide scale use of microbial oils as a source for biodiesel will require advances in large scale cultivation, dewatering, and oil extraction. greencarcongressDOTcom/2012/11/wahlen-20121123.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354301200636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:46:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354301313947-21</Id><Title>Time to buy TRP - Keystone pipeline will be approved</Title><Msg>TRP just pushed through $46, heading for $50. When Obama approves Keystone pipeline early next year the stock could easily jump 20%. Like XOM but its tlat lining to down. TransCanada on the other hand could be an easy double by the end of 2013.</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1354301313947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:48:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354301885103-22</Id><Topic><Title>Time to buy TRP - Keystone pipeline will be approved</Title><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1354301313947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:48:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree and from I've been reading approval looks like a slam dunk in the next couple months. Even Obama wants Keystone now for job growth and good riddance to Middle East oil.</Msg><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1354301885103</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 13:58:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354303041141-23</Id><Title>Boehner growing a tail?</Title><Msg>Considering his position, at the head of the losing party, fighting a battle that is already lost, he is probably starting to feel flames of Hellfire already...</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354303041141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:17:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354305346818-24</Id><Topic><Title>GALE @ 2.20 ★★★ DCTH @ 1.60 ★★★ ANX @ .59 ★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★</Title><Username>edgewater_nj_09</Username><Timestamp>1352140586766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-05 13:36:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sickle cell being fast tracked by FDA.</Msg><Username>newfdatweets</Username><Timestamp>1354305346818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:55:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354312233386-25</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner growing a tail?</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354303041141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:17:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Soon he will start to cry and say OK to everything the Dems want but not what is good for the USA.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1354312233386</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 16:50:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354315306056-26</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner growing a tail?</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354303041141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 14:17:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Boehner was smart he would preserve his forces for a Fabian strategy. He will annihilated if he gives battle... I don't think the House GOP sees it that way though. They'd rather go down fighting... That will be good for the country.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354315306056</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 17:41:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354320212884-27</Id><Topic><Title>Wealth Tax</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354295231953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:07:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the rich are moving their $ now. Your #$%$ is not going to pick their pocket you #$%$ POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354320212884</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:03:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354320256534-28</Id><Topic><Title>The World Is Ending</Title><Username>russellmarubini9576</Username><Timestamp>1321667042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-11-18 20:44:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ POS</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354320256534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 19:04:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354336234814-29</Id><Topic><Title>Wealth Tax</Title><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354295231953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 12:07:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Little drummer boy speaks again. You should be ashamed of yourself. The war budget is almost up to $1 trillion/year, with not a plan to speak of from your corner to pay for it, except borrowing $1 trillion/year. The government has the means to raise that much tax and will eventually. It has the power to hound evaders of its power to the end of the earth if it needs too... You have nothing to tax that though, there's no doubt about that..</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354336234814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-30 23:30:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>