<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355548183204-1</Id><Title>Republican Reading Material</Title><Msg>so you can stop being so ridiculous and become like your forefathers who made America great: google: Treitschke's History of Germany in the nineteenth century. You can find it online easily enough, downloaded in English from the University of California for free. You will see what government is for and what the Progressives had in mind. Oh they read it...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355548183204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 00:09:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355551493348-2</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan House of Fascists March In Lock Step..</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355461445508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 00:04:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know how to say city hall in German, wahleee boy? Rathaus... lol</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355551493348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 01:04:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355570164986-3</Id><Title>Defensive Stock</Title><Msg>Exxon is a defensive stock: it defends it's shareholders against accumulating wealth. Five years of underperformance. Total return since spring of 2008 including dividends: less than zero percent. Drastic underperformance relative to its peers over this period. Stock and its present management a real joke.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355570164986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:16:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355572267425-4</Id><Topic><Title>Infernal: Still stupid after all these years !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1355446591604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 19:56:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at how fast america is sinking. And the poor are going to get much poorer. When the poor can't eat anymore send them to wahlee and #$%$ maxipad the #$%$ POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1355572267425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:51:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355572315002-5</Id><Topic><Title>Infernal: Still stupid after all these years !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1355446591604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 19:56:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH I forgot to say that maxipad is a big #$%$ c--t.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1355572315002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:51:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355578112241-6</Id><Title>U.S. states threaten lawsuit against EPA over regulations</Title><Msg>U.S. states threaten lawsuit against EPA over regulations Tue, 11 Dec 2012 22:43 GMT Source: reuters // Reuters By Andrew Longstreth NEW YORK, Dec 11 (Reuters) - A coalition of seven eastern states led by New York plans to sue the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency for failing to issue new guidelines to curb methane emissions, a greenhouse gas that may be linked to climate change. In a letter on Tuesday to EPA Administrator Lisa Jackson, the top law enforcement officials for the seven states said the agency should have addressed methane emissions when it revised emission control standards for the oil and gas sector in August. The seven states threatening litigation, which included Connecticut and Delaware, were among those that were most affected by Superstorm Sandy, which has renewed debate over the impact of climate change. The other states in the coalition include Maryland, Rhode Island, Vermont and Massachusetts. In their letter, the states said recent dramatic weather patterns were linked to methane emissions from the oil and gas sector. "From severe droughts and heat waves to a string of devastating storms in the northeast over the last two years, it is becoming ever more apparent that increasing greenhouse gas pollution contributes to climate disruption in the U.S. and around the globe," the state attorneys general wrote. The EPA said it would review the letter and respond . Last year, the EPA received comments about proposed rules for regulations of certain pollutants from the oil and gas sector. Those included comments form trade associations, public interest groups and major energy companies, including Chesapeake Energy Corp, Devon Energy Corp and Chevron Corp . In August, the EPA published its final rules. At the time, it said it would "continue to evaluate the appropriateness of regulating methane with an eye toward taking additional steps if appropriate." In their letter, the states argued that the EPA missed a deadline required by law to determine whether new regulations over methane are needed. "While it is clear that methane from oil and natural gas development contributes substantially to climate change pollution, regulators have failed to require the industry to use available and cost-effective measures to control these emissions," said New York Attorney General Eric Schneiderman, whose office is leading the coalition. The states said they are willing to explore solutions outside litigation, but said they would file a lawsuit in federal court if no resolution is reached. Some of the states preparing the lawsuit against the EPA were part of a failed effort to sue power companies to curb their emissions. Last year, the U.S. Supreme Court found that their claims that pollution from power companies created a public nuisance were "displaced" by the Clean Water Act and the EPA, which has authority to regulate emissions. The lawsuit, first filed in 2004, warned about the dangers that global warming posed to coastal areas in the United States. As severe flooding becomes more common, the lawsuit claimed, New York City, including its subway stations, airports and bridges "will experience more frequent and severe flooding from global warming-induced sea level rise, causing hundreds of billions of dollars in damages and wreaking havoc on the daily life of the City." trustDOTorg/alertnet/news/us-states-threaten-lawsuit-against-epa-over-regulations</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355578112241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 08:28:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355578392544-7</Id><Title>Celtic agrees to $3.1B ExxonMobil takeover</Title><Msg>Celtic agrees to $3.1B ExxonMobil takeover Calgary Herald-9 hours ago CALGARY — Shareholders in junior producer Celtic Exploration Ltd. have approved its sale to American giant ExxonMobil for $3.1 billion. The company ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355578392544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 08:33:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355589532933-8</Id><Topic><Title>Celtic agrees to $3.1B ExxonMobil takeover</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355578392544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 08:33:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you realize this was a friendly "buyout" that was 2 MONTHS AGO ??</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1355589532933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 11:38:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355591155698-9</Id><Topic><Title>Defensive Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355570164986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:16:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The premise that equity is a viable tool to accumulate wealth is where your error and the frustration from it lies. An example from the past, involving this very company, is helpful. At one time there were hundreds of small businesses involved in oil refining, and many hundreds more that sold candles, kerosene, waxes, lubricants, and other items related to petroleum. Standard Oil and a few other major corporations drove them all out of business. When the stock boosters calculate past returns on equities they count Standard Oil's returns, and do not count the returns from all the companies it ran out of business. That method of calculating return on business equity is not complete, and deliberately deceptive. Other examples include counting GM's stock gains during the 1920s and ignoring the massive losses suffered by the suppliers of horses, fodder for horses, and buggy whips, carriages and carts etc. The companies involved in those areas competing with the automobile, and the losses accruing to them from the changing technology, were not included in the equity returns recorded in the stock hucksters' sales material. They did not get counted simply because of the primitive state of Wall Street and the business organization of the economy. Today when the technology changes the losses will get counted in the equity averages... Gambling on a single stock is not investing either it is pure speculation. You should expect to lose, and lose big if the single stock does not measure up. It is to be expected that it will not to. Technology changes, and just because it has not caught up to the oil industry when prices were low and there was but a small profit motive pushing change does not mean it won't when conditions change. They have changed...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355591155698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:05:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355592950330-10</Id><Title>how much more demand destruction is possible or likely?</Title><Msg>Okay so the demand destruction for the consumer can go to zero in theory at least. The question is how much more demand will be lost in tough economic times? One has to keep in mind that the rest of the world that did not account for much growth in oil demand is starting to use more. It is entierly possible that oil demand goes flat and prices still climb. Its getting tougher and more costly to find and produce oil and even in flat demand prices will have to climb. Thats mid term. long term oil is going much higher.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1355592950330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 12:35:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355597276656-11</Id><Topic><Title>Defensive Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355570164986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:16:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its certainly true that no money has been made in stocks overall since 2000. They went from being underpriced in the 1970s and early 1980s to being so overpriced by 2000 that the value of stocks likely will be destroyed for another generation or more. Also the zero per cent interest rates allow companies to pay measly dividends (certain types of stocks pay more but overall stocks pay out less of their earnings to shareholders than ever) because of no competition from bonds. It has been noted that during the last 2 to 3 decades there has been an enormous transfer of wealth from shareholders to CEOs through stock options, low dividends, and various shenanigans like options backdating etc. Between stock manipulations ( mostly legal unfortunately) and the artificial zero percent rates (massive money printing, quantitative easing etc) and the completely phoney inflation numbers ( in real life it's true that no prices are rising EXCEPT food, gasoline, electric and gas bills, tuition, insurance, and that other non necessity- health care). Between all these factors people (those who have been responsible-or foolish enough-to try to save for their future) have been robbed of their savings on a scale unprecedented in human history.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355597276656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:47:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355597574847-12</Id><Title>Hillary Clinton Known Drunk</Title><Msg>passes out from too many margaritas, bangs head on a hard obstacle, and obtains concussion; and now doesn't have to testify about Benghazi. And the Demoncrap-controlled US Press covers for her as usual. Too many margarita symptons include dehydration, fainting, and stomach virus-like conditions. LOL! "Secretary of State Hillary Clinton fainted and hit her head, resulting in a concussion, the State Department said Saturday. The agency also said Clinton is recovering at home but did not say when the incident occurred. She purportedly fainted at State Department headquarters in Washington. Philippe Reines, the deputy assistant secretary of state, said Clinton was suffering from a stomach virus, became dehydrated and fainted."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355597574847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:52:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355599354256-13</Id><Topic><Title>Defensive Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1355570164986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 06:16:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The price level is too high in America which is the source of the trade deficit and unemployment rate. It is elevated because of speculators and their phony wealth, which has been built up through the various stock huckster schemes, real estate huckster schemes, and gold huckster schemes, and the wholesale theft of shareholder money through executive and employee options and enormous pension benefits since the mid-1990s. Economically speaking, it cannot go on this way. Something will give. Either wages will fall on their own accord under the pressure of the relentless outsourcing of jobs by corporations, thus lowering unemployment when they finally do fall enough, or the various bubbles will crash and bring down America price levels that way. In the meantime as more and more wealth accumulates at the top it is just hoarded and doesn't circulate, which is deflationary speeding wages downward. The Fed has said it will stop its pumping (buying bonds with money borrowed from commercial bank reserves) when unemployment does come down. No doubt they will do that, but by then equities will a ruin and the other manias will have run their course too. This always happens when central banks try to pump their way to prosperity. Commodities go up, stay up until the end of the pumping is in sight, and then crash... The one standout is the Reichsbank which actually did print money - as in real notes - to buy German government debt after World War I. It did not borrow from the German banks because the German banks did not have sufficient deposits - the money was withdrawn in cash to flee the Versailles Treaty (1919) and loaded on trains and sent to places such as Zurich for safe keeping, after being converted to dollars. Interest rates eventually climbed to several trillion percent on an annualized basis as this went on. The Fed's not that stupid, and has no such difficulties borrowing depositor's fund - it just buys bonds with other banks' money...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1355599354256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:22:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355600864348-14</Id><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Msg>Can we sacrafice HIM to a volcanoe or something? This is what that bloated freak said, Former Arkansas governor Mike Huckabee (R) weighed in on the massacre at an elementary school in Newtown, Conn. on Friday, saying the crime was no surprise because we have "systematically removed God" from public schools. "We ask why there is violence in our schools, but we have systematically removed God from our schools," Huckabee said on Fox News. "Should we be so surprised that schools would become a place of carnage?" This line of reasoning isn't new for Huckabee. Speaking about a mass shooting in Aurora, Colo. over the summer, the former GOP presidential candidate claimed that such violent episodes were a function of a nation suffering from the removal of religion from the public sphere. "We don't have a crime problem, a gun problem or even a violence problem. What we have is a sin problem," Huckabee said on Fox News. "And since we've ordered God out of our schools, and communities, the military and public conversations, you know we really shouldn't act so surprised ... when all hell breaks loose."</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355601350400-15</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Clinton Known Drunk</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355597574847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Invester the molester when you're done lying to yourself and the board the reality you will awaken to is that she is the NEXT President of The United States.. I think you'll be the drunk. Considering that we have a Black TWO TERM President now and in four years and a month we'll have a woman President.. It's kinda fun to watch you live your lie as you squeal, slither and shreak about them being "communists" and "liberals" even though both are extremely centrist if not slightly to the right in policy and politics.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355601350400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:55:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355602474158-16</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US is a nation suffering from the validation (via Fox news etc) of conservative mis-information.</Msg><Username>toxicdumber1</Username><Timestamp>1355602474158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 15:14:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355607213763-17</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I left the US about 18 months ago and I'm now living in a Country that has a national health care system and its illegal to own an automatic and semi-automatic weapon. I now know what real freedom is.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1355607213763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:33:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355607641371-18</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Clinton Known Drunk</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1355597574847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 13:52:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You say the DASOS is lying, but its actually you, and you know it. Americans seem now to be able to recognize lies from the right. 4 more years.</Msg><Username>mainst9</Username><Timestamp>1355607641371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 16:40:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355616350373-19</Id><Topic><Title>Huckabee States "Godless Schools" To Blame For Massacre</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355600864348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 14:47:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope you get shot by a thug, which ruptures one or more internal organs, and you have to wait months for a transplant, while living of a machine in the hospital. Have a nice life sucker for it will get ugly soon for you!</Msg><Username>rugers6</Username><Timestamp>1355616350373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:05:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355617588309-20</Id><Title>House GOP plans to put fuel standard on trial in next Congress</Title><Msg>House GOP plans to put fuel standard on trial in next Congress By Zack Colman - 12/15/12 04:13 PM ET House Republicans plan to put the renewable fuel standard on trial next Congress, a House Energy and Commerce Committee aide told The Hill. Committee staff is gearing up for hearings on the subject, citing recent concerns from the AAA motor club, automakers and the oil industry that the rule is pushing a high-ethanol fuel blend onto the market they say will damage cars. “If Congress observes the data, I think they will conclude we are putting the consumer at risk currently,” said AAA CEO Robert Darbelnet. He said his staff has been advised about potential hearings on the fuel standard and E15, the fuel blend comprised of 15 percent ethanol compared with the standard 10 percent. The biofuels industry has heard the war cries growing louder in recent weeks, and is prepared to do battle. “I say bring it on. We’re going to win this fight,” Renewable Fuels Association CEO Bob Dinneen told The Hill recently. The renewable fuel standard requires refiners to blend 36 billion gallons of ethanol into traditional transportation fuel by 2022. To meet accelerating blending targets, refiners will need to start pumping out fuels with higher ethanol concentrations. The biofuels industry will therefore increasingly rely on E15 fuel. Refiners are expected to break through that “blend wall” beginning in 2014, which worries AAA, automakers and oil-and-gas lobby shop the American Petroleum Institute (API). The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) determined earlier this year that cars could fill up with E15 with no adverse effects as long as they were made in the 2001 model-year or later. But AAA and the auto industry argue E15 fuel is dangerous for cars. They say EPA erred in only testing the fuel’s effects on emissions control systems, rather than the entire car. AAA, along with API, says it is concerned about consumers. Darbelnet noted 12 major manufacturers can or will void warranties for E15-related damage on cars made before the 2012 model years. “You can’t get around that. It’s not just one or two manufacturers. It’s all of them,” Darbelnet said. Darbelnet said EPA should suspend all E15 sales — it currently is sold at just a handful of gas stations — to work on a solution with automakers and fuel retailers. “If we’re focused on what we think should come out of the hearings, I see it as an opportunity to raise policymakers’ awareness about the concerns that have been made around E15,” he said. API recently changed its tack and is now calling for a full repeal of the fuel mandate. Bob Greco, API’s downstream group director, said he believes this year’s drought has incited more congressional opposition to the fuel mandate. Meat producers contend the mandate for corn ethanol production choked off supplies they needed for feed, driving up prices. The EPA ruled the drought — not the fuel rule — was responsible for the price increase. A potent opposition to E15 can be built from those lawmakers concerned about the feed vs. fuel issue, and those worried about the blend’s effects on cars, Greco said. “I think there’s going to be a lot of interest,” Greco told The Hill. “There’s a growing chorus.” Dinneen insisted any congressional hearings would exonerate the claims made against E15 and the fuel mandate. “Hearings on the RFS (renewable fuel standard) are not necessary, but should they proceed, we believe the hearings would shine a spotlight on the success of the RFS in terms of energy independence, job creation and environmental benefits. It would quickly become clear there is no need to legislate changes to the RFS which is working exactly as intended,” Dinneen said in a statement to The Hill. Dinneen has said the fuel is safe and will not damage cars, calling it the most tested fuel in EPA history. Sensing an upcoming assault on the fuel rule, the biofuels industry has rallied in recent months to defend the mandate. The industry says maintaining stability is vital for attracting investment in “advanced” biofuels made from non-edible feedstock, which are just now coming online in commercial volume. But groups like API are determined to tear it down. Greco said last month that API is “bringing our resources to bear” to repeal the mandate in the next Congress. Dinneen said that effort is designed to protect Big Oil’s market share. “Ultimately, this probably isn’t a fight about corn ethanol. Ultimately, this is a fight about the next generation [of biofuels]. The ethanol industry has become a tremendous success. We’ve become a victim of our own success because we’ve awakened the oil companies,” Dinneen said. Tom Buis, president of biofuels industry group Growth Energy, said the industry is “talking to everybody, and continually,” about the need to preserve the fuel mandate. Buis said the policy has helped boost rural economies, and that the next generation of biofuels is poised to do the same. He said lawmakers from farming states and districts would likely defend the standard. Still, with advanced biofuels starting to reach commercial production levels, Buis said he has made no mistake that the oil industry will take the offensive — and Capitol Hill could serve as the battleground. “Yeah it is a fight. They don’t want to give up their market share,” Buis said. “Of course we’re going to be ready. You prepare for the worst, and hope for the best.” thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/273047-house-gop-plans-to-put-fuel-standard-on-trial-in-next-congress</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355617588309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:26:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355618684959-21</Id><Topic><Title>House GOP plans to put fuel standard on trial in next Congress</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355617588309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:26:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The API and the oil industry should realize that biofuel mandates are there for a purpose. To protect the environment and American consumers from foreign oil. The oil industries market share will continue to erode and the API should also realize that E20 was tested at the very same time as E15. E20 is ready to be pumped! I assume Obama will mandate E20 no later than January 1, 2015. My opinion</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1355618684959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 19:44:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355621803594-22</Id><Title>The administration said running guns to Mexico was a good thing!</Title><Msg>Anybody remember Fast and Furious. Does Obama really mean what he says? Killing innocent victims in the drug wars in Mexico? What happen to common sense.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1355621803594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:36:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355621875639-23</Id><Title>FOX, CBS and ABC report a second gunman was led out of the woods near school</Title><Msg>CBS acknowledges removing report from their website. Do not let your kids see shrinks. 30 million kids strung out on tobacco.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1355621875639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:37:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355621914899-24</Id><Title>Great we are sending Arms to rebels to kill innocent victims and children</Title><Msg>Ok so what is the difference? NADA! Especially in Syria. There have been hundred of children killed in Syria since the US stirred up the hornets nest in Syria by support the warlords.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1355621914899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:38:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355621941521-25</Id><Topic><Title>The administration said running guns to Mexico was a good thing!</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1355621803594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:36:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you know that conservative lies are now easily recognized? Just your headline says you're a liar.</Msg><Username>mainst9</Username><Timestamp>1355621941521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:39:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355621966969-26</Id><Title>Sending F-16 to Egypt is such a good thing</Title><Msg>The object of the game is to have blood on your hands</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1355621966969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:39:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355622092100-27</Id><Title>Fast and Furious</Title><Msg>Since the innocent children did die with american handguns tied to holders fast and furious. So what is your point? The facts are there and you can't deny. Just look it up for once and you might learn something</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1355622092100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-15 20:41:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>