<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345523351000-1</Id><Topic><Title>A CALL FOR CARTER</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345299350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>....a stabilized banking system and low, but positive growth. Although private enterprise has the cash to spend, they are not, for unrelated reasons. What is relevant is that Libertarians are too stupid to see what is in front of them. You think zero because you aren't able to 1/ answer the question you have replied to, and 2/ your intellectual capabilities are zero.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345523351000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 00:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345524712000-2</Id><Title>Mitt Romney believes</Title><Msg>Gay men should be able to make out in front of elementary schools. He is for TARP, Stimulus, Romneycare, Gay Marriage,bailouts,open borders. The world's most free press in the world portrays our Democracy as holy. No wonder we have to spend trillions to force our brand democracy down the throats of third world nations. Blonde nineth graders with pierced tongues craving thier rapping classmates is not what Middle East nations construe as freedom. Porn on their childrens cell phones and a sixty percent divorce rate is what our trillion dollar a year defense budget is paying to export.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345524712000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 00:51:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345532161000-3</Id><Title>Todd Akin misspoke</Title><Msg>"I Misspoke—What I Meant To Say Is 'I Am Dumb As Dog $%*^ And I Am A Terrible Human Being'" theonion.com/articles/i-misspokewhat-i-meant-to-say-is-i-am-dumb-as-dog,29256/</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1345532161000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 02:56:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345533469000-4</Id><Title>Ryan Defended Stimulus When Bush Wanted It</Title><Msg>Total Hypocrisy he said you have to "SPEND" !! Fiscal Conservative what a lier !!! http://search.yahoo.com/search;_ylt=AvuPkvIwM1ZHD_7b45mxPcqbvZx4?p=paul+ryan+video+on+2002+feb+14&amp;toggle=1&amp;cop=mss&amp;ei=UTF-8&amp;fr=fptb-hpd03</Msg><Username>bankhouseone</Username><Timestamp>1345533469000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 03:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345538341000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Todd Akin's hatred or stupidity?</Title><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345433577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Akin takes ignorance to an entirely new frontier. Is it no surprise that the Tea Party-endorsed Akin, who, like vice-presidential candidate Paul Ryan, is opposed to abortion even in instances of rape.</Msg><Username>mainst9</Username><Timestamp>1345538341000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 04:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345542157000-6</Id><Title>Proof of treas</Title><Msg>Google "dishonorable disclosures" YouTube is not allowing this video or associated websites to be linked on YouTube. See now. Feel free to read the video information before watching. Thanks.</Msg><Username>mackgreene33</Username><Timestamp>1345542157000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 05:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345544077000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Proof of treas</Title><Username>mackgreene33</Username><Timestamp>1345542157000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 05:42:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's getting swift-boated is he?</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1345544077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 06:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345544796000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Proof of treas</Title><Username>mackgreene33</Username><Timestamp>1345542157000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 05:42:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another depiction of the lack of understanding from an Obama hater. Proof? It's hearsay.....and lies. "When the video discusses the supposed briefing Hollywood got days after the raid, Obama is shown speaking in a small theater to Tom Hanks, Steven Spielberg and others. The only problem is, that image was taken in March 2010 at the White House Family Theater before a screening of the HBO mini-series "The Pacific," The Hollywood Reporter points out. It's unlikely that Obama is spilling secrets about how he killed bin Laden--a whole year before it happened."</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345544796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 06:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345548485000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Proof of treas</Title><Username>mackgreene33</Username><Timestamp>1345542157000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 05:42:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba does not follow the Constitution which makes him a traitor. Nobumba was born in kenya and he is not qualified to be press. And 298 is a sewer rat commie traitor and will be deported soon.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345548485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 07:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345548584000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney believes</Title><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345524712000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 00:51:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>basha you are a commie c--t.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345548584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 07:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345548625000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Remember When Paul Ryan Shorted America?</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345521919000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 00:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STFU you commie POS nut job.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345548625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 07:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345548702000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats planning complete destruction of Iran civillian infrastructure</Title><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345479686000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:21:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And 298 is a commie sewer gutter rat traitor to america. You belong in a zoo with other animals.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1345548702000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 07:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345550426000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats planning complete destruction of Iran civillian infrastructure</Title><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345479686000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:21:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahleee seems to be into feminine things like kneee pads, lips and now duches. Maybe a new ticket sonce Ohoror is toast? How about the wahleee ticket. Platform supports 3rd world policies. GO OUT AND VOTE</Msg><Username>wahleee.duche</Username><Timestamp>1345550426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345550768000-14</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE REPUBLICAN MENTALITY IS IN LEADERSHIP!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345482381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:06:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.google.com/hostednews/ap/article/ALeqM5hkrEZ8h4bHIoz4CGF0M90un6I2Ig</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345550768000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:06:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345552771000-15</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE REPUBLICAN MENTALITY IS IN LEADERSHIP!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345482381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:06:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARE SOCIALISTS</Msg><Username>wahleee.duche</Username><Timestamp>1345552771000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:39:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345555647000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Happy for Exxon Mobil Corpo (NYSE: XOM) - I think we are in the Hole Stretch..</Title><Username>ramirezollie87</Username><Timestamp>1345553069000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:44:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Share market indices are grouped according to geography, company size and/or business sector. The indices are made up of individual component shares, which are averaged out into numerical readings determined by each separate share price; Kindly read documents carefully before investing- It’s a suggestion</Msg><Username>adan.mills57</Username><Timestamp>1345555647000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:27:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345557964000-17</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>Does this dog EVER go up ??????</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1345557964000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345559131000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Happy for Exxon Mobil Corpo (NYSE: XOM) - I think we are in the Hole Stretch..</Title><Username>ramirezollie87</Username><Timestamp>1345553069000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:44:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never missed a single article from you. Thank you and please keep it coming.</Msg><Username>deborah.beasley18</Username><Timestamp>1345559131000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345559335000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1345557964000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:06:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock now more than $25 below CVX before this management took over stock was always 20 to 25 points above CVX. Stock horrible performer last 4 years. Company has been run into the ground by Mr. Tillerson et al (absolutely horrible XTO acquisition, consistent earnings shortfalls, production shortfalls etc). Even XOM apologists must admit that this management is just terrible. Management will NEVER live down the moronic destructive XTO deal.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1345559335000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:28:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345560635000-20</Id><Title>Australia - $23-a-tonne carbon price, which started on July 1</Title><Msg>Al Gore praises Australia on climate change measures Date August 21, 2012 - 11:41AM The Gillard government's carbon price has already "inspired the world" to press ahead with measures to tackle climate change, former US vice-president Al Gore says. Labelling Australia one of the "canaries in the coalmine" for the effects of global warming, Mr Gore told a breakfast launch in Canberra of a new Climate Commission report there was much cause for optimism about global efforts to solve the problem. Speaking via video presentation, Mr Gore said that the Queensland floods and Black Saturday bushfires of recent years showed that "we must act now". "The consequences of the climate crisis, of course, are already visible all round the world, and some of the worst, unfortunately, can be seen in Australia over the last few years," Mr Gore said. "Australia is one of the proverbial canaries in the coalmine of the climate crisis. Just as that canary once warned of toxic gasses that build up in coalmines, Australia today is one of the places that is an early alert signal for the climate as a whole." But there were also encouraging signs that the world was beginning to act to solve the problem, he said. [b]The world's leading economies were taking steps to cut their emissions, with Australia prominent among them with the $23-a-tonne carbon price, which started on July 1.[/b] "This year in Australia, for the first time, in a move that has inspired the world - I hear it everywhere - carbon polluters are being held accountable for the global warming pollution they pour in the atmosphere every single day. "Policy actions like Australia's historic achievement are beginning to unlock innovative approaches to the climate crisis that will provide new sources of sustainable economic growth and good jobs while simultaneously solving the climate crisis. We're not there yet, but fortunately we are gaining momentum and we can solve this problem. "I salute Australia's strong commitment to solving the climate crisis and I know it's going to continue to be a crucial player in building a global solution to this global problem." The Climate Commission's report, The Critical Decade: International Action on Climate Change, seeks to counter the criticism at home that the Gillard government's carbon price is getting too far ahead of the rest of the world, making Australia economically vulnerable. It puts Australia around the middle of the pack when it comes to dealing with climate change. Ninety countries representing about 90 per cent of greenhouse gas emissions were taking some sort of action to cut emissions, the report says. http://www.smh.com.au/environment/climate-change/al-gore-praises-australia-on-climate-change-measures-20120821-24jmv.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345560635000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:50:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345560993000-21</Id><Title>EPA brief explains decision to reject industry challenge to biofuels rule</Title><Msg>EPA brief explains decision to reject industry challenge to biofuels rule By Zack Colman - 08/20/12 11:35 PM ET The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) filed a brief Monday explaining its decision to deny a petition that would have exempted refiners from part of a biofuel blending mandate. The documents filed Monday with the U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia reveal the reasoning behind EPA's move to shoot down the American Petroleum Institute’s (API) challenge of the renewable fuel standard (RFS). EPA determined that enough advanced biofuels — generally understood to be made from non-food products — existed to meet that portion of the RFS for 2012. “EPA reasonably considered the production capacity likely to be developed throughout the year, while API would have EPA rely narrowly and solely on proven past cellulosic biofuel production,” EPA said in its brief. “EPA reasoned that lowering the advanced biofuel volume in these circumstances would be inconsistent with EISA’s [the Energy Independence and Security Act of 2007] energy security and greenhouse gas reduction goals, and decided to leave the statutory advanced biofuel volume unchanged.” The EPA refused API's request to get out of the RFS in May, inflaming the oil industry group and its Republican allies, who have said the RFS props up an industry that would not otherwise exist. They say EPA requires refiners to blend cellulosic biofuels — those made from non-edible feedstocks, such as yard waste or switchgrass — even though no such biofuels are produced domestically at commercial scale. EPA's argument for sticking with the RFS target might also play into GOP complaints that the agency is taking an activist approach to regulating carbon emissions. API has charged in the past that EPA set an aspirational benchmark for cellulosic biofuels with the goal of creating a market, disregarding actual production capacity in the process. In lieu of blending actual gallons to meet that mark, API said that refiners were forced to purchase credits or import cellulosic biofuels to honor that obligation. The RFS requires refiners to blend 21 billion gallons of advanced biofuels into traditional transportation fuel by 2022. Of those 21 billion gallons, 16 billion must come from cellulosic biofuels. When Congress expanded the RFS through EISA, it predicted 2 billion gallons of advanced biofuels would be available in 2012. It said 500 million gallons of that would come from cellulosic biofuels. EPA revised the cellulosic target to 8.65 million gallons this year, but maintained in the court filing that enough other sources of advanced biofuels — such as Brazilian sugarcane ethanol and excess biodiesel — existed to satisfy the larger 2 billion gallon mark. “[B]ecause EPA estimates that one type of advanced biofuel will not be available in the quantity that Congress anticipated when setting the advanced biofuel applicable volume, EPA must determine whether other types of advanced biofuel will be available to satisfy that shortfall,” EPA wrote, adding that the agency “concluded that other advanced biofuels are likely to be available in sufficient volumes to meet the overall advanced biofuel requirements of the statute.” In its court filing, EPA said its estimates were based on a “reasonably attainable” amount of cellulosic biofuels for 2012. It argued that the fact it offers credits “means that obligated parties always have the means to comply with the cellulosic standard, and at a cost that is predictable.” http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/244463-epa-denies-challenge-to-biofuel-rule</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345560993000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345561112000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1345557964000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:06:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is the XOM plan for the future? They need to push a forward vision for shareholders that goes beyond the quarterly report. Buybacks and acquisitions do not seem to help us. How about restructuring? In the meantime, a competitive yield would be nice.</Msg><Username>jhenryallin</Username><Timestamp>1345561112000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345561480000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Happy for Exxon Mobil Corpo (NYSE: XOM) - I think we are in the Hole Stretch..</Title><Username>ramirezollie87</Username><Timestamp>1345553069000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:44:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone capable of buying 100k or more shares of probably wouldn't want to show off like you. Your point is well taken though.</Msg><Username>sylvia_sylvia67</Username><Timestamp>1345561480000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345561505000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo most excellent thing Since Sliced Bread..</Title><Username>eddy.price80</Username><Timestamp>1345558811000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds good to me.I will be sure to look into that.</Msg><Username>cole.coleman79</Username><Timestamp>1345561505000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345562277000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo most excellent thing Since Sliced Bread..</Title><Username>eddy.price80</Username><Timestamp>1345558811000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pumper. Lots of them on this board.</Msg><Username>jhenryallin</Username><Timestamp>1345562277000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345562447000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Defended Stimulus When Bush Wanted It</Title><Username>bankhouseone</Username><Timestamp>1345533469000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 03:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW !!! What a POS this guy will do anything to destroy the economy so they can win.</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1345562447000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:20:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345563183000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Defended Stimulus When Bush Wanted It</Title><Username>bankhouseone</Username><Timestamp>1345533469000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 03:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was #$%$ Ryan voting against Bush and Cheney when they doubled welfare spending in their first four years in the White House? Be sure the majority of GOP filth in the House and Senate were eager to double off of the Clinton highs the amount of social spending in the United States. These open border maggots cannot wait to bill middle class taxpayers for more trillion dollar wars the neo con Trotskyite paymasters on Wall Street order up. Dollar devaluation is a Republicans favorite tax.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345563183000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:33:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345563507000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Happy for Exxon Mobil Corpo (NYSE: XOM) - I think we are in the Hole Stretch..</Title><Username>ramirezollie87</Username><Timestamp>1345553069000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:44:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another good news, it's no possible to continue to come down</Msg><Username>wendy.weiss99</Username><Timestamp>1345563507000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345565479000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Happy for Exxon Mobil Corpo (NYSE: XOM) - I think we are in the Hole Stretch..</Title><Username>ramirezollie87</Username><Timestamp>1345553069000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:44:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am staying.And a least 95% (probably a lot more) customers will.It is a hassle to switch.</Msg><Username>kim.sloan60</Username><Timestamp>1345565479000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:11:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345567419000-30</Id><Title>SOUNDS LIKE REPUBLICANS!</Title><Msg>http://www.abc15.com//dpp/news/region_phoenix_metro/central_phoenix/valley-woman-told-she-could-not-hand-out-free-bottled-water-in-summer-heat</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345567419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345568954000-31</Id><Title>Court strikes down EPA air pollution rule</Title><Msg>Court strikes down EPA air pollution rule The court says the rule 'stands on an unsound foundation' and the agency went too far. | AP Photo Close By ERICA MARTINSON | 8/21/12 12:01 PM EDT In a rebuke to the Obama administration, a federal court took a hammer Tuesday to a controversial EPA regulation aimed at forcing states to be “good neighbors” on air pollution. The U.S. Court of Appeals for the D.C. Circuit said Tuesday that the EPA’s Cross-State Air Pollution Rule overstepped the boundaries laid out by Congress. Power companies, coal companies, labor unions, trade associations and state and local governments had challenged the rule, which EPA finalized in August 2011. “To put it colloquially, the good neighbor provision requires upwind states to bear responsibility for their fair share of the mess in downwind states,” the 2-1 opinion of the three-judge panel says, noting EPA’s critical role in determining what that fair share is. But the agency went too far, the court decided, and the rule “stands on an unsound foundation” by requiring steep pollution cuts from states beyond what they actually contribute to other states’ air quality problems. EPA also took too much federal control when it simultaneously set “federal implementation plans” for states, telling them how and where to make pollution cuts to meet air emission limits, the ruling says. The court struck down those plans, saying they were based on “rickety statutory logic” and that EPA’s argument that it could do both at once was “extraordinarily unpersuasive.” The agency’s approach upended the process and placed the “federal government firmly in the driver’s seat at both steps,” the court said. Judge Judith Rogers strongly disagreed with Judges Brett Kavanaugh and Thomas Griffith, saying in a 44-page dissent that the ruling will result in “a redesign of Congress’s vision of cooperative federalism between the States and the federal government in implementing the [Clean Air Act] based on the court’s own notions of absurdity and logic that are unsupported by a factual record,” among other problems. She said the decision represents “a trampling on this court’s precedent on which the [EPA] was entitled to rely … rather than be blindsided by arguments raised for the first time in this court.” John Walke, senior attorney and director of the Natural Resources Defense Council's Clean Air Program, said the majority of the court "got the precedent badly wrong." He said the group will urge the Obama administration to appeal based on the statements in Rogers’s dissent. The Bush administration’s “Clean Air Interstate Rule” — a predecessor to the cross-state rule that the court struck down in 2008 for not requiring enough of some states — will remain in effect while the EPA goes back to the drawing board, the court decided. http://www.politico.com/news/stories/0812/79940.html?hp=r5</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345568954000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345570780000-32</Id><Title>EPA seeks input on ethanol mandate waiver requests</Title><Msg>EPA seeks input on ethanol mandate waiver requests WASHINGTON | Tue Aug 21, 2012 4:40am IST (Reuters) - The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency on Monday said it has begun weighing requests to suspend the U.S. ethanol mandate, which requires refiners to blend ethanol into gasoline, and is seeking public feedback. The governors of North Carolina and Arkansas asked the agency last week to temporarily waive the U.S. quota on ethanol made from corn, because the worst drought in 50 years has driven corn prices higher and hurt livestock producers who depend on the grain for feed. The EPA asked on Monday for public comment on the need for an ethanol waiver. The 30-day comment period will begin once the notice is published in the Federal Register. "This notice is in keeping with EPA's commitment to an open and transparent process to evaluate requests the agency receives under the Clean Air Act, and does not indicate any predisposition to a specific decision," agency spokeswoman Alisha Johnson said in a statement. By law the agency has until November 13 to make a decision on the waivers, meaning EPA could act on the requests after national elections on November 6. Aimed at reducing U.S. reliance on foreign oil, the Renewable Fuels Standard, or RFS, would require 13.2 billion gallons of ethanol to be made from corn this year. The EPA is seeking input on whether the RFS would severely hurt the economies of Arkansas, North Carolina or any other part of the United States and what effect a waiver would have on ethanol demand and corn prices. The agency is also asking, if a waiver is needed, how much should the mandate be eased and when should it apply. A petition by Texas Governor Rick Perry in 2008 was rejected when the agency said waiver requests had to show the mandate itself was severely harming a region's economy and not just contributing to economic damage. U.S. livestock groups have argued that complying with the mandate at a time of historic national drought is causing major economic harm to meat and dairy producers. It is unclear that a waiver would weaken corn prices. Refiners will likely continue buying almost as much ethanol even without the mandate since they use it as an additive to make cleaner-burning fuel required in much of the country. Ethanol industry groups say the mandate offers some flexibility for fuel blenders responsible for complying with the RFS, including the ability to buy bankable credits if blenders cannot buy enough physical ethanol to meet requirements. http://in.reuters.com/article/2012/08/20/us-usa-ethanol-epa-idINBRE87J0S720120820</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345570780000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:39:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345573556000-33</Id><Title>SPEAKING of REALITY!</Title><Msg>http://www.nytimes.com/2012/08/21/opinion/wikileaks-and-the-global-future-of-free-speech.html?_r=1&amp;nl=opinion&amp;emc=tya2_20120821&amp;pagewanted=print</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345573556000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 14:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345574801000-34</Id><Topic><Title>SPEAKING of REALITY!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345573556000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 14:25:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-19311098</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345574801000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 14:46:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345576406000-35</Id><Topic><Title>SPEAKING of REALITY!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345573556000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 14:25:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't like either one of those stories...WTF. I think that XOM should pay a bigger dividend. Look at WHZ...they pay $0.89 Q dividend. Why if XOM makes so many Billions of dollars every Q, don't they give more to share holders? Instead of paying workers (CEO) so much..pay them in shares of stock that pay a 12% Q dividend. If you want you can vote me in as CEO, or NOT...back to our story.</Msg><Username>doctorevilstwin</Username><Timestamp>1345576406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345576602000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1345557964000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:06:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Down sixty cents at 3:15 Eastern. Where are all the pumpers???</Msg><Username>jhenryallin</Username><Timestamp>1345576602000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:16:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345579028000-37</Id><Topic><Title>SPEAKING of REALITY!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345573556000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 14:25:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Michael Moore and Oliver Stone. What a joke. If they were making films in Ecuador, Correa would probably throw them in jail where they belong anyway.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345579028000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345583210000-38</Id><Topic><Title>SOUNDS LIKE REPUBLICANS!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345567419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://thecaucus.blogs.nytimes.com/2012/08/21/g-o-p-approves-strict-anti-abortion-language-in-party-platform/#postComment</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345583210000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345585012000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Worth $500Mil Pays A Lousy $3 Mil in Taxes</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1345582836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He should be legitimately raped.</Msg><Username>bonus_stick</Username><Timestamp>1345585012000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345589441000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Worth $500Mil Pays A Lousy $3 Mil in Taxes</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1345582836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tax code was written by your Democrat political heroes. It is enforced by your Democrat political heroes. Efforts to change to a "fair" systeme have been rebuked by your Democrat political heroes, most of whom are very wealthy or, have you not noticed. It would be good of you to focus your attention in a direction where it might matter.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345589441000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345589632000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Akin Represents GOP Position On Women</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1345582544000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:55:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a uneducated pup.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345589632000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345591066000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1345557964000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:06:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trade it between $80 and $88 and make your money off the churn with other shareholders. Don't look for XOM management to treat their shareholders like anything better than GARBAGE. They're too busy sucking at the teets of the buy-back pool.</Msg><Username>tsobie</Username><Timestamp>1345591066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345592218000-43</Id><Title>Romney to lay out *comprehensive energy plan*</Title><Msg>Romney to lay out 'comprehensive energy plan' By Ben Geman - 08/21/12 04:46 PM ET Mitt Romney plans to roll out an energy policy blueprint on Thursday, according to published reports. The presumptive GOP White House nominee signaled his plans at a Houston, Texas, fundraiser on Tuesday, according to The Washington Post. “We will be, I believe before the end of this week, in New Mexico describing a comprehensive energy plan, particularly as it relates to fossil-based fuels,” he said. “I know that we have members of the media here right now, so I’m not going to go through that in great detail so I can save a bit of that until a little later in the week. But your input is something I wanted to retain before we actually cross the Ts and dot the Is on those policies,” he told donors. Romney is slated to campaign in New Mexico on Thursday, Reuters notes. Energy is already playing a prominent role in the presidential race. President Obama has been taking aim at Romney’s opposition to extending tax credits that help finance wind energy projects, while Romney used an Ohio campaign stop last week to allege Obama is hostile to coal and oil-and-gas. Romney has already described several aspects of his energy proposals. He has vowed to approve the Keystone XL oil sands pipeline, and seek a major expansion of oil-and-gas leasing on federal lands and waters — including Pacific and Atlantic Coast waters that remain off-limits under Obama. Romney backs opening the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge to drilling, which would take Capitol Hill approval, and has called for fast-track permitting for energy projects. Elsewhere, he has attacked Environmental Protection Agency regulations, including rules that force cuts in mercury and other air toxics from coal-fired power plants, alleging it's too costly, and wants to strip EPA’s power to regulate greenhouse gas emissions. Romney, according to his website, supports federally backed R&amp;D into alternative energy, but opposes efforts such as loan guarantees that are aimed at commercializing specific technologies. “There is a place for government investment when time horizons are too long, risks too high, and rewards too uncertain to attract private capital. However, much of our existing energy R&amp;D budget has been devoted to loan guarantees, cash grants and tax incentives for projects that might have gone forward anyway. As president, Mitt Romney will redirect clean energy spending towards basic research,” his platform states. http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/244627-romney-to-lay-out-energy-plans</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345592218000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:36:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345592439000-44</Id><Title>Dems want Obama to appeal ruling that nixed emissions rule</Title><Msg>Dems want Obama to appeal ruling that nixed emissions rule By Ben Geman - 08/21/12 02:03 PM ET A pair of senior Capitol Hill Democrats is urging the Obama administration to appeal a Tuesday federal court ruling that struck down a major rule to cut power plant pollution. But other lawmakers applauded the appellate decision to vacate Environmental Protection Agency’s Cross-State Air Pollution Rule, underscoring political divides over the White House's green agenda. “I encourage the Administration to appeal the decision. In the meantime, as Chairman of the Clean Air and Nuclear Safety Subcommittee in the Senate, I will be working with this Administration, the impacted states and my colleagues to ensure we find a swift solution to ensure all states do their fair share to clean up our air if that appeal is not successful,” said Sen. Tom Carper (D-Del.) in a statement. Rep. Edward Markey (D-Mass.), a senior member of the House Energy and Commerce Committee, similarly urged the administration to “appeal this misguided decision by the courts so that Massachusetts and other states impacted by harmful emissions from old, polluting coal plants can clean up their air.” The U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit, in a 2-1 decision released Tuesday, sent EPA back to the drawing board on the rule to curb soot- and smog-forming pollution from more than two dozen states in the eastern half of the country. Environmentalists say the rule provides vital public health protections, while critics call the measure too aggressive, alleging it will impose economic burdens. Sen. Rand Paul (R-Ky.), who sponsored an unsuccessful resolution to overturn the regulation, cheered the court decision. “I will continue to use the resources at my disposal to fight against an out-of-control EPA overreach into the rights of states and the lives of citizens,” he said in a statement. Sen. James Inhofe (R-Okla.), the top Republican on the Environment and Public Works Committee, also called the decision good news, and alleged EPA has an “extremist agenda.” “I am pleased that the courts have reined in EPA on this illegal, flawed rule,” he said in a statement. “With [the Cross-State Air Pollution Rule], EPA moved too far too fast, setting unrealistic deadlines for states to meet its stringent requirements.” http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/244577-dems-to-obama-appeal-ruling-that-nixed-emissions-rule</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345592439000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345593454000-45</Id><Title>Poet Using Agrivida Technolgy to Turn Corn Waste Into Fuel</Title><Msg>Poet Using Agrivida Technolgy to Turn Corn Waste Into Fuel By Andrew Herndon - Aug 21, 2012 1:35 PM MT 0 Comments Poet LLC, the largest U.S. producer of corn-based ethanol, will use technology from Agrivida Inc. to develop processes to turn crop waste into biofuel. Poet, based in Sioux Falls, South Dakota, is seeking to implement Agrivida’s systems for processing corn stover, the stalks and leaves that remain after the crop is harvested, in its existing cellulosic ethanol process, according to a statement today. Poet has operated a cellulosic ethanol pilot plant since 2008 and its first commercial facility is expected to begin production next year in Iowa. The Agrivida technology may reduce the cost of converting plants into fuel, Wade Robey, chief technology officer for closely held Poet, said in the statement. “If successful, Agrivida’s novel approach to increase the functionality and value delivery of corn stover will work well with other technologies being developed by Poet,” he said. Agrivida is developing seeds that make plants easier to break down than traditional crops and systems to convert them into fermentable sugars, according to the company’s website. Poet’s cellulosic technology may be used to produce as much as 1 billion gallons (3.8 billion liters) of ethanol a year if deployed at all of its 27 corn-based biofuel plants, according to the statement. An estimated 160 million to 250 million dry tons of corn stover is available each year for processing, Medford, Massachusetts-based Agrivida said. That’s enough to produce as much as 25 billion gallons of cellulosic biofuels or chemicals. http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-08-21/poet-using-agrivida-technolgy-to-turn-corn-wast-into-fuel.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345593454000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345593998000-46</Id><Title>E15 Sold at Second Retail Station in Kansas</Title><Msg>E15 Sold at Second Retail Station in Kansas By Renewable Fuels Association | August 21, 2012 The sale of E15 fuel has expanded to Ottawa, Kan., at the Zarco 66 station located at 2518 east Logan. This is the second retail gas station to offer E15 in the United States. A grand opening promotion will be announced soon. On June 8 the U.S. EPA gave final approval for the sale and use of E15 ethanol blends in light duty vehicles made since 2001. Late last week, the U.S. Appeals Court for the District of Columbia Circuit sided with the EPA and its partial waiver approval for E15 in a 2-1 decision. Zarco 66 was the first retail station to offer E15 on July 10 in Lawrence, Kan., with the help from the Kansas Corn Commission and local ethanol producer East Kansas Agri-Energy. “We are excited to add a high octane renewable fuel choice for our customers on the go in Ottawa, Kansas as we will continue to reduce our dependency on foreign oil through the use of renewable energy sources,” said Scott Zaremba, owner of Zarco 66 stations. America’s growing use of domestically-produced ethanol reduced wholesale gasoline prices by a national average of $1.09 per gallon in 2011, according to an updated study authored by professors at the University of Wisconsin and Iowa State University. Specifically in the Midwest, savings were $1.69 per gallon. “American consumers are looking for a choice when it comes to fueling their vehicles, and they now have one more domestic, renewable fuel option with E15 becoming more commercially available,” said RFA President and CEO Bob Dinneen. “Ethanol continues to help consumers during these difficult economic times by lowering prices at the pump and supporting more than 400,000 jobs across the country that can’t be outsourced.” The RFA is working diligently with the petroleum industry, gas retailers, automakers, and consumers to ensure E15 is used properly. E15 remains the most tested fuel ever approved by EPA and is perfectly safe and effective for approved engines. The Department of Energy conducted six million miles of testing on E15—the equivalent of 12 round trips to the Moon—and found no issues. In order to offer E15 under the waiver conditions set by EPA, producers and retailers must register with EPA and adhere to the misfueling mitigation plan developed by the RFA and approved by EPA. That plan is available here. In addition, the RFA has also developed an E15 Retailer Handbook available at no cost to retailers looking to offer more choices to their customers. The handbook is available here. Petroleum marketers and station owners can find more information on E15, blender pumps and incentives by visiting the BYO Ethanol Campaign's website at http://www.ethanolproducer.com/articles/9050/e15-sold-at-second-retail-station-in-kansas</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345593998000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345594480000-47</Id><Title>U.S. Department of Agriculture gives Sampson County biofuels plant the go-ahead</Title><Msg>U.S. Department of Agriculture gives Sampson County biofuels plant the go-ahead Published: 07:07 PM, Tue Aug 21, 2012 U.S. Department of Agriculture gives Sampson County biofuels plant the go-ahead By John Ramsey Staff writer A company planning a $170 million biofuel refinery in Sampson County will clear its last hurdle before construction today when the U.S. Department of Agriculture announces a federal government guarantee for financing the project. Chemtex, an international engineering company with offices in Wilmington, plans to use its new technology to convert grasses and other plants into 20 million gallons of ethanol a year starting in 2014. Secretary of Agriculture Tom Vilsack said the refinery, to be built near Clinton, will provide a new stream of income for farmers, add jobs to a rural community and reduce dependence on foreign oil. And the new technology, which relies on inedible grasses such as miscanthus and switchgrass, won't compete with the food supply, a common criticism of corn-based ethanol. Vilsack said the new technology gives the Chemtex facility a better chance to succeed than two previous corn ethanol facilities that failed in the region. "It takes a lot less energy to grow these grasses than it does corn," Vilsack said in a telephone interview. "We think there's great energy potential. This biorefinery is going to help us learn more about how to produce it." The USDA is expected to announce this morning its guarantee of $99 million in loans for Chemtex, which company executives say will pave the way for getting loan applications approved. The planned refinery will employ 65 people with average salaries expected to exceed $48,000 a year. It is expected to create 250 indirect jobs for suppliers, maintenance workers and drivers to transport the crops from the fields to the refinery. The Sampson County facility will be the first in the nation to use a new Chemtex process that essentially blasts the grasses with steam to expose their sugars. The sugars are then fermented into ethanol. Chemtex officials say the refinery will be a sort of proving ground to demonstrate the technology in the United States. A similar Chemtex plant in Italy is scheduled to open later this year. The USDA previously approved $4 million through its Biomass Crop Assistance Program for 4,000 acres of miscanthus and switchgrass in 11 southeastern North Carolina counties. The program will pay farmers up to three-quarters of the establishment costs along with five years of rent payments. The deadline for farmers to sign up for the program is Sept. 14. Chemtex will need between 20,000 and 30,000 acres of energy crops. It has soft commitments for about half of its needs. Chemtex is asking farmers to consider planting on marginal lands that are not good for planting corn or soybeans. But a major part of the acreage likely will be hog waste spray fields. The Biofuels Center of N.C., which has a goal to replace 10 percent of the state's fuel imports by having 600 million gallons of renewable liquid fuels produced in the state, has identified 100,000 acres of spray fields in Sampson, Duplin and Wayne counties that could potentially be used for biocrops. http://fayobserver.com/articles/2012/08/21/1198392?sac=fo.business</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345594480000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345594491000-48</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Department of Agriculture gives Sampson County biofuels plant the go-ahead</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345594480000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:14:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>State environmental workers are still studying how to plant the crops in spray fields in a way that complies with waste regulations. The USDA says the grasses may make the spray fields more environmentally effective than the typical Bermuda grass currently planted there. The USDA loan guarantee is part of a program that has funded eight other refineries in the U.S. that are creating fuel from products such as solid waste, algae and agricultural residue. Vilsack said the program is another step in a long line of government partnerships with new industries to help them get started. He compared it to the interstate highway system being built to support a budding car industry. He said the U.S. in the past three years has gone from importing 62 percent of its oil to importing 45 percent. Vilsack said the Department of Defense, especially the Navy, is looking closely at new technologies to help it reduce dependence on foreign oil. Chemtex documents say North Carolina has enough available land to support as many as 15 refineries, which could mean 5,000 new jobs and a $2 billion boost to the state's economy. Chemtex, which counts Toyota among its partners on the project, has an agreement with Gulf Oil to buy all of the ethanol it produces in Sampson County.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345594491000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345594756000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Poet Using Agrivida Technolgy to Turn Corn Waste Into Fuel</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345593454000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:57:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, that story reads like an old Cold Fusion story: "...may reduce the cost of...", "If successful....", "...may be used to produce as much as....", "...if deployed in all 27 corn based...". This isn't a story, it's an advertisement that seeks to plow the ground for a big DOE grant. Wanna bet? None of this points to the fact that the corn being developed and grown is not for human or animal consumption. Food resources are being diverted away from food production. Using the stalks to add efficiency (if it works as advertised), does not negate the fact that you are utilizing an ineffecient oxygenate that will add more to pollution (full cycle) than available atlernatives. All while immorally depriving the world of food and driving up the price of food. Yep, it's subsidized by the tax payer too. Just plain stupid.</Msg><Username>ontogeny2phylogoney</Username><Timestamp>1345594756000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345595022000-50</Id><Topic><Title>Akin Represents GOP Position On Women</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1345582544000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:55:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're filth raul.</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1345595022000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345595339000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Worth $500Mil Pays A Lousy $3 Mil in Taxes</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1345582836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you intentionally choosing to mix apples and oranges in an attempt to mislead folks? The US system does not tax based on worth but on earnings. Much better analysis (but can't easily be done) would be to calculate lifetime fed taxes/lifetime earnings for Romney and the typical citizen. The fact that Romney is not making much income now means he is (relative to what he used to) paying a lower rate. But how much was he paying when he was earning tht 500 million in worth? I bet his lifetime tax/earnings is much greater than the typcial American's. Typical wallboard, never afraid to ignore realities and make a judgement based on a slanted basis.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1345595339000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345595359000-52</Id><Topic><Title>A CALL FOR CARTER</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345299350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think about the people who were living in their own, modest, paid for homes before the smooth tongued three card Marney man came to visit, and now the family lives under a piece of plastic under the bridge! Reality time~ We have all been playing three card Marney with the slicks, and just like the homeless, We didn't know what the game was! Most still don't, it isn't general reckoning time yet!</Msg><Username>donny_d_drivle</Username><Timestamp>1345595359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345598702000-53</Id><Title>the good ole angry left...</Title><Msg>.....</Msg><Username>obummerbgone</Username><Timestamp>1345598702000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345599053000-54</Id><Title>Obammy---get yo hands out my pockets gay boy</Title><Msg>......</Msg><Username>obummerbgone</Username><Timestamp>1345599053000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:30:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345599818000-55</Id><Topic><Title>ONE TERM CHIMPANZEE</Title><Username>naplesfl_luxury_penthouse</Username><Timestamp>1341964880000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-10 20:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These color-driven anti-Obamas are everywhere.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345599818000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345602309000-56</Id><Title>GOP covering up Fast &amp; Furious</Title><Msg>A high ranking Mexican drug cartel operative alleges that the US Government's Fast and Furious gun operation was not about tracking guns but rather about supplying them to a drug cartel-and in much larger numbers than Attorney General Eric Holder has admitted-in return for the violent gang's help in wiping out rival drug runners. Jesus Vincente Zimbada-Niebla was the logistics coordinator for the powerful Sinaola Cartel. He has been quietly held in various US prisons since before the fast and furious story broke. Zimbada-Niebla claims that the US helped finance and arm the Sinaola Cartel through Fast and Furious in exchange for information that allowed the DEA, ICE and other US agencies to take down rival drug cartels. The Sinaola Cartel was thus given a monopoly and permitted to traffic massive amounts of drugs across the US border from 2004 to 2009. With the evidence and testimony provided from the ongoing Congressional investigation into Fast and Furious, it is now apparent that the criminal activity continued for more than two years after the 2009 date claim of Zimbada-Niebla's first hand knowledge. In a motion for discovery filed in federal court in July of 2011, Zambada-Niebla claims: "The Sinaola Cartel, under the leadership of the defendant's father Ismael Zambada and Chapo Guzman, received carte blanche to continue to smuggle tons of illicit narcotics into Chicago and the rest of the United States in exchange and was also protected by the US government from arrest and prosecution in return for providing information about rival cartels, which helped Mexican and US authorities capture or kill thousands of rival cartel members. His trial is scheduled for Oct 9, and look for Issa and FOX News to facilitate a bipartisan cover up of the CIA managed drug war.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345602309000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345602384000-57</Id><Topic><Title>Poet Using Agrivida Technolgy to Turn Corn Waste Into Fuel</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345593454000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:57:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.aei.org/article/energy-and-the-environment/alternative-energy/biofuels/ethanols-a-big-scam-and-bush-has-fallen-for-it/</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1345602384000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345602452000-58</Id><Topic><Title>Poet Using Agrivida Technolgy to Turn Corn Waste Into Fuel</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345593454000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:57:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://money.cnn.com/2008/03/05/news/bush_ethanol/index.htm</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1345602452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345602612000-59</Id><Topic><Title>A CALL FOR CARTER</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345299350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VOTE THIS DUDE OUT BEFORE ITS TOO LATE....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1345602612000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345603067000-60</Id><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Msg>Higher taxes on the wealthy, if they are imposed in 2013, will be passed downward by reductions in wages and firings. The lack of pricing power in the poor economy makes it unlikely the pass through would be to prices. Lower wages will mean lower demand for oil, food, and many other consumer staples. This will be bad for the stock market in generally. The silver lining is the reduction in consumption will increase the national savings rate, relieving the wealthy of the burden of funding the deficit with bond purchases - instead the monies will find their way to automation and new technologies, which will quicken the pace of firings, and wage reductions mentioned above.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345603364000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Akin Represents GOP Position On Women</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1345582544000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:55:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's way too generous.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345603364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345603489000-62</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The people will demand this: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Basic_income_guarantee</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1345603489000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345603779000-63</Id><Topic><Title>GOP covering up Fast &amp; Furious</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345602309000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are FOS..................</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1345603779000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345604023000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Higher taxes on the wealthy, if they are imposed in 2013, will be passed downward by reductions in wages and firings." You wish. The burden of tax by the wealthy when their tax rates are reinstated will still be less than the comparison. Hence, any firings will just reduce the production of their wealth, and reduced wages will cause production-affecting disputes, as shown many times before. Firings and reduced wages come when the total production/wealth per se is significantly reduced, not the % subtraction of the upper component of net wealth.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345604023000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:53:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345604913000-65</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tax incidence is determined by the price elasticity of demand and supply. "less than comparison" has nothing to do with anything as tax incidence is not determined by inter-termporal relations or relations mutually exclusive to the demand/supply relationship and the elasticity factors therein. There are thousands of goods and services in the economy, and many thousands more contractual relations with unique elasticity relations. All that is required to make the buyer of products pay taxes and any increase is purely elastic supply, or for most supply that is more elastic that demand. To pass taxes into lower wages all that is required is purely elastic demand for labor, or demand that is more elastic than the supply of labor. The "wealthy" have all the powers of capital, technology, and mobility of the same, making their ability to shift taxes to consumers and worker only increase over time. What's worse for workers and consumers, if the current economic arrangement results in the wealthy paying a tax they will notice it and tax measures to stop doing so in the future... Some wealthy will no doubt pay, but it will be tiny and falling fraction of the whole...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345604913000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345605211000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All that processing and nothing useful coming out. Please provide solutions, not ceaseless loops of despair.</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1345605211000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345605864000-67</Id><Title>The Murder of 12 yr old Mary Phagan</Title><Msg>The Leo Frank Case Murder in Georgia - 1913 http://72.52.208.92/~gbpprorg/judicial-inc/MiscPics.htm Leo Frank was a bisexual pedophile, and a suspected drug addict, who managed a pencil factory in Atlanta via 1913. One day he demanded sex from a 12 yr. old employee named Mary Phagan, she refused, so then he brutally raped and murdered her. Frank, and a handyman, drag the body to the basement where they were going to burn it in the factory furnace the next day. That night, a watchman finds the body - calls the police - Franks is arrested - found guilty and sentenced to hang. The governor commutes the sentence, and Marietta finest families broke into jail and lynched him This incident lead to the creation of ADL in 1913. Today the Je_wish community hails Leo Franks as a innocent martyr, a victim of anti-Semitism. The Victim Mary Phagan, a 12 yr. old girl who was an employee of the National Pencil Factory, in Atlanta.. The Murderer Leo Frank was a New York, Cornell-educated J_ew, who was living in Atlanta. Leo was President of his local B'nai B'rith, active in civic affairs, a local socialite, and Phagan's supervisor at the National Pencil Factory. Frank was sexual pervert, who was homosexual,and preyed on young girls. He forced employees to have sex with him. The Witness James Conley worked at the pencil factory as a sweeper and handyman, and walked in on the murder.</Msg><Username>vida_blue_50</Username><Timestamp>1345605864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345605892000-68</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to think there is a way that the income of the "wealthy" can be redistributed. This is a pipe dream. The most you will ever be able to redistribute is what income the wealthy are too lazy to take counter-measures to avoid having redistributed, or a few instances of unique goods/services where the supply cannot be made to be elastic because of some insurmountable technical barrier. Those instance represent a tiny minority of the universe of economic relations. Further, most wealth in the economy is earned by producing a good or service, so trying to tax "unearned wealth" to transfer income is not going to work for long, and in that case tax incidence works for investments too, and taxes are passed into the cost of capital... You would do well to stop trying to define happiness by something you will never acquire. In times past people looked to the study of the scriptures for happiness if they could not acquire wealth. There is also the option of actually doing something useful that can earn wealth: in this day and age becoming a corporate manager is probably your best bet...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345605892000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:24:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345606159000-69</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you're saying that when employers wealth is threatened, they attempt to retain their wealth by reducing the inferior wealth of employees even further. There are protections from assessing employees as a commodity, In the absence of these safeguards, unproductive disputes ensue. It would be one stupid executive that would think that reduce productivity, and hence profits, through firings or reduced wages to retain a further portion of profits to supplement a personal tax increase.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345606159000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345606308000-70</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad, you have a blind spot. Best of luck to you. http://www.usbig.net/papers.php</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1345606308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:31:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345606668000-71</Id><Title>Nathan Levi Bar-Jonah-A Real Life Hannibal Lechter</Title><Msg>http://blockyourid.com/~gbpprorg/judicial-inc/a_Nathan_bar_jonah.htm A Cannibal That Ate Children Nathan killed, butchered, and ate his victims. He started in 1974, and was finally stopped in 2002. Nathan Starts In 1974, When He Was 17 Years-Old In 1974, Nathan pleads guilty to impersonating a policeman and assaulting an eight-year-old boy, for which he received one year of probation. This was the first time he was caught, but most suspect he was on the prowl since puberty. Nathan Attacks Two Boys In 1977 In 1977, Nathan kidnapped and choked two boys. He was convicted of attempted murder, and was sentenced to 20 years in prison. What did he do for the three years since his last arrest? A Zi_onist Psychiatrist Puts Him In A Mental Hospital Nathaniel Levi Bar-Jonah said he had fantasies involving murder and cannibalism, and he was transferred to the Bridgewater State Hospital for Sexual Predators. He was released in 1991. Another Assault Then on August 9th, 1991, Mr. Bar-Jonah is arrested for battery on a 7-year-old boy, during an incident outside an Oxford post office. He is sentenced to two years probation, on the condition he move to Montana with his mother. Moves To Montana In 1991 He moved to Great Falls in August 1991, to serve out a two-year sentence of probation. December 18, 1993 Bar-Jonah molests an 8-year-old boy he is babysitting in Great Falls, Montana. He is charged, but the case is later dropped when the mother refuses to let the boy testify. Feburary 6, 1996 Ten-year-old Zachary Ramsay disappears on his way to Whittier Elementary School in Great Falls. December 13, 1999 Nathaniel Bar-Jonah is arrested while lurking around the Lincoln Elementary School in Great Falls in the early morning dressed as a policeman. According to police, he is carrying a stun gun, a can of pepper spray, a fake police badge and a toy revolver. He quickly becomes the focus of the Ramsay investigation. December 17, 1999 Police search his apartment and find nude photos of him and young boys June 6, 2000 Police dig up a portion of Bar-Jonah's garage and recover a bunch of human bones. On December 18, 2000, Bar-Jonah is charged with the kidnapping and murder of Ramsay. Authorities contend Bar-Jonah ate the boy's remains. February 26, 2002 Nathan stands trial in Great Falls, Montana Evidence Police found 28 boxes of potential evidence that links Bar-Jonah to Zachary's disappearance. Investigators have found stun guns, knives, batons, a blue police-style coat, police badges. They also found a list of names, including Zachary, young relatives and children of friends. Police Found Recipes Police also found writings where Bar-Jonah allegedly makes references to "Little Boy Stew," "Little Kid Desert," "Little Boy Pot Pies". Authorities reveal that Bar-Jonah ate the boy's remains and also fed them to unwitting friends and family. Police Suspect More Victims Bar-Jonah kept a list of 27 names that police suspect could be his Massachusetts victims from 1963 to1977. The story sends law enforcement scrambling to find earlier atrocities the suspected serial killer may have committed. Their search includes Arkansas, Florida, Colorado, and into Canada. Nathan Was Convicted On Three Counts Nathan received the maximum sentence of 130 years without parole. Prison video. High-Priced Lawyers His attorneys appealed to the state supreme court and lost. Why No Publicity? A cannibal that is suspected of eating 27 children, with a possibility of dozens more. The guy is pedophile that lived with his Momma, so where did he get the money for his legal team?</Msg><Username>vida_blue_50</Username><Timestamp>1345606668000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345606900000-72</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>going forward. http://www.peakprosperity.com/crashcourse/chapter-1-three-beliefs You provide the solutions.</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1345606900000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345607357000-73</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The theory of tax incidence is not mine. It is settled economics, equivalent at this point to a Law of Physics. You might as well try to prove that 1+1 = 3 as defeat it. The conclusions are even more stark for your goal of income or wealth redistribution when the concept of game theory and strategic decision making is introduced which strives to actively increase profits by altering the terms of economic relations, technology, etc and shift taxes to workers and consumers. If you attempt to tax income, tax incidence, not the statutory placement of the tax will determine who pays. The taxation of wealth, which for it to work, would require a constitutional amendment, would not work either, as capital, like goods and services, has a price which can be used to shift tax burdens placed on it. Inflation is just a way of diluting capital, and a tax on capital, and the capital &amp; capital market is very sophisticated and adept at passing such things into the cost of capital. Perhaps you think you are getting a free ride by running up the debt to pay for giveaways to the poor, or allowing them to run it up with schemes like the CRIA. Not so. The interest rate will just rise on the debt eventually and when it does the poor's living standard will be reduced even more. They are enjoying the fools paradise every spendthrift enjoys... "Basic Income Guarantee" will just be money coming out the pocket of one lower income person into the pocket of another. Europe already has similar arrangements and $10/gallon gas, and sky high grocery prices, and massive rents for filthy little apartments should give you some indication that the theory of tax incidence is working quite efficiently there making the poor pay very nearly all the cost of government...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345607357000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345607603000-74</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Motivation to retain wealth via actions that reduced costs, which also guarantee reduced production, doesn't sound like a principle akin to the Law of Physics.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345607603000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345607656000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have mistaken the direction of your response.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345607656000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345607771000-76</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Business strive to maximize profits. That goal drives rational decision making. They can and will lower the income of their workers to pass taxes through. For much of the wealth of the wealthy, the work will be done by managers who's terms of employment and compensation is dictated by their skill at performing this task. In many case you can expect the worker to be gotten rid of altogether. Cloud computing is making it possible to do away with much IT staff. Robots do not require healthcare benefits and work for nothing, but their upkeep cost. Oh the workers welfare can be reduced. If you want to avoid this outcome do something about reducing the cost of government, and asinine plans like Obama's to "tax the rich." It won't work... If you want to argue the merits of these issues on some theological plane find somebody else. Those concept, and such nonsense such as a "living wage" is irrelevant to the discussion.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345607771000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345607931000-77</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345603067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:37:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't it a matter of what workers (executives vs others) are tax-impinged on a return the % for upper brackets, not the company/business?</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1345607931000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:58:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>