<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345177268000-1</Id><Topic><Title>HEY..any CNBC Mkt "Pumper's" in here ??</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1345168565000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 21:56:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't really care much about it anymore. I'm just sitting in cash. It makes no difference to me how long it takes to crash - it will crash; that is the key thing. The sustainable yield on stocks is around 8%. The stock market has a long way to go downward before it achieves that dividend yield. At this point there is so much fraud going on with accounting, and so many underfunded being pensions and stock option dilution schemes going on it is difficult to calculate any real positive yield for stocks at all.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345177268000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 00:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345177535000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Study: 26 corporations paid more to CEOs than in federal taxes</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345156342000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 18:32:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a prime example of the principle agent problem at work. The government needs to step in and tax executive pay above certain levels at 95%. That would put an end to the abuses once and for all. Executives worked for far less in generations past and did much more constructive work.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345177535000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 00:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345181028000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Markey: Romney-Ryan ticket would cut Big Bird to pay Big Oil</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345154614000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 18:03:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Say it ain't so, Romney Ryan would stop spending tax payers dollars on a muppet!</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1345181028000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 01:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345182705000-4</Id><Title>EPA to Approve Sorghum As New Source of Biofuel</Title><Msg>EPA to Approve Sorghum As New Source of Biofuel Deena Shanker | 16 August, 2012 | Biogas, Clean Tech There is some good news for American farmers amid a summer of drought and low crop yields: The Environmental Protection Agency is planning to approve the use of sorghum, a grain similar to corn that can be grown with a third less water, to make biofuel. Officials say they expect the decision to give farmers a new stream of income, prop up the biofuels industry and, of course, protect the environment. It should also help bring the United States closer to meeting its goal of annually producing 36 billion gallons of renewable fuels by 2022. Matt Hartwig of the Renewable Fuels Association called the decision “a good first step.” Currently, the U.S. uses only two advanced biofuels: sugar cane-based ethanol imported from Brazil and domestic biodiesel, a combination of petroleum diesel and renewable sources. Most of what is made in the U.S. is conventional ethanol made from corn — causing some critics to complain that the diversion is raising food prices for consumers. Of course, those critics fail to note that part of the problem is that corn has become the go-to ingredient for everything from soda to cereal. Because sorghum is not typically used in human food, this move should lead to fewer complaints. However, it is used in feed for poultry, cattle and other livestock, so it is not far-fetched to worry that the move could lead to higher meat and dairy prices. One Kansas plant run by Western Plains Energy L.L.C. has already started investing in the new sub-industry, putting $30-$40 million into renovations to assure it will be one of the first to turn the crop into advanced ethanol. “We’re going to try to produce over 50 million gallons (of advanced ethanol) per year,” said Curt Sheldon, the plant’s chief accounting officer. “At today’s prices, we could probably pay for the project in two to three years.” http://revmodo.com/2012/08/16/epa-to-approve-sorghum-as-new-source-of-biofuel/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345182705000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 01:51:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345182837000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Markey: Romney-Ryan ticket would cut Big Bird to pay Big Oil</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345154614000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 18:03:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...And who is going to teach my children how to count to ten?</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345182837000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 01:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345183278000-6</Id><Title>SD tops in electricity from wind</Title><Msg>SD tops in electricity from wind New report says state can generate 22 percent of its power from turbines By: Staff reports, The Daily Republic South Dakota ranks first in the nation for the amount of its own electricity it can produce from wind energy, according to a new report from the U.S. Department of Energy. The 2011 Wind Technologies Market Report, released this week, finds that in 2011 South Dakota could generate about 22 percent of its electricity from wind energy, which was tops in the nation. “This report shows that America can lead the world in the global race to manufacture and deploy clean energy technologies,” Energy Secretary Steven Chu said in a news release about the report. Nationally, wind power represented 32 percent of all new electric capacity additions in the United States last year and accounted for $14 billion in new investment. The percentage of wind equipment made in America also grew. Nearly 70 percent of the equipment installed at U.S. wind farms last year — including wind turbines and components like towers, blades, gears, and generators — is now from domestic manufacturers, doubling from 35 percent in 2005. The report found that in 2011, roughly 6,800 megawatts of new wind power capacity was added to the U.S. grid, a 31 percent increase from 2010 installations. The United States’ wind power capacity reached 47,000 MW by the end of 2011 and has since grown to 50,000 MW, enough electricity to power 13 million homes annually or as many homes as in Nevada, Colorado, Wisconsin, Virginia, Alabama and Connecticut combined. The country’s cumulative installed wind energy capacity grew 16 percent from 2010, and has increased more than 18-fold since 2000. The report also finds that six states, including South Dakota, now meet more than 10 percent of their total electricity needs with wind power. The growth in the industry has also led directly to more jobs throughout a number of sectors and at factories across the country. According to industry estimates, the wind sector employs 75,000 American workers, including workers at manufacturing facilities up and down the supply chain, as well as engineers and construction workers who build and operate the wind farms. In South Dakota, the industry supported 1,000 to 2,000 direct and indirect jobs in 2010. The report found that 2013 may see a slowing of domestic wind energy deployment due in part to the possible expiration of federal renewable energy tax incentives. The Production Tax Credit (PTC), which provides a tax credit to wind producers in the United States and has helped drive the industry’s growth, is set to expire at the end of this year. The wind industry projects that 37,000 jobs could be lost if the PTC expires. Working in tandem with the PTC, the Advanced Energy Manufacturing Tax Credit provides a 30 percent investment credit to manufacturers who invest in capital equipment to make components for clean energy projects in the United States. http://www.mitchellrepublic.com/event/article/id/68994/group/homepage/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345183278000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 02:01:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345183580000-7</Id><Title>GAO: EPA rules pose acceptable "reliability challenges" for utility industry</Title><Msg>GAO: EPA rules pose acceptable "reliability challenges" for utility industry By Zack Colman - 08/16/12 05:51 PM ET A Government Accountability Office (GAO) report released Thursday said the implementation of four environmental rules will likely pose electric “reliability challenges,” though not the full-blown problems Republicans and the utility industry have claimed. The nonpartisan GAO said the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) rules studied “are not expected to pose widespread concerns” regarding electric reliability. It estimated between 2 to 12 percent of coal-fueled capacity might shut down as a result of the rules. But the report added “EPA and some stakeholders GAO interviewed indicated that these actions should not affect reliability given existing tools.” Sen. Jay Rockefeller (D-W. Va.) said the report was a win for the rules’ proponents. “We must address the health and environmental concerns related to the power sector, and this report shows that we can do it responsibly," he said in a statement Thursday. Still, the report was not a clean victory for the EPA’s defenders. The report said power plant operators possess the ability to overcome “reliability challenges,” though doing so in coal-dependent states will be more difficult. The GAO report acknowledged federal coordination needs to improve to evaluate industry progress under the regulations, especially to help power plant operators meet the rules’ compliance targets. “Some other stakeholders GAO interviewed identified potential reliability challenges,” the report said. “Among other things, it may be difficult to schedule and complete all retrofits to install controls and to resolve all potential reliability concerns associated with retirements within compliance deadlines.” The rules GAO studied were: The Cross-State Air Pollution Rule; the Mercury and Air Toxics Standards; the proposed Cooling Water Intake Structures regulation; and the proposed Disposal of Coal Combustion Residuals regulation. Republicans have denounced the EPA proposals. They say procuring the technology needed to comply with the rules will take longer than EPA is willing to give. GOP lawmakers, and the electric power industry, contend the rules will shutter too many coal-fired plants, potentially leading to more electricity blackouts. They also say it will increase electricity bills for residents in coal-heavy states. The GAO report partially refuted the cost claim. It said the rules would increase rates unevenly – the coal-reliant South being hardest hit – but that over time costs could decrease compared with historical fluctuations. The rise of natural gas will also eliminate some of the cost and reliability concerns, the GAO report said. Cheap natural gas is already replacing coal as a source of electric power, and that alone could push power operators to shut down coal plants, the report said. Republican staff for the House Energy and Commerce Committee, which has held several hearings on the rules and their effects on electric reliability, told The Hill it was still reviewing the report. The GAO report builds on an August 2011 report by the nonpartisan Congressional Research Service (CRS) that said utility industry claims about the rules were excessive. That report found the regulations would not result in a significant number of power plant retirements. The CRS report also said public health benefits from instituting the rules far outweighed the costs. http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/244043-gao-utility-industry-can-meet-epa-regs</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345183580000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 02:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345184693000-8</Id><Title>Merkel pledges 'speedy' EU deal ~ Read final 5 paragraphs</Title><Msg>Merkel pledges 'speedy' EU deal Trade negotiations key to growth in Europe and at home: Harper By Lee Berthiaume, Postmedia News August 16, 2012 8:11 PM OTTAWA — Prime Minister Stephen Harper has indicated he is done with offering European governments advice on how to tackle the region’s economic crisis — at least in public. “I’m not going to comment publicly on how Europe addresses the particulars of those issues,” Harper told reporters during a press conference with German Chancellor Angela Merkel on Parliament Hill, Thursday. “I have great confidence in the chancellor’s leadership. We have great confidence in our European friends.” In June, Harper issued a stern challenge to Europe to pull itself out of its debt crisis with its own funds and overhaul the eurozone with structural changes that create a “genuine” financial union. It was the latest in a series of similar comments that prompted sharp criticism from some European leaders, including European Commission President Jose Manuel Barroso. Barroso suggested the world should be contributing funds to help Europe and defiantly insisted that the continent would not take “lessons” from others about how to run an economy. The Harper government has steadfastly refused to provide any Canadian money to help bail Europe out of its debt crisis, which was front and centre during Merkel’s two-day trip to Canada, Wednesday and Thursday. But while Harper refused to make any public comments about what Europe needs to do as it continues to tackle its very serious economic problems, Merkel praised Canada for practicing what it has been preaching to other countries. “You have a free trade system. You have a sound budgetary policy. And you have quite strict rules for the banking system,” she said. “If you look at the last global economic crisis, Canada has weathered this quite well. So there’s something we can learn. “Canada is not only counselling something to others that they themselves are not doing at home. Quite the contrary. It’s tested and proven. And that’s important to me.” The two leaders sought to present a united front as they plugged Canada’s free trade talks with the European Union and advocated for a long-term solution for Europe’s financial crisis – not the politically expedient solution. They dismissed questions about whether Canada’s refusal to contribute to a $450-billion bailout fund for troubled eurozone economies would derail the free trade deal, with the two leaders calling the issues unrelated. Rather, Harper and Merkel held up the pending Canada-EU trade negotiations as key for economic growth in both countries and the EU as a whole. http://www.calgaryherald.com/business/Merkel+pledges+speedy+deal/7102780/story.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345184693000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 02:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345184704000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Merkel pledges 'speedy' EU deal ~ Read final 5 paragraphs</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345184693000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 02:24:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Merkel, who has become increasingly isolated in Europe and her own country, had arrived seeking an ally in Harper as the two have been preaching a similar message of fiscal austerity. Harper didn’t disappoint, repeatedly praising the German leader’s refusal to cave to pressure and simply throw more money at the crisis. “One of the things I appreciate about Chancellor Merkel’s leadership is the willingness, including at times of urgency and stress, her desire to not just find any solution but to find correct and good solutions,” Harper said. In return, Merkel offered strong support for Canada’s trade talks with Europe, which the Harper government is hoping will bolster its credentials on the economic front. “We feel very much committed to this,” Merkel said through a translator. “We want a speedy conclusion of this agreement. It will be an agreement of the EU with Canada that is of the broadest possible base. “Once I go back to Germany, I will see to it that these negotiations come to a speedy conclusion because at a time where there is lack of growth in the world, we — Canada and Germany — are convinced that free trade is one of the best engines of growth that we can have. Protectionism is one of the greatest dangers to growth.” Harper pledged during the last election to conclude negotiations on the trade agreement by the end of this year, and he and Merkel reiterated the importance of finishing the deal as soon as possible. Reports indicate the talks are entering the final stages, though a number of contentious issues remain unresolved, including intellectual property protection, government procurement and Canada’s supply-managed agricultural sectors. “Both of our countries, both of our economies need increased trade. It is essential for growth,” Harper said. “This is important for both of us. We’ve set an ambitious timetable to achieve that. Negotiations are going well and I am confident that we will successfully conclude it.” In addition to the economy and free trade, the two leaders also discussed ways for Germany to take advantage of Canada’s natural resource wealth. “The supply of commodities has become a strategically important issue for many, many governments in the world and this is why we are happy to have close co-operation with a country that is as rich in natural resources as Canada,” Merkel said. Merkel, a former environment minister whose country has been a global advocate for green energy, sidestepped a question about whether she is concerned about the oil sands’ carbon emissions. “We are familiar with the problems that are there with respect to the oil sands,” she said. “That doesn’t mean, however, that any other extraction of oil is free of CO2 emissions. One has to give solid scientific foundation to this, and Germany will come out strongly in favour of this.” Merkel wrapped up her two-day trip to Canada with a stop in Halifax where she attended a conference on marine biology and signed an agreement on science and technology.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345184704000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 02:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345190588000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Markey: Romney-Ryan ticket would cut Big Bird to pay Big Oil</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345154614000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 18:03:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The communist govt. @$$hole.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1345190588000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 04:03:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345201819000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Stock split</Title><Username>joelverburg</Username><Timestamp>1345160833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stench raised a motion for a 3 for 1 Splitz,which is rumored to have been taken up. I believe announcement will come 9/14. It is also rumored of a second div Hikez,for 2012,will be disclosed in 3 Q.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1345201819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345201871000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Markey: Romney-Ryan ticket would cut Big Bird to pay Big Oil</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345154614000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 18:03:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, if you could do it, then you could try.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345201871000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345202214000-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Stench Connection!</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1345122157000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 09:02:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also think,,that HES worth looking at.When Strait shutz,,domestic production will bring in 150 oil.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1345202214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345206943000-14</Id><Title>US Reliance on Saudi Oil Heads Back Up</Title><Msg>http://www.cnbc.com/id/48698518 The United States is increasing its dependence on oil from Saudi Arabia, raising its imports from the kingdom by more than 20 percent this year, even as fears of military conflict in the tinderbox Persian Gulf region grow.</Msg><Username>Low_Mac</Username><Timestamp>1345206943000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 08:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345219951000-15</Id><Title>Oil going much, much higher! Americans used to $4/gal gas now.</Title><Msg>Americans have no problem with $5 or $6/gal gas. It's already much higher in Europe.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1345219951000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345221749000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Executives Pay Government Subsidized</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345142620000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 14:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Asinine as always wahleee boy. Did you even bother to read the article?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1345221749000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 12:42:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345223268000-17</Id><Title>Amazing news in the works for Exxon Mobil Corporation</Title><Msg>What do yall think about the RSI and MACD indicators of Exxon Mobil Corporation? http://NYSESTOCKQUOTES.INFO</Msg><Username>kerriegrantham04</Username><Timestamp>1345223268000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345223736000-18</Id><Topic><Title>False Left vs Right Paradigm</Title><Username>joe_rudi_49</Username><Timestamp>1345131394000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a `Real1 Dreamer Tory, still, if the World was the way you think it should be,,,. Reality TV rules, or rather, the rulers rule through the TV, what we need are some new script writers, Take your blinders off and think about this, why can't we play from a script which offers the possibility of a peacefull, happy, secure future for the World?</Msg><Username>donny_d_drivle</Username><Timestamp>1345223736000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 13:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345226572000-19</Id><Title>B.C. newspaper tycoon proposing $13-billion oil refinery for Northern Gateway oil (with poll)</Title><Msg>B.C. newspaper tycoon proposing $13-billion oil refinery for Northern Gateway oil (with poll) By GORDON HOEKSTRA, VANCOUVER SUN August 17, 2012 10:36 AM VANCOUVER - B.C. community newspaper tycoon David Black proposed today building a $13-billion oil refinery near Kitimat to use all of the crude from Enbridge's controversial Northern Gateway pipeline. It would mean tankers would ship refined fuels like gasoline off of B.C. northwest coast, not heavy oil from Alberta, reducing environmental risks, says Black. A refinery also promises 10 times as many jobs as an export pipeline. Black is hoping his proposal will change opposition from British Columbians and first nations, many of which have rejected the $6-billion project because they say the economic rewards for B.C. are not great enough to offset the risk and consequence of an oil spill on the pipeline or off the northwest coast of British Columbia. Last month, B.C. Premier Christy Clark also declared the province would not even consider the Northern Gateway project unless it gets a much greater share of the economic benefits. Acknowledging that oil producers that want to ship oil on the Northern Gateway pipeline are not in favour of a refinery in B.C., Black said his new company, Kitimat Clean Ltd., is submitting an environmental assessment application to build the refinery. Does the refinery proposal affect your stance on the pipeline? No, I am still against the Enbridge pipeline. Yes, I would be for the pipeline if this proposal guarantees reduction on environmental risks and economic rewards for BC Not sure. Vote View Results Since the economic returns from a refinery are less than exporting oil, and no company has stepped forward to spearhead the project, he decided to do it himself, said Black. He first proposed the idea to Canada's oil companies seven years ago when he was chairman of the B.C. Progress Board, and resurrected the idea 11 months ago. "I am hoping to serve as a catalyst to attract an industry consortium that will undertake the project. But if no industry player steps forward during the two-year environmental assessment I will do all that I can to organize the capital and build the refinery," said Black, who owns 150 community newspapers in B.C. and the United States. Added Black: "I think the pipeline and the refinery are crucially important to our northern communities, to B.C., to Alberta and to Canada. We must protect the environment, but we must create jobs for the next generation as well. It is our responsibility to do both." The proposed refinery in Kitimat would provide many more jobs than an export pipeline. http://www.vancouversun.com/business/Newspaper+tycoon+proposing+billion+refinery+Northern+Gateway/7106304/story.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345226572000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345226586000-20</Id><Topic><Title>B.C. newspaper tycoon proposing $13-billion oil refinery for Northern Gateway oil (with poll)</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345226572000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The refinery is estimated to create 3,000 jobs, half of those directly in the refinery and the other half in contract jobs. Another 6,000 workers would be hired during the five-year construction period. Black is proposing to reduce capital costs from Canada's high labour rates by building refinery modules offshore to be shipped to Kitimat. The Northern Gateway pipeline is estimated to create about 350 permanent and contract jobs in B.C., one-tenth of the permanent jobs a refinery would create. A pipeline would also create thousands of jobs during its three-year construction phase. The planned Northern Gateway pipeline is meant to open up new markets for crude from the Alberta oilsands, breaking the reliance on the U.S. market, and as a result bringing a higher price for Canada's oil, an estimated $25 billion more a year. That goal can be achieved with a refinery on the coast with access to Pacific Rim markets, said Black. The refinery will also remove any threat of "catastrophic" offshore pollution from heavy crude oil because refined fuels such as diesel, gasoline and kerosene evaporate, said Black. There would also be about 30 per cent less tanker loads into Kitimat because the diluent used to thin the crude oil shipped to Kitimat would be stripped out during refining and sent back to Alberta via pipeline. Black also argues that building the refinery in B.C. will ensure it is a state-of-the-art facility with a lower environmental footprint than in other areas. While it will produce about seven million tonnes of carbon dioxide emissions, those emissions would have been produced anyway, he said. Black has briefed the B.C. premier, Clark, but he said the province hasn't told him what their position on his proposal is yet. He added there are many legitimate concerns from first nations along the pipeline. "In my view we should not proceed with the pipeline or refinery unless there is confidence that any pipeline leakage will be immaterial," said Black.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345226586000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:03:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345227092000-21</Id><Title>Court upholds E15</Title><Msg>Court upholds E15 (8/17/2012) The U.S. Court of Appeals for the D.C. Circuit rejected multiple challenges to the Environmental Protection Agency’s (EPA) allowance of E15 into the commercial marketplace in opinion written in the case of Grocery Manufacturers Association v. EPA. “The appellate court decision helped ensure that groups with ulterior motives will not derail the expansion of domestic, renewable fuel. E15 will allow ethanol to further lower gas prices, lower U.S. dependence on foreign oil and improve our economy,” said POET CEO Jeff Lautt. “POET, as part of POET-DSM Advanced Biofuels, is now building a commercial cellulosic ethanol plant that will use corn cobs, leaves, husk and some stalk to produce renewable fuel. Crop residue could be used to produce nearly 8 billions of gallons of ethanol for the U.S., but only if drivers are given the option to use it. E15 gives cellulosic ethanol a viable market,” Lautt said. http://www.feedstuffs.com/ME2/dirmod.asp?sid=F4D1A9DFCD974EAD8CD5205E15C1CB42&amp;nm=Breaking+News&amp;type=news&amp;mod=News&amp;mid=A3D60400B4204079A76C4B1B129CB433&amp;tier=3&amp;nid=54343528F4ED4DDAB4A39E150C1695FE</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345227092000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345227494000-22</Id><Title>EPA recognizes Kuehnle AgroSystems for algae biofuel work</Title><Msg>EPA recognizes Kuehnle AgroSystems for algae biofuel work By U.S. EPA | August 17, 2012 U.S. EPA Regional Administrator Jared Blumenfeld has recognized Kuehnle AgroSystems for the company’s innovative work in producing algae for use in biofuels as part of the Pacific Southwest region’s environmental awards program. “EPA is pleased to recognize Kuehnle AgroSystems for its innovative techniques that can turn a tank of algae into a tank of gas,” Blumenfeld said. “This clean-tech company’s work on renewable biofuels will help make Hawaii energy self-sufficient, and it protects the quality of our air, water and land.” The EPA Pacific Southwest region’s Environmental Awards program acknowledges commitment and significant contributions to the environment in California, Arizona, Nevada, Hawaii, Pacific Islands and tribal lands. Groups and individuals were selected from nominees received this year from businesses, local, government officials, tribes, media, environmental organizations and community activists. Most biofuels used as replacements for oil are grown on large tracts of agricultural land, but algae has the potential to produce a high density, efficient biofuel feedstock on industrial land. Kuehnle AgroSystems, a Hawaii-based company, has built a system to continuously produce algae for biofuel. Their system pipes carbon dioxide and wastewater from an oil refinery into tanks that accelerate algae growth, and demonstrate emission reductions. In November 2011 their project, constructed at Chevron’s Hawaii oil refinery, successfully achieved the nation’s first connection of industrial CO2 from an oil refinery with a working algae production site. In addition, to demonstrating its technology in partnership with Chevron, the company also has done significant work with the U.S. military to grow algae for biofuels. Kuehnle also works on overseas biofuels operations, aquaculture farms for shrimp and fish, and companies such as General Atomics, which operates a large algae production facility on the island of Kauai using algae sourced from Kuehnle. http://biomassmagazine.com/articles/7956/epa-recognizes-kuehnle-agrosystems-for-algae-biofuel-work</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345227494000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:18:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345228023000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Court upholds E15</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345227092000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:11:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EPA Defeats Challenge to Higher Ethanol Levels in Fuel By Sara Forden - Aug 17, 2012 11:30 AM MT 2 Comments A challenge to an Environmental Protection Agency rule allowing higher concentrations of corn- based ethanol in gasoline was thrown out by a U.S. Appeals Court ruling that the groups pressing the case had no right to sue. Grocery, auto and petroleum industry associations filed suit against the agency in November 2010, saying that rules allowing for increased used of corn-based ethanol in auto fuel would push up the price of food and gasoline and harm engines. The court today ruled the groups couldn’t show they had suffered specific harm as ... http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_C/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=22088&amp;tid=83358&amp;mid=83358&amp;tof=1&amp;frt=2</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345228023000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345228636000-24</Id><Title>Texas Claims a Victory Against EPA, But the Point May Be Moot</Title><Msg>Texas Claims a Victory Against EPA, But the Point May Be Moot August 14, 2012 | 1:32 PM By Terrence Henry You wouldn’t know it from much of the coverage out there, but a “victory” for Texas in its ongoing conflict with the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) Monday is something of a moot point. The 5th Circuit Court of Appeals handed down a 2–1 ruling yesterday saying that the EPA hadn’t properly rejected the state’s ‘Flexible Permitting Program.’ That was a system put in place in the nineties that was used by about ten percent of industrial facilities in the state to obtain air permits. (The rest of the facilities in the state used a standard permit approved by the EPA.) The court found that “the EPA based its disapproval on demands for language and program features of the EPA’s choosing, without basis in the Clean Air Act or its implementing regulations.” All three judges in the ruling were appointed by Republican presidents. The state Attorney General Greg Abbott, Texas Commission on Environmental Quality (TCEQ) and several industry groups filed the suit, saying the EPA didn’t have the right to reject the permitting program. But while Texas fought the EPA’s decision, behind the scenes almost all of the facilities in the program went ahead and got a standard, federally-approved permit anyway. And the TCEQ also submitted a new Clean Air plan to the EPA (partly modeled after federal standards), which the agency approved in June. (The TCEQ points out that the new plan isn’t related to the old Flexible Permitting Program.) So what’s the point of suing the EPA for permits no one really uses anymore? “This is all kind of beating a dead horse,” says Elena Craft with the Environmental Defense Fund. “The reality is that nothing on the ground is going to change.” Craft was part of a petition to the EPA filed by several environmental groups asking for the old flexible permitting program to be revoked. She says this week’s decision probably won’t change anything in that regard. “The [old] program still has to be approved by the EPA,” Craft says. “The court says they didn’t find the EPA’s reasons for disapproving is complete. That doesn’t mean the program has a green light going forward. It means the EPA has to do a better job proving why [the TCEQ permitting] doesn’t meet federal requirements of the Clean Air Act.” Part of the issue was how long it took the EPA to get around to rejecting the flexible permit program. It was originally submitted by Democratic Governor Ann Richards in 1994, but the EPA didn’t get around to a final disapproval until 2010, according to the ruling. “Sixteen years tardy,” as the court put it. In statements, the TCEQ and Attorney General Abbott are painting the decision as a victory. Regardless of where things stand now in the permitting process, they say the suit is justified in fighting federal overreach. “It is a victory for Texas, our environment, and our economy,” the TCEQ says in a statement. “We regret that Texas businesses were forced into an additional, unnecessary permitting process by the EPA, even though existing permits were legal and protective of the environment.” The governor weighed in, too. “It’s unfortunate we had to go to such extremes to fight back against this troubling trend of overreach and reckless political activism by the Obama Administration that shows no regard for the impact on jobs or our economy,” Governor Rick Perry said in a statement. But.. http://stateimpact.npr.org/texas/2012/08/14/texas-claims-a-victory-against-epa-but-the-point-may-be-moot/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345228636000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345228651000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Claims a Victory Against EPA, But the Point May Be Moot</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345228636000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But since all of the facilities under the old permitting program have already submitted new permits that would come into compliance with the EPA, it’s not clear what the point of the lawsuit is anymore. Update: The TCEQ, in response to a request for comment, says that “the TCEQ does not know of any permit holder that plans to submit another application to go back to a flexible permit. It’s important to understand that the court ruling does not result in the TCEQ’s flexible permit rules being automatically SIP-approved (by EPA). This will take more time, and the court did not specify how long EPA has to re-visit approval/disapproval of TCEQ’s flexible permit rules.” The TCEQ also says that of the 140 flexible permits under the old program, 21 were “voided or transitioned to another permit” before the EPA disapproved them in 2009. Since, 71 of the permits were “de-flexed,” or changed to a standard permit. And 42 other permits are pending to do the same. That leaves only six facilities in the state that still haven’t changed their old flexible permit. “We see time and again that Texas has challenged the EPA on a number of issues, and at every turn they’ve been denied by the court,” Craft of the Environmental Defense Fund says. “Or if they call it a victory, it’s a victory with no value or meaning. They’re in the same boat as before.” As StateImpact Texas covered in a report earlier today, battles between the Attorney General (and in some cases, the TCEQ) and the EPA are simply part of the status quo these days in Texas. The Texas Tribune notes there are six separate cases filed by Abbott against the EPA, at a total cost of over $350,000. (In all, Abbott has spent more than $1.25 million in court cases against the federal government, with almost half of that money going to private law firms, according to the Tribune.) Backstory aside, will facilities now try and go back to the old flexible permitting program? “I don’t see that happening,” Craft says. “There’s been so much attention around it that it doesn’t seem sensible to operate under a permit that has all the liabilities associated with it.” Because the old permits are liable under government and civil suits for potentially violating the Clean Air Act, Craft says it makes sense for facilities to stick with their new, federally-approved permits. Now the EPA has 45 days to resubmit its rejection to the appeals court, or three months to appeal to the Supreme Court, according to Texas Energy Report. You can read the 5th Circuit Court of Appeals ruling in full below:</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345228651000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345234199000-26</Id><Topic><Title>World Business Leaders Say Obama Better 4 Economy</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345233738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who would you want, someone who said take my jobs and money or buy USA? He is still giving money to everyone overseas just because.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1345234199000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345234323000-27</Id><Title>Amazing news in the works for Exxon Mobil Corporation</Title><Msg>What do yall think about the RSI and MACD indicators of Exxon Mobil Corporation? http://STOCKOPTIONCHARTSFREE.INFO</Msg><Username>genevaschein</Username><Timestamp>1345234323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345234342000-28</Id><Title>The Street - Article</Title><Msg>It's got to tick Cramer off that his web site, the Street, has reiterated their "buy" recommendation on Exxon. He has hated this company for years. http://www.thestreet.com/story/11667101/1/exxon-mobil-corporation-stock-buy-recommendation-reiterated-xom.html?puc=yahoo&amp;cm_ven=YAHOO</Msg><Username>Ploddingalong98</Username><Timestamp>1345234342000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345234412000-29</Id><Topic><Title>World Business Leaders Say Obama Better 4 Economy</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345233738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's giving America away and these leaders say keep it coming. Have you seen the trade deficit and debt?? Yet you keep voting for this usurper.</Msg><Username>eagle1776321</Username><Timestamp>1345234412000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345234820000-30</Id><Topic><Title>World Business Leaders Say Obama Better 4 Economy</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345233738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both parties aggressively exporting/outsourcing American jobs for larger Wall Street profits. Slave labor nations where teens work 80 hours a week are the favorite landing point of former US jobs. US politicians grease the skids for nations like China and North Korea to harvest the United States manufacturing base. Manhattan wins as America is gutted by whore Republicans and Democrats.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345234820000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:20:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345235326000-31</Id><Topic><Title>World Business Leaders Say Obama Better 4 Economy</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345233738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And why is this bad? What difference does it make how low wages drop to?</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345235326000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345235549000-32</Id><Topic><Title>False Left vs Right Paradigm</Title><Username>joe_rudi_49</Username><Timestamp>1345131394000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would like to see Obama do what I wrote (throw Bibi under the bus) because it would mean the end of his political career - he would lose New York, and Florida by wide margins. I do not really care about the issue of whether Bibi's agenda is or is not of value to U.S. interests.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1345235549000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345236609000-33</Id><Topic><Title>World Business Leaders Say Obama Better 4 Economy</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345233738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course the other nations want Obama instead of Romney. They like how Obama wants to siphon the wealth out of America and hand it to the UN. It's all part of his "spread the wealth" plan. Of course if you paid attention to the detail: "The result was different among respondents in the United States, where a slim majority thought Romney would be better for their businesses than Obama." Americans want Romney not Obama.</Msg><Username>yankeeddandy</Username><Timestamp>1345236609000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:50:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345238821000-34</Id><Topic><Title>False Left vs Right Paradigm</Title><Username>joe_rudi_49</Username><Timestamp>1345131394000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Transatlantic types are terrified anyone deviate from the MSNBC, FOX,CNN war propaganda tyhe bankers spew. The Manhattan media ownership is about as diverse as the ownership of big studios in Hollywood. 85% of textbooks are published by the five publishing houses.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1345238821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 17:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345239435000-35</Id><Topic><Title>World Business Leaders Say Obama Better 4 Economy</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345233738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama wants to siphon the wealth out of America and hand it to the UN." You stupid idiot.</Msg><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1345239435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 17:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345239526000-36</Id><Topic><Title>EPA recognizes Kuehnle AgroSystems for algae biofuel work</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1345227494000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 14:18:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The article doesn't say much about anything, nothing about efficiencies or performance, cost? Until it is verified how much a gallon of diesel can be produced and sold to the general public, hopefully cheaper than diesel today, I will neither hold my breath nor get my hopes up. The timing of this article appears to be more political than anything else.</Msg><Username>superknocknevis</Username><Timestamp>1345239526000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 17:38:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345243811000-37</Id><Topic><Title>World Business Leaders Say Obama Better 4 Economy</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345233738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot!</Msg><Username>cries_foul</Username><Timestamp>1345243811000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 18:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345246494000-38</Id><Title>MKT&gt;XOM down...better sell this POS</Title><Msg>really ! before it returns to the $50s!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1345246494000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345247616000-39</Id><Title>gravel and frac sand</Title><Msg>being from Calgary came accross microcap company with 100% increase in rev and net income supplying gravel for infrastructure projects Fort McMurray where all Canadian oilsands are located. PE below 10/ Produces gravel in Fort McMurray. Management owns about 44%. Have produced enormous profits relative to their market cap but the stock trades for 5X trailing earnings. If you believe in the oil sands and the construction of these big plants and roads, this is the play for you because they are pretty much the dominant gravel producer there. Also have a frac sand deposit which is very valuable for fracing needs. Short positions have all but evaporated. Athabasca Minerals</Msg><Username>madik_2000</Username><Timestamp>1345247616000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:53:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345249862000-40</Id><Topic><Title>World Business Leaders Say Obama Better 4 Economy</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345233738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, let's nots that 25% of these world wide executives responsed "neither" to an either / or question. Such is not a valid answer. We might not know who and even might disagree with who and we might not ever be able to go back and factually prove who is better. But we do know that unless the world would perform exactly the same under either, then one of them would be better. So either they polled some real idiots OR the poll questions were poorly structured and/or worded. But let's also dig a little deeper and we'll accept that all of these folks were really Einsteins. The poll also said that American execs said Romney was better. So we can easily surmise, if you want a Pres. that is better for those outside US, you choice is Obama. If you want one better for the US, your choice is Romney. This actually makes plenty of sense. Given the level of gov't spending Obama endorses, at least some has to trickle outside of the US to the businesses these very exec run. However these execs don't have to pay the taxes to support Obama's level of spending. In effect, they are getting free money from the US gov't (some more than others as already seen and some more directly than others as already seen) w/o the tax burden that will gut this country. So they get money, they don't pay the taxes to get that money, and the largest competition they face (US companies and economy) gets gutted in the meantime. They woudl be stupid to not pick Obama.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1345249862000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345250738000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Stock split</Title><Username>joelverburg</Username><Timestamp>1345160833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you have been offered a wager for $30k that your cr@p won't happen. Still waiting for you to take it up.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1345250738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 20:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345252761000-42</Id><Topic><Title>World Business Leaders Say Obama Better 4 Economy</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1345233738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THEY WANT USA TO BE SOCIALIST You should know better than that cousin Wahleee. Having a sperm snack tonight???</Msg><Username>wahleee_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1345252761000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345255196000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Stock split</Title><Username>joelverburg</Username><Timestamp>1345160833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 19:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it will have to hold 95 for four mos. and will "only" split 2/1,never has split 3/1 and never will.</Msg><Username>wdsjr22949</Username><Timestamp>1345255196000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345255299000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Stock Tips to Get the Most Out Of Your Investments</Title><Username>lloydmassey67</Username><Timestamp>1345204584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 07:56:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your life will never be the same again after investing  your amount on such shares ,can grunt u on these. hope for the best.</Msg><Username>drake.wong94</Username><Timestamp>1345255299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345258470000-45</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>Getting monotonous market at multi year high Exxon down again. Dow up 70 points this week Exxon doesn't budge. When is this thing supposed to go up. In this big rally I can't remember day this stock has gone up one per cent. Stock remains nearly ten points below 2008 price and can't break 88. Never saw such an under performer on a daily basis. The XTO deal alone would be enough to call XOM theworst managed energy company ever, but there's all kinds of other reasons: production shortfalls,earnings disappointments etc. The last 5 years (since current management took over) really lousy for investors.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1345258470000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 22:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>