<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353993785986-1</Id><Title>Harry Reid the Country needs "Filibuster Reform" in 2013 !! Screw McConnell no power !!</Title><Msg>TeaReptards filibuster over 300 times this has never happened in US history the most has been like 4 thats correct 4 only !!! The TeaReptards would have done it long time ago.</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1353993785986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 00:23:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354015228461-2</Id><Title>PraPra Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Msg>Unlike Wahleee's Greedful alias, PraPra has no logic whatsoever - just a political cuss.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354015228461</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 06:20:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354017721294-3</Id><Topic><Title>Greedful Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1353927170760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 05:52:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pivsup, I hope my theories are incorrect - time will tell. I have never believed Obama was not born outside the US. I have read Obama's book "Dreams from My Father" and enjoyed it immensely. Obama was born in Hawaii and understandably struggled alot in his early life with his mixed white European and black African ancestory. He decided to take up the plight of the poor primarily black minorities by becoming a community organizer and then a politician. His primary goal is the transfer of wealth from primarily white middle to upper economic classes to primarily black and brown lower economic classes. Simple as that. Since I'm white upper middle class, I don't agree with his political agenda. I can understand why the lower economic classes vote for him and the Demoncraps since who votes against Santa Claus? But it looks like their are plenty of ignorant white middle and upper class US voters who have approved of his goal of transferring their wealth, via even more taxes, to the lower economic echelons. Unfortunately, we have so many lower echelon people, as well as government "workers", living off the taxpayer dollars of working private sector people that there is no way the budget will ever be balanced and no way the debt will start decreasing. All we need is for China to "pull the rug out from under us" by convincing the world that the US dollar is no longer a reasonable standard for world trade, and to shift to their currency. At that point, the US economy will implode, we will go into a Depression like we have never seen, there will be very little jobs to support the government and the lower echelons, and the lower echelons will start rioting nationwide. Martial law will be declared and Obama will be ruled the de facto Hugo Chavez Dictator of the USSA.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354017721294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 07:02:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354021300500-4</Id><Topic><Title>Greedful Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1353927170760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 05:52:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Invester the molester you're an Idiot.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1354021300500</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 08:01:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354024533929-5</Id><Topic><Title>Greedful Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1353927170760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 05:52:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at least he doesn't suuukkk coooooccccc</Msg><Username>wahleee_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1354024533929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 08:55:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354026069234-6</Id><Topic><Title>Greedful Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1353927170760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 05:52:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Russian Newspaper: Obama Was Re-Elected by “Illiterate Society” Read more: conservativebyteDOTcom/2012/11/russian-newspaper-obama-was-re-elected-by-illiterate-society/#ixzz2DQnmlzQ8 In my opinion, the Russian article is trying to deepen the divide between the "haves" and the "have nots". Mitt's gaff declaring 47 million people would vote for Obama cost him the votes he needed to win. Compassionate Conservatism could have won the election, but the gaff came off appearing discompassionate toward poor people. Don't blame the victims who were deceived by all the lies coming from the left or the right. Show them some compassion toward and a path for them to follow by leading them out of poverty.. There are policy changes requiring no new taxes that can help, but Obama has other plans.</Msg><Username>dogshitforbrains</Username><Timestamp>1354026069234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 09:21:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354031240297-7</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>Miserable dog of a stock is wrapping up its fourth straight year of underperforming every single major average. The Tillerson years have been one big disaster: earnings misses every quarter, production shortfalls every quarter, the worst acquisition in history-XTO. Unbelievable how such massive assets have been so badly managed by this crew. XOM is the most poorly managed major oil company in the world and the shareholders pay a huge price. Those who bought the stock many years ago are in better shape since the company used to have excellent management until Rex Tillerson and his group of clowns took over.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1354031240297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 10:47:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354036094021-8</Id><Topic><Title>Doha climate talk urges more emission cuts by developed world - legally binding accord requiring industrialized countries to cut their carbon emissions</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353987841757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 22:44:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>might as well go #$%$ in an erupting volcano.</Msg><Username>eagle1776321</Username><Timestamp>1354036094021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 12:08:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354036230103-9</Id><Title>Heads Up Gentlemen ! Socialism is Moving Into High Gear !</Title><Msg>Obama's next target is nationalization of the oil and gas industry in the U.S. CSPAN was alive this morning with poorly disguised "new" policy agendas led by bipartisanpolicy.org. Your recent "good fortune" in sand and shale revenues are being eyed as the "obvious" solution to balancing the budget through "fair share taxation". (Never mind you are already being nailed for something like 44% already as a industry based upon comments by Jack Gereard of the API.) BOHICA !</Msg><Username>disillusionedmale</Username><Timestamp>1354036230103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 12:10:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354037605003-10</Id><Topic><Title>Heads Up Gentlemen ! Socialism is Moving Into High Gear !</Title><Username>disillusionedmale</Username><Timestamp>1354036230103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 12:10:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure your right. The left wing has been salivating over the thought of nationalizing the oil industry for years. Some of the issues that may prevent this are, that so many are invested in oil, though mutual funds and pensions, hopefully there would be a public outcry against it. I don't believe that our government has ever taken over a healthy industry due to constitutionality issues. Also, the number of attorneys the oil industry would marshal against such a move would tie it up in the courts for decades.</Msg><Username>mwds06</Username><Timestamp>1354037605003</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 12:33:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354040787691-11</Id><Topic><Title>Petraeus Scandal Reveals Massive Islamic Infiltration In Obama Administration</Title><Username>dogshitforbrains</Username><Timestamp>1353926405997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 05:40:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one hates Moslems more than Lebanese Christians hate Moslems. The fact that Ms. Kelly is a Lebanese Christian indicates that she has nothing but contempt for Moslems. We Americans have no understanding of the Middle East as your post and its referense so richly indicate. No Lebanese Christian indicates a "massive Islamic infiltration" anywhere.</Msg><Username>l_2_3z</Username><Timestamp>1354040787691</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:26:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354040953025-12</Id><Title>“having one of the OPEC leaders in charge of climate talks is like asking Dracula to look after a blood bank.”</Title><Msg>Doha Climate Talks: First Farce, then Tragedy Published by Martha Pskowski, November 27th, 2012 The lead-up to COP18 which started in Doha, Qatar this week, would have been farcical, if not for the tragic reminder from Hurricane Sandy that climate change is deadly, and is already upon us. But for a moment, let’s appreciate the ironies: Rio+20, “The Future We Want,” summit in June of this year was declared a failure on almost all counts. The tepid commitments, all voluntary, sound exactly like the future fossil fuel industries want. That meant many decisions were deferred to Doha, including finance, carbon markets, and REDD+, because the COPs are the negotiating arm of the UNFCCC. Protester in Rio, June 2012. Sounds reasonable? Think twice- COP18 is in Qatar, an OPEC nation with some of the highest emissions per capita that has been barely involved in climate negotiations. International campaigners Avaaz posted, “having one of the OPEC leaders in charge of climate talks is like asking Dracula to look after a blood bank.” At least we can turn to our “climate leaders,” like the EU. Turns out the debt crisis has our European friends a little distracted from their climate commitments. Spain, Germany, Italy, the U.K. and France have all cut aid to renewables. Well there are some “easy” issues to resolve in Doha, like fund transfers from wealthy countries to developing countries for mitigation and adaptation, right? But the farce continues- just in time for the conference to start, an international report finds that most wealthy countries are falling embarrassingly short of their commitments thus far for fund transfers. So much for the easy stuff. Okay, at least they off-set their emissions! 25k metric tons of carbon was “eliminated” in the CDM carbon market to off-set 10,000 participants traveling to Doha. Yet this comes amidst mounting evidence that the carbon markets are broken, with the value of credits in the CDM plunging 93% in two years, and the EU system failing to reduce emissions. (I’ll spare the gory details of CDM’s social injustice.) Yet, somehow in the fracas, carbon speculators are optimistic for Doha. Unlike the negotiators, they’ve figured out they can still make a handsome profit even if emissions don’t drop. In the rush to appease and appeal to business interests, negotiators have bought into a “Green Economy” narrative, where climate solutions are reduced to financial and technological fixes. REDD+, CDM, and other carbon offsets allow industrialized countries to avoid shifting their economies off fossil fuels, and speculators in new carbon markets reap the rewards. The Doha skyline. The choice of some climate justice groups to skip the trip to Doha is looking better and better. So is the COP system broken? Can we expect anything out of Doha? With Sandy barely behind us, and more storms on the horizon, a meaningful U.N. process may feel like our last hope. However most major decisions are made in preparatory meetings, such as those in Bonn and Bangkok this year. While the presence of critical voices is important, so far the COPs have proven to leave out indigenous peoples, youth, and others most impacted by climate change. We can’t count on negotiators to broker our future with fossil fuel corporations. The recent position paper from Focus on the Global South offers a critique and an alternative: “The capitalist system is seeking to get out of this economic crisis through a process of reconfiguration that implies a new process of exploitation of humans and nature… …To confront the interests and power of corporations, our struggle must have as starting point the daily life of the people affected by climate change and not the UNFCCC negotiations.” Around the world, more and more people are connecting the dots and challenging the root causes of climate change and false solutions. From the Tar Sands Blockade in Texas, to First Nations in British Columbia, to indigenous communities impacted by REDD+ in Mexico, people are taking a stand for their communities and ecology. As Hurricane Sandy showed, if we aren’t already, we all may soon be on the frontlines of climate change. As Focus on the Global South writes, “A ‘one size fits all’ model like neoliberalism or centralized bureaucratic socialism is not the answer. Instead, diversity should be expected and encouraged, as it is in nature.” Real solutions come from the grassroots. itsgettinghotinhereDOTorg/2012/11/27/doha-climate-talks-first-farce-then-tragedy/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354040953025</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:29:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354041479574-13</Id><Title>Time to start shorting...</Title><Msg>SPY and whatever else strikes the eye. High volume and liquidity is the important thing...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354041479574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:37:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354041921548-14</Id><Topic><Title>Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1354031240297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 10:47:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The economy is dead in the water and sinking fast 1. Energy prices are out of control and the stock market and economy has NEVER risen against a tide of rising energy prices without crashing fast and hard. 2. Energy consumption in a tailspin in American and Europe, plus China and India are slipping too. The current rate of decline in Europe is the worst since before the Great Depression, which then set a new standard of decline. 3. Debt/GDP is approaching catastrophic proportions, especially considering points #1 and #2...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354041921548</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:45:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354042088315-15</Id><Topic><Title>Heads Up Gentlemen ! Socialism is Moving Into High Gear !</Title><Username>disillusionedmale</Username><Timestamp>1354036230103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 12:10:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In Norway, one of the most successful socialist countries, the Government is the major stockholder in most of the large corporations. This does not exclude private persons, mutual funds, etc. from also owning shares. Statoil is the Norwegian oil company. I own shares in it and you can too. But more than half the shares are owned by the Norwegian Govt. The Govt. collects dividends on these shares, which helps fund the generous benefits their citizens enjoy.</Msg><Username>co1trane</Username><Timestamp>1354042088315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:48:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354042131936-16</Id><Topic><Title>Time to start shorting...</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354041479574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:37:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short position at 100% @$141.05 average on SPY. 100% means the maximum dollar amount I short, doesn't mean all I could short if I felt like but the most I short or trade anything</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354042131936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:48:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354042331053-17</Id><Topic><Title>Invest suffers from paranoia</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1354026562181</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 09:29:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Court joker does not disappoint.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354042331053</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:52:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354042657196-18</Id><Title>Republicans Refuse to Admit that Keystone XL will Bring Oil Through America, Not to It - Wyoming U.S. Sen. Barrasso pushes Obama on Keystone XL pipeline</Title><Msg>Republicans Refuse to Admit that Keystone XL will Bring Oil Through America, Not to It By: RmuseNovember 26th, 2012 Politicians who lack factual data to make their point on an issue often use fallacies as a rhetorical tool, and they can be used purposefully to win arguments because they appeal to emotion and not reason. Devoid of facts to back up their arguments, Republicans have little option but appealing to emotions, but instead of fallacies, they intentionally deliver false statements and the payoff is nearly always not in the public’s best interest. For the past year, the GOP has lied to the American people about the benefits of the Keystone XL pipeline, and as the President and Congress work to avoid the so-called fiscal cliff, there is little mystery that Republicans will use the pipeline’s approval as a bargaining chip to give the oil industry greater subsidies even as they attempt to cut their taxes. The President and Democrats could protect the environment and Americans’ health if they informed the people that Canadian tar sand is not coming to America, but through it on its way to China and Europe. As organizations such as the World Bank, the United Nations, World Meteorological Organization, and an alliance of the world’s largest investors appealed to governments to boost clean-energy investment and ramp up action on climate change, Republicans and some Democrats are pressuring President Obama to approve the Keystone XL pipeline without regard for global warming. Ignoring reports that greenhouse gas levels reached a new record, the pipeline’s proponents concern for big oil’s profits supersede their disregard for the environment and the population’s health. The potential for an ecological disaster is so great that a single spill could have devastating consequences for generations, and a University of Nebraska at Lincoln analysis of the pipeline finds that it could have 91 major spills in 50 years. A tar sands leak in Michigan two years ago has cost taxpayers over $800 million so far, and engineers still are unsure how to clean up tar sand crude that sinks making cleanup all the more difficult; if possible at all. TransCanada, the pipeline’s owner, has been exposed by a former TransCanada engineer who raised alarms about lax inspections and shoddy work that prompted the Canadian government to send an open letter admonishing TransCanada that an investigation was launched for noncompliance and that future lapses will not be tolerated. Canada’s energy regulator announced a sweeping audit of TransCanada’s operations after a long series of accidents, shutdowns and pipeline safety infractions that plagued the pipeline after TransCanada was forced to shut its leak-prone Keystone I tar sands pipeline down for four days after finding cracks, corrosion and other defects that lead to ruptures. TransCanada has a sordid history as a pipeline operator, but congressional representatives loyal to the oil industry are desperate to approve construction of the pipeline between Canada and Texas to enrich the oil industry. There are myriad reasons to deny TransCanada’s application to build a certain ecological disaster through the center of the nation, but proponents are ill-inclined to tell the public the truth about Keystone XL. One of the advertised benefits of the pipeline is that it will bring gas prices down, but TransCanada and industry experts agree that Keystone XL tar sands will increase domestic gas prices. When John Boehner touted the pipeline’s construction creating hundreds-of-thousands of jobs, it turned out that TransCanada gave U.S. officials a job number that was 67 times higher than number they used in Canada, and it was revealed that Boehner invested in 7 tar sand companies the previous year leading the SEC to consider an investigation of share price manipulation and to bolster his portfolio’s worth. Besides only creating 2,500 temporary and 50 permanent jobs, industry professionals agree that clean energy jobs far outweigh the potential for temporary dirty oil jobs. President Obama has been an advocate for reducing our dependence on fossil fuels and emphasized the importance of climate change and renewable energy and he made it a part of his campaign, but approving Keystone XL is a step in the wrong direction. To be fair, there are benefits associated with building the pipeline, but they are the hundreds-of-millions of dollars flowing to oil companies like ConocoPhillips and Valero Energy for selling the refined tar sand to Asia. Every other aspect of the pipeline is a detriment including poisoning a crucial natural resource, Nebraska’s Ogallala Aquifer, which is the country’s largest source of freshwater for drinking and irrigation for millions of Americans throughout the country. Add to that the devastation to agriculture, and besides dehydrating millions of Americans, the food supply would be adversely impacted for decades, if not longer. The task for President Obama is incredibly easy, and he can garner major support for denying TransCanada a permit to begin construction of the pipeline if he dispenses with rhetoric and tells the American people there is no value in building the pipeline. Americans will hardly support jeopardizing precious clean drinking water and a stable food supply if they realize that the pipeline will exist to enrich a couple of oil companies, Speaker of the House John Boehner, and provide a steady supply of gasoline to China. politicususaDOTcom/republicans-refuse-admit-keystone-xl-bring-oil-america.html ----------------------------------------------------------------------- Wyoming U.S. Sen. Barrasso pushes Obama on Keystone XL pipeline 3 hours ago • By ADAM VOGE Star-Tribune energy reporter (1) Comments Sen. John Barrasso is among a group of senators seeking face time with President Barack Obama over a controversial pipeline. The Wyoming Republican signed his name to a Nov. 16 letter asking the president for a meeting to discuss the Keystone XL pipeline extension, a TransCanada-owned, 36-inch diameter pipeline which would transport Canadian crude through a series of states including Montana and South Dakota and ending in Louisiana. The letter was written by Sen. Max Baucus, D-Mont., and Sen. John Hoeven, R-N.D., and signed by 16 other lawmakers. It asks the president to expedite the project. "Nothing has changed about the thousands of jobs that Keystone XL will create," the group wrote. "Nothing has changed about the energy security to be gained through an important addition to the existing pipeline network built with sound environmental stewardship and the best modern technology." No part of the line would traverse Wyoming, but Barrasso said in a statement that people in the Cowboy State understand energy needs and can get behind the project. "In Wyoming, we have first-hand knowledge of how energy projects like the Keystone XL pipeline create good jobs for working families," he said. "Keystone XL is ready now to create thousands of jobs, while at the same time increasing America’s energy security." The road for Keystone XL extension approval has been long. Canadian and U.S. phases of pipeline -- often called the Keystone pipeline -- are completed and operational, but proposed U.S. additions have yet to be approved. TransCanada proposed the XL extension in 2008. Late last year, Congress passed a bill mandating a decision on the project from Obama within 60 days. Obama rejected the application in January, saying the deadline didn't allow for a proper review process. The president has since said the project is a priority for his administration. TransCanada's route through Nebraska has drawn extensive criticism from environmental groups and landowners. Many worried about the initial route proposal, saying that it crossed unconfined aquifers and other sensitive areas. The company redrew the route and submitted a new plan which it says avoids such areas. The company began construction on the southern part of the line -- which runs from Oklahoma to the Gulf of Mexico -- earlier this year. Barrasso said Obama should turn his attention toward the project, especially now that he's secured re-election. "The politics surrounding this decision should also be over," he said. "If the president is serious about improving our economy and helping America become an energy independent nation, he’ll approve the Keystone XL pipeline immediately." A final decision on the project is expected sometime early next year. tribDOTcom/business/energy/wyoming-u-s-sen-barrasso-pushes-obama-on-keystone-xl/article_b2c5fb1a-26e1-52f9-8e29-976a21402740.html?comment_form=true</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354042657196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:57:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354042792839-19</Id><Title>Republicans Refuse to Admit that Keystone XL will Bring Oil Through America, Not to It - Wyoming U.S. Sen. Barrasso pushes Obama on Keystone XL pipeline</Title><Msg>Headline Republicans Refuse to Admit that Keystone XL will Bring Oil Through America, Not to It ---------------------- ----------------------- Headline Wyoming U.S. Sen. Barrasso pushes Obama on Keystone XL pipeline</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354042792839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:59:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354043646841-20</Id><Title>Interest rate spiral</Title><Msg>It may well be impossible to balance the budget given the current political reality. So the bond market will have enforce a new reality one of these days. Rising interest rates will force the government to abolish Medicare and terminate the $1 trillion or so in tax deductions in the Tax Code. Then the budget will balance. Taxing bond holders to raise revenues will not work either, at least not treasury bill holders, as the tax rate will simply get passed into the interest rate... Most government debt is short term too... Shorting long term Treasury Bonds would be a good move once the Fed starts to run out of bank reserves to manipulate rates with. It will run out eventually, at least from a practical point of view, as its continuing borrowing of reserves reduces bank lending and makes the economy worse and worse the longer it goes on. The politicians will eventually end the policy. If they resort to actual printing of money the short term rate will rise at parabolic rate, destroying the government's credit for all time.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354043646841</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 14:14:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354044285735-21</Id><Topic><Title>Time to start shorting...</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354041479574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:37:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cha -ching... covered at $140.79... will wait until they get hopeful again</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354044285735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 14:24:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354047856559-22</Id><Topic><Title>What Buffett Is Missing in His Tax Plan</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353959368769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 14:49:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think the spending is bad now just think what it will look like with just a 5% interest rate on $16.3, $17, $25 trillion in debt. Then start applying an 8% rate, then 10%, then 15%. If it starts printing money, instead of borrowing bank money to pay its bills, the interest rate will just spiral up faster still. It gets ugly. The corporations can be taxed to just about any number you can think of. Gold can be purchased at whatever price the Treasury sees fit as legal tender to inspire faith in the debt and avert the collapse of the government. Dividends can be taxed at 90% if they want. They can try to tax interest at 90% too, but that will just make the interest rate go up faster and faster...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354047856559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:24:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354049138822-23</Id><Title>HMS Britannia listing at bow...</Title><Msg>Its national credit card is very nearly maxed out. The North Sea oil reserves that had been underpinning the pound and its socialist government since the 1970s, and paid for a great deal of climate change rubbish since the 1980s, are nearly gone and the taxes they generated nearly gone. It has all but shut down its once mighty coal industry, the same one that led it out of the middle ages to the richest most powerful Empire. Gas drilling has been banned too. Nuclear is no good anymore. London's financial "industry" is a shadow of itself and would have collapsed totally in 2008 if not for the British government putting the national credit on the line to nationalize most of it. In the end, the financial industry produces very little, especially when an equally good, and even more bloated one exists in New York, Europe, and Japan... Nothing they do these days could be construed as capitalism unless you count constructing new financial derivatives and banking ponzi schemes capitalism. It will end badly.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354049138822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:45:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354052171335-24</Id><Topic><Title>Greedful Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1353927170760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 05:52:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't agree with invest in this post but I guess you didn't read the 2nd and 4th sentences. Comprehension seems to be a problem of yours. As to Soros he has openly stated that he wants to see a single global government. It's not exactly a secret.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354052171335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 16:36:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354052287717-25</Id><Topic><Title>PraPra Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354015228461</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 06:20:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>prapra is indeed a wahleee alias. I don't think greedful is. While I don't agree with greedful, wahleee boy could not fake that much intelligence no matter how hard he tried.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354052287717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 16:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354052569860-26</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid the Country needs "Filibuster Reform" in 2013 !! Screw McConnell no power !!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1353993785986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 00:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reid, Obama and Clinton all gave major speeches in the Senate strongly opposing these same changes when they were proposed by the Republicans when the latter controlled the Senate and wanted to stop Dem filibusters. They said it would ruin the government. Interesting how things appear to have changed. But then you are a devotee of hypocrisy. As to the Senate, the Dems control it currently so don't need to filibuster to block legislation. Reid just refuses to let the Senate vote obn anything he doesn't like - such as a budget for example. He is widely hated in the Senate, including my many Dems. And for good reason.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354052569860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 16:42:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354060303029-27</Id><Title>Falling off the Fiscal Cliff would help the U. S. long term</Title><Msg>It would put all the burden on the politicians. It would make the fools really look like fools. It would have the common people marching on Washington. It may even lead to a REVOLUTION!!! It will help the people, because it would be an open wound needing intensive care.</Msg><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1354060303029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 18:51:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354062476309-28</Id><Topic><Title>PraPra Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354015228461</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 06:20:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Cuss"? More Southern Stupid on display. Is stupid part of the school curriculum down there? Losing certainly is. You lose....AGAIN! Hahahahahahahahahahahahahaha!!!! AAAAAAAHahahahahahahahahahaha!</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1354062476309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:27:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354063744443-29</Id><Title>The Best- and Worst-Run States in America</Title><Msg>How well run are America’s 50 states? The answer depends a lot on where you live. Every year, 24/7 Wall St. conducts an extensive survey of all fifty states in America. Based on a review of data on financial health, standard of living and government services by state we determine how well each state is managed. For the first time, North Dakota is the best run. California is the worst run for the second year in a row. Which one is run by Dems???</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354063744443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:49:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354066388214-30</Id><Topic><Title>The Best- and Worst-Run States in America</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354063744443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>California's average income is quite a bit higher than that small rural state you mention, and it has more college educated people too and technical talent - whenever DARPA or one of the defense contractors is looking for a place to construct bombers or particle beam weapons, or some such device they look to California. Of course for the price of a house around the Getty Center in Brentwood you could probably buy several counties in ND though... I don't know what one would do with those counties but you could buy them. Grow weeds or wheat?</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354066388214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 20:33:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354066899794-31</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Refuse to Admit that Keystone XL will Bring Oil Through America, Not to It - Wyoming U.S. Sen. Barrasso pushes Obama on Keystone XL pipeline</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354042792839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 13:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Green Agenda will go down in flames. Obama, just today, stuck his finger in the eye of the EU blocking their carbon tax on U.S. airlines. China has already ordered its airlines not to pay the tax. As for the pushers of the Green Agenda fraud. Well, there's lots of historical examples of what happens to such people. The French Revolution is most instructive... It is neither here nor there where the oil goes anyway. The oil market is global.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354066899794</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 20:41:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354068260914-32</Id><Topic><Title>The Best- and Worst-Run States in America</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354063744443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not so much as you think, and North Dakota has essentially no debt. CA has the lowest debt ratings of any state and plays budget games every year. It's cost of living is much higher. Companies are leaving CA because of the tax and regulatory burdens and this will likely accelerate over time. That said, the weather is MUCH better in CA; so long as the big one doesn't hit, it's more pleasant living if one can afford it.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354068260914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 21:04:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354069425575-33</Id><Topic><Title>The Best- and Worst-Run States in America</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354063744443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To be more specific, CA median income is 57,287 (only 10th), unemployment is 11.7% and 16.6% are below the poverty line. ND median income is 51,700, 3.5% unemployment and 12.2% are below poverty line. Difference in taxes and cost of living way more than offsets the diff in median income. So, forgetting the climate, it's pretty clear which state is better run.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354069425575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 21:23:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354070520640-34</Id><Topic><Title>The Best- and Worst-Run States in America</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354063744443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those with limited means can go out past Edwards AFB and live cheaply, in a rural existence if they like that, or up in the mountains. No place in the South can match California on weather - too much humidity, and then there the hurricanes, and the schools are atrocious. California's private schools are excellent, and its universities top notch as I mentioned before. I can't say I really care about the debt situation as I don't invest in state bonds. The budget is headed for balance anyway, thanks to the tax increase they just put through and huge spending cuts, something that cannot be said for a state like Texas even with its oil and rather meager investments in teachers, fire and police. Texas' climate is just dreadful - too much humidity. No place beats California's weather...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354070520640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 21:42:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354070915523-35</Id><Topic><Title>The Best- and Worst-Run States in America</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354063744443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It depends on your perspective. The land costs more in California for a reason... If you want cheap land can find it easily as mentioned before, even in California. The income is lower out in a place like Barstow, or Victorville, where the land is cheap, about the same as you'd find in one of those rural states... The rural states do not have the colleges, and the defense labs, and the industry, and the biotech research centers, and the computer factories, and the enormous law firms, or the huge financial services industry, some of which actually does produce something useful... Neither do you have the ports which handle more commerce than the GDP of most other states, or the marinas filled with billions of dollars in yachts, etc, etc... Comparing a rural economy with the biggest urban economy in the country leaves much to be desired.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354070915523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 21:48:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354072222925-36</Id><Title>Group to sue EPA to force U.S. carbon rules for transport - Propose an "upstream" cap-&amp;-trade system targeting oil</Title><Msg>Group to sue EPA to force U.S. carbon rules for transport Tue Nov 27, 2012 7:00pm EST By Valerie Volcovici WASHINGTON, Nov 27 (Reuters) - A policy reform group plans to issue a notice on Wednesday informing the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency that it will file a lawsuit to force the agency to use federal rules to cap and charge for carbon emissions from the transportation sector. The Institute for Policy Integrity, a part of New York University's Law School, said it is acting because U.S. fuel efficiency standards are not stringent enough. The group sent the formal petition to EPA Administrator Lisa Jackson, requesting that she "propose and adopt regulations" that would set up an emissions trading system to curb carbon output from fuel used in vehicles and aircraft. The group said a comprehensive cap-and-trade system, which would set both a mandatory limit and price on each ton of carbon emitted, would be more effective than the Obama administration's fuel economy standard, which requires that new cars achieve an average of 54.5 miles per gallon by 2025. "Over the past four years, the Environmental Protection Agency has put several regulations in place to decrease greenhouse gas emissions, which contribute to climate change. But none are as comprehensive and cost-effective as placing a cap on emissions," the group said in a statement. Energy analysts are braced for a litany of lawsuits against the environmental regulator following Obama's re-election from environmental groups that want the EPA to take stronger action and from opponents of its rules. Michael Livermore, executive director of Policy Integrity, told Reuters that, if the agency remains in a "holding pattern" and delays the implementation of new pollution rules, he expects other groups to take legal action. The recent devastation that Superstorm Sandy caused along the U.S. East Coast highlighted the need for the administration to work faster to bring down carbon emissions, the group said. Policy Integrity petitioned the EPA to take the following actions: - Determine that greenhouse gases from vehicles and aircraft endanger public welfare - Propose an "upstream" cap-and-trade system targeting oil refiners - Propose joint rule making with the Federal Aviation Administration to incorporate fuels used in aircraft into the cap and trade system reutersDOTcom/article/2012/11/28/epa-carbon-idUSL1E8MRD4X20121128</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354072222925</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:10:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354072315603-37</Id><Title>Propose an "upstream" cap-and-trade system targeting oil refiners</Title><Msg>... Nov 27 (Reuters) - A policy reform group plans to issue a notice on Wednesday informing the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency that it will file a lawsuit to force the agency to use federal rules to cap and charge for carbon emissions from the transportation sector... ... Propose an "upstream" cap-and-trade system targeting oil refiners ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354072315603</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:11:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354072677238-38</Id><Topic><Title>The Best- and Worst-Run States in America</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354063744443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But in Texas we can cook out side or wash our car and not think someone will call the cops on us. If it wasn't for high tax people pay or Uncle Sam California could not pay any of its bills</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1354072677238</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:17:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354072701157-39</Id><Topic><Title>Propose an "upstream" cap-and-trade system targeting oil refiners</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354072315603</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:11:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sen. Jim Inhofe Touts Petitions Critical of Environmental Protection Agency Posted by Chris Casteel on November 27, 2012M at 4:06 pm Sen. Jim Inhofe, R-Tulsa, a frequent critic of the Environmental Protection Agency, said at a Capitol Hill news conference on Tuesday that the reelection of President Barack Obama will make it difficult to defeat some of the regulations under consideration by the agency. Inhofe joined with leaders of the Heartland Institute, a Chicago-based think tank that promotes free-market solutions to social and economic issues, to deliver petitions signed by about 16,000 people. The petitions call on Congress to rein in the agency and say, in part, “Whereas, regulators at the EPA, having lost their war to scare America into giving them legislation that would allow them to seize control of virtually all energy production and use, are perverting the Clean Air law to give themselves unprecedented powers to regulate American society.” Inhofe said the agency is currently crafting regulations that would regulate oil and gas drilling, the boilers used by manufacturers and farm dust. The costs of those, he said, would pale in comparison to the costs of rules regulating greenhouse gas emissions. Rules aimed at addressing climate change, he said, would constitute the largest tax increase in American history but accomplish nothing. Think Progress, a blog that is a project of the Center for American Progress Action Fund, noted that environmental groups have shown far more support for new rules than the Heartland Institute was able to generate for its anti-EPA petition. “Over the last two years, as the agency has finalized new regulations for mercury, air toxics, and global warming pollution, groups supportive of such measures have acquired record numbers of comments in favor of the rules,” according to a post on the blog. “Earlier this year, environmental and public health groups collected and delivered more than 3.2 million comments supporting EPA’s carbon pollution standard for power plants; in 2011, they collected more than 800,000 comments supporting EPA’s Mercury and Air Toxics Standard; and so far in 2012, groups have collected more than 420,000 comments supporting the EPA’s soot pollution standard. “Environmental organizations say the 3.2 million comments in support of EPA regulation of CO2 is the most of any federal rule, ever.” blogDOTnewsokDOTcom/politics/2012/11/27/sen-jim-inhofe-touts-petitions-critical-of-environmental-protection-agency/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354072701157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:18:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354072832606-40</Id><Topic><Title>Propose an "upstream" cap-and-trade system targeting oil refiners</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354072315603</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:11:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Greens are quite insane, which one should consider when they consider prospects for the economy...There is no doubt they will succeed in destroying more of the economy of the Western world, and reducing the living standard for most people in it even more than they already have, before, that is, they are annihilated, politically. The left, itself, will consume them as they offer nothing of use to most people. I can't say I will allow my living standard to be reduced - it's easy enough to profit from the failure they will cause... You should be ashamed of yourself to spread such rubbish across the net, however.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354072832606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:20:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354073424121-41</Id><Topic><Title>The Best- and Worst-Run States in America</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354063744443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are misinformed about California - you will not be arrested for washing your car. California is subsidizing quite a few rural states too. If we got a federal dollar back for every dollar in federal tax paid the state would be richer still, as would New York and other rich urban states. You can find plenty of studies on just which states are being subsidized by states like California. Basically the list comprises most of the "red" rural states and the federal funds redistributed from places like Brentwood go to pay for food stamps for the obese across the South, and much else besides, and also subsidize lower tax rates in those states. The allocation of federal funds should be reformed to stop such abuses...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354073424121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:30:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354074343435-42</Id><Title>API files suit against US EPA for 2013 biodiesel usage increase</Title><Msg>API files suit against US EPA for 2013 biodiesel usage increase By Ron Kotrba | November 27, 2012 The American Petroleum Institute filed a lawsuit in the U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Nov. 26 against the U.S. EPA for its decision to mandate the use of 1.28 billion gallons of biodiesel in 2013, a 28 percent increase from the 2012 requirement of 1 billion gallons, the statutory minimum. The institute also filed a petition with EPA to reconsider the biodiesel increase, as did the American Fuel &amp; Petrochemical Manufacturers last week. “EPA’s overzealous 2013 biodiesel mandate is unworkable, could raise the costs of making diesel fuel, and should be reduced,” said Bob Greco, API group downstream director. In EPA’s announcement about the 2013 increase, which came out in September, the agency said, “Producers of biodiesel, the largest contributor to biomass-based diesel, have significantly greater production capacity than will be required by to­day’s final rule. Moreover, many facilities that are producing volume currently are underutilizing their capacity, and can ramp up production relatively quickly. Finally, the biodiesel industry is already producing at a rate consistent with an annual volume of about 1.3 billion gallons which is enough to meet our established standards.” “In its final rule, EPA admitted the costs of increasing the biodiesel volume requirement for 2013 outweighed the benefits by as much as $425 million,” Greco said. In its final rule, however, EPA stated, “We estimate the cost of producing this increment in biomass-based diesel would range from $253 to $381 million in 2013. Adding the estimate of 2013 costs to the total 2013 fuel pool would suggest a diesel fuel cost increase of less than 1 cent per gallon.” In addition to $41 million in energy security benefits, EPA listed other benefits from the boosted mandate, including “GHG emissions reduction benefits and both direct and indirect employment benefits in rural areas due to increased biodiesel production. Impacts on water quality, water use, wetlands, ecosystems and wildlife habitats are expected to be directionally negative …” Greco continued, however, saying, “Furthermore, fraudulent biofuel credits that have plagued the system since last year and have yet to be resolved could inhibit industry’s ability to meet EPA’s higher biodiesel mandate.” EPA has uncovered more than 140 million invalid renewable fuel credits, known as RINs, generated by three biodiesel companies, representing between 5 and 12 percent of the biodiesel market. “The fraudulent RIN problem is having, and will continue to have, significant impacts on the biodiesel marketplace that make it more difficult for companies to comply with EPA’s mandate,” Greco said. On a Nov. 27 media call with API, Biodiesel Magazine asked Greco why API has not acknowledged the recent progress made in addressing the RIN issue through EPA’s early release of draft Quality Assurance Plan guidelines for RIN verification programs, as the agency nears issuance of a proposed rule to restructure the RIN program. “We have not overlooked that,” Greco said. “In fact, we have pushed EPA to move faster on this, and as you mentioned, EPA is now close to releasing a proposed rule, hopefully we will see a final rule by middle of next year. But that doesn’t get to the underlying problem of accepting fraudulent RINs, the need for some certainty of how those will be treated by EPA, and also how it’s going to provide assurance until the final rule comes out. We will not have one by Jan. 1. We are working with EPA to get some assurance on that, but we haven’t gotten that yet.” The oil refiners and importers, referred to as “obligated parties” under the RFS, have been pushing for an “affirmative defense” with EPA, meaning they will not be punished with fines, penalties and notices of violation, as they have this year under EPA’s “buyer beware” stance for the good-faith purchase of what might later turn out to be invalid RINs. Speaking to EPA’s increase of the biodiesel mandate to 1.28 billion gallons next year, a decision EPA considered for more than a year, Greco said, “It was completely discretionary. EPA did not need to increase the mandate beyond the 1 billion gallons in the statute … EPA should not have gone beyond the statutory minimum of 1 billion gallons in 2013.” “It’s disappointing that the petroleum industry continues to fight advancements toward clean, renewable fuels—even as it embraces alternative energy in its marketing,” said Anne Steckel, vice president of federal affairs for the National Biodiesel Board. “The EPA clearly determined, in an independent analysis, that increased biodiesel production is good for the country. Last year alone, our industry supported more than 40,000 jobs, and next year the RFS is projected to save U.S. consumers $120.25 million at the pump. Going forward it will help consumers even more by expanding fuel options so that we’re not so dependent on imported oil and so vulnerable to this endless cycle of price spikes.” Greco also told reporters on the call that the RFS in its entirety should be eliminated because “it is not working well” and because it will require higher blends of ethanol in gasoline “that could harm vehicles,” he said. “We believe the renewable fuel standard is unworkable and should be repealed. Despite repeated and ongoing efforts to address the program’s shortcomings—through regulatory petitions, legal actions and suggested solutions to implementation concerns—little has been done to make the program workable, and sometimes actions have been taken that make matters worse. There is a fundamental flaw in the enabling statute so the only way to fix it is to scrap the law and start over if Congress believes such a program is necessary.” Greco said the RFS program was enacted at a time when the U.S. energy landscape was far different than what it is today. “With the current boom in domestic oil and natural gas development, we are steadily reducing our foreign energy dependence, well beyond what the RFS program has achieved,” Greco said. “The notion that we need a renewable fuel standard to promote energy independence and security, as the 2007 statute is named, has been turned on its head by the tremendous growth in domestic oil and natural gas.” Steckel said, “We would encourage the oil industry to drop these lawsuits and work constructively toward improving our energy security with a mix of traditional and renewable fuels.” Last week, the American Fuel and Petrochemical Manufacturers petitioned EPA to scale back its 2013 biodiesel mandate, to which Steckel responded, “The EPA was well aware of all of the issues AFPM has raised as it made its independent analysis and, ultimately, the agency made the right decision.” biodieselmagazineDOTcom/articles/8818/api-files-suit-against-us-epa-for-2013-biodiesel-usage-increase</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354074343435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:45:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354074423435-43</Id><Title>API files suit against US EPA for 2013 biodiesel usage increase</Title><Msg>API files suit against US EPA for 2013 biodiesel usage increase By Ron Kotrba | November 27, 2012 ...In EPA’s announcement about the 2013 increase, which came out in September, the agency said, “Producers of biodiesel, the largest contributor to biomass-based diesel, have significantly greater production capacity than will be required by to­day’s final rule. Moreover, many facilities that are producing volume currently are underutilizing their capacity, and can ramp up production relatively quickly. Finally, the biodiesel industry is already producing at a rate consistent with an annual volume of about 1.3 billion gallons which is enough to meet our established standards.”...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354074423435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:47:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354074923049-44</Id><Topic><Title>API files suit against US EPA for 2013 biodiesel usage increase</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354074423435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:47:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...then gave the EPA discretion to set future annual targets... truckinginfoDOTcom/news/news-detail.asp?news_id=78646&amp;news_category_id=42</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354074923049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:55:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354074988379-45</Id><Topic><Title>API files suit against US EPA for 2013 biodiesel usage increase</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354074423435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:47:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>URLs at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354074988379</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:56:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354075563957-46</Id><Topic><Title>The Best- and Worst-Run States in America</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354063744443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We're not talking about which states are nicer but which states are well run. Given California's advantages it's fiscal mess is even more despicable.It's fall is coming soon. Enjoy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354075563957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 23:06:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>