<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343967525000-1</Id><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Msg>Rex Tillerson CEO of XOM has made some world-class blunders (XTO cash squandering debacle, and cash wasteful excessive share buybacks, and huge personal exec. compensation packages). CVX has replaced XOM as industry standard due to T. Rex's failed leadership. Shareholders have gotten shafted by this out-of-control T. Rex. He is a bull headed unenlightened person who operates unchecked by his passive Board. Enough is enough. T. Rex should be retired immediately with no bonus. Dividend payouts should be returned to 40% as they were 25 years ago. Let's put shareholders first, and get rid of this T. Rex.</Msg><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343977361000-2</Id><Title>200 DOLLAR OIL ON THE WAY DUE TO WAR WITH IRAN</Title><Msg>VERY SOON GET READY AND WATCH!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>salomonbernstein</Username><Timestamp>1343977361000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 03:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344004598000-3</Id><Title>Split?</Title><Msg>Has there been any rumors about a 2 for 1 split on this stock??</Msg><Username>jtddetailing</Username><Timestamp>1344004598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344005205000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Split?</Title><Username>jtddetailing</Username><Timestamp>1344004598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. All the majors are up today.</Msg><Username>jhenryallin</Username><Timestamp>1344005205000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344005925000-5</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BRAVO! He has vested options out the ying-yang and can feed off the buyback pool for decades to come. Get someone in there who has some loyalty to the general shareholders.</Msg><Username>tsobie</Username><Timestamp>1344005925000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344006071000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Split?</Title><Username>jtddetailing</Username><Timestamp>1344004598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only the one you're trying to float now. Not so nice try.</Msg><Username>tsobie</Username><Timestamp>1344006071000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344006919000-7</Id><Title>Midwestern Governors Urge Automakers to Support B20</Title><Msg>Midwestern Governors Urge Automakers to Support B20 Wisconsin Ag Connection - 08/03/2012 The Midwestern Governors Association has formally asked major diesel engine and vehicle manufacturer to support the use of biodiesel blends of at least 20 percent in all diesel-powered equipment. The group of nine state executives, including Wisconsin Governor Scott Walker, says more than 13 states are encouraging use of higher biodiesel blends from B2-B20 through a variety of state policies. "As Governors, we see increasing the use of biodiesel as an important part of diversifying our nation's energy portfolio," the MGA said in a letter sent to 23 automakers and Original Equipment Manufacturers. "We will continue to encourage policies that will expand consumer access to higher blends of biodiesel." Members also noted that as biodiesel use grows in the marketplace, there are significant advantages to ensuring all diesel vehicles are compatible with higher blends. According to the National Biodiesel Board, more than 65 percent of the diesel engine and vehicle manufacturers selling equipment in the U.S. already publicly support the use of B20 biodiesel blends. "It is our firm belief that companies that support B20 will capture market share from those companies that choose not to support B20--especially in the Midwest," the letter said. Biodiesel is a renewable fuel made from agricultural byproducts and co-products, such as soybean oil. http://www.wisconsinagconnection.com/story-state.php?Id=918&amp;yr=2012</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344006919000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:15:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344020234000-8</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you should read the proxy statement? Tillerson has no vested options.</Msg><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344020234000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:57:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344026829000-9</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perho... what happens when chevron loses their Brazil assets, including their biggest deep water oil project, then also loses their Canadian assets and also their huge Australian assets, simply because chevron refuses to settle the Ecuador case?... Brazil and Ecuador have a treaty that facilitates reciprocal enforcement of judgements... chevron is in both Canada and Australia to fight the Ecuador attempt to seize those assets too... losing those assets, chevron undoubtedly won't be able to payout dividends... oh well... and now the largest shareholders of chevron are urging chevron to cut a deal with Ecuador... oh my... don't think we'll be buying anymore shares of chevron anytime soon... have a nice day...</Msg><Username>be.pick</Username><Timestamp>1344026829000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:47:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344027348000-10</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If true, how is any of that happens, how is any of it going to make the XOM CEO a better exec...</Msg><Username>jhenryallin</Username><Timestamp>1344027348000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344027412000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corpo XOM Didn't Catch me with my Pants Down.</Title><Username>wisecolon432</Username><Timestamp>1344005466000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More and more of the same tired stuff....</Msg><Username>jhenryallin</Username><Timestamp>1344027412000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344027452000-12</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exxon up 15.51% for the year(87.94 high 67.03 low) . Chevron up 11.72 % for the year ( high 112.28 low 86.68) .</Msg><Username>rbcamer55</Username><Timestamp>1344027452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344031367000-13</Id><Title>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending August 1, 2012</Title><Msg>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending August 1, 2012 Release Date: August 2, 2012 In the News: Natural gas consumed for power generation (power burn) declined slightly for the report week, while remaining high for recent years. After extremely hot temperatures last month receded some, natural gas demand for power generation decreased below last year’s levels. Despite this week’s declines, power burn this summer has been at historically high levels, partly because of a much warmer-than-normal July. In particular, the Southeast has shown large year-over-year increases in power burn. Southeast power burn peaked this summer at 12.5 billion cubic feet (Bcf) per day on July 26, according to BENTEK Energy LLC (Bentek) data. According to NOAA, temperatures over much of the United States are forecasted to be above normal in the next weeks, which may result in a rebound of natural gas demand for power generation. NOAA predicts high temperatures in the 90s and above over much of the country in the next few days. Overview: (For the Week Ending Wednesday, August 1, 2012)•Natural gas prices increased modestly for the report week (Wednesday to Wednesday) at many of the country’s trading locations, with an exception at the Algonquin Citygate trading point (for delivery into Boston), which registered an increase of 39 cents per million British thermal units (MMBtu). The Henry Hub price closed at $3.20 per MMBtu, up 1 cent for the week. •The natural gas futures market trended steadily higher over the week. At the New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), the September 2012 natural gas contract gained 12 cents per MMBtu to close at $3.171 per MMBtu yesterday. •Working natural gas in storage rose last week to 3,217 Bcf as of Friday, July 27, according to the U.S. Energy Information Administration’s (EIA) Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report (WNGSR). An implied storage build of 28 Bcf for the week positioned storage volumes 472 Bcf above year-ago levels. •The natural gas rotary rig count, as reported by Baker Hughes Incorporated on July 27, declined by 13 to 505 active units. Meanwhile, oil-directed rigs increased by 2 to 1416 units. more summary data Prices: Natural gas prices increased modestly over the report week at most spot market locations. At most trading points across the country, spot prices increased less than a nickel for the week. Moderate temperatures in most regions over the week contributed to the low price variance. The largest price increase occurred at Algonquin Citygate trading point (for delivery into Boston), which increased by 11 percent from $3.58 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.97 per MMBtu yesterday. A forecast of warmer-than-normal temperatures for New England likely contributed to the increase. The NYMEX September 2012 futures contract rose by 4 percent from $3.052 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.171 per MMBtu yesterday. The settlement price increased significantly on Monday to $3.214 per MMBtu, the highest level since January. The 12-Month Strip (average of August 2012 to July 2013 contracts) also increased by 3.7 percent over the same period from $3.412 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.539 per MMBtu yesterday.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344031367000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344031428000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending August 1, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344031367000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Total consumption for the report week registered an overall decrease, with slightly higher industrial sector demand being offset by decreases in other sectors. According to estimates from Bentek, domestic natural gas consumption declined by 2 percent from last week, driven by decreases in power, residential, and commercial demand. Industrial sector consumption increased slightly by 0.3 percent. Total supply for the week was essentially unchanged, and registered a slight decrease of 0.3 percent, reflecting the drop in dry gas production. According to Bentek estimates, domestic weekly dry gas production was 0.1 percent lower than the previous week (although 3.2 percent above the same time last year). Imports from Canada decreased by 1.9 percent. Liquefied natural gas (LNG) sendout dropped sharply, down 10.7 percent from last week; sendout volumes remain well below (39 percent) year-ago levels. more price data Storage Working natural gas in storage increased to 3,217 Bcf as of Friday, July 27, according to EIA’s WNGSR. This represents an implied net injection of 28 Bcf from the previous week. This week’s injection was 28 Bcf below the 5-year (2007-2011) injection of 56 Bcf, and 15 Bcf below last year’s injection of 43 Bcf. Since April 27, injections of working natural gas into underground storage have fallen short of both year-ago levels and the 5-year average, although stocks remain well above historical levels. Inventories are currently 472 Bcf (17.2 percent) greater than last year at this time and 407 Bcf (14.5 percent) greater than the 5-year average. Two of the three storage regions posted increases this week. Inventories in the East and West regions increased by 30 Bcf over the week (with the 5-year average net injection of 49 Bcf) and 4 Bcf (with the 5-year average net injection of 5 Bcf), respectively, while the Producing region posted a decrease of 6 Bcf in working gas stocks (with the 5-year average net injection of 3 Bcf). In the Producing Region, working natural gas inventories decreased 8 Bcf (3.3 percent) in salt cavern facilities and increased 3 Bcf (0.3 percent) in nonsalt cavern facilities. Temperatures during the storage report week were 2.6 degrees warmer than the 30-year normal temperature and 1.9 degrees cooler than the same period last year. Temperatures in the lower 48 States averaged 77.9 degrees, compared to 79.7 last year and the 30-year normal of 75.3. While overall temperatures were a few degrees warmer than normal, temperatures varied somewhat across Census Divisions. The West North Central and East North Central Census divisions in the Midwest were particularly warm, averaging 6.4 and 4.9 degrees, respectively, warmer than the 30-year normal. Temperatures in the New England Census division were cool, averaging 0.7 degrees cooler than the 30-year normal.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344031428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:03:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344031633000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending August 1, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344031367000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:02:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Source U.S. Energy Information Administration Archived here... http://www.talkstock.com/tm.asp?m=424400&amp;mpage=1&#424452;</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344031633000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344033079000-16</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>goodness jhenryallin and y'all's other alias that all too often post together... we've increased XTO's reserves from 45 Trillion to 82 Trillion, making the purchase a tremendous bargain... Rex, in his early beginnings with the company came to understand fracking, thus he knew that XTO was a gem in the rough... and now, the price of gas is goin' up... have a nice day...</Msg><Username>be.pick</Username><Timestamp>1344033079000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:31:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344036789000-17</Id><Title>Summit to show algae’s potential as renewable fuel</Title><Msg>Summit to show algae’s potential as renewable fuel Rich Keller, Editor, Ag Professional | August 3, 2012 ShareThis With all the complaints about corn being used for ethanol production and the emphasis on rapidly advancing cellulosic ethanol production processes, one other method for biofuel production has received considerably less attention with the agricultural industry. That is algae-based fuel production. Even though those in agriculture don’t talk about algae as a source of fuel, there appears to be huge interest in algae as the source of renewable biofuel and much more. More than 800 scientists and stakeholders from around the world attended the Algae Biomass Summit last year, and attendance is anticipated to be larger at this year’s sixth annual conference in Denver, Colo., Sept. 24-27. The summit will showcase, in its engineering and analysis track, nearly 30 presentations by leading research scientists from national and corporate laboratories. The sessions will inform technical audiences about the latest in algae growing methods, biofuel and oil analysis and other developments related to growing and harvesting algae for fuels, food, feed and more, explained the Algae Biomass Organization (ABO) in announcing the summit. ABO admits that advances in engineering are still key to wide-scale commercial production of algae-based products. Top researchers in the world will be attending and presenting at the summit, said Phil Pienkos, principal group manager, Applied Sciences for the National Bioenergy Center at the National Renewable Energy Laboratory and chair of the Algae Biomass Summit. "Combined with the incredible advances in algae biology, we're seeing significant opportunities to increase yields, while reducing energy and water requirements and maximizing co-product potential," he said. In a broad claim of superiority for algae production, ABO included the following statement in its summit announcement: “Products made from algae are the natural solution to the energy, food, economic, and climate challenges facing the world today. Algae have the power to simultaneously put fuels in vehicles, recycle CO2, provide nutrition for animals and people and create jobs for millions of Americans.” The ABO is the trade association for the U.S. algae Industry. More information about algae production can be found at http://www.agprofessional.com/news/Summit-to-show-algaes-potential-as-renewable-fuel-164743696.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344036789000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344037499000-18</Id><Title>Lawmakers push EPA to waive corn ethanol requirement</Title><Msg>Lawmakers push EPA to waive corn ethanol requirement By Zack Colman - 08/02/12 11:46 AM ET The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) should waive a corn ethanol production target for as long as possible to reduce costs for ranchers, a bipartisan group of lawmakers said Thursday. The congressmen discussed a letter signed by 156 legislators that urges EPA Administrator Lisa Jackson to scale back the renewable fuel standard (RFS) in the face of a nationwide drought. Rep. Steve Womack (R-Ark.) said the shortage of corn combined with this year’s target of blending 13.2 billion gallons of corn ethanol into traditional transportation fuel has increased operational costs for livestock companies in his district. “The price of corn is killing these companies. And if something isn’t done and done fast, many of them will have to reduce production, which will lead to layoffs,” Womack said. The EPA administrator can waive the ethanol target in part or in whole if reaching it causes severe economic or environmental harm. “That provision was written for conditions like the one we experience today,” Womack said. A pair of corn ethanol trade groups is holding a press conference at noon Thursday in support of the ethanol target. Reps. Bob Goodlatte (R-Va.) and Jim Costa (D-Calif.), who sponsored a bill that would let the EPA reduce the corn ethanol target by as much as 50 percent when corn stocks run low, also implored Jackson to invoke the RFS waiver. Goodlatte said in a response to a question from E-2 Wire that the bipartisan letter shows momentum exists for his bill, though he did not indicate any specific plans for it. Both Goodlatte and Costa favor eliminating the corn ethanol portion of the RFS, but want to preserve the part that sets a quota for “next generation” cellulosic biofuel. They say corn ethanol production has raised food prices both domestically and internationally by tying corn production to fuel. http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/241847-lawmakers-push-for-epa-to-end-corn-ethanol-requirement</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344037499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344037667000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Lawmakers push EPA to waive corn ethanol requirement</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344037499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:44:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production http://ethanolrfa.org/pages/weekly-ethanol-feed-production Ethanol Production % of Gasoline Demand SHRINKING</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344037667000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344037848000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Lawmakers push EPA to waive corn ethanol requirement</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344037499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:44:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>National Weather Service Enhanced Radar Image http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/index_loop.php Upper Mississippi Valley Sector http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/uppermissvly_loop.php Central Great Lakes Sector http://radar.weather.gov/Conus/centgrtlakes_loop.php</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344037848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344043417000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Lawmakers push EPA to waive corn ethanol requirement</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344037499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:44:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Corn export premiums lower at US Gulf Coast August 02, 2012 RECORDER REPORT 0 Comments Export premiums for corn at the US Gulf Coast were flat to lower on Tuesday, pressured by poor demand amid ample available supplies of cheaper South American grain, traders said. US corn export program seen shrinking substantially in 2012/13 as drought reduces the Midwest crop and as Brazil will likely export record volumes after its largest-ever corn harvest. Brazilian corn for August-September shipment was offered at a $35-per-tonne or larger discount to US Gulf corn on a FOB basis, according to Reuters data. Taiwan's MFIG bought 60,800 tonnes Brazilian corn via a tender on Tuesday. Several US corn cargoes have been cancelled over the past two weeks. Talk that up to nine cargoes of mostly new-crop corn sold to China may have been canceled, a trader said. Four of the cargoes canceled were confirmed last Thursday by USDA. Taiwan Sugar seeks 23,000 tonnes US corn, 12,000 tonnes US soyabeans via a tender. Argentina seen growing more corn and wheat as export quota system updated. Soyabean export premiums at the US Gulf were mostly steady to weaker, with nearby values easing in tandem with lower CIF barge basis bids, traders said. July and first-half August CIF basis bids fell sharply on Tuesday as August futures were entering delivery and as demand from domestic processors faded. Soyabean export demand was muted, with some Chinese inquiries for October US shipments and new-crop South American shipments generating few new sales, traders said. Wheat export premiums at the US Gulf Coast were weaker on sluggish demand. US wheat was not competitive in the world market after prices rallied since mid-June, traders said. Jordan bought 100,000 tonnes Black Sea wheat via a tender on Tuesday. Awaiting results from a tender by Algeria to buy a nominal 50,000 tonnes soft wheat. The country most likely to buy French-origin wheat. Russia said it would be able to maintain an exportable grain surplus, even after a drought-hit harvest. Western Canada's CWB grain-marketing monopoly ends on Tuesday. Canadian wheat seen entering new markets. http://www.brecorder.com/agriculture-a-allied/183/1222993/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344043417000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:23:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344044415000-22</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe you need to get your facts (and opinons straight) 1) XOM is still the industry golden standard on operations, strategy, etc. They are now and always have been conservative in the finance world. 2. IIRC the XTO deal was done with treasury stock not cash. Plus it will be a very good deal in the long run. Yes NG is down, but XTO had other assest (i.e. the NGLs can condensate heavier properties.) You can't just look at NG price and evaluate the deal. Plus in teh long run, NG will come up in price in the US (the rest of the world it still is up.) 4) XOM halted granting options about/over a decade ago. Any options Rex might still have were granted then and are likely to run out of time here very soon (so that problem, if one considers it a problem, is gone soon.) The remaining employee options XOM has (ormight have) outstanding are from aquired companies (particularly XOM). Those will also expire or be exercised 'soon'. Employee options are a nothing. 5) Yep Rex is 'overcompensated' but that is not unique to xom or even to the oil biz. It is indemic in biz today. Rex's compensation is inlign with his 'peers'. It is that all the corp big wigs are overcompensated. Changing CEO's won't fix that (the next will just also be overcompensated.) Even moving your investments won't fix it as that exec will just be overcompensated. 6) 25 years ago is a very long time. The market has changed dramatically since then. So have tax rules (for both XOM and individuals). To insist on going back in time does not mean what worked then will necessarily work now. Stock buybacks are effectively the same as dividends anyway. Except they allow the investor the choice if he wants to pay taxes now or 5, 10, 50 years from now. Plus if you look at XOM's performance over those 25 years, they are well up there compared to broad markets and most other large cap stocks in the US. BTW, if you really don't like XOM, its divi, its strategy, its boss, or whatever you can freely choose to leave anytime you want. 2)</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1344044415000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344044848000-23</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't hold your breath waiting for Ecuador to win and collect even close to the scale your are espousing.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1344044848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344045766000-24</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the SEC Form 4 disclosing insider trading and "stock options". http://www.secform4.com/insider-trading/1198805.htm</Msg><Username>tsobie</Username><Timestamp>1344045766000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:02:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344046039000-25</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fore,well said,i guess he can read the share price of 87 plus or the div. inc. yr over yr.by the way i still have some 14,15 and 28 dollar xom,that should tell him something!!</Msg><Username>wdsjr22949</Username><Timestamp>1344046039000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344046826000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Split?</Title><Username>jtddetailing</Username><Timestamp>1344004598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No and why are you trying to start them about a meaningless topic.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1344046826000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:20:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344048030000-27</Id><Topic><Title>XOM's T.Rex has to go!</Title><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1343967525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:18:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TYVM, BTW, still have my very first shares of XOM (and I actually have them as they were a gift and given in parper certificate form. The rest are all in street name and only electronic). Those shares are now under $10/sh. Just wish i had been given more or had been smart enough to buy more, sooner.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1344048030000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344052374000-28</Id><Title>Almost there</Title><Msg>If XOM can just add another $1.25 it should be a easy run to $95.00.</Msg><Username>bhenning32</Username><Timestamp>1344052374000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 23:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>