<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356874129693-1</Id><Topic><Title>A Purified Elite America</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356825754436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 19:02:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welfare will be abolished completely under nobumba. He will run out of $ when the rich send their assets overseas. Lots of poor hungry people coming soon. We will see who gets the last laugh on the dumbocraps.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1356874129693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 08:28:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356875257820-2</Id><Title>To listen to the left boast</Title><Msg>...you would think they actually won something. What they won was the US Presidency without control of the US House. In the United Kingdom such an absurdity cannot happen as such a government cannot govern. New elections would be held, and held, and held again until something was elected that could govern. The US Constitution prevents such flexibility. The US founders, you see, rejected the flexibility of their English heritage, and opted for a new design. So what we have now is a ship with no captain, rudderless, and adrift, and headed into a tempest. The tempest promises to be most severe - the biggest depression in modern history, most probably. The payoff will be what gets elected in 2016. 4 years of such idiocy and collapse is bound to backfire on the Party most visibly in charge. Obama has made himself prominent in the "cliff" negotiations and that helps too... *oil price out of control *budget deficit out of control *trade deficit out of control *medical prices skyrocketing with no end in sight *no national transportation policy except Congressional pork. *an energy policy that consists of EPA destroying the coal industry, and if they have their way natural gas too *a monetary policy that consists of deliberately pumping and inflating the stock market, something that has never stimulated the economy, and, in point of fact, caused the Great Depression.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356875257820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 08:47:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356876466310-3</Id><Title>Congress supports biofuels for the military *want 50% of their fuel from advanced biofuels by 2020</Title><Msg>Congress supports biofuels for the military Rich Keller, Editor, Ag Professional | December 28, 2012 According to the Environmental Entrepreneurs organization, passage of the U.S. Defense Department authorization bill clears the way for biofuel industry growth. Congress on Dec. 21 gave its endorsement to the military’s advanced biofuels programs by passing the National Defense Authorization Act (NDAA) without including controversial proposals that would have banned the Department of Defense from expanding its use of advanced biofuels. After passage, Environmental Entrepreneurs (E2) co-founder Nicole Lederer said, “This is good for the military, but it’s also good for our economy and our environment. “Just like it did with industries ranging from aviation to the internet, the military is leading the country on deploying advanced biofuels. By turning back short-sighted attempts that would have kept the military dependent on a single fuel source—oil—Congress has cleared the way for the Department of Defense to continue to make investments in advanced biofuels that will have positive impacts on the industry and our economy.” According to a recent E2 report, more than 14,000 jobs and about $10 billion-plus in economic activity could be created if the military meets its previously announced biofuels goals. The Air Force and Navy—two of the biggest users of oil in the world—want to get 50 percent of their fuel from advanced biofuels by 2020.” E2 Environmental Entrepreneurs is a national “community” of business leaders who promote sound environmental policy that builds economic prosperity, according to its website. For more details on the potential impacts of the military’s biofuel programs, see E2’s website section by clicking here. agprofessionalDOTcom/news/Congress-supports-biofuels-for-the-military-184983311.html?ref=311</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356876466310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 09:07:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356877175442-4</Id><Title>Kansas ethanol plant poised to start up anaerobic digester soon</Title><Msg>Kansas ethanol plant poised to start up anaerobic digester soon By Holly Jessen | December 28, 2012 PHOTO Construction on an anaerobic digestion system (shown here in October) at a Kansas ethanol plant is now completed, with startup planned soon. Western Plains Energy If all goes as planned, a 50 MMgy ethanol plant in Oakley, Kan., will someday produce advanced biofuel from sorghum. To qualify as advanced biofuel, the company will power the plant with methane from its anaerobic digester system as well as utilizing other advanced technologies. There are several things that must fall into place before that happens, however. First, Western Plains Energy LLC needs to complete startup of its digesters—which it is poised to do soon. In fact, the company had planned to begin operations the day after Christmas but that was delayed due to weather conditions. “We are currently doing further thermal protection and will start up next week,” CEO Steve McNinch told Ethanol Producer Magazine on Dec. 27. “We want to make sure if we have to stop after we start that the plant is safe from freezing.” At full digester capacity, which the company expects to reach in March, the digesters will produce enough methane to completely refire the plant’s thermal oxidizer and boiler. In other words, the facility won’t need to use any natural gas and could someday even generate its own electricity with additional equipment. “The main focus right now is just getting the plant’s boilers off of natural gas and on methane but it’s certainly something we’re looking at moving forward,” he said. The U.S. EPA published a final rule for a grain sorghum fuel pathway in the Federal Register on Dec. 17. As expected, dry mill ethanol plants using natural gas and sorghum meet the lifecycle greenhouse gas emission reduction threshold of 20 percent, compared to petroleum fuel, qualifying it as a renewable fuel. However, ethanol plants using specified forms of biogas energy for process energy and all but 1.5 kwh electrical power per gallon of ethanol qualify as an advanced fuel with more than 50 percent reduction, compared to petroleum. Although Western Plains Energy will have an operating digester, to qualify as an advanced biofuel producer the final rule also calls for combined heat and power (CHP,) which the company does not utilize, McNinch said. However, the company does have other advanced technologies in place and petitioned the EPA for a separate pathway a little more than a year ago. With the final rule now published in the federal register the EPA can rule on Western Plains Energy pathway. “I believe they will rule favorably but it’s not final until they sign it,” he said. In the past, Western Plains Energy has used a mixture of corn and sorghum—commonly known as milo—however, the plan is to switch over to 100 percent milo when the digesters reach full gas capacity. “We’ve been 100 percent milo more often than we’ve ever been 100 percent corn,” he said. “Milo has kind of been our niche all around. When you live in a desert you have to use what grows well and grain sorghum certainly grows well here. It’s much more drought tolerant.” Western Plains Energy received a $15.6 million grant from the Kansas Department of Commerce, which it used to help build the digester system, installed by Himark biogas. Although the project was estimated to cost between $35 and $40 million, the final tally is somewhere upwards of $40 million. Still, McNinch said he doesn’t expect future digester projects to be that expensive. “There was a lot of engineering being done as we were building,” he said. The digester will primarily be fed with mature from a local feedlot. Other ingredients include thin stillage from the ethanol plant and food waste. Although there is interest in powering ethanol plants with biogas, full-scale adoption of the technology has been slow. ethanolproducerDOTcom/articles/9411/kansas-ethanol-plant-poised-to-start-up-anaerobic-digester-soon</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356877175442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 09:19:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356877948305-5</Id><Topic><Title>A Purified Elite America</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356825754436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 19:02:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ship USA is a big one, and heavily armored, and can hit a lot of icebergs without going down. I expect it to just plow through this ice field. The dollar is unlikely to be impacted much, as people will look ahead to the purified future that awaits after Obama is out. The dollar will probably take a hit on the severe selling of stocks next week, and I expect to move from £ to $ on that move. The ocean of wealth is deep and vast so carrying the US government to more sane future will be fairly simple. Obama being in the Oval Office, at the helm, for the run through the ice field is quite useful. In 2016 the Democratic Party will confront a Republican Party much changed from 2012, much changed...lol... For the average American things promise to become quite bad between now and then.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356877948305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 09:32:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356878870019-6</Id><Title>Solar Helps Delay Power Station Construction shelved due 2 suppressed wholesale electricity prices &amp; demand 4 electricity less than expected</Title><Msg>Solar Helps Delay Power Station Construction by Energy Matters In another example of solar power helping to stave off construction of fossil fuel based power plants, Energy Australia has decided to put the brakes on what was originally to be a 1GW gas fired power station. According to The Age, Energy Australia had applied to build the station at Yallourn in Victoria, but then revised plans to construct a smaller peaking power plant - which it has now also shelved due to suppressed wholesale electricity prices and demand for electricity less than expected. The company says there is no need to build the facility until much later this decade. The Australian Energy Market Operator stated earlier this year weakening demand was due to a number of factors, including uptake of rooftop solar panel systems and households and businesses stepping up energy efficiency efforts. A July report from REC Agents Association (RAA) revealed over previous three years electricity consumption in the eastern states' National Electricity Market had dropped by 3.2 %. While average wholesale electricity prices may have also dropped, thanks also in part to renewable energy's impact on the Merit Order Effect; the benefit certainly doesn't appear to be passed onto households. In fact, residential power bills in Victoria are set to increase again from January 1, adding to the pain caused by two price hikes this year. The additional burden will likely see some households New Year resolutions lists including striving for a cheaper power bill by going solar. According to national solar provider Energy Matters, a good quality 3 kilowatt solar power system installed in the Melbourne region can return a substantial financial benefit; particularly when focus is placed on self-consumption rather than exporting any surplus electricity to the mains grid. Victoria isn't alone in suffering under the pressure of continual and substantial power price hikes. Last week we reported the Australian Energy Regulator's (AER's) latest State of the Energy Market report reveals residential electricity prices have jumped 91% over the past five years nationally. energymattersDOTcomDOTau/indexDOTphp?main_page=news_article&amp;article_id=3532</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356878870019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 09:47:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356879578758-7</Id><Topic><Title>Solar Helps Delay Power Station Construction shelved due 2 suppressed wholesale electricity prices &amp; demand 4 electricity less than expected</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356878870019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 09:47:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coming soon! Peak natural gas in America! December 2013 - January 2014 LNG, by the time it has been developed the market will likely have vanished</Msg><Username>moooooooooooooooooooooooo4u</Username><Timestamp>1356879578758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 09:59:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356881809813-8</Id><Title>US Debt Limit Fight</Title><Msg>Congress will have to approve another increase in the US debt in January or February to avoid shutting down about 40% of the US government. The Republicans need to show some spine and force Obama to slash welfare and other waste. In the meantime, proving that he will not get his way, by not agreeing to his fiscal cliff plan, would be helpful too. After crossing the Rubicon, to so speak, on the cliff, there's not much to lose by going for broke and seeing which branch of the US government is the most powerful... In the end Congress is the most powerful. As paymaster to the military, and everything else they hold all the cards...Perhaps Boehner does not have the spine to lead. A new stronger leader should be picked...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356881809813</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 10:36:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356883629946-9</Id><Title>Kansas’ largest wind farm set to begin operation 438 megawatts</Title><Msg>Kansas’ largest wind farm set to begin operation Complex with 276 turbines covers parts of four southern counties, could power 160,000 homes. BY STEVE EVERLY The Kansas City Star Posted on Wed, Dec. 26, 2012 10:14 PM MARC MORRISON | Courtesy of BP The largest wind farm to be built in Kansas, Flat Ridge 2 is set to begin operations by year’s end. The wind farm, jointly owned by BP Wind Energy and Sempra U.S. Gas &amp; Power, is on a 66,000-acre site in south-central Kansas. Flat Ridge 2, jointly owned by BP Wind Energy and Sempra U.S. Gas &amp; Power, is on a 66,000-acre site covering parts of Harper, Barber, Kingman and Sumner counties in southern Kansas. The project has 274 wind turbines, each with capacity to generate 1.6 megawatts of electricity or a total of 438 megawatts. That’s enough to supply electricity to 160,000 homes. Besides being the largest wind farm in Kansas, the $800 million project is the largest ever to be built all at once, instead of in phases. The owners said the giant wind farm was built in Kansas in part because of its business environment but largely because of its wind resources, which have been ranked the second best in the United States. “Kansas is blessed by very strong winds,” said John Graham, the CEO of BP Wind Energy, which is a unit of the BP oil and natural-gas conglomerate. The opening of the wind farm will be a boost to Kansas, which has been relatively slow to take advantage of its wind. It is ranked ninth in the amount of wind-energy installations. The Kansas Energy Information Network says the state has 2,192 megawatts of wind energy capacity not counting Flat Ridge 2. Iowa, by comparison, has 4,536 megawatts of installed capacity, making it the third highest in the U.S. Nevertheless, Kansas still has felt some economic benefit from its wind energy. The Kansas City law firm of Polsinelli Shughart, in a study financed by groups or companies connected to the wind industry, found that wind energy had created 3,484 construction jobs, 262 operation and maintenance jobs, and 8,569 indirect and induced jobs in Kansas as the investment rippled through the state’s economy. The leasing of land for the wind turbines has meant $273 million in additional income for landowners and $208 million in revenue for community organizations and local and county government, the study concluded. Those numbers would grow further as more wind farms are built. But wind energy’s future is unclear, in part because of the low price of natural gas, which has made it an economical option to generate electricity. Wind energy has been bolstered by requirements in many states, including Kansas and Missouri, that electric utilities use renewable energy to meet part of electricity demand. Wind energy has also been boosted by the Production Tax Credit, which is used to reduce the price of electricity produced to help make it more competitive. Both aids have been attacked by opponents of renewable energy, and the tax credit, set to disappear at the end of the month, has been under the most immediate threat. In contrast to the wind-farm opening, some manufacturers have pulled back, in part because of uncertainty about the tax credit. One big manufacturer, Siemens Energy, in September cut 900 jobs in the U.S., including 256 at its factory in Hutchinson, Kan. BP Wind Energy, which previously built a smaller 100-megawatt wind farm in Kansas, says it has more land in the state for additional wind turbines, but those plans are on hold until the future of the incentive is resolved. Graham of BP Wind Energy said an additional six years probably was needed until the cost of wind turbines declined enough, along with some increases in efficiency, to allow wind energy to be competitive without the Production Tax Credit. “The reality is the industry needs it,” he said. The hope is the incentive will be renewed as part of the fix to avoid the “fiscal cliff” in Washington. Republican Gov. Sam Brownback and the state’s two U.S. senators support renewing the credit, but they’re exceptions to the general GOP opposition to renewal. One idea being discussed is a one- year extension with wind-energy projects under construction getting a second year to ensure they can be completed and qualify for the credit. The American Wind Energy Association, a trade group, has proposed a six-year phaseout that would start at 100 percent of the current credit and gradually decline over the period Dorothy Barnett, acting director of the Climate and Energy Project, a Kansas group seeking to reduce greenhouse gas emissions, said her preference would be a simple renewal of the credit, but a six-year phase-out would show that supporters of wind energy also understood the federal government’s need to get its deficit under control. “I hope we can come to some sort of compromise,” she said. But one of the toughest opponents of the tax credit said the six-year phaseout was insufficient. U.S. Rep. Mike Pompeo, who represents the 4th District of Kansas, said the American Wind Energy Association’s plan didn’t pass the laugh test. The wind industry is made up of multi-billion dollar companies who can stand on their own two feet, he said. He also would consider a phase-out but only if it quickly moved the industry off the taxpayer dole. “Without a real phase-out on the table, the only remaining solution is for the wind PTC (tax credit) to expire as scheduled at the end of the year,” he said in a in a statement. kansascityDOTcom/2012/12/26/3981957/largest-wind-farm-in-kansas-to.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356883629946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:07:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356884116276-10</Id><Topic><Title>Kansas’ largest wind farm set to begin operation 438 megawatts</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356883629946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:07:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sempra completes Maui wind farm December 28, 2012 6:00 am • Morgan Lee(0) Comments San Diego-based Sempra Energy has announced the completion of a wind farm in southeast Maui capable of powering 10,000 island homes. Perched on a ridge of the Haleakala volcano, the Auwahi Wind power plant consists of eight new turbines and a battery designed to sustain power during light wind conditions. The plant was built by Sempra U.S. Gas &amp; Power and BP Wind Energy under a 20-year contract with Maui Electric, a subsidiary of Hawaii's dominant regulated utility. The state is requiring utilities to increase the share of electricity generated from renewable sources to 40 percent by 2030. California's renewable portfolio standard requires 33 percent renewable generation by 2020. In a written announcement on Wednesday, Sempra recognized the support of neighbors to the project including the Ulupalakua cattle ranch. nctimesDOTcom/blogsnew/business/energy/sempra-completes-maui-wind-farm/article_569ea7ba-d28b-5221-91c8-c695fa290936.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356884116276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:15:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356886513131-11</Id><Topic><Title>Fire Congress</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1356625411278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-27 11:23:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you going to cry Max when the market tanks? I don't think the Republicans are children, and the fiscal cliff is really just the sideshow to the debt limit fight. You should not underestimate what a powerful party, in control of the most powerful branch of the US government, is capable of...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356886513131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:55:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356886588874-12</Id><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Msg>He is destroying the economy so he can be re-elected January 3rd. If he gives ground he will lose the GOP vote. So, he will let the country go off the 'cliff' for his re-election. Nice guy, eh? Just the kind of #$%$ you want in power. Shoot him.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356886770482-13</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Contempt of Parliament is a powerful concept... read up on it some.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356886770482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:59:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356888517560-14</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Believe me, I have. Hitler hated Parliament. He was able to get an entire nation to revolt. Don't think the US cannot have a revolution. It happens.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356888517560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 12:28:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356888566208-15</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I trust that you are being "watched"!</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1356888566208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 12:29:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356889697491-16</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hitler was elected, and retained the Reichstag for show. The Catholic Center Party gave him the votes to pass the Enabling Act which made him all powerful. It was all quite legal...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356889697491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 12:48:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356890058287-17</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've been asleep at the wheel, rewind, for months. You might want cover your eyes the next couple of months too...The irreconcilable situation of two Parties running a country, neither with the power to rule unless the other allows it, is not likely to be settled in a way that suits Wall Street. They live in the land Oz you should remember... Watch and learn.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356890058287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 12:54:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356894966011-18</Id><Title>Desperate Politicians &amp; Media</Title><Msg>Every time a big gambler on Wall Street has found themselves on the wrong side of the "fiscal" cliff trade they've had some imbecile in the media print a story uttered by Senate Republicans, or Wall Street's Senator from New York, expressing optimism about a deal. They very conveniently leave out all talk of the House of Representatives. That is by design because no leader from there has ever expressed any optimism about any deal involving Obama's plan, or Reid's plan, or any Senate plan. The one plan they did put up for a vote, one far short of anything the Democrats want, could not pass within the Republican Party, and if Boehner forces a vote on such a measure he might as well resign as speaker, and even then it probably would still fail a full house vote. The Republican majority is quite large, and most of them are extremely conservative, and they have nothing but contempt for the Democrats. The media is by far the most irresponsible group within American society. They are responsible for perpetuating a gross fraud on the American people in many ways, this latest example being just their most recent. Something should certainly be done about them in the years ahead, as current policies spin out of control to their ruinous conclusion - ruinous for most people, but not unexpected... The fiscal cliff is small issue to the big trend, but just another example...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356894966011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 14:16:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356896088508-19</Id><Title>Hitler killed far fewer Jews than Stalin...Stalin slaughtered 66 million Christians</Title><Msg>A seven month on the ground investigation by a team of RED CROSS investigators determined 272,000 people died in German camps. With full cooperation from United States military officials and Soviet military officials, the New York Times reported that in the 1946 Red Cross report that of the just over quarter million people who died in the camps, a large part of them were clergy and gypsies. There was no mention of gas chambers or genocide.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1356896088508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 14:34:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356897737473-20</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like you and Harry Reid are in desperate need of an intense refresher course on the Constitution. I don't need to "watch" any more. I have seen enough to know whats coming and Wall Street has little to nothing to do with "it".</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1356897737473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 15:02:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356898975870-21</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your judgement is poor and your attitude obnoxious. I don't know why I respond to you. I could care less what Reid wants, except to know what he wants and why, and how he will behave. The Constitution is irrelevant except to pinpoint precisely why the current impasse exists. The impasse suits me fine. It will most certainly not suit the gamblers on Wall Street, you included, and there is a 100% chance that when it crashes this ridiculous stock will too. You believe you are right winger, but a poor one... I expect there to be no place for you when the end game of economic collapse plays out the next couple of years. You will become quite poor indeed, along with many beggars besides. It will be a fearsome face you look up in the new face of the Republican Party that picks up the pieces. Considering your facile yelps of freedom and liberty it will be a fearsome for you indeed...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356898975870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 15:22:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356899632247-22</Id><Topic><Title>Hitler killed far fewer Jews than Stalin...Stalin slaughtered 66 million Christians</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1356896088508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 14:34:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That war could have been over in 5 minutes by a simple phone call made by Churchill to Hitler. Hitler never wanted to attack England. He approved of the British Empire - as most sensible people at the time did. The war raged on and on for a reason. The New York press and the London press loved the war, and Churchill's entire life was based around fighting wars or writing about fighting them. Lord Halifax came very close to being Prime Minister instead of Churchill, too, and if that had happened the phone call would have been made...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356899632247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 15:33:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356900093017-23</Id><Topic><Title>Desperate Politicians &amp; Media</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356894966011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 14:16:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so much for the media's optimism. The Senate Republicans have torpedoed the talks, such as they were... The House GOP will kill any deal anyway....</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356900093017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 15:41:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356902227137-24</Id><Topic><Title>Desperate Politicians &amp; Media</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356894966011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 14:16:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your pretty #$%$ stupid you #$%$ POS #$%$ Nobumba wants to and will collapse america.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1356902227137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 16:17:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356902342203-25</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt it.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1356902342203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 16:19:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356902603381-26</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you doubt is irrelevant. The Nazi party representatives were elected. They did hold the biggest voting block. Hitler was their leader. The Catholic Center Party did support them and allow them to pass the Enabling Act. These are facts. Your ignorance is just makes you look ridiculous.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356902603381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 16:23:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356903227550-27</Id><Topic><Title>Desperate Politicians &amp; Media</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356894966011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 14:16:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You silly libertarian creed is as much responsible for Obama as the Democrats. You should be ashamed of yourself, but then that is doubtful except you will surely miss the the money you lose gambling. In the end that's all you are - a silly gambler. Disgusting.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356903227550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 16:33:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356906888795-28</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Incoherent, ill-advised rubish. You have no idea what you are talking about. Nothing more than uneducated guessing about subjects with which you have no activity knowledge.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1356906888795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 17:34:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356907281744-29</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Incoherent, ill-advised rubish. You have no idea what you are talking about. Nothing more than uneducated guessing about subjects with which you have no activity knowledge." You should list your positions and daily losses going forward so that people can keep track of the extent of your asininity and arrogance. Who knows the example might even cure you of your condition and then you could have at least something left for the future...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356907281744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 17:41:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356908587754-30</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner is an egotistical SOB!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1356886588874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:56:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and binny, Your entire statement sounds like Contempt of Parliament. The reading material I had in mind for you was the English Civil War. Contempt of Parliament was expanded from a theoretical concept, rarely used, to a broad field and tool of governance. Kings and nobles could not stand up against it. Americans are much more passive. Your wording is coarse and not very well thought out, but perhaps typical, at least of many of the ranters that frequent this board.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356908587754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 18:03:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356911498582-31</Id><Topic><Title>Kansas’ largest wind farm set to begin operation 438 megawatts</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356883629946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:07:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On a calm day 0megawatts. like wind and solar power but if it has to compete on a level playing field with nat gas?</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1356911498582</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 18:51:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356914709868-32</Id><Topic><Title>Hitler killed far fewer Jews than Stalin...Stalin slaughtered 66 million Christians</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1356896088508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 14:34:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yet you can not watch a movie without the jews telling us about it</Msg><Username>chart2001</Username><Timestamp>1356914709868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 19:45:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356916415081-33</Id><Topic><Title>currency trade</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356715269305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-28 12:21:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold most £ to buy $. 1.6161 to 1.6169...+0.05% At this point mostly dollars and some pounds and euros... Going off the "cliff" will actually strengthen the dollar, although Wall Street's hysterical reaction pushes it the other way as it has done the past few days...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356916415081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 20:13:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356916660991-34</Id><Topic><Title>Hitler killed far fewer Jews than Stalin...Stalin slaughtered 66 million Christians</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1356896088508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 14:34:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jews were very heavily represented in the Bolshevik Revolution, 10 times or so their proportion of the Russian population. This should not be forgotten.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356916660991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 20:17:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356922831880-35</Id><Title>Wind Energy Firms Scrambling To Complete Projects By Year’s End</Title><Msg>Wind Energy Firms Scrambling To Complete Projects By Year’s End December 30, 2012 Image Credit: Jesus Keller / Shutterstock redOrbit Staff &amp; Wire Reports – Your Universe Online As 2012 draws to a close, American energy companies are racing to complete wind turbines in order to take advantage of a federal tax credit that expires once the clock strikes midnight on December 31. According to Matthew L. Wald of the New York Times, developers will need to have their wind farms fully operational before Tuesday in order to take advantage of a special wind energy tax credit. Companies that meet the deadline will be able to take a 2.2 cent tax credit for each kilowatt-hour worth of wind power produced during the first 10 years of operation, Wald said. That could amount to as much as $1 million for a large turbine, but turbines that are not operational before the start of 2013 are not eligible, he added. “Congress, which last renewed the credit as part of the 2009 fiscal stimulus package, balked at an extension this year,” the Times reporter explained. “Opponents argue that the money spent so far, about $14.7 billion, is enough, and that a renewal could cost about $12.2 billion were it to last for 10 years. They also complain that the credit allows wind machines to be profitable even when there is a surplus of electricity and the market price for it falls to zero. “The tax credit could be equal to one-sixth to one-half of the revenue from the wind turbine, depending on electricity prices in the area of the generator,” Wald added. “Wind advocates say that the wind production tax credit did not cost the taxpayers any money, because it stimulated economic activity, in the form of manufacturing and construction, that was taxed at the federal, state and local levels.” The tax credit amounts to about 30 percent the cost of building a large turbine, BBC News Environment Correspondent Matt McGrath said on Friday. It has lapsed three times previously – in 1999, 2001, and 2003, and each time it led to a drastic reduction in the number of wind farms being built in the US. Industry officials are hopeful the incentives will ultimately be renewed. “There’s a good chance we could get this extension, it is very hard to predict, but the industry is not making bets on the Congress getting it done,” Rob Gramlich, senior vice president at the American Wind Energy Association told the BBC. However, McGrath notes that even if such an extension were to be approved, “there is likely to be a significant curtailment of wind installations in 2013. Wind energy companies say they need longer time frames to negotiate deals to sell the power they generate.” As manufacturers rush to complete their projects before the deadline, the construction of wind turbine facilities has been outpacing that of new natural gas plants in recent months, Ehren Goossens and Christopher Martin of Bloomberg News reported earlier this month. “New wind capacity reached 6,519 megawatts by Nov. 30, beating the 6,335 megawatts of natural gas additions and more than double those of coal, according to data from Ventyx Inc.,” they said. “A surge of wind-farm connections in November and December could double the amount of wind capacity added this year to as much as 12 gigawatts, according to New Energy Finance.” redorbitDOTcom/news/science/1112755430/wind-turbine-energy-federal-tax-credit-subsidy-expiring-123012/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1356922831880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 22:00:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>