<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349950151677-1</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI BLUES PART 2 - THE HEARINGS!</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1349896971854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No but this country will collapse under nobumba.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1349950151677</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 06:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349950278638-2</Id><Topic><Title>Where's your money, Romney believers ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1349398373610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:52:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To all, dont bet with maxi dopey he is poor and dos'nt have 2 nickels to rub together. He is a poor boy commie bum that sucks off society.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1349950278638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 06:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349955919273-3</Id><Title>XOM UNION GUYS ARE NOW 86% FOR MITT ROMNEY ! WOW</Title><Msg>ITS ALL ABOUT SAVING AMERICA</Msg><Username>fillups481</Username><Timestamp>1349955919273</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 07:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349961972068-4</Id><Title>Romney Backs Renewable Fuel Standard</Title><Msg>Romney Backs Renewable Fuel Standard By Dave DeWitte, Reporter Story Created: Oct 9, 2012 at 5:34 PM CDT (Story Updated: Oct 9, 2012 at 5:34 PM CDT ) VAN METER, Iowa - The Iowa Renewable Fuels Association Tuesday thanked Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney for affirming his support for the Renewable Fuels Standard during a campaign stop in Van Meter. The Renewable Fuels standard provides a floor of demand for ethanol, which has been one of Iowa's fastest growing industries in the past decade. Romney's Agricultural Prosperity white paper, released during the Van Meter stop, said "Romney recognizes that biofuels are crucial to America's energy future and to achieving his goal of energy independence, and he supports maintaining the Renewable Fuel Standard to guarantee producers the market access they have been promised as they continue to move forward." Romney met with Iowa Renewable Fuels Association President Brad Albin and Iowa Renewable Fuels Association Board Member Walt Wendland briefly during his Van Meter stop, the association said, expressing his support for the Renewable Fuel Standard. Wendland is the CEO of Golden Grain Ethanol near Mason City and Homeland Energy Solutions of Lawler. Albin is vice president of manufacturing for the Renewable Energy Group. President Barack Obama, who is seeking re-election, has previously voiced support for the Renewable Fuel Standard. kcrg</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349961972068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349963078521-5</Id><Title>Exxon Mobil, warned Tuesday that its third-quarter earnings would be “substantially lower” than in the second quarter</Title><Msg>Chevron Cuts Its Forecast for 3rd-Quarter Earnings By THE ASSOCIATED PRESS Published: October 9, 2012 Chevron, the second-largest American oil company after Exxon Mobil, warned Tuesday that its third-quarter earnings would be “substantially lower” than in the second quarter. The company said in its interim earnings update that its oil production fell in the first two months of the quarter and that it had received a lower price for the oil it sold. In addition, Chevron said, its revenue from refining and marketing dropped as a fire damaged its refinery in Richmond, Calif., and Hurricane Isaac disrupted production at a refinery in Mississippi. American production fell by 19,000 barrels a day in the first two months of the quarter, largely because of the hurricane, the company said. International production dropped as well. The average price Chevron realized for a barrel of oil in the United States dropped to $95.44 in July and August, compared with $103.91 in the quarter from April through June. For international oil, the price dropped to $96.86 from $99.21. Charges for the quarter are expected to be higher as well, and foreign currency losses will hurt results. In the second quarter, Chevron, based in San Ramon, Calif., earned $7.2 billion, or $3.66 a share. Analysts had forecast net income of $6.2 billion, or $3.08 a share, for the third quarter, according to FactSet. Chevron is scheduled to report its third-quarter results on Nov. 2. The company issued its warning after the stock market had closed. In after-hours trading, Chevron’s shares fell 1.3 percent to $115.84. Chevron’s shares reached a high, closing at $117.96, last Tuesday. The stock is up about 10 percent so far this year compared with a gain of nearly 9 percent for Exxon Mobil. The shutdown of a crude unit at Chevron’s Richmond refinery in early August has contributed to a shortage of gasoline in California. The average price for a gallon of regular has spiked to $4.67 there this week. Chevron said Tuesday that the crude oil unit was expected to remain offline until the end of the year. nytimes</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349963078521</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 09:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349967110952-6</Id><Topic><Title>XOM says invest in teachers!? LOL!</Title><Username>boar292hog</Username><Timestamp>1349901367991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:36:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hate all those stupid whiny XOM commercials wasting our shareholder money! They should be about what a great and innovative company XOM is meeting our energy needs!! Thank God for TIVO because I fast forward all of them. BTW the Chevron ones are even worse!!!</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1349967110952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 10:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349968912898-7</Id><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending October 5, 2012</Title><Msg>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending October 5, 2012 U.S. crude oil refinery inputs averaged 14.7 million barrels per day during the week ending October 5, 97 thousand barrels per day below the previous week’s average. Refineries operated at 86.7 percent of their operable capacity last week. Gasoline production decreased last week, averaging 8.6 million barrels per day. Distillate fuel production decreased last week, averaging 4.3 million barrels per day. U.S. crude oil imports averaged 8.2 million barrels per day last week, up by 115 thousand barrels per day from the previous week. Over the last four weeks, crude oil imports have averaged 8.4 million barrels per day, 517 thousand barrels per day below the same four-week period last year. Total motor gasoline imports (including both finished gasoline and gasoline blending components) last week averaged 502 thousand barrels per day. Distillate fuel imports averaged 114 thousand barrels per day last week. U.S. commercial crude oil inventories (excluding those in the Strategic Petroleum Reserve) increased by 1.7 million barrels from the previous week. At 366.4 million barrels, U.S. crude oil inventories are above the upper limit of the average range for this time of year. Total motor gasoline inventories decreased by 0.5 million barrels last week and are near the lower limit of the average range. Finished gasoline inventories decreased while blending components inventories increased last week. Distillate fuel inventories decreased by 3.2 million barrels last week and are below the lower limit of the average range for this time of year. Propane/propylene inventories increased by 0.3 million barrels last week and are above the upper limit of the average range. Total commercial petroleum inventories decreased by 4.4 million barrels last week. Total products supplied over the last four-week period have averaged 18.5 million barrels per day, down by 2.4 percent compared to the similar period last year. Over the last four weeks, motor gasoline product supplied has averaged about 8.7 million barrels per day, down by 3.3 percent from the same period last year. Distillate fuel product supplied has averaged 3.8 million barrels per day over the last four weeks, down by 3.5 percent from the same period last year. Jet fuel product supplied is 0.9 percent lower over the last four weeks compared to the same four-week period last year. eia Data Overview (Combined Table 1 and Table 9) eia ------------------------------------- BLOOMBERG DOLLAR INDEX SPOT bloomberg ------------------------------------- Energy Futures Prices Below you may find all the futures prices &amp; quotes for: Crude Oil, Heating Oil, Gasoline RBOB, Natural Gas, ICE Brent Crude Oil, Ethanol (E) and more. Real Time Streaming Futures Quotes (CFDs) forexpros -------------------------------------- e85prices -------------------------------------- gasbuddy -------------------------------------- biodiesel -------------------------------------- Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report October 11, 2012 Released: October 11, 2012 at 10:30 a.m. (eastern time) for the Week Ending October 5, 2012. Next Release: October 18, 2012 Notes and Definitions Beginning with the report period for the week ending March 16, 2012, EIA is including salt dome and nonsalt facility subtotals for the Producing Region in the Summary section. The sum of the components may not equal the total for the Producing Region, because of independent rounding. Summary Working gas in storage was 3,725 Bcf as of Friday, October 5, 2012, according to EIA estimates. This represents a net increase of 72 Bcf from the previous week. Stocks were 236 Bcf higher than last year at this time and 269 Bcf above the 5-year average of 3,456 Bcf. In the East Region, stocks were 67 Bcf above the 5-year average following net injections of 42 Bcf. Stocks in the Producing Region were 160 Bcf above the 5-year average of 1,047 Bcf after a net injection of 27 Bcf. Stocks in the West Region were 42 Bcf above the 5-year average after a net addition of 3 Bcf. At 3,725 Bcf, total working gas is above the 5-year historical range. Working gas stocks in the Producing Region, for the week ending October 05, 2012, totaled 1,207 Bcf, with 260 Bcf in salt cavern facilities and 947 Bcf in nonsalt cavern facilities. Working gas stocks increased 15 Bcf in the salt cavern facilities and increased 12 Bcf in the nonsalt cavern facilities since September 28. An historical series of the salt and nonsalt subtotals of the Producing Region is available for download at eia URLs at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349968912898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 11:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349975000571-8</Id><Title>Survey: Adult film industry favors Obama</Title><Msg>The adult entertainment industry overwhelmingly favors President Barack Obama over Mitt Romney, a new industry poll finds. "In spite of being in an era of declining industry revenues due to the glut of free content available online and rampant piracy, the majority of adult insiders side with the Democratic incumbent Obama over the Republican candidate...," writes XBIZ, the adult industry news organization that conducted the poll. 68 percent of the 339 respondents polled said they would like to see Obama elected, while 13 percent said Romney, less than the 14 percent who said they wanted “someone else."</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349975000571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:03:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349978786458-9</Id><Title>Agreeing to agree on energy policy</Title><Msg>Agreeing to agree on energy policy By CHARLIE MELANCON | 10/11/12 5:04 AM EDT When it comes to determining how best to meet our future energy needs, there are no Republican solutions, nor Democratic solutions. That’s why I believe leveraging the presidential election to turn U.S. energy policy into the latest political football is bad for America. Consider the current debate on natural gas. Republicans recently tried to paint the Obama administration as opponents of the fuel. They cited the Department of Energy’s recent delay of a report on the economics of exporting natural gas, which was pushed back from a March 2012 release date, because of complexities in #$%$ing the global natural-gas marketplace. It’s now going to be released after the election, and Republicans say it’s an attempt to punt the debate. Yet, what Republicans conveniently ignore is that the Obama administration’s new power plant rules are crafted in a way that ensure all new facilities will run on natural gas, not coal or even alternative energy sources. While such a mandate may bring unintended consequences and needs to be closely examined, suggesting President Obama is against natural gas doesn’t pass the smell test. This is precisely the kind of election-year stunt that undermines earnest attempts to develop energy proposals, on which both parties should be able to agree. Americans deserve better. In this election year, both Democrats and Republicans proclaim to support plans that include a wide mix on energy sources. You just have to drive by a gas station and see the ever-increasing price for a gallon of gas to realize that our current dependence on foreign oil is bad for our wallet, not to mention a myopic foreign policy. Electricity bills are on the rise as well. Most Democrats want natural gas to be part of our energy solution, but don’t want to put all of our eggs in that basket. Those of us who were on the front lines in the aftermath of hurricanes Katrina and Rita saw firsthand just how volatile natural gas costs can be. As natural gas prices reached record highs, it was clear that we needed a diversified energy portfolio to keep America powered. The best approach is one that galvanizes numerous industries to develop scenarios, and then to #$%$ all based on their price, viability and environmental impact. The fact remains that no one single fuel is perfect (even natural gas), and that all energy sources bring certain risks and rewards. But there is a right way and a wrong way to determine which products are best for American families, the environment and our economy. The right way is to allow energy producers to develop their products in the open market. The wrong way, and the one we have seen too often in recent months, is to insert political pressure and try to paint one solution as the only way to move our country away from our dependence on foreign energy. To put it more simply: We cannot solve our energy problems based on the prevailing political winds. If government creates policies that give one industry a distinct advantage over another, the end result will be an inferior product at a higher price. I marveled the other day at all of the people standing in front of the Apple store, waiting for the new iPhone. Apple has created products that fit a specific societal need and has become very rich in the process. It didn’t need a government advantage to beat its competition. Apple was driven by the concept of building something that would make people want its specific product, even at a premium. When the marketplace puts companies — whether they make electronics or energy — on a level playing field, it motivates everyone to strive for success. When one company, or one product, is given an advantage — either through subsidies, decreased regulation or governmental mandates — innovation is stifled. Natural gas should be part of the solution to our energy crisis, and I look forward to the DOE’s #$%$ment of the impact gas exports will have on pricing. But, our federal government must also support efforts to ensure we can honestly #$%$ which energy solution best fits our needs. That means doing the things that help all fuel sources thrive, from issuing more oil drilling permits for the Gulf of Mexico, to encouraging the private sector to better harness the potential of renewable energy sources like wind and solar. If we do the right things to boost all technologies, the end result is likely to be increased marketplace competition, which equates to more jobs, better products and competitive pricing. But, when we inject partisan politics into the mix, we create an environment in which the deck is stacked. And, at the end of the day, it is virtually impossible for the best products to win. A presidential election is a time to think big, and it is encouraging to see all sides wanting to move ahead with energy projects based right here at home. So let’s agree that we’re in agreement, and not politicize a topic that is so vital to our future. Charlie Melancon, a Democrat from Louisiana, served in the U.S. House of Representatives from 2005 to 2011. He was a member of the Energy &amp; Commerce Committee. politico</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349978786458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349978931894-10</Id><Topic><Title>Survey: Adult film industry favors Obama</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349975000571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 13:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I watched PBS Frontline on Wed. night where they showed the early years of Romney and Obama. I was extremely impressed with Romney's early forming years. He showed great character before and after his college years. His near death made him a better man in his opinion and changed his outlook for the better. His dynamic rise in the business world during Bain and afterwards makes him a strong, intellectual person who deserves to be President. Compared to Obama's background, Romney is heads above Obama in directing the USA. He definitely will be our next President next year. Bye, bye Obama, you were a big mistake for our country.</Msg><Username>floridahank</Username><Timestamp>1349978931894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349979501036-11</Id><Title>Oil, business groups sue SEC over disclosure rule</Title><Msg>Oil, business groups sue SEC over disclosure rule By Ben Geman - 10/10/12 08:16 PM ET Oil industry groups and the U.S. Chamber of Commerce are asking a federal court to overturn new Securities and Exchange Commission rules that will force oil, gas and mining companies to disclose their payments to foreign governments. The lawsuit, filed Wednesday with the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia, escalates a battle between industry and human rights groups over controversial transparency rules required under the 2010 Dodd-Frank financial reform law. The American Petroleum Institute (API), U.S. Chamber and other groups say the regulators failed to justify what they call burdensome rules, and allege they will force companies to publicly disclose sensitive information. “The rule as written would impose enormous costs on U.S. firms and put them at a competitive disadvantage against government-owned oil giants not subject to the rule,” said API President Jack Gerard in a statement. The rule forces SEC-listed oil, natural gas and mining companies to reveal payments to governments related to projects in their countries, such as money for production licenses, taxes, royalties and other aspects of energy and mineral projects. It’s aimed at increasing transparency to help undo the “resource curse,” in which some impoverished countries in Africa and elsewhere are plagued by high levels of corruption and conflict alongside their energy and mineral wealth. The rules have been championed by an array of anti-poverty and human rights groups, and backers range from Bono to Bill Gates to George Soros. But the rules have faced pushback from companies including ExxonMobil, Chevron and Shell. The oil industry argues the rule will put SEC-listed companies at a disadvantage when competing against state-owned companies such as Russia’s Gazprom and the China National Petroleum Co. [Click here, here, and here for more of E2-Wire’s coverage of the battle over the rules.] The lawsuit cites the SEC’s estimate that the rule will bring roughly $1 billion in initial industry compliance costs, and ongoing compliance costs in the $200 million to $400 million range. “The rulemaking record shows that the costs will actually be far greater, as U.S. oil and mining companies are forced to allow competitors access to sensitive commercial information, and to abandon projects to foreign state-owned companies in countries that forbid the disclosures or that simply refuse to do business with U.S. companies because they do not wish the disclosures to be made,” the lawsuit states. The lawsuit drew quick criticism from Global Witness, which noted the Dodd-Frank provision “was intended to shine a light on billions in payments to governments from oil, gas and mining companies and to decrease opacity in this industry.” “Secrecy around payments enables corrupt government officials and political elites to siphon off or misappropriate revenues for personal gain, rather than development. It has been said that 'sunshine is the best disinfectant' – this lawsuit begs the question, what are oil companies trying to hide?,” said Jana Morgan, assistant policy adviser with Global Witness. The Independent Petroleum Association of America and the National Foreign Trade Council joined the suit against the SEC, which approved the rules in a split 2-1 vote in August. Gerard said the industry supports transparency, citing work with the Extractive Industries Transparency Initiative (EITI). It’s a voluntary collaboration that brings together nations, companies and nongovernmental groups aimed at ensuring government revenues from energy and mining projects provide public benefits. “We’ve been working hard to increase transparency for a decade, but this rule could interfere with ongoing efforts by making U.S. firms less competitive against state owned firms in China and Russia that have no interest in transparency,” he said. But advocates of the rules say the Dodd-Frank law is intended to go further than EITI. The new lawsuit alleges the SEC’s rule is illegal for several reasons. The industry groups claim that the regulators “misread” the Administrative Procedure Act by requiring public disclosure of company’s reports. The lawsuit also claimed the rule is “arbitrary and capricious” because it doesn’t define “project” as activities in a “geologic basin or province.” “This definition would have protected U.S.-listed companies from potentially billions of dollars in compliance costs, by providing certainty in application and by permitting companies to aggregate innumerable individual payments made under various contracts as long as they all related to extraction of a particular resource in a particular geologic area,” it states. It also challenges the SEC’s decision not to allow exemptions from the rules when foreign governments bar such disclosure; claims the regulators failed to properly analyze whether the rule creates burdens that are “necessary and appropriate” to further Congress’s goals; and that the SEC’s cost analysis was flawed. An SEC spokesman defended the regulation. “While we are still reviewing the suit, we believe our legal interpretation and economic analysis are sound, and we look forward to defending the rule that Congress directed us to write,” SEC spokesman John Nester told The Wall Street Journal. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349979501036</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349979790287-12</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI BLUES PART 2 - THE HEARINGS!</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1349896971854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With 4 more yrs of Obama, this country will be in shambles financially. China now owns us financially already and they will not tolerate Obama's wasteful projects and corruption much longer before the pull the trigger and demand us to give China $$$ that aren't worthless. I look for China to make a big move going into owning gold over the US $$$, and we'll be in a real depression. If Romney is President he has the business/industrial knowledge to at least begin to deal with $$$ reality and perhaps get a much better relationship with China-- the soon to be world's leader in many areas when it gets itself under control.</Msg><Username>floridahank</Username><Timestamp>1349979790287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:23:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349979940351-13</Id><Title>Westmore Fuel Cuts The Ribbon On New York Biodiesel Facility</Title><Msg>Westmore Fuel Cuts The Ribbon On New York Biodiesel Facility by NGT News on Thursday 11 October 2012 Westmore Fuel Company Inc. has opened its new biodiesel terminal in Port Chester, N.Y., integrating renewable fuel into both on-road diesel fuel and heating oil. The biodiesel is supplied by Ultra Green Energy Services LLC, which produces the fuel from recycled fat and oil feedstock. The company notes that the new terminal has expanded the distribution area of biodiesel into Westchester and Fairfield counties (in New York and Connecticut, respectively) and serves as "an important linchpin for the overall infrastructure base for biodiesel in the metro New York area." Westmore Fuel installed a 20,000-gallon storage tank for B-100 biodiesel, as well as equipment to blend the fuel with other diesel fuels and distribute it on four tanker-truck filling racks. The project garnered $200,000 in incentives from the New York State Energy Research and Development Authority and assistance from the National Biodiesel Foundation (NBF). "We are thrilled to have such a great partnership with Westmore that will provide a reliable supply of high-quality, precision-blended biodiesel to such an important metropolitan region, reaching important new fleets and customers," says Tom Verry, NBF's executive director. ngtnews</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349979940351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 14:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349996487814-14</Id><Title>Tax Experts Show Why Mitt Romney's Middle-Class Tax Cut Would Work</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney has proposed a significant overhaul of America’s income tax code, revolving around three principles: reducing tax rates for everyone, achieving deficit neutrality, and ensuring that taxes on the middle class go down. Two months ago, a center-left think tank called the Tax Policy Center claimed that such a tax reform was “impossible,” and that Romney’s plan would raise taxes on middle- and lower-income households by $86 billion a year. This led the Obama campaign to claim that Romney was raising taxes on the middle class to pay for “tax cuts for the rich.” But several critics have found flaws in the think tank’s assumptions. Adjusting for these assumptions validates Romney’s claim that his plan would cut taxes for middle- and lower-income households at the expense of the rich. President Obama has been going around claiming that Romney was seeking a “$5 trillion in tax cuts that favor the wealthy,” because part of Romney’s plan involves reducing tax rates for everyone by 20 percent, which some estimate as costing the Treasury $5 trillion in revenue over ten years. But Obama’s claim doesn’t take into account the fact that Romney intends to fund those tax cuts by reducing or eliminating many of the deductions and loopholes in the tax code that primarily favor the wealthy. Two months ago, the Tax Policy Center—a joint enterprise of the Urban Institute and the Brookings Institution—put out a report in which they made several assumptions about Romney’s approach to deductions and loopholes, concluding that it would be “impossible” for Romney to cut income tax rates by 20 percent, and keep the government’s tax revenues the same, without raising taxes on the middle class. If Romney insisted on keeping his plan revenue-neutral, argued the TPC authors, Romney’s plan would “likely result in a net tax increase for lower- and middle-income households and tax cuts for high-income households” of $86 billion a year in 2015. (The authors defined “high income” as income above $200,000 per year.) But the authors of the TPC report—Samuel Brown, William Gale, and Adam Looney—made a number of assumptions that others have rightly pointed out to be flawed. Indeed, five simple adjustments of TPC’s assumptions turn their $86 billion shortfall into a $40 billion surplus. TPC ignores three important tax expenditures First, the TPC authors assumed that it would be “off the table” for Romney to “reduce tax expenditures that aim to promote saving and investment.” But while that is indeed a general goal of Romney’s approach, Romney hasn’t issued a blanket opposition to such changes. As Matt Jensen and Alex Brill of the American Enterprise Institute have pointed out, there are a few such tax expenditures that conservatives have long considered to be “on the table.” These include: (1) eliminating the deduction for interest income on state and local bonds, and (2) income related to the inside buildup of life-insurance products. Indeed, in response to the Jensen critique, the TPC authors produced an update to their paper, conceding that these two changes would raise as much as $25 billion and $20 billion, respectively, from high earners. That brings the alleged middle-class shortfall down from $86 billion to $41 billion. Furthermore, as Curtis Dubay of the Heritage Foundation has noted, the TPC authors “assume that the Romney plan would not change the step-up in basis of capital gains at death.” Let me try to translate. Romney’s plan would eliminate the estate, or “death” tax. Under our current code, if you inherit a house from your parents, and then later sell it, because you already paid estate tax on the home, when you sell it you’re only liable for the capital gains that have accrued since your parents died. However, if we eliminate the estate tax, we need to change that rule so that capital gains apply to the preceding period when your parents owned the home, which is called the “carry-over basis.” Dubay calculates that eliminating this deduction for people with incomes over $200,000 would raise approximately $19 billion in 2013, which we can call $20 billion for 2015. That brings the TPC shortfall from $41 billion to $21 billion. TPC included Obamacare taxes, but not spending, in their baseline Mitt Romney has pledged to repeal Obamacare, which includes new taxes on upper-income earners: a 0.9 percent surcharge on “earned income” and a 3.8 percent surcharge on “unearned income.” The TPC authors count this as revenue that Romney has to make up elsewhere, without taking into account that Romney would also repeal Obamacare’s spending. This is clearly incorrect on their part. Alex Brill calculates that this change takes another $29 billion in 2015 revenue out of TPC’s alleged middle-class shortfall, turning a $21 billion shortfall into an $8 billion surplus.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349996487814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349996543585-15</Id><Topic><Title>Tax Experts Show Why Mitt Romney's Middle-Class Tax Cut Would Work</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349996487814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:01:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The TPC report assumes that Romney’s plan would have no effect on economic growth We’ve established that with four simple adjustments, we can turn TPC’s alleged $86 billion in new taxes on middle- and lower-income households into an $8 billion surplus. But it’s important to note that the TPC analysis is static, and assumes that the plan would do nothing to improve economic growth, leading to increased tax revenues. The TPC authors acknowledge this fact, arguing that “there are particular reasons to be skeptical that revenue-neutral tax cuts will have much effect on growth.” But, just to be sure, the TPC authors used the work of Gregory Mankiw and Matthew Weinzierl to estimate that optimistic assumptions about economic growth could add an additional $53 billion in tax revenue to Romney’s plan. If we decide to reduce these optimistic assumptions by 40 percent, resulting in $32 billion in additional income from growth, we arrive at a total surplus of $40 billion for the Romney plan: $8 billion with static scoring, and $40 billion with dynamic scoring of economic growth. There are other estimates out there. Harvey Rosen of Princeton suggests that the Romney plan could add $25 to $58 billion in revenue from economic growth. Alex Brill of AEI calculates that every 0.1 percent in extra GDP growth per year would add $13 billion in revenue. Further thoughts There may be other aspects of the TPC study that bear additional analysis. It’s not clear whether or not TPC modeled the impact of their assumptions on payroll taxes. Some tax expenditures, most notably the tax exclusion for employer-sponsored health insurance, significantly reduce revenues from the payroll tax. In addition, it’s not obvious why someone making $200,000 is considered “rich” while someone making $190,000 is not. The arithmetic would work out quite differently if “middle- and low-income households” were defined as those with less than $150,000 or even $100,000 in income. I’ll say one thing in defense of the TPC authors. While their analysis missed a few things, and contains a few bits of inflammatory and biased language, their report isn’t a piece of hackery, especially in comparison to some of the shoddy work from Families USA and the Commonwealth Fund that I’ve recently reviewed. The TPC authors assume in their report that Romney is successful at reducing and/or eliminating a wide swath of tax expenditures that primarily benefit the wealthy, even though Congress has been reluctant to eliminate those expenditures in the past. It may be that Romney can’t convince Congress to go along with his proposal. But that’s different from saying that his proposal is a fraud, or that Romney’s lying when he says that his plan will cut taxes for the middle class. The math I’ve walked through above shows that Romney’s plan can, indeed, achieve all of his stated objectives. That’s a big part of why he won last week’s debate, and why President Obama is struggling to find a better argument against him. UPDATE 1: Ryan Ellis of Americans for Tax Reform and Josh Barro of Bloomberg further debated these points on Twitter. Ben Domenech and Brad Jackson interviewed Curtis Dubay for their Coffee &amp; Markets podcast. Dubay is less charitable toward the TPC authors than I am. William Gale says (somewhat poutily) that the adjustments I describe above are “an interesting development and should be pursued.” Romney campaign surrogates and right-wing media outlets have focused on the idea that new taxes on saving and investment should be imposed. After decades of these same outlets claiming that taxes on saving and investment are bad for the economy, scholars at AEI, Heritage, some academics and the Wall Street Journal editorial page appear lined up behind higher taxes on some forms of interest income, and removal of tax-deferral on some long-term saving products, as a way to finance part of the Romney tax plan. This is an interesting development and should be pursued. To be clear, though, pursuing this policy wouldn’t be refuting our earlier study, it would be accepting the constraints and conclusions there and finding a way around them. UPDATE 2: Joseph Lawler corrects the false meme that Romney’s tax plan has somehow moved left. Romney has said all along that taxes on the wealthy could go up under his plan: On the day Romney produced the outline of his plan to reduce the marginal rates in each bracket by 20 percent, he also stipulated that the rate reductions wouldn’t entail a lowered tax burden for rich folks, saying that he would limit deductions and exemptions for high income folks in order to “continue to have progressivity in our code” and not add to the deficit. He specifically mentioned that he would “make sure the top 1% keeps paying, paying the current share they’re paying or more.” So Obama’s insinuation that Romney is hiding his previously stated desire to cut the overall tax burden of higher-income earners is not correct. In fact, it’s worth pointing out that, at the time he announced his plan, Romney was attacked by his Republican opponents for engaging in stealth class warfare against wealthy folks with his tax plan – exactly the opposite of Obama’s charge. Rick Santorum accused Romney of “campaigning as an Occupy Wall Street adherent” with his newly-released tax plan.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1349996543585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349997721847-16</Id><Topic><Title>Draft Dodger Romney Angers Dead Vet's Mother After Politicizing Her Sons Death</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1349897653356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:34:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You want to criticize Mitt Romney for not serving in the military? Fine. Then explain to us when Obama ever served in the military. You dumbocrap #$%$ want to make military service an issue this go round? What about last election? McCain's service in the military didn't convince you to vote for him then, why on earth do you clowns think it has anything to do with this election? You're just a bunch of hypocritical, lying, P.O.S.</Msg><Username>yankeeddandy</Username><Timestamp>1349997721847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349997827949-17</Id><Title>J. B. HUNT TRANSPORT SERVICES, INC. REPORTS REVENUES AND EARNINGS FOR THE THIRD QUARTER 2012</Title><Msg>J. B. HUNT TRANSPORT SERVICES, INC. REPORTS REVENUES AND EARNINGS FOR THE THIRD QUARTER 2012  Third Quarter 2012 Revenue: $1.3 billion; up 11%  Third Quarter 2012 Operating Income: $133 million; up 12%  Third Quarter 2012 EPS: 65 cents vs. 57 cents LOWELL, ARKANSAS, October 11, 2012 - J. B. Hunt Transport Services, Inc., (NASDAQ:JBHT) announced third quarter 2012 net earnings of $78.2 million, or diluted earnings per share of 65 cents vs. third quarter 2011 net earnings of $68.7 million, or 57 cents per diluted share. Total operating revenue for the current quarter was $1.3 billion, compared with $1.17 billion for the third quarter 2011. Load growth of 15% in Intermodal (JBI) and 38% in Integrated Capacity Solutions (ICS) helped drive 15% and 30% increases in segment revenue, respectively. Dedicated Contract Services (DCS) segment increased operating revenue by only 1% primarily driven by the start up of new accounts occurring later than expected, while Truck (JBT) segment revenue declined primarily due to operating approximately 9% fewer trucks. Current quarter total operating revenue, excluding fuel surcharges, increased 10.5% vs. the comparable quarter 2011. Operating income for the current quarter totaled $133 million vs. $119 million for the third quarter 2011, as positive results from load growth and improved network balance in JBI and load growth in ICS were partially offset by cost pressures experienced in DCS and JBT. Net earnings rose 14% to $78.2 million in the current quarter from $68.7 million in 2011, primarily due to the growth of revenue, slightly less interest expense and a slightly lower tax rate. The effective income tax rate for the quarter was in 38.25% in 2012 and 38.5% in 2011. Segment Information: Intermodal (JBI)  Third Quarter 2012 Segment Revenue: $794 million; up 15%  Third Quarter 2012 Operating Income: $97.9 million; up 25% JBI segment revenue grew 15% on load volume that increased a similar 15% over the third quarter of 2011. Eastern network load growth and transcontinental load growth were 22% and 11%, respectively, primarily from the continued customer conversion of highway traffic to intermodal. The combination of traffic mix, customer rate increases and changes in fuel surcharges kept revenue per load virtually flat compared to a year ago. jbhunt</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349997827949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:23:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349998863894-18</Id><Title>Oil-and-gas industry 'wary' of tax reform</Title><Msg>Oil-and-gas industry 'wary' of tax reform By Bernie Becker - 10/11/12 05:03 PM ET A top lobby for the oil-and-gas industry said Thursday that its members had some concerns about a push to overhaul the tax code. Stephen Comstock of the American Petroleum Institute told reporters that, while the industry understood the value of a streamlined tax system, the group’s members haven’t pressed too hard for a simpler code. “Tax reform will be a complicated process,” said Comstock, API’s manager for tax policy. “I think our members are wary of how that process will take place. But they are absolutely willing to be at the table, and engaged in how should it come about.” Comstock also suggested that his industry might not have too much to gain from a tax revamp. “We may not always come out ahead,” Comstock said. “We’re not in a position of asking for anything." “We’re really in a position now of looking at those things that are important to the industry, important to the members, and educating them on why they’re important,” Comstock added, referencing the group’s discussion with policymakers. The comments from API come just days after Mitt Romney, the GOP nominee for president, suggested that tax breaks used by the industry would “probably” have to be eliminated under his plan for tax reform, which calls for lowering the top corporate rate from 35 percent to 25 percent. Rep. Fred Upton (R-Mich.), the chairman of the House Energy and Commerce Committee, has also said in recent days that he could get on board with eliminating tax breaks for oil-and-gas if alternative energy subsidies were also scrapped. More broadly, the oil-and-gas lobby’s stance also underscores the difficulty of tax reform — which, if successful, would almost certainly stick some taxpayers or sectors with a higher tax bill. At Thursday’s briefing, Comstock said that his group had not discussed Romney’s comments, made in last week's presidential debate, with the campaign. With the economy scheduled to hit the so-called “fiscal cliff” of tax increases and spending cuts at the end of the year, many on Capitol Hill are also looking at 2013 as a key year for tax reform. But with federal deficits still elevated, the oil-and-gas industry has also faced repeated attempts from Democrats to roll back certain incentives outside of tax reform, such as expensing for drilling costs. Part of the industry’s defense is that it already shells out more to governments than most industries, with API saying that oil-and-gas paid an effective tax rate of almost 45 percent between 2006 and 2011. But Comstock acknowledged that rate combined taxes paid to federal, state and foreign governments. Citizens for Tax Justice, a liberal group, has released reports saying that big oil companies like ExxonMobil (14 percent) and Chevron (25 percent) paid lower rates when just considering their federal tax bill. API also said it was gearing up to defend its tax preferences once again during the lame-duck session of Congress. “For the long-term stability, and back to this pro-growth idea and how do we continue to grow the economy and create jobs, it’s certainly not with punitive taxes,” said Brian Johnson, a senior tax adviser at API. The White House has targeted the big oil companies as it looks to reduce the deficit. But President Obama also released a draft plan this year that would reduce the top corporate rate to 28 percent. Sen. Charles Schumer (D-N.Y.) joined the call to decrease the corporate tax rate this week, even as he also said individual tax rates should not be slashed during tax reform. For their part, GOP lawmakers have also proposed lowering the top rate to 25 percent. the hill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1349998863894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350001874893-19</Id><Topic><Title>ingernal is so stupid...............</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1349996844904</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:07:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you. You can't even spell (or copy) infernal. Your post clearly indicates your level of intelligence, or lack thereof. You're not doing a very effective bully job - more practice needed. Nuff said.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350001874893</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>