<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350194569516-1</Id><Topic><Title>The Neighbor Test....</Title><Username>pmm_boston</Username><Timestamp>1350128887627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 07:48:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A better test would be: would you let Biden babysit your children? XD</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1350194569516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 02:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350212847526-2</Id><Topic><Title>The Neighbor Test....</Title><Username>pmm_boston</Username><Timestamp>1350128887627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 07:48:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahleee #$%$ you braindead freak. As for biten his next job is selling used cars in the ghetto.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350212847526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350212928057-3</Id><Topic><Title>Some people post all day long must be on government assistance</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1350181646522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:27:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is typical wahleee and maxi pad both commie brothers.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350212928057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350212973850-4</Id><Topic><Title>Analysis: Do black people support Obama because he's black?</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350181163152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>97% of them and who is racist?</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350212973850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350213134720-5</Id><Topic><Title>If This Happened At Republican Office It Would Be ALL DAY Coverage on Fox.</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350145309670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When they performed a lobotomy on wahleee they reversed his comprehension portion of his brain. And that mixed with bad dope has him all f--ked up. Poor soul must also be possessed by the devil; nobumba.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350213134720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350213225182-6</Id><Topic><Title>The VP Debate Lyan Ryan Beating Rewind</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350172215409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some one else had to write that for wahlee. The commie party wrote it.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350213225182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350213303711-7</Id><Topic><Title>How Republicans Support The Troops</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350136623927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:57:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at thumbs down for wahleee, no one ever agrees with the little sissy girly.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350213303711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350213359491-8</Id><Topic><Title>The People Republicans Support Are Anything But Patriots</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350171682940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>start crying wahleee clown your buddy commie devil is getting voted out.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350213359491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 07:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350217089398-9</Id><Topic><Title>Analysis: Do black people support Obama because he's black?</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350181163152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with Samuel L. Jackson; most all of the black people voting for Hussein are racists - at least he admits it. I suppose that white people, when fully understanding what Mr. Jackson has said, should no longer feel a twinge of self doubt when they vote for white people instead of black people. Thank you Mr. Jackson!</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350217089398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350219001524-10</Id><Title>Bioheat consisting of 12% biodiesel B12 blended with the NY state-mandated ultra-low sulfur heating oil burns cleaner than natural gas</Title><Msg>New Heating Oil Rail Facility Opens in East Comments Off Posted by Joanna Schroeder – August 2nd, 2012 A new heating oil rail facility has official opened in Yaphank, Rhode Island owned and operated by Ultra Green. The terminal will receive diesel fuel produced from vegetable oils or other fats and then will blend the fuel with traditional heating oil to create Bioheat. The biodiesel will be delivered in rail cars and the facility can store up to 250,000 gallons on site. This October, New York City’s biodiesel mandate (Bioheat) will take effect. “The new BRT Terminal will help us ensure the economic, as well as environmental, success of the NYC Bioheat mandate, and provide lower-cost Bioheat for all of Long Island,” said Michael Cooper, vice-president of Ultra Green prior to the ribbon cutting event. “A Bioheat consisting of 12% biodiesel (B12) blended with the New York state-mandated ultra-low sulfur heating oil burns cleaner than natural gas. We’re working to ensure that every fuel dealer in the region can provide clean, reliable, and renewable Bioheat to its customers.” Ultra Green was one of the first companies to market biodiesel dating back to 1999 and has been blending Bioheat since 2001. Today the company supplies biodiesel through the self proclaimed largest network of wholesale terminals in the New York/New Jersey region. domesticfuel</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350219001524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 08:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350221047240-11</Id><Title>4 Scary Dem Facts</Title><Msg>4 scary Dem facts By CAROLINE BAUM From bloomberg view Last Updated: 10:50 PM, October 13, 2012 Posted: 10:09 PM, October 13, 2012 Here are four things the 2012 Democrats don’t want you to know. No. 1: Middle-class taxes are going up. Unless the US generates a lot more wealthy Americans — unless we can “grow the rich,” so to speak — raising taxes on upper-income earners won’t solve the deficit problem. The top 10% already pay 70% of the federal income tax. Given the federal government’s predilection for spending every dime that comes in (and more), the awful truth is that the government will have to trickle down the income ladder to scoop up the revenue needed to reduce the deficit. No. 2: “Forward” is really backward. The Obama campaign adopted “Forward” as its slogan for the 2012 election and features it prominently at events. As a rallying cry, it’s not much better than backward. When Lenin started his own underground newspaper in 1905, he called it Vperyod (Forward). Someone on Team Obama either doesn’t know history or has a warped sense of humor. If the president’s advisers were looking to counter the accusation that Obama is a socialist, invoking Lenin was a bad choice. No. 3: Medicare, not Granny, is going over the cliff. Forget the back-and-forth accusations about which party plans to raid Medicare to the tune of $716 billion and deprive seniors of their due. Democrats still want us to believe Medicare as we know it can be preserved. It can’t. It has been running a cash-flow deficit since 2008 and will go broke in 2024. Medicare can be reformed, retooled or revamped, but it can’t continue in its present state. No. 4: A Volt in every driveway? The 23 million unemployed and underemployed Americans must be wondering about all the fuss over a $40,000 plug-in hybrid car. With an array of government subsidies and tax credits for GM and its suppliers — and even a hefty tax credit for buyers — the Volt has literally been willed into existence. We really can live without a Volt in every driveway.</Msg><Username>pmm_boston</Username><Timestamp>1350221047240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 09:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350228927392-12</Id><Title>Mitt Romney, show us your underwear</Title><Msg>http://messages.yahoo.com/Government_%26_Politics/By_Country_or_Region/United_States/Politics/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=18066891%23americasbecomingafasciststate&amp;tid=2134695&amp;mid=2134695&amp;tof=5&amp;frt=2</Msg><Username>charitymindvoid</Username><Timestamp>1350228927392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 11:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350236830231-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Neighbor Test....</Title><Username>pmm_boston</Username><Timestamp>1350128887627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 07:48:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what went thru my mind when Martha Stewart became a felon and went to jail. Just was hoping martha never moved into my tenement. Probably a lot of people breathed a sigh of relieve when that "dangerous" Martha was taken off the street. Not to minimize what Martha did but really did not think she was a danger to society that had to be locked up at tax payers expense. Its and old story but in the case of Martha the punishment did not fit the crime Happy to report that Martha Stewart has not moved into any of the cockroach infested places in my neighborhood and former tenement.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1350236830231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 13:47:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350237041867-14</Id><Topic><Title>The Neighbor Test....</Title><Username>pmm_boston</Username><Timestamp>1350128887627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 07:48:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would not mind if Mr. Biden moved into my tenement, but dont think he would fit in.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1350237041867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 13:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350254975614-15</Id><Topic><Title>Do you want a teabagger for a neighbor ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350253008471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 18:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its sorta strange how all the teabags think "they" live by Constitution and scream about their "right" to keep and bear arms--but they ALWAYS leave out the part about " well regulated " and "militia" we can argue the "well regulated" part as the gop will tell you that wallstreet was well regulated before disaster struck but NEVER have any of the tough talk pickup driving whitefilth been part of a militia. Their idea of proud military service is the "w' and rush bimbo annular cyst deferments.</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1350254975614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 18:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350256019931-16</Id><Topic><Title>Do you want a teabagger for a neighbor ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350253008471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 18:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, me and by brothers live in Florida, we all have guns, and we hate anyone who doesn't look like us. We are all black racist gang-bangers who will only vote for Obama because he is at least half black and we will shoot anyone with our illegally owned guns if they look at us cross-ways. Yep, I'm Pivsup (aka Maxwizard) the tough black gang banger.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1350256019931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 19:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350263825910-17</Id><Topic><Title>Do you want a teabagger for a neighbor ?</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1350253008471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 18:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxipad has severe brain damage do to a botched up lobotomy. Wahlee and maxipad are commies and will be deported after election.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350263825910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350263924898-18</Id><Topic><Title>4 Scary Dem Facts</Title><Username>pmm_boston</Username><Timestamp>1350221047240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 09:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba has to go.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1350263924898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 21:18:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350267165093-19</Id><Topic><Title>4 Scary Dem Facts</Title><Username>pmm_boston</Username><Timestamp>1350221047240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 09:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She should have went with three. The fourth is the give away that the opinionated is off her rocker. How the government checks cashing PMM? You have no problems with yours right? You hypocrite.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350267165093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 22:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350267594888-20</Id><Title>Oil Drops a Second Day as Iran Offers Uranium-Enrichment Deal</Title><Msg>Oil Drops a Second Day as Iran Offers Uranium-Enrichment Deal By Ben Sharples and Ayesha Daya - Oct 14, 2012 5:42 PM MT 1 Comment Oil fell for a second day in New York after Iran reiterated an offer to suspend domestic production of medium-enriched uranium before European leaders meet to discuss tighter sanctions on the Persian Gulf country. Futures slipped as much as 0.9 percent. Iran is ready to enter talks about its nuclear program in exchange for guaranteed supplies of 20 percent-enriched uranium for its Tehran Research Reactor, said Ramin Mehmanparast, a Foreign Ministry spokesman, according to a report by Press TV yesterday. The European Union reached a preliminary agreement to intensify sanctions to increase pressure on the Gulf nation to curb its nuclear program, EU diplomats with knowledge of the matter said. “If the news coming out from Iran indicating that it’s willing to suspend 20 percent enrichment for reactor fuel is true and they reach an agreement, then we might see a push to the downside” for oil, Nabil Farhat, a partner at Al Fajer Securities, an Abu Dhabi-based broker, said yesterday. Crude for November delivery fell as much as 79 cents to $91.07 a barrel in electronic trading on the New York Mercantile Exchange and was at $91.19 at 10:37 a.m. Sydney time. The contract declined 0.2 percent on Oct. 12 to $91.86. Prices are down 7.7 percent this year. Brent oil for November settlement slid 62 cents to $114 a barrel on the London-based ICE Futures Europe exchange. The European benchmark grade’s premium to West Texas Intermediate was at $22.81, from $22.76 on Oct. 12. Iran Sanctions Officials from the EU’s 27 nations agreed in Brussels on Oct. 12 to add several entities to the sanctions list to hinder the Iranian government’s ability to raise funds for its atomic program, which the U.S. and its allies say may be aimed at producing weapons, according to the officials, who declined to be identified because the talks were private. The proposed sanctions must now be approved by the bloc’s foreign ministers, who meet today in Luxembourg. Oil exports from Iran will probably remain at lower-than- normal levels for the next few years because of the sanctions, Antoine Halff, the head of the International Energy Agency’s oil industry and markets division, said on a conference call with reporters on Oct. 12. Crude shipments have been “stable” in recent months, said Mohammad Ali Khatibi, Iran’s governor to the Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries, according to the Tehran-based Donya-e-Eqtesad newspaper yesterday. bloomberg</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350267594888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 22:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350267715974-21</Id><Topic><Title>Oil Drops a Second Day as Iran Offers Uranium-Enrichment Deal</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350267594888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 22:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like those sanctions these filthy war mongering right wingers hate are working.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1350267715974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 22:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350269892481-22</Id><Topic><Title>4 Scary Dem Facts</Title><Username>pmm_boston</Username><Timestamp>1350221047240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 09:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She "should have went"? You obviously did well at Harvard Mr brain death.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350269892481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 22:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350269957322-23</Id><Topic><Title>Oil Drops a Second Day as Iran Offers Uranium-Enrichment Deal</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1350267594888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 22:19:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are obviously going to fall for that again? Once a fool always a fool wahleee boy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1350269957322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 22:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>