<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346041085000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Refers to Rape as a ‘Method of Conception’</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040139000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:02:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do the right-to-lifers include capital punishment in their ideology over there in the US ?</Msg><Username>boz451</Username><Timestamp>1346041085000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:18:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346041216000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dan Senor? The Fox News contributor? Heh heh! The Fox News contributor = originator of lies.</Msg><Username>boz451</Username><Timestamp>1346041216000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:20:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346041964000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush's Iraq adventure was a failure because it was conducted by the rules advocated by such liberal philosophers as Judge Robert Jackson, a judge who did not even attend law school. The U.S. has lost every war it fought since his grand philosophical theories were put on the display so many years ago, and very foolishly upheld for the U.S. to live up to. It's time you joined him in his Ivory Tower wahleee boy - an Ivory Tower erected on a fortress who's walls and battlements were erected in the fires of war by methods that do not bear mention in polite company. It's not easy business building a state and leading it. Your chosen fool of the moment has done no better...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346041964000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346042157000-4</Id><Topic><Title>HOW AN IMBECILE SOUNDS!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1345811208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 08:26:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think air currents and atmospheric pressures have more to do with it than anything. The left would certainly agree that those are more important, unless of course a political cheap shot can be gained by blaming it on "god."</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346042157000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346043817000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush's Iraq adventure eventuated because his lies were believed. But how? The presentation for invasion at the UN Security Council was so poor!</Msg><Username>farmer_suit_tickles</Username><Timestamp>1346043817000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 01:03:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346049938000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AIPAC is the lobby that is the most feared in DC. There is not a close second. The Brent Scocrofts and George Shultz's have been replaced by Daniel Senor's and a slew of neocons. But the central bankers in London and Manhattan use Israel to create the war/terror/security complex needed to usher in one currency for an unelected one world government. Goldman Sachs and their ilk render Bush and Obamney as puppets. Manhattan will always bang the drums for war. Obviously the Rockefellers and Rothschilds were at least partially motivated by the massive oil fields the Czar had denied them in Russia when they bankrolled the Bolshevik Revolution. With their tool Lenin they locked up rights to the richest fields in Russia, and profitted from the massive debts of WWI and WWII in the process.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346049938000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 02:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346057760000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Bush = Obama = Romney</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1345947577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One single currency in Europe didn't come from the creation of war/terror/security complex. Central bankers in London and Manhattan hated it. So what are you talking about?</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1346057760000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 04:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346066988000-8</Id><Topic><Title>WOULD YOU AGREE ....</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346006796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:46:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.nytimes.com/2012/08/26/health/research/with-rise-of-gene-sequencing-ethical-puzzles.html?src=me&amp;ref=general&amp;pagewanted=all&amp;pagewanted=print</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346066988000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346067593000-9</Id><Topic><Title>WOULD YOU AGREE ....</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346006796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 14:46:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.nytimes.com/2012/08/26/sunday-review/how-long-do-you-want-to-live.html?src=me&amp;ref=general&amp;pagewanted=print</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346067593000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346068191000-10</Id><Topic><Title>SPEAKING of MITT ROMNEY!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346010568000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:49:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.nytimes.com/2012/08/26/opinion/sunday/too-late-to-shake-that-etch-a-sketch.html?pagewanted=print</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346068191000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346070446000-11</Id><Topic><Title>SPEAKING of MITT ROMNEY!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346010568000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:49:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.economist.com/node/21560864</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1346070446000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346076976000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Took $1.2 Billion Fed $ To "Save Olympics"</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346073188000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:13:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As soon as you learn to accept your frailty, you will cease to project it on others.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1346076976000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:16:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346078313000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Took $1.2 Billion Fed $ To "Save Olympics"</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346073188000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:13:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're filthy raul.</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1346078313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346079051000-14</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Those of Jackson's words that were mentioned, were in regards to the point that the criteria to conduct war not be on policy." A peace-nik lacks understanding as to when to fight a war or why, which is why the term is apt for the Judge Jackson in question. Such a person also "does not know how wars are won" as the very reason for their being a peace-nik is to avoid the realities of what it takes to win a war. Your Judge Jackson does not understand when to fight, how to fight, or why to fight. His attitudes on policy are useless, and the US's record of defeats or costly draws since he uttered his words does not support their value. His attitude is natural to members of the academic elite of the conquering power though. The victory that gave him the luxury to make his impractical and useless remarks was not won by his philosophy but rather by the fire-boming of cities, an act deliberately aimed at civilians, especially so in places like Dresden where the fires were stoked to turn the city into the equivalent of a blast furnace, or in Tokyo where special bombs were selected to start a firestorm. The nuclear bombing raids were not much different. The US also rounded up up minorities in camps when it saw fit, and injected mental patients with plutonium to see what would happen, and engaged in many other things the conqueror try very hard to expunge from the record. Yet again you cling to the irrelevant date of 1506. Yes, Machiavelli led the Florentine defense and was building up its army that year. He got a chance to bring the army he was responsible for into combat a couple years later and was victorious. What does that prove? It proves nothing except that he managed to win a victory. The discussion is not about military commanders or the organization of armies but about states and "Princes" (or Presidents). Machiavelli was neither a prince, nor a President, nor a head of state of any kind. If the topic was the Medici your irrelevant date would begin to have meaning, but even then it is poorly picked. The conduct of this or that "Prince" or Princes that failed to understand the art of war and lost, is not important to the discussion. Those that failed to form solid states could be expected to lose just as Machiavelli's book indicates. You obviously lack the knowledge to back up your other asinine remarks. Pathetic, as always...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346079051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346079417000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Sniff an affluence and do fasten is the noise of XOM !</Title><Username>mcgeedennis793</Username><Timestamp>1346070534000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i do not pretend to be pro-flws. i also believe the stock is under-valued. i will continue to hold my current position until the time is right to exi</Msg><Username>danielsdirk538</Username><Timestamp>1346079417000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346079560000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Took $1.2 Billion Fed $ To "Save Olympics"</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346073188000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:13:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahleee boy lacks breeding, and has no experience doing anything. People like Romney are naturally suspect to him.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346079560000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:59:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346079943000-17</Id><Title>New Analysis on Exxon Mobil Corporation Suggests Drop</Title><Msg>Wow! Exxon Mobil Corporation is not looking good right now. MUST READ! http://WWW.HOTSTOCKMARKETPICKS.INFO</Msg><Username>deidrapokorny</Username><Timestamp>1346079943000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346081239000-18</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here you again demonstrate your inability to comprehend. Jackson's words were mentioned in regards to the point that the criteria to conduct war not be on policy, which has nothing to do with Germans. I know you now know the significance of 1506, and that your cowardly recognition to the contrary is again demonstrated by you again pushing it to the wayside. "Centuries of societal stability (post Machiavelli [1506])" For you not to have seen the relevance of the date, you are obviously not a scholar of Machiavelli. You also have no idea about relevancy. "There is no surer way of keeping possession than by devastation..." This remains one of the most stupidest, present day comments posted on this board.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346081239000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346081526000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. What a stupid post. The Iraq invasion failed because it wasn't conducted by the guidelines set in place by those that are not war mongers like you. Your statement is so wrong....it's incredibly stupid. But of course, it's likely to be just a lie.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346081526000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:32:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346081663000-20</Id><Title>Ethanol</Title><Msg>Shouldn't sales for all oil majors increase by about 15% next year if ethanol is not used as a "filler" in gasoline???</Msg><Username>jpmang</Username><Timestamp>1346081663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346082899000-21</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But Americans border guards are forbidden to respond when federales south of the border are shooting at our border guards, or when the IAF incessantly straifs for hours the world's most sophisticated reconnaisance ship, the USS Liberty.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346082899000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:54:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346083075000-22</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A peace-nik is smart enough to keep all of his five sons out of the neo con's global strike force, the US military. He skipped out him self in the loser war against the communist Vietnamese and their Russian and Chinese backers.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346083075000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346083501000-23</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Supreme Court Justice Robert L. Jackson, U.S. Representative to the International Conference on Military Trials, "Statement by Justice Jackson on War Trials Agreement," August 12, 1945 (Department of State Bulletin) -- "We must make clear to the Germans that the wrong for which their fallen leaders are on trial is not that they lost the war, but that they started it." Your statement that his statement has nothing to with the Germans is factually, and quite obviously a deliberate lie. His is attempting to put the Germans on trial for starting the war as per his opinion that aggressive war is not a legitimate tool of foreign policy. He is entitled to his opinion, but his assertion of it is not evidence of its value, especially not from a citizen of the United States, and especially not one as educated as Judge Jackson. The fact is the United States engaged in aggressive war against England in the war of 1812 and invaded Canada. It engaged in aggressive war against the Cherokee nation and other Indian tribes of the Southeastern United States, and West. In the case of the Cherokee it marched a people off their lands in defiance of A Supreme Court ruling, using the threat of aggressive war and coercive means in violation of law to advance its national aims. It engaged in aggressive war against Mexico several times as and when it suited it. The think pretext it used to invade Mexico and seize half of it does not speak well for the any unique "Just War" moral principles of the United States. It engaged in aggressive war against Spain seizing Cuba, Puerto Rico, and the Philippines. It engaged in aggressive war against the civilian population of the Philippines, killing hundreds of thousands in its efforts to subdue it. It engaged in aggressive war, or more precisely the threat of it, when it seized Panama. Judge Jackson's remarks are entirely hypocritical coming from the Chief U.S. Prosecutor at the Nuremberg Trials, the one who aims to put the Germans on trial for starting an aggressive war. The U.S. was not built on his philosophy but by methods exactly opposite to it. The subject of the Nuremberg Trials was, however, the conduct of war, not whether aggressive war was justified no matter what your Judge Jackson says. No doubt your Judge Jackson's intent was to confound the legitimate right of a sovereign power to start an aggressive war with its conduct as he had no basis to make his claim against aggressive war, but a sound one on German conduct during the war. I'm not interested in playing trivial pursuit with you. 1506 is irrelevant to the development of Western civilization, the countries that constitute, or its extremely militaristic bellicose nature. It did not acquire those traits in 1506 and they became even more pronounced and it even more violent and bellicose in subsequent years. The military revolution and the professionalization of war had not even begun. That would begin in the 17th century... Your discussion is worthless...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346083501000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346083632000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Ethanol</Title><Username>jpmang</Username><Timestamp>1346081663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The USDA estimates a 12% decrease in corn production. I live in the cornbelt and from what I see it will be at least a 50% decrease in production. Surely what corn is harvested will have to be used for feeding purposes rather than ethanol production.</Msg><Username>penguin_011</Username><Timestamp>1346083632000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:07:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346084345000-25</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Wobbling like a Fish out of Water. Shorts in there..</Title><Username>brady.mccormick42</Username><Timestamp>1346069642000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:14:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a ton of helpful information on that site, so glad I found this.</Msg><Username>park.jefferson92</Username><Timestamp>1346084345000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:19:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346085121000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is rich and you R poor.</Title><Username>g2al34</Username><Timestamp>1346082575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:49:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's eight digit book deal and slew of speeches fetching seven digits are right around the corner. Clinton's first speech at the synagogue in Miami after leaving the White House netted him over a million dollars. Pretty obviious why guys like Mark Rich get pardoned.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346085121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:32:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346085499000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Ethanol</Title><Username>jpmang</Username><Timestamp>1346081663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the corn farmers loby, didn't exist, and ethonal, was produced from suger beets,(like it's been done in Brazil for years),the price of fuel would be down over 30%,and petroleum profit margens would still be high.</Msg><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1346085499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346088903000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Ethanol</Title><Username>jpmang</Username><Timestamp>1346081663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ethanol is a gimmic, I can take 10 gal of regular gas and go as far as I can on 11 gal of 10% ethanol. A complete waste of tax payers $$$.</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1346088903000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346089346000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ethanol</Title><Username>jpmang</Username><Timestamp>1346081663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are correct about the sugar ethanol Brazil studied EVERY ethanol type/blend as oil imports were destroying their economy with no solution short/long in site the only FEASIBLE "NET" energy was sugar ethanol more calorie out than put in but in the USA we got the "W" and the "special interest" at that time ADM and Koch bros so the "science" of the GOP chose corn--its a loser and a joke--but man those big guys reap billions in PROFITS and in subsidy oh well--live and don't learn funny I remember how just "recently" the govt started "picking" losers and winners and the govt should stay out of markets--I wonder where the fox and mittens were then ??</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1346089346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346089392000-30</Id><Title>TRUE!!</Title><Msg>The number of people now getting free stuff outnumbers the people paying for the free stuff. We have one chance to change that in 2012. Failure to change that spells the end of the United States as we know it.</Msg><Username>zeegypzee</Username><Timestamp>1346089392000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346089694000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Ethanol</Title><Username>jpmang</Username><Timestamp>1346081663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure the gop convention will reflect on their glory here are couple links just in case they skip http://www.aei.org/article/energy-and-the-environment/alternative-energy/biofuels/ethanols-a-big-scam-and-bush-has-fallen-for-it/ http://money.cnn.com/2008/03/05/news/bush_ethanol/index.htm and on top of that sadness--you still find the whitetrash that screams about govt spending but wants more of the bush years back ??</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1346089694000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346090782000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Ethanol</Title><Username>jpmang</Username><Timestamp>1346081663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will Media Remember Gore's 1994 Tie-breaking Vote Mandating Ethanol Read more: http://newsbusters.org/blogs/noel-sheppard/2008/04/22/will-media-remember-gores-1994-tie-breaking-vote-mandating-ethanol#ixzz24lrnWDQy As the international disaster of ethanol begins taking its toll on the planet -- and, maybe more important, as press outlet after press outlet finally begins recognizing it -- will media remember that Vice President Al Gore cast the tie-breaking vote in the Senate requiring this oxygenate be added to gasoline? After all, regardless of recent reports blaming ethanol for world hunger problems, rising food costs, and increased greenhouse gases, it seems highly unlikely green media will want to tie any of these problems to Nobel Laureate Gore. Read more: http://newsbusters.org/blogs/noel-sheppard/2008/04/22/will-media-remember-gores-1994-tie-breaking-vote-mandating-ethanol#ixzz24lrV0dL7</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1346090782000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:06:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346093455000-33</Id><Topic><Title>TRUE!!</Title><Username>zeegypzee</Username><Timestamp>1346089392000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney cannot change anything. As Senator Barry Goldwater stated, the United States would be better off if New York City and Hollywood fell into the ocean.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346093455000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346093632000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Big, Fat, LIAR!</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346092697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More liberal myth but, you should credit the author.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1346093632000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346093700000-35</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just because something was stated 'long ago' (BTW, closer to 500 years in this case not 600) does not negate either its accuracy or usefullness. As one example, Machiavelli also extolled the advantages of the republican form of gov't over principalities/monarchies. To use your logic, one would have to conclude since Machiavelli was extolling the virtues of republicanism 500+ years ago, we need to revert to a monarchy because his words are 'old'. Thus they must be out of date, inaccurate and useless.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346093700000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:55:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346093955000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day, Another NRA Sponsored Shooting</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346093683000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical of wallboard, all he knows to post are lies.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346093955000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:59:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346094315000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Big, Fat, LIAR!</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346092697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your choice of a subject line is very apropos as a description of yourself (and all you post.)</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346094315000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346095003000-38</Id><Title>Obama: I Just Don't Get It</Title><Msg>We've just completed 4 years with Barak Obama as president and he's neck-and-neck in the polls with Romney. After 4 years, we have un-employment stuck well above 8%... ... we're running massive, $1.2 Trillion (with a "T", Virginia) annual deficits... ... The economy is barely growing more than 1%... it's effectively stalled out... ... government spending is increasing exponentially and the only idea Obama has to cut the deficit is to raise taxes on the rich... which would only cut about 1/16 of it... &gt; businesses have stopped hiring &gt; Ratings agencies have lowered the credit quality of US Treasuries... for the FIRST TIME &gt; Obamacare hugely expands the size of government and most Americans oppose it. I DON'T GET IT... WHY is this presidential race even COMPETITIVE? Could it be simply that the top 1% of U.S. earners (who provide 39% of federal tax revenues) are being totally overwhelmed by the bottom 49% of U.S. earners (who collectively pay no income tax and provide no federal tax revenues)?... ... isn't that what's been happening in Venezuela? Hugo Chavez of Venezuela and Raul Castro of Cuba have both said they support Obama... ... are THOSE the endorsements we should pay heed to? If we really CARED about the future we're leaving for our children... then would we elect Obama and let him do this to us for ANOTHER 4 YEARS?</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1346095003000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346096167000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually not only did he attend law school but he completed it. But he was denied a degree (and thus did not graduate) because of his age. (He was only 20 and was denied a degree because he was under 21. More importantly, at that time (he passed the bar in 1913), becoming a lawyer via apprenticeship instead of law school was still common.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346096167000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:36:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346096423000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: I Just Don't Get It</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1346095003000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"WHY is this presidential race even COMPETITIVE?" Never discount the difficulty in displacing an incumbent. Do not underestimate the powers and advantages an incumbent inherently has.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346096423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346096818000-41</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Wobbling like a Fish out of Water. Shorts in there..</Title><Username>brady.mccormick42</Username><Timestamp>1346069642000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:14:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am waiting for. Thanks for giving out this article for free.</Msg><Username>abbott.morton80</Username><Timestamp>1346096818000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:46:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346096964000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your post is not only completely unrelated to the topic, but is as always just another lie.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346096964000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346098566000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day, Another NRA Sponsored Shooting</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346093683000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I LOVE Walhiee! He puts his idiocy in writing! no denying it! excellent! thanks W!</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1346098566000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:16:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346098659000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wallboards 'other' kind of post...personal attacks.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346098659000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:17:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346098841000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day, Another NRA Sponsored Shooting</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346093683000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not coherent. You keep coming up with all the wrong answers. (F)</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1346098841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346099004000-46</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Machiavelli is a brilliant political philosopher. I do not think his reputation is in any danger. His work will go on being taught for another 500 years at least, just as it was for the past 500. Millions of influential political leaders have read and incorporated his ideas into their own over the years. Hundreds of philosophers, political scientists, and historians have buttressed his ideas with even more support. Arrogant leftist imbeciles do not believe in such things as wisdom acquired through experience, which is the purpose of historical analysis. (if the do engage in historical analysis the typical method is to telescoping present liberal ideas backwards, distorting the historical record) They take their own opinions as facts and truths, rather like Barack Obama does when he decides he can make law through executive orders, or concoct policies in areas such as energy or taxation that many, many years of experience indicates will not work. Such arrogant liberal fools are naturally quite surprised when their "innovations" fail. The liberal fools are quite lucky everyone does not think as they do, and blindly ignore the past. If they did there is no way it would be possible to get anyone to buy the mountain of Treasury debt the U.S. is accumulating. They are not buying that based on any belief in Barack Obama's ability to guide the economy to a recovery. The expectation is that the past ability of Americans to succeed will be repeated in the future. Implicitly they assume that Obama will be gone some day and things will get better - somehow.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346099004000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346099343000-47</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day, Another NRA Sponsored Shooting</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346093683000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at least you got something right. Guns don't kill people any more than cars do. Suppose you want to ban cars? People kill people with guns the same as people kill people with cars. No difference. Your mis-directed attack on the gun is merely another example of your leftist ( no personal responsibility ) mentality. What a warped and confused little person you are.....</Msg><Username>yankeeddandy</Username><Timestamp>1346099343000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:29:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346099376000-48</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day, Another NRA Sponsored Shooting</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346093683000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Keep denying that you and they are institutionalizing murder in the name of gun co profits." Your obscene and verbose language does not impress wahleee boy. I was inclined to take liberal stands on gun ownership in the past, but I think now a more conservative stance is in order. If your wild ranting and raving is indicative of left-wing attitudes, it is important for good conservative Americans, to buy large arsenals. We must strive for more gun company profits too - those will be helpful in developing better weapons going forward. More arms for war and keeping the peace are important - just like Machiavelli said years ago.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346099376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346100202000-49</Id><Title>Exxon to buy IOC</Title><Msg>Anyone heard the whisper XOM to buy inter oil IOC for $175 per share. Shell is also eager as a result on New Guinea LNG find (largest in the world). Thanks</Msg><Username>loveai12</Username><Timestamp>1346100202000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346102193000-50</Id><Topic><Title>RNC Is The Roach Motel</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100324000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:45:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A can of black flag is needed. we would have expected no less from you wal he he. Please wipe your,there's still a tiny bit of bs around your lips. if you ever find something nice to say, raise your hand and place it over your mouth... you better pray that owe-bamba is not re-elected as this country is on the brink of bankruptcy, much worse than greece. maybe you should go and move to greece.....dismissed...</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1346102193000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346103520000-51</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just because something was stated 'long ago' does not guarantee its accuracy or usefulness in the present day.</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1346103520000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346103714000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day, Another NRA Sponsored Shooting</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346093683000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're filth raul.</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1346103714000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346103750000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The current State Dept reeks of Dan Senor types. Every time we do something you tell me Americans will do this and will do that. I want to tell you something very clear: don't worry about American pressure on Israel. We, the Jewish people, control America, and the Americans know it." Ariel Sharon retorting to Foreign Minister Peres telling his worry to the Prime Minister Sharon that Americans might "turn against us" if Israel continues policies of continued violence. Thus we can understand why in 2011 prime minister Netanyahu received 29 standing ovations while adressing the US Congress.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346103750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346103917000-54</Id><Topic><Title>RNC Is The Roach Motel</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100324000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:45:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wahlee lost his brain when the doctors performed a lobotomy on him. Ignore the simple minded poor little girly.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1346103917000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:45:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346104046000-55</Id><Topic><Title>Jesus Spoke About Helping The Poor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since when are you religious devil man.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1346104046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346104108000-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: I Just Don't Get It</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1346095003000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only thing he going to get is a fat foot in his @$$.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1346104108000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346104184000-57</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is rich and you R poor.</Title><Username>g2al34</Username><Timestamp>1346082575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:49:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rich or poor we all have the same opportunity in america, its your choice.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1346104184000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346105077000-58</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"To ravage, to slaughter, to usurp under false titles, they call empire; and where they make a desert, they call it peace" Tacitus, speaking through the mouth of an enemy on the might of Rome... The alliance of America and Israel is very powerful. America is much more powerful than Rome ever was... What is perplexing is why its enemies think they can win or accomplish anything by provoking it. If they ever do succeed in provoking a conflict they will wish they had not.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346105077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:04:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346105579000-59</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Your statement that his statement has nothing to with the Germans is factually, and quite obviously a deliberate lie." You have an enormous problem with comprehension. This matter has already been dealt with, in your erroneous statement that Jackson's words were quoted in regard to the Germans....see immediately below. 1/."..you mention in regards to the Germans" Wrong. You have a real problem with comprehension. 2/. Here you demonstrate your extreme inability to comprehend, which diverts your ability to argue points towards zero (by vector?). Those of Jackson's words that were mentioned, were in regards to the point that the criteria to conduct war not be on policy. You have a huge problem with comprehension. Your tangential rants originate from an unfocussed, babbling mind. A mind that is so clouded it comes out with stupid comments like: "Bush's Iraq adventure was a failure because it was conducted by the rules..."</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346105579000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346105874000-60</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>save your ranting and raving for someone who cares... F--- off.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346105874000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346105933000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US has a strong history of lying about being provoked into a conflict.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1346105933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346106042000-62</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As did Rome for over 500 years...They were at war for almost every single year. That takes a lot of provoking. It's amazing how rich and unified they became doing that too.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346106042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346106046000-63</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The coward gives up. Phew. Its been hard to communicate through your intense inability to comprehend.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1346106046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:20:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346106195000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They were at war for almost every single year." You're envious? War mongers like you will say anything start a war.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1346106195000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:23:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346106379000-65</Id><Topic><Title>All-out-war</Title><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346013971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 16:46:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What!?!?!?!!! Bush's Iraq invasion was a failure because it was NOT conducted by the rules!!!!</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1346106379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346106776000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know who replaced the Romans wahleee boy? The Germans and their allied tribes. They were more warlike. The Romans became soft and lazy during the Pax Romana. They had queers everywhere by the end of it, and their women behaved disgracefully, and the men behaved like women much of the time. They forgot who they were and even went so far as to have an African Emperor. The Germans were a much more industrious people - farmers, miners, and good breeders. The society of lawyers, "artists" and queers was scattered....</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346106776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:32:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346107014000-67</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not wahlee you looney tune!</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1346107014000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346107239000-68</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every liberal queer on this board has been named wahleee boy. Didn't you know that?</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1346107239000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346107534000-69</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: I Just Don't Get It</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1346095003000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You hit the nail on the head about there are now more worthless scum "takers" ,like Wahleeee and Maxwizard, than there are productive "givers" in the US. The worthless scum "takers" will always vote Democrat no matter what since the Democrats give them their freebies. If Obama wins this year, the US as we knew it is gone.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1346107534000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:45:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346108274000-70</Id><Topic><Title>RNC Is The Roach Motel</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100324000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:45:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wahlee lost his brain when the doctors performed a lobotomy on him. Ignore the simple minded poor little girly. WHEN EVER A ROACH APPEARS LIKE WAL HEE HEE OR OWE-BAMBA, YOU STEP ON THEM AND CRUSH THEM BEFORE THEY MULTIPLY!</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1346108274000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346108629000-71</Id><Topic><Title>Filthy Right Wing Terrorists</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346104363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:52:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More drugs for you and, possibly a straight-jacket. You are exploding for all the wrong reasons. Call Debbie Wasserman. The two of you are like-minded morons. If that does not work, try Valerie Jarrett. But, don't waste your time on obama. He does what he is told to do by those who are trying to manipulate your demise. You are such a pushover!</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1346108629000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:03:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346109287000-72</Id><Topic><Title>Jesus Spoke About Helping The Poor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of Jesus, you can't! You are only qualified by your humanity. Your thought process is a detriment to your being.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1346109287000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346110046000-73</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: I Just Don't Get It</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1346095003000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pivsup, you going to New Orleans with your black brethren to loot and pillage after this Hurricane like you did after Katrina? Now you be careful and don't get shot by whitey, you hear?</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1346110046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346110793000-74</Id><Topic><Title>Jesus Spoke About Helping The Poor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're filth raul.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1346110793000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346111711000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Whats Wrong Now?</Title><Username>hulda_tammi45</Username><Timestamp>1346077289000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:21:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Profit</Msg><Username>kit_belen944</Username><Timestamp>1346111711000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346113905000-76</Id><Topic><Title>Big, Fat, LIAR!</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346092697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a very accurate description of both you and the author of that idiotic opinion piece.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346113905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346114786000-77</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day, Another NRA Sponsored Shooting</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346093683000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Evidence? Of course not - it's wahleee boy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346114786000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:46:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346115177000-78</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah but you ARE another wahleee boy alias. And a truly pathetic one. It's 100% clear from your posting history.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346115177000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346115353000-79</Id><Topic><Title>RNC Is The Roach Motel</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100324000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:45:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't be true. If the RNC was a roach motel, you would be its chairman.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346115353000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346115855000-80</Id><Topic><Title>The "Donald" ....</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1346108779000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:06:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't deal with the fact that he is successful? Not surprising. Losers like you have that problem. But you probably believe Soros is a really great guy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346115855000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:04:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346116289000-81</Id><Title>You guys are really getting into the right to bear arms</Title><Msg>Shootings all over the place! So much effort and research in the US into finding a factor that will determine a person's likelihood of mass shooting, when the rest of the world already uses a very simple system: who(m)ever wants to use automatic and/or semi-automatic weapons owns them.</Msg><Username>boz451</Username><Timestamp>1346116289000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:11:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346116851000-82</Id><Topic><Title>Jesus Spoke About Helping The Poor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gov't entitlement programs are not charity. They are NOT what Jesus stood for. Charity is much more efficient and effective when done at a local level. As to your generalizations, coservatives in general and religious conservatives (all religions, not just Christians) on average give more proportionally. There are plenty of exceptions in both directions. But generally, Americans are more than willing to help the needy. But that is far different than supporting some gov't entitlement program.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346116851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:20:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346116872000-83</Id><Topic><Title>List of the board's biggest idiots:</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1346116543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the same person?</Msg><Username>sporty_new_look</Username><Timestamp>1346116872000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346117171000-84</Id><Topic><Title>Jesus Spoke About Helping The Poor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure the practice of benevolent giving and caring is not what the Gov. does, but the blameless circumstances that induces the practice is the same, which liberal Gov.s address and the selfish taking republicans don't.</Msg><Username>sporty_new_look</Username><Timestamp>1346117171000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:26:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346117414000-85</Id><Topic><Title>Jesus Spoke About Helping The Poor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With or without Obamacare, please tell us who in the US is not able to get needed health care? Every state has a system to provide care to the poor and indigent. No one is talking about eliminating that safety net. For seniors, we have a different universal system, Medicare. Again, no one is talking about eliminating that system either. Our system of paying for healthcare is far from perfect. Obamacare (IMO) will turn out to be much worse. But paying for and providing care are two different issues.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346117414000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346117761000-86</Id><Topic><Title>Jesus Spoke About Helping The Poor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346100064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The two are not the same. Not in practice, implementation, fairness, results, effectiveness, etc. Also, studies have consistenly shown that while both 'give', Republican's consistenly give more proportionally than Dems. Dems want to take by force from the haves and resistribute to the have nots REGARDLESS if those have nots are "blameless" or not. Charity is one chosing to give their own possessions, $'s, time, etc to those one percieves as truly needy. There ia are very good reason 'charity begins at home'.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346117761000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346118230000-87</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Chief Advisor Dan Senor</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346040336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:05:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your attacks on me neither 'scare' me nor influence me. I strongly doubt they influence others (at least not in the manner you would prefer.) They only speak about you and your deficiencies.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346118230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346118396000-88</Id><Topic><Title>The "Donald" ....</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1346108779000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:06:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's you who are the jealous clown - try to deal with it.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346118396000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346118507000-89</Id><Topic><Title>List of the board's biggest idiots:</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1346116543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just keep practicing the phrase "President Romney." Soon it will flow smoothly off your tongue.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346118507000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346118580000-90</Id><Topic><Title>Big, Fat, LIAR!</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346092697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First, why are you afraid to provide attribution to Krugmann? Why try to make it appear you formed some kind of cognitive opinion? Second, his 'attacks' on both Ryan and now Christy are only opinions based on slanted interpretation and spin. He equates extending unemployment benefits (and extending them to less than what we have now) to writing checks to pay off Dem/Obama contributers and gov't take over of entire (or nearly entiree) industries. While he is much better in his presentations, he is still just using phony strawman arguments. Facts are facts. But when you then choose to interpret them and spin them you have moved well outside the factual state.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346118580000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346119079000-91</Id><Topic><Title>List of the board's biggest idiots:</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1346116543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we were, we would have to be the most talented poster ever. Our styles are so disparate and yet we never mess up in style or our differences in substance (because guess what, we don't agree on everything.) As to the upcoming elections. While I certainly hope Romney wins (I likely will not vote for him but he will still win my state), I have never come close to saying Obama has no chance. The inherent advantages that come with incumbancy are always difficult to overcome. The previous two Presidents proved that.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346119079000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346119870000-92</Id><Topic><Title>Economic Growth Is Unsustainable</Title><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1346030932000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 21:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Impossibility statements are the very foundation of science. It is impossible to: travel faster than the speed of light; create or destroy matter-energy; build a perpetual motion machine, etc. By respecting impossibility theorems we avoid wasting resources on projects that are bound to fail. Therefore economists should be very interested in impossibility theorems, especially the one to be demonstrated here, namely that it is impossible for the world economy to grow its way out of poverty and environmental degradation. In other words, sustainable growth is impossible." http://www.jayhanson.us/page37.htm</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1346119870000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346120381000-93</Id><Topic><Title>Another Day, Another NRA Sponsored Shooting</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346093683000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Black on white assualt ratio is 40 to 1. Obey your television. The self annointed in New York City who preside over America's adult education system (Fox News, CNN, MSNBC and most of all the NY Times) are hell bent on confiscating the taxpayer's guns. Recent gun confiscation in Australia has resulted in a significant spike in crime.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1346120381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346120827000-94</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Wobbling like a Fish out of Water. Shorts in there..</Title><Username>brady.mccormick42</Username><Timestamp>1346069642000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:14:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think this is a great resource for any one looking for good reliable information. Don't listen to the bashers, get your own information and make your own educated decisions.</Msg><Username>hollowayb98</Username><Timestamp>1346120827000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346122659000-95</Id><Topic><Title>Big, Fat, LIAR!</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346092697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. Where did I call Krugmann a liar? You yes, him not yet. 2. I already deconstructed his myth breaking about Ryan. He is now doing the same with Christie. 3. he claims the bail out of the auto biz is what turned around Michigan. Even if this is/were true, at over $100K per job saved (using the admins numbers, which could easily be proven bogus themselves) I am not sure it was such a very good investment anyway. 4. While it may not be as populare (and personally I would prefer the gov't stay out of all such deals) at least there is a chance (maybe even already has happened) that the state will profit from it help to private enterprises. OTOH, another gov't operated tunnel to NYC will only be an ongoing costs for NJ to support. Even where such to become profitable, those $'s would not flow to NJ. 5. Krugmann also equates taxcredits reduced to taxes paid. Taxes paid are revenue to the gov't. Tax Credits are COSTS to the gov't . Thus reducing credits does NOT generate revenue but lowers costs. Q.E.D a credit reduction is not a tax. If I stop handing you money, I am not making you pay more. I am just cutting your off the dole. Which depending on circumstances, may or may not be a good (and more important but harder to define fair) thing to do. There are plenty of people (but not all) getting gov't handouts that should not be getting such. Would you like to refure more of his strawman arguments and OPINIONS? You might continue to agree with his opinions over mine. I would be surprised if not. But that doesn't make his opinions facts like you like to claim.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346122659000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346122902000-96</Id><Topic><Title>Big, Fat, LIAR!</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346092697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw wallboard, I am leaving now. So feel free to post some idiotic claim and come back in an hour (when I have not seen it) and claim I am dodgin. I might see it tomorrow or later and take the time to rip it apart. But it won't happen tonight. Good Night to you V.I.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346122902000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 23:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346125466000-97</Id><Topic><Title>here we go...</Title><Username>gautreauxclsm0389</Username><Timestamp>1346085987000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getting good benefit.</Msg><Username>oversonlkn80516</Username><Timestamp>1346125466000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 23:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>