<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353318447814-1</Id><Topic><Title>In case you missed it ...................</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1353283227773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like the #$%$ devil from hell. Watch the destruction of america and your free bees and checks will slowly disappear. We will have the last laugh as you starve. As for the election voter fraud + lies and cheats are in the dumbocrap party. There is a group recording all the dumbocrap voters cause when its all over they will be held responsible. Like nazi Germany time is running out for you sewer rat #$%$ slobs.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1353318447814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 04:47:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353333251726-2</Id><Title>Atlantic Liberal MPs join chorus of support for eastern crude pipeline</Title><Msg>Atlantic Liberal MPs join chorus of support for eastern crude pipeline Calgary Herald-19 hours ago That's compared to the strong resistance from various groups about the environmental impact of the firm's Keystone XL pipeline that would run ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353333251726</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:54:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353334177902-3</Id><Title>World Bank Warns Of Catastrophic Effects From 4 Degree Warming</Title><Msg>World Bank Warns Of Catastrophic Effects From 4 Degree Warming Agence France Presse|29 minutes ago The World Bank warned that global temperatures could rise by four degrees this century without immediate action, with potentially devastating consequences for coastal cities and the poor. Issuing a call for action, the World Bank tied the future wealth of the planet -- and especially developing regions -- to immediate efforts to cut greenhouse gas emissions from sources such as energy production. "The time is very, very short. The world has to tackle the problem of climate change more aggressively," World Bank President Jim Yong Kim said on a conference call as he launched a report conducted for the global lender. "We will never end poverty if we don't tackle climate change. It is one of the single biggest challenges to social justice today." The study said the planet could warm 4.0 degrees Celsius (7.2 Fahrenheit) above pre-industrial levels as early as the 2060s if governments' promises to fight climate change are not met. Even if nations fulfill current pledges, the study gave a 20 percent likelihood of a four-degree rise by 2100 and said that a three-degree rise appeared likely. UN-led climate negotiations have vowed to limit the rise of temperatures to no more than two degrees. "A four-degree warmer world can and must be avoided. We need to hold warming below two degrees," Kim said. "Lack of ambitious action on climate change threatens to put prosperity out of reach of millions and roll back decades of development." UN Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon said in a statement that the study showed the need to hold nations to their commitment, made last year in Durban, South Africa, to put in place a legally binding new climate agreement by 2015. The more than 190 nations in the UN Framework Convention on Climate Change start their latest annual talks on November 26 in Qatar. Global temperatures have already risen about 0.8 degrees Celsius. The planet has charted a slew of record-breaking temperatures over the past decade and experienced frequent disasters some experts blame on climate change, most recently superstorm Sandy, which ravaged Haiti and the US East Coast. The report said that, if temperatures rise by four degrees, regions will feel different effects -- recent heatwaves in Russia could become an annual norm and July in the Mediterranean could be nine degrees higher than the area's warmest level now. Under that scenario, the acidity of the oceans could rise at a rate unprecedented in world history, threatening coral reefs that protect shorelines and provide a habitat for fish species. Rising sea levels could inundate coastal areas with the most vulnerable cities found in Bangladesh, India, Indonesia, Madagascar, Mexico, Mozambique, the Philippines, Venezuela and Vietnam, the study said. "Many small islands may not be able to sustain the communities at all. There would be irreversible loss of biodiversity," Kim said. The study found that the most alarming impact may be on food production, with the world already expected to struggle to meet demand for a growing and increasingly wealthy population that is eating more meat. Low-lying areas such as Bangladesh, Egypt, Vietnam and parts of Africa's coast could see major blows to food production, with drought severely hindering agriculture elsewhere, the study said. Flooding can also contaminate drinking water, increasing illnesses such as diarrhea. The dire warnings were designed to encourage bolder action, but the report did not focus on potential steps. Identifying one area, Kim called for less reliance on coal, which is the dirtiest major form of energy but is politically sensitive in the United States and China due to industry jobs. Kim said that the World Bank was determined to support renewable energy in its lending, saying: "We do everything we can not to invest in coal -- everything we possibly can." The fight against climate change has faced political obstacles in a number of nations including the United States, where many conservative lawmakers have called action too costly and cast doubt on the science. Kim, a physician and former president of Dartmouth College who was tapped for the World Bank by US President Barack Obama, said that 97 percent of scientists agreed that human activity was causing climate change. "As someone who has lived in the world of science for a long time, 97 percent is unheard-of consensus," he said. The report was carried out by German-based Climate Analytics and the Potsdam Institute for Climate Impact Research. The World Bank said it did not consider the study a substitute for next UN-backed scientific assessment on climate change expected in 2014. businessinsiderDOTcom/world-bank-warns-of-catastrophic-effects-from-4-degree-warming-2012-11</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353334177902</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:09:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353334285409-4</Id><Title>Sen. Wyden: Congress ‘in the dark’ on natural gas exports</Title><Msg>Sen. Wyden: Congress ‘in the dark’ on natural gas exports By Ben Geman - 11/18/12 02:34 PM ET Sen. Ron Wyden (D-Ore.), the incoming chairman of the Energy and Natural Resources Committee, said the Energy Department must provide lawmakers more information about proposals to ramp up U.S. natural gas exports. “The first thing that the department has to do is deal with the fact that Congress is in the dark on this issue,” Wyden said in an interview broadcast Sunday on Platts Energy Week TV. Wyden is skeptical of an array of companies' applications to export liquefied natural gas, fearing it could raise prices at a time when low costs and abundant supplies are helping manufacturers that rely on the fuel. The three-term Democrat in October wrote to Energy Secretary Steven Chu asking for a detailed description of factors the department will consider as it weighs applications to export gas from Oregon, the Gulf Coast and elsewhere (a list of projects under review is here). The department is also working on a closely watched – and delayed – economic analysis of the proposed exports. Wyden has not flatly come out against the export proposals, but showed in the Platts interview that he’s wary of the idea. “If we make the right decisions with respect to natural gas, I think it is going to be absolutely key to growing jobs in the manufacturing sector,” he said. Elsewhere in the wide-ranging interview, Wyden reiterated plans to reexamine federal loan and grant programs for green technologies. The programs have come under attack following the 2011 bankruptcy of Solyndra, the advanced solar panel maker that received a $535 million Energy Department loan guarantee in 2009, and bankruptcies and headwinds that have faced several other federally backed companies. “Post-Solyndra, it is time to go in there and re-do those policies. Right now they are not doing enough to encourage innovation,” Wyden said. In the interview, he also vowed to focus on the future of the nation’s gridlocked nuclear waste policy, and conduct oversight of the Interior Department’s offshore energy branch, which was reorganized and strengthened after the 2010 BP oil spill in the Gulf of Mexico. Wyden is slated to inherit the committee gavel from Sen. Jeff Bingaman (D-N.M.), who is retiring from the Senate. Check out the whole interview here. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/268639-sen-wyden-congress-in-the-dark-on-natural-gas-exports</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353334285409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:11:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353336216186-5</Id><Title>Google Clean Energy Funding Nears $1 Billion</Title><Msg>Google Clean Energy Funding Nears $1 Billion comment 1 Posted November 16, 2012 With a fresh $75 million equity investment in an existing Iowa wind farm, Google is closing in on a billion bucks committed to the renewable energy sector. The company said on Thursday that it bought an equity stake in a 20-turbine, 50-megawatt wind farm near Rippey, Iowa, a little farm town about an hour’s drive northwest of Des Moines. North Dakota wind farm, where Google made an equity investment in 2010 (image via Google) Here’s Google’s rationale behind the move: We’ve taken two approaches to greening the grid in Iowa, a state where we operate a data center. Back in 2010, we entered into a long-term contract to purchase wind energy from NextEra Energy Resources’ Story County II wind farm. This time, we’re investing directly into a wind project, which has been contracted to sell all of the energy to the Central Iowa Power Cooperative, an Iowa-based utility that will deliver the energy to local consumers. We’re happy to help make more renewable energy available to Iowans and to support the growing wind energy industry in the state. Google noted that the Rippey wind farm uses turbines made in Arkansas by Nordex USA. Before the new Iowa wind farm move, Google had said the green projects it was backing were capable of generating 1.8 gigawatts of power. According to the company, its roster of investments includes: •$94 million in four Recurrent Energy solar projects in the Sacramento, Calif., area; •$75 million in a Clean Power Finance fund to finance solar installations at some 3,000 homes; •$280 million in a SolarCity fund for similar residential installations; •a total of $178 million in BrightSource, backing the Ivanpah power tower solar project in the Mojave Desert; •an undisclosed amount for a 37.5 percent equity stake in Atlantic Wind Connection, which would provide transmission for up to 7,000 MW of offshore wind power in the Mid-Atlantic region; •$157 million into the Alta Wind Energy Center, a cluster of wind farms north of Los Angeles; •$100 million into Shepherd’s Flat, the giant, 892-MW Oregon wind farm that was recently completed; •$38.8 million into two North Dakota wind farms with total generating capacity of 169.5 MW; •and about $5 million for an equity stake in an 18.65-MW solar power plant in Brandenburg, Germany. theenergycollectiveDOTcom/node/144326</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353336216186</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:43:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353336779295-6</Id><Topic><Title>Atlantic Liberal MPs join chorus of support for eastern crude pipeline</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353333251726</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:54:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NS: Alberta's oil would be welcomed in Atlantic provinces, says MP Published on November 19, 2012 By The Canadian Press Halifax West MP Geoff Regan says environmental concerns appear to be stalling approval of the Keystone XL pipeline to Texas and the Northern Gateway pipeline which would ship through B.C. for export to Asian countries. Topics : TransCanada Corp. , Alberta , Nova Scotia , Texas [FORT MCMURRAY, AB] — A Liberal MP from Nova Scotia has paid a visit to the oilsands, saying that Alberta may be having struggles in accessing foreign markets but the province's crude is always welcome in the East. Halifax West MP Geoff Regan says environmental concerns appear to be stalling approval of the Keystone XL pipeline to Texas and the Northern Gateway pipeline which would ship through B.C. for export to Asian countries. But Regan says the struggling economies of the Atlantic provinces would be encouraged by the notion of bringing Canadian oil eastward, where residents rely on Middle Eastern imports. Calgary's TransCanada Corp. is studying the possibility of shipping as many as one million barrels a day of western crude to eastern refineries. To do so, it would convert part of its natural gas mainline partly to oil service. CEO Russ Girling has called the project both technically and economically feasible. Company officials have also said they don't expect to see a big environmental pushback because eastern Canadians are keenly aware of how such a plan would positively affect fuel prices where they live. Regan also says competitive wages in the oilsands could put pressure on companies back east, such as Irving, to offer a bigger paycheque for skilled workers. "The tradespeople will be saying, `do I want to go home and work for $10 an hour less plus take a haircut on my benefits?' '' said Regan. "I think they're going to have to be competitive. Some people will want to stay home but still, when the opportunities still exist out here I think they're real and that's something that will have to factor in." Regan also said there's a national benefit in terms of security of the oil supply. "I think there is a strong interest in Atlantic Canada and in Eastern Canada generally in the idea of having access to Canadian oil," he said. "The fact of the matter is that if there's a connection to the East coast, one of the important benefits of that for Alberta and for the oilsands is that you get the international price." nsDOTdailybusinessbuzzDOTca/Provincial-News/2012-11-19/article-3122996/NS%3A-Albertas-oil-would-be-welcomed-in-Atlantic-provinces,-says-MP/1</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353336779295</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:52:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353337490134-7</Id><Title>All the Tides Rise Exxon Mobil Corpo - Get on it Before it runs Aground...</Title><Msg>Educated investors are talking about and purchasing XOM now.. It makes perfect sense if you are looking to get a Short term gain.. XOM . The Fundamentals look great and analysts place the 1 year target price at 93.74. Also check...XOM website BigTeasuryStock</Msg><Username>deunice55</Username><Timestamp>1353337490134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:04:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353337766326-8</Id><Topic><Title>All the Tides Rise Exxon Mobil Corpo - Get on it Before it runs Aground...</Title><Username>deunice55</Username><Timestamp>1353337490134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm in with 48,000 shr</Msg><Username>inezodonnell58</Username><Timestamp>1353337766326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:09:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353337766865-9</Id><Topic><Title>All the Tides Rise Exxon Mobil Corpo - Get on it Before it runs Aground...</Title><Username>deunice55</Username><Timestamp>1353337490134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm in with 48,000 shr</Msg><Username>inezodonnell58</Username><Timestamp>1353337766865</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:09:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353338091619-10</Id><Title>Is It Time To Divest From Exxon?</Title><Msg>Is It Time To Divest From Exxon? Forbes-50 minutes ago Is It Time To Divest From Exxon? ... controversial goal: persuading colleges to drop their investments in companies like Exxon Mobil, Chevron, ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353338091619</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:14:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353340146280-11</Id><Title>Mitt Romney aide: Need more tax revenue - Hubbard said revenue should only come in the form of eliminating deductions</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney aide: Need more tax revenue By KEVIN ROBILLARD | 11/19/12 8:30 AM EST Mitt Romney’s top economic adviser continued his post-election about-face on Monday, pushing for raising more tax revenue from the rich as a way to start paying down the federal deficit. “Obviously, we would be better in my view if we didn’t raise taxes on anyone and we did everything on the spending side,” Glenn Hubbard, the dean of Columbia’s business school, said on MSNBC’s “Morning Joe.” “We just had an election. We’re going to have to have some compromise. And I think step one is figure out how to raise some revenue without killing the economy.” Hubbard said revenue should only come in the form of eliminating deductions, not by increasing tax rates, as President Barack Obama has suggested. He also said that solving the nation’s deficit problem will require more than upper-class tax hikes. “If you raise every tax on the rich that the president has proposed, it’s about 1 percent of GDP,” Hubbard said. “But our long-term problems are more like 10 percent of GDP. And we know from people who have studied fiscal consolidations are really all about spending cuts.” politicoDOTcom/news/stories/1112/84033.html?hp=l5</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353340146280</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:49:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353341916724-12</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney aide: Need more tax revenue - Hubbard said revenue should only come in the form of eliminating deductions</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353340146280</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:49:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it took Nancy Pelosi about half a second to say that proposal is unacceptable. There is no way the White House will negotiate against its own Congressional leadership and take the position of the Romney campaign. There will be no deal...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353341916724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:18:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353342005974-13</Id><Title>Time to Short the S&amp;P 500...</Title><Msg>.....</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353342005974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:20:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342325361-14</Id><Topic><Title>All the Tides Rise Exxon Mobil Corpo - Get on it Before it runs Aground...</Title><Username>deunice55</Username><Timestamp>1353337490134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm in with 48,000 shr inezodonnel Gosh, that is $4,195,200.00. I just added 12 1/2 shares to my portfolio and I thought I was doing pretty good. You must be a very rich person. The people I know (2) that seem to be well-to-do never talk about what they are worth or how much they make. Are you one of those democrats that want to raise taxes? Looks like you can afford it. I'd be careful about your wealth, Mr Obama is going to be coming after it. Be on the lookout for the 'brown shirts'</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1353342325361</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:25:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342592061-15</Id><Topic><Title>All the Tides Rise Exxon Mobil Corpo - Get on it Before it runs Aground...</Title><Username>deunice55</Username><Timestamp>1353337490134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are talking to a spammer. He owns nothing...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353342592061</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:29:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343246626-16</Id><Topic><Title>In case you missed it ...................</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1353283227773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You did get the little storm trooper to wave his flag. lol The Democrats will reign supreme for decades to come. The tax rate over $1,000,000 in income will probably be 90% before it is over, which is about the inflation adjusted level of the 1960s... I look forward to this future: 1) lower P/E, safer stock market 2) more money for schools, universities, and better technology 3) cheaper real estate encouraging more mfg to take advantage of the lower cost USA. 4) more money for infrastructure 5) and last but not least the useless financial "capitalist" (speculator) crew who have been feeding off decades of low taxes will have to find something useful to do...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353343246626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:40:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344169480-17</Id><Topic><Title>All the Tides Rise Exxon Mobil Corpo - Get on it Before it runs Aground...</Title><Username>deunice55</Username><Timestamp>1353337490134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are talking to a spammer. He owns nothing... Thanks, thought he might be one of those rich democrats that don't pay their taxes like the ones Obama has in his cabinet.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1353344169480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:56:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353344354785-18</Id><Title>Topped up</Title><Msg>XOM has found support around 85.06. The technical indicator at foxchart website shows 88% chance up.</Msg><Username>drigvze</Username><Timestamp>1353344354785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:59:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344435810-19</Id><Topic><Title>In case you missed it ...................</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1353283227773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is it everyone wants more money for schools? They teach things that will not get you a job in this life time and most say you must go to college . Not everyone wants or needs the cost of college to make money .</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1353344435810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:00:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353345591408-20</Id><Topic><Title>All the Tides Rise Exxon Mobil Corpo - Get on it Before it runs Aground...</Title><Username>deunice55</Username><Timestamp>1353337490134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think your right fundamentals are the way to go. Like it....</Msg><Username>lisa.hensley46</Username><Timestamp>1353345591408</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:19:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353345733454-21</Id><Topic><Title>In case you missed it ...................</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1353283227773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When they cut taxes in the 1980s they boosted the return for speculating in stocks and real estate, and created an environment that encouraged people to get degrees in fields that contribute little if anything to the economy. Just look the resume of the typical Wall Street banker and you will see. Then there are tens of millions of financial-pro wannabes who have wasted vast amounts of time and money to become loan officers, or real estate agents, or set up a business to speculate in either stocks or real estate, or perhaps got an education to feed off the needs of the speculators. There a big group of students who go to college without any direction at all, too, and get useless degrees in philosophy or art because they don't know what else to do - they just get caught up in the free wheeling chaos of speculator capitalism and mindlessly spend time and money. The universities just shifted their curriculum to satisfy the demand. The universities and schools are just as important as ever for technology, however, and the government will need to take a firm hand to reshape the educational system. Ripping the speculators out by the root is task #1...Higher taxes will achieve it. Just give it time. The Democrats and Progressives are very good at social engineering, so there is no doubt they will remake the society once they are firmly in charge.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353345733454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:22:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353345823110-22</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Short the S&amp;P 500...</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353342005974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:20:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Up to 5% short...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353345823110</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:23:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353347240850-23</Id><Topic><Title>In case you missed it ...................</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1353283227773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Max - the Speculator Par Excellence, collecting the spoils from a Party he hates, and doesn't even know how or why it came about. When you have lost all your money join your buddy wahleee boy under the overpass...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353347240850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:47:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353347558676-24</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Short the S&amp;P 500...</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353342005974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:20:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10% short</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353347558676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:52:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353351913457-25</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Short the S&amp;P 500...</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353342005974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:20:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ring, ring, ring... Short at $138.51, 138.70 covered at $138.49... The market is obviously being manipulated at the $138.50 level by someone</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353351913457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:05:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353353347639-26</Id><Topic><Title>In case you missed it ...................</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1353283227773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxidopey never had 2 nickels to rub together. He is just a poor big mouth #$%$ rebel rouser.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1353353347639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:29:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353354380965-27</Id><Topic><Title>In case you missed it ...................</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1353283227773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many times have you been told only take 12 hours and make an A not take full load and get out and get a job. Universities need money long term to pay for football.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1353354380965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:46:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353355810715-28</Id><Topic><Title>In case you missed it ...................</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1353283227773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 19:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Universities need money long term to pay for football." Football should not be a priority, I agree. I imagine a tax rate of 70% or 90% on the salaries of football stars, and other wage earners collecting more than $1 million, would reduce the incentive to engage in such frivolous and useless occupations. We need more medical professionals to bring healthcare costs down. We need more physicists, chemists, and engineers to develop new energy sources, improve the efficiency of existing ones, and reduce pollution. We need to educate more people in the sciences so they can become teachers in the sciences at the secondary level - we don't need more football coaches teaching history, or more courses in home economics. There are enough accountants, and MBAs and journalists or political "scientists" to last us quite some time - so much less focus on those subjects is in order. It's obvious how it got this way.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353355810715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:10:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353359124275-29</Id><Topic><Title>World Bank Warns Of Catastrophic Effects From 4 Degree Warming</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353334177902</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:09:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you know what the World Bank represents? If God wants to warm the terperature of the earth by 4 degrees, that is what will happen and, there is NOTHING that man can do about His will. The UN? Yeah, thats the answer Sparkey. The United Nations is a "Body" with brain cancer. What a joke!.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1353359124275</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:05:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353359785518-30</Id><Title>Tax-and-Spend: The Essence of Superior Urban Civilization</Title><Msg>The city has always been the place where the most taxation-and-spending was going on. Back in the Middle Ages if you went to a city such as Paris, London, Cologne, Hamburg, or Amsterdam, or any other urban area, you could expect to pay much higher taxes than you would if you remained in the countryside or in the sticks. Rustics paid low taxes and urban dwellers paid high taxes. The taxes paid for many useful things: guild halls, courts, police, fire, fortifications, militias, eventually standing armies, navies, upkeep up ports, the building and upkeep of roads, schools, universities, hospitals, etc, etc... These services allowed business to thrive more and more and knowledge and technology to accumulate in such places. Complex networks of contracts, the basis for banking, finance, and corporate forms of business organization required the services paid for by the taxes. The taxes tended to increase over time over the centuries as the machinery of government became more and more advanced. The cities did not revert back to farms or woods, either, they got richer and richer. Still the countryside and areas populated by rustics, hicks, or backwoodsmen remained lightly taxed. Industry would attempt to exploit the labor of such places, or collect a key natural resource, but the profit and capital from it fled such backward places even though the taxes were lower there. ..... Today the same holds true: the urban dwellers live and prosper by high taxes, and the rustics still cling to a more primitive existence based on low taxes, and a lower level of public services. Whenever the rustics elect their brand of politician the result is poor for everyone. Either they attempt to lower taxes to make the world as they would like it, or borrow-and-spend, which to them is the next best thing, inflating a bubble of credit which collapses eventually. Bush was the last rustic President of course, but there have been others...W was unique though: he had the education of an elite urban dweller, but still preferred the rustics and their ways...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353359785518</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:16:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353364060858-31</Id><Topic><Title>Tax-and-Spend: The Essence of Superior Urban Civilization</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353359785518</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:16:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The city, and the machine of tax-and-spend at is core, is also the source of the Nation too. Nations did not arise whole, they had to be conquered and systematically developed. Places like Paris became the power center of the French Kings and the wealth of the city, harnessed in taxes, was used to conquer what is today France, incorporating other major urban areas one by one, and their countryside into its orbit. The Sun King came to reside at Versailles, outside Paris. Then Republic based itself on Paris, sending its armies across Europe. London was the power base of the English Kings, and from there they subdued all of lower England, then Wales, then northern England, the Scotland, Ireland, and eventually 1/4 of the world. Modern Germany comes from the Prussian base of power in Berlin. It eventually drew all the cites of Germany, except Austria and its power base in Vienna, into its orbit... Moscow was the power base of the Russian Czar, before they built a city from nothing at St. Petersburg, and the used these twin power bases as a springboard to conquer the East of Russia and South (Ukraine)... Russia was not blessed with many good ports, rivers, and locations for cities, however, and remained poor and backward for many centuries. What became the United States of America, as opposed to what came before, which was a collection of backward rural colonies, was based on the key urban centers of New York, Boston, Philadelphia, Baltimore, and the new city of Washington. From this core of civilization, came the legal and administrative basis to conquer everything to the West. A war fought with the South to extinguish its competing vision of society and economy based on slavery, rural planters, and limited government...The South consistently blocked taxes and public spending until its vision was swept into the dustbin of history. The urban power reigned triumphant. The urban power has overcome its latest test of defeating a Republican rural state coalition, and now is poised to further the development of the Nation...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353364060858</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:27:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353372452773-32</Id><Title>EPA’s Weaker Coal Rule Not Weak Enough for Coal Industry</Title><Msg>EPA’s Weaker Coal Rule Not Weak Enough for Coal Industry By Jim Snyder - Nov 19, 2012 12:43 PM MT. In response to industry complaints, the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency has proposed softening its rule to cut mercury and other pollution from new coal-fired power plants. An industry trade group says the changes, which include a slightly higher level of allowable mercury emissions, don’t go far enough to ensure coal remains an alternative to natural gas. The EPA released its revised rule Nov. 16. “I’m not sure it’s sufficient to fix the problem, even for new sources,” said Scott Segal, director of the Electric Reliability Coordinating Council, a utility group that includes Atlanta-based Southern Co. (SO) While Segal said utilities were reviewing the proposal, he said the revisions would still constrain a utility’s ability to build a new coal plant. EPA’s mercury rule is one of several environmental regulations Republicans in Congress and industry lobbyists have argued will raise electricity costs and hurt the economy. The administration of President Barack Obama has said the health benefits outweigh the costs. The changes proposed by the EPA last week don’t affect requirements the agency issued in December for existing coal- fired plants. Both limits seek to cap pollution of mercury, air toxics and particulate matter from coal. The EPA said it reconsidered the pollution limits after new information and analysis became available. The changes announced won’t go into effect until March, after a public comment period. ‘Modest Weakening’ John Walke, clean air director for the Natural Resources Defense Council, said the changes amounted to a “modest weakening” of the limits the agency had set. Most of the associated health benefits of the pollution limits come from the requirements for existing coal-fired power plants, which weren’t affected by EPA’s announcement, Walke said. “The updated standards would only apply to future power plants, would not change types of state-of-the-art pollution controls that they are expected to install, and would not significantly change costs or public health benefits of the rule,” the EPA said in a statement. Both Segal and Walke predicted industry critics would continue to challenge the limits in court. Southern, one of the biggest users of coal in the U.S., and other power producers had complained the requirements for new plants under the Mercury and Air Toxics Standards rule, or MATS, were unattainable. The company is pleased that the EPA “acknowledged the flaws” in the rule, Tim Leljedal, a Southern spokesman, said in an interview. He said executives were still reviewing the changes. bloombergDOTcom/news/2012-11-19/epa-s-weaker-coal-rule-not-weak-enough-for-coal-industry.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353372452773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:47:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>