<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352632563453-1</Id><Title>maxipads check</Title><Msg>Wait a couple of years and when his welfare check bounces we will have the last laugh. As for me I transfered my $ out of the states. This country will fall alot faster with the $ being transfered out of america. And these poor dumb slobs thought they were going to pick our pockets. Joke is on them when they cant touch our $. Ha ha ha ha wahleee and maxi pad dummies you will go hungry soon.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1352632563453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 06:16:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352638858606-2</Id><Title>THERE A WAR ON WHITE PEOPLE ! THATS WAS OBAMA THESIS AT HARVARD ! READ MY POST ON GM WEB SITE</Title><Msg>.............................</Msg><Username>whitewhite106</Username><Timestamp>1352638858606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 08:00:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352649107780-3</Id><Title>Axelrod: Boehner's comments 'encouraging' - closing some of these loopholes and applying them to deficit reduction</Title><Msg>Axelrod: Boehner's comments 'encouraging' Comments (4) By DAVID CATANESE | 11/11/12 9:18 AM EST President Barack Obama's long-time political strategist, David Axelrod, said on Sunday House Speaker John Boehner's comments on the approaching fiscal cliff were "encouraging." "I think that the speaker's comments have been encouraging, and obviously there's money to be gained by closing some of these loopholes and applying them to deficit reduction. So I think there are a lot of ways to skin this cat so long as everybody comes with a positive, constructive attitude toward the task," Axelrod said on CBS' "Face the Nation." Axelrod noted that exit polls showed about 60 percent of Americans agreed with the president on raising taxes on the wealthiest. "It is obvious that we can't resolve the challenge here simply by cutting the budget - we've cut by a trillion-one. There are more cuts to be made, but you need new revenues. But everyone - every objective person who's looked at this agrees on that. So, the question is where is that revenue going to come from?" Axelrod said. "The president believes it's more equitable to get that from the wealthiest Americans who have done very well and frankly don't need those tax cuts." politicoDOTcom/blogs/politico-live/2012/11/axelrod-boehners-comments-encouraging-149221.html?hp=r6</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352649107780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 10:51:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352653235577-4</Id><Topic><Title>Allen West--more tea bag flushed</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1352340710350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 21:11:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did the ref steve rewind invest infernal the 4skin and yank get their lips unstuck from that ebony booty or did they get taken down in the flush of that sambo bimbo??? the cockroach collection has run from the light</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1352653235577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 12:00:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352657350505-5</Id><Title>Epic Collapse Coming</Title><Msg>1. Falling tax rates on capital have been the lynch pin of rising stock prices for 3 decades. 2. Cheap money is another key element and it cannot get cheaper. 3. Wealth accumulating in the accounts of the wealthy to be invested is another important element. Like a water building up behind a dam it was only a matter of time till it topped it...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352657350505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:09:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352657590048-6</Id><Topic><Title>maxipads check</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1352632563453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 06:16:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The money in the stock market cannot be "transferred out" without collapsing those markets. Someone has to own it, and nobody will when they figure out the logic of what is coming. The wealth will quite simply be annihilated.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352657590048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:13:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352657962436-7</Id><Topic><Title>THERE A WAR ON WHITE PEOPLE ! THATS WAS OBAMA THESIS AT HARVARD ! READ MY POST ON GM WEB SITE</Title><Username>whitewhite106</Username><Timestamp>1352638858606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 08:00:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The women voted for it. Women must be indulged in their fancies, too. It just works better that way. Of course this means making as much money off the situation as possible</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352657962436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:19:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352658948319-8</Id><Title>2012 Year of Disaster</Title><Msg>1. Mega Heat wave 2. Strongest Hurricane or storm of any kind in the North Atlantic, by pressure and atmospheric disturbance, ever recorded. 3. Solar Cycle peaking 12/21/12 4. 26000 year cycle coming to an end 12/21/12 - the Sun and planets will align with the center of the galaxy on that day. What do Einstein's theories say about space-time, and the behavior of the Sun when that happens? How exactly was it possible for a bunch of people without computers to encode a calendar with that day? The economic situation is beyond words...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352658948319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:35:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352659454809-9</Id><Title>Bible Code - Obama/Romney</Title><Msg>You will find Obama, President in there. You will not find no such reference to Romney on 2012 or any other year... Prophecy? Of course. Could you make money on it? Of course... Like clockwork.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352659454809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:44:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352663536316-10</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Year of Disaster</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352658948319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:35:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a mathematical fact that the sun and planets will line up that way on that day. It is a fact that the date was encoded by people who would have found it next to impossible to calculate without the aid of computers, much less see a reason to even try. It would have required mathematics that was not even invented yet to make it practical at all. Europeans could not replicate a calendar of such accuracy until quite recently, nor did they see a reason to even try. Yet here we have this calendar... The Hurricane is a fact. The heat wave is a fact. The solar cycle is a fact. Your cynical attitude does not speak well for you, which is another fact, although it is certainly entertaining in a way. Enjoy your losses ahead...They promise to be horrific, quite aside from the astronomical significance of the above, which is unknown and unknowable. There are more than enough facts in play to ensure them. As for the day in question: It does look like someone with quite advanced technology was trying to leave a calling card - we will see why soon enough.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352663536316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 14:52:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352665415811-11</Id><Topic><Title>Allen West--more tea bag flushed</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1352340710350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 21:11:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately the cockroach collection and their disciples, like you, won the election. The price to be paid is yet to come.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352665415811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 15:23:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352665592609-12</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Year of Disaster</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352658948319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:35:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very interesting indeed! 1 + 2 + 2 + 1 + 2 +0 + 1 + 2 = 11, and many significant events throughout history occur when the numerical date adds to 11 or multiple of 11. Thanks for the heads-up!</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1352665592609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 15:26:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352666061475-13</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Year of Disaster</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352658948319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:35:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You figured out about how long the solar cycle is... Why would you care about that number? It's useful for predicting what the sun will do. I can't imagine why anyone would care about that... As for humans... Well they've been on this planet for quite some time and are used to thinking in terms of cycles of quite orderly length... Up, down, up, down...Do that for 10,000 or so years and it starts to get remembered somehow - almost like a fear of spiders does not have to be learned by nearly all humans. Men like titties too. No learning required. So - keep the solar cycle in mind - you can make lots of money with it...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352666061475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 15:34:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352668695343-14</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Year of Disaster</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352658948319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:35:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fun cycles of 11 years length and the trouble that awaits around them: 2012 ... -11 2001: recession &amp; crash 2000-2002 -11 1990: recession 1990/1991 -11 1979: Iranian Revolution, Global Depression 1979-1982 -11 1968: recession 1969/1970 -11 1957: Suez Crisis and global recession 1957 -11 1946: recession 1945/1946 -11 1935: middle of Great Depression -11 1924: recession covered up by massive Federal Reserve "stimulus" till 1928... -11 1913: recession 1913, World War I begins 1914, NYSE shut down for months -11 1902: recession 1902-1904 -11 1891: London &amp; Paris stock market crash 1890; NYSE crash 1892-1893; depression -11 1880: Crash of Railroad boom 1881/1882 -11 1869: Franco Prussian War 1870, leading to crash 1872/1873 -11 1858: Crash of 1857, recession 1857/1858 -11 1847: Crash 1846-1848, Year of Revolutions 1848 -11 1836: Crash of 1837, global depression -11 1825: Crash of 1825/1826, run on Bank of England, depression -11 1814: Crash 1814-1816 -11 1803: Napoleonic Wars begin, crash of British bond market... ...........etc...etc...etc</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352668695343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:18:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352673271441-15</Id><Topic><Title>Allen West--more tea bag flushed</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1352340710350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 21:11:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>West was paid and bought, I agree there, but it's not an issue of race.</Msg><Username>makesnosense99</Username><Timestamp>1352673271441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:34:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352673700900-16</Id><Topic><Title>Allen West--more tea bag flushed</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1352340710350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 21:11:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps Mr West can now pursue an acting career in Hollywood, which his talents and ambition are more suited .</Msg><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1352673700900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352674890644-17</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Year of Disaster</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352658948319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:35:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Solar Cycle 23 peaked in the fall of 2001. The average length of a solar cycle is 11 years with a small margin of deviation of +/- a year or so. That brings the peak of the next one to fall 2012, right in line with 12/21/12. Obviously you ignored all the weathermen when the Hurricane was coming in and missed the its abnormally low pressure and extreme strength and storm surge resulting from it- especially for so late in the year. Solar Cycle is irrelevant you say? I think not. The farmers in the Midwest would find your attitude a bit odd too considering what happened to their crops this past summer. Crop prices as we've headed to the peak of the current solar cycle were to be expected too. Try subtracting in multiples of 11 off 2001 and 2012 and you will see some other interesting years. Yes, indeed. If you take it back far enough you will find that 1066 is pegged as a "Year of Disaster- Just so as it is written in the Anglo-Saxon Chronicle. Of course the Normans were coming, but they were intrigued by year 1066, and inspired by the English's attitude. Yes they kept track of these things long, long ago - at least the monied classes did... Blithely advance into the darkness if you like - it suits you.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352674890644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 18:01:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352676377738-18</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Year of Disaster</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352658948319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:35:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truly stupid. What matters if the peak. Cycle 23 peaked 9/6/2011. You can add 1 +11 can't you? We know the current one has not peaked yet, either and we know the trajectory of peaks, so it is not hard to project. It could well get worse this winter as far as events go- in fact that is highly likely given the track record. As for the last peak...9/11/01 came a few days latter, possibly picked deliberately to coincide with a time of troubles. The Islamic people have a long tradition of picking their dates carefully. Exactly why 2001 was picked is neither here nor there though - it happened as these things have a way of doing... If you think this year is going normally you are far into the fringe of delusion - certifiable in fact. The economic facts and political events so far should give you pause....Even more frightful political events await as this year closes out. All is not well in Camelot, although you don't seem to care. Lose it all. It will be entertaining.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352676377738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 18:26:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352676428349-19</Id><Topic><Title>2012 Year of Disaster</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352658948319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 13:35:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9/6/2001...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352676428349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 18:27:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352678607298-20</Id><Title>Allen West and Joe Walsh will NOT be receiving a GOV'T CHECK !!!</Title><Msg>How sweeeet it is OH YEAH can someone take a picture of these #$%$ on the unemployment line.</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1352678607298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 19:03:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352678757765-21</Id><Topic><Title>GOP DO NOT GET MARIA,JOSE,MARK DOESN'T MATTER ITS ABOUT "POLICY" !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1352577242124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 14:54:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP just don't get it oh CMON Hillary run !!!!!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1352678757765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 19:05:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352679572929-22</Id><Topic><Title>Allen West and Joe Walsh will NOT be receiving a GOV'T CHECK !!!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1352678607298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 19:03:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a minute NOW they will be receiving more GOV'T CHECKS !! Damn thats what I call WASTEFUL GOV'T SPENDING !!!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1352679572929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 19:19:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352682723202-23</Id><Title>Sun Spots - Predicting the Future</Title><Msg>google: Sunspot Cycles &amp; Human History It provides a sketch of the pattern which is perfectly obvious: wars &amp; economic disasters occur with much higher frequency around the peaks of sunspot activity. The 19th-21st centuries are very easy to follow as the history is clear and the sunspot data quite good. Peaks are very easy to calculate, and to predict the next one you just watch the data using +11 years from the previous peak to identify when the next peak should be - a band of +/- a year around it is a good margin of safety. For example the period of actual peak for solar cycle 15 was 1916-1918 (World War I). + 11 years gives you 1926-1930 as your next period maximum danger. The stock market crashed utterly during this period which is not very surprising. More recent peaks occurred from 1978-1980 - cycle 21. +11 gives you 1988-1992 as your next period of maximum danger - a recession as it turns out. +11, +/- 1, from cycle 22's actual peaking period (1988-1990) gives you 1997-2002 as a danger zone - a solid recession and 50% stock crash. +11 years from the cycle 23's actual peak comes in squarely on 2012 with a usual margin of chaos into 2013.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352682723202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 20:12:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352683680586-24</Id><Title>Republicans say deal can be done on U.S. "fiscal cliff"</Title><Msg>Republicans say deal can be done on U.S. "fiscal cliff" By Alister Bull WASHINGTON | Sun Nov 11, 2012 5:27pm EST (Reuters) - A senior Republican senator voiced confidence on Sunday that U.S. lawmakers would forge a deal on the year-end "fiscal cliff," while a top aide to President Barack Obama signaled a willingness to compromise over raising tax rates on the rich. Republican Senator Bob Corker said increasing tax revenues from wealthier Americans would have to be part of the plan, but he stressed closing loopholes rather than raising top tax rates as many Democrats favor, provided spending is also tackled. "I am optimistic," Corker told "Fox News Sunday." "I think there is the basis for the deal. ... There is a way of getting there on the revenue side. The real question is: can we come to terms on the entitlement side?" Obama has invited congressional leaders to the White House on Friday to discuss the issue, with only 50 days left until the end of the year. Unless Congress acts first, $600 billion in tax hikes and automatic federal spending cuts would take effect at the end of December, with a potentially devastating impact on the economy. The Obama administration and congressional leaders are attempting to negotiate a deal to avoid the fiscal cliff, and instead work toward a deficit-reduction package in the next session of Congress that begins in January. 'SKIN THIS CAT' Top Obama aide David Axelrod, asked if it was possible to raise enough revenue to curb the deficit without increasing the top tax rate, praised the "encouraging" remarks by Speaker of the House of Representatives John Boehner, the top Republican in Congress, on the need to tackle the problem. "Obviously, there is money to be gained by closing some of these loopholes and applying them to deficit reduction," Axelrod told CBS's "Face the Nation." "So I think there are a lot of ways to skin this cat, so long as everybody comes with a positive, constructive attitude toward the task." Boehner last week repeated his party's commitment to not raise anyone's tax rates, but said that he would be open to a compromise that includes changes in the tax code that bring in more revenue, something fiscal conservatives in his party have argued strongly against in the past as tantamount to a tax hike. Tax cuts first put in place under Republican former President George W. Bush are due to expire at the end of the year for all Americans unless Congress acts. That would lift the top rate of income tax from the current 35 percent for households earning more than $250,000 a year to 39.6 percent. Obama won re-election on Tuesday after a campaign in which he called for wealthier Americans to pay a bit more in taxes. But a range of deductions, including on mortgage interest payments and charitable giving, can significantly lower the effective tax rate that most affluent U.S. households pay. 'MATHEMATICALLY IMPOSSIBLE' Another influential Democrat, Senator Charles Schumer, voiced skepticism that it would be possible to raise enough revenue to lower the deficit sufficiently without lifting the tax rate on the rich, but said he is open to hearing other ideas. "The only way mathematically that I've seen to do it, is go to that 39.6 percent rate. If someone can show another plan that doesn't do that ... we could look at it. But no one has shown one because I think it is mathematically impossible," Schumer said on NBC's "Meet the Press." Limiting some deductions while closing loopholes is the middle ground proposed in 2010 by a commission created by the president and led by Republican Alan Simpson and Democrat Erskine Bowles. Republican Senator Lindsey Graham urged Obama to sign on to its recommendations while pledging to do the same. "Say 'yes' to Simpson-Bowles, Mr. President. I'm willing to say 'yes' to Simpson-Bowles. We need more revenue in Washington. We need more private sector jobs. We don't need to raise tax rates," he said on CBS's "Face the Nation." Graham also warned that no Republican will vote for higher tax rates, and that reform of entitlement programs - such as the Social Security retirement program, the Medicare health insurance program for the elderly and disabled, and the Medicaid health insurance program for the poor - must also be tackled. "We will generate revenue from eliminating deductions and loopholes. But we will insist our Democratic friends reform entitlements. ... That is where the big money is at." Failure to convincingly tackle the fiscal cliff could unsettled financial markets and risk another downgrade of the U.S. credit rating, while imposing a heavy burden on a fragile recovery that could even tip the economy back into recession. Democrat Kent Conrad, chairman of the Senate Budget Committee, voiced optimism that the country would avoid the fiscal cliff, and said Congress must agree on a measure that wins some time to work out a more detailed plan to overhaul the tax code and entitlement programs. "You can't settle every detail in these next few weeks. What you can do is agree on a framework agreement that sets out for the (congressional) committees of jurisdiction how much they need to save, how much money needs to be raised," Conrad said on "Fox News Sunday." reutersDOTcom/article/2012/11/11/us-usa-fiscal-idUSBRE8A80WV20121111</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1352683680586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 20:28:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352685221887-25</Id><Title>Cost Over run</Title><Msg>Billions of dollars. Beautiful Exxon you dumb azzes</Msg><Username>dukdre23</Username><Timestamp>1352685221887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 20:53:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352686132181-26</Id><Title>Can Medieval Heat Cool Warming Worries?</Title><Msg>A flurry of recent scientific papers has tried to measure the warmth of the "Medieval Warm Period" (MWP) of about 1,000 years ago. Scientists have long debated whether it was cooler or warmer than today, and whether the warmth was global or regional. The point for nonscientists: If recent warming has precedents, some might find it less alarming. Until the late 1990s, researchers generally agreed that the MWP was warmer than today and that the "Little Ice Age" of 1500-1800 was colder. Then in 2001 the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change adopted the "hockey stick" graph devised by Michael Mann at the University of Virginia and colleagues. Using temperature indicators such as tree rings and lake sediments, the graph rewrote history by showing little warmth in the 11th century and little cold in the 17th, but a sharp spike in late-20th-century temperatures. That graph helped to persuade many people (such as me) that recent temperature rises were unprecedented in scale and speed in at least 1,400 years. But critics of the graph pointed out that it used a statistical technique that overemphasized hockey-stick shaped data from unreliable indicators, such as tree rings in bristlecone pine trees and Scandinavian lake sediments influenced by 20th-century land-use changes. Four recent studies have now rehabilitated the MWP as a period of unusual warmth, though they disagree on whether it was as warm or warmer than today. Jan Esper of the University of Mainz and his colleagues looked at pine wood densities from Sweden and Finland and found "evidence for substantial warmth during Roman and medieval times, larger in extent and longer in duration than 20th-century warmth." Bo Christiansen of the Danish Meteorological Institute and Fredrik Ljungqvist of Stockholm University looked at 32 indicators across the Northern Hemisphere and found the level of warmth during the peak of the MWP "in the second half of the 10th century equaling or slightly exceeding the mid-20th century warming." Thomas Melvin of the University of East Anglia and colleagues reanalyzed one of the tree samples from Sweden used in the "hockey stick" and concluded: "We can infer the existence of generally warm summers in the 10th and 11th centuries, similar to the level of those in the 20th century." A fourth study of creatures called diatoms in Chinese lake sediments found that the period "between ca. A.D. 1150 and 1200 was the warmest interval of the past 1,000 years." Taken together, these studies cast doubt on the IPCC's conclusion in 2007 that "the evidence is not sufficient to support a conclusion that [Northern] hemispheric mean temperatures were as warm, or the extent of warm regions as expansive, as those in the 20th century as a whole, during any period in medieval times." But was the medieval warm period confined to the Northern Hemisphere? I consulted a database of papers collated by the climate-skeptic website CO2Science.org, run by the Center for the Study of Carbon Dioxide and Global Change, a nonprofit research center in Tempe, Ariz. The database contains numerous published studies of isotopes and other indicators in caves, lake sediments and other samples from Chile, New Zealand, South Africa and Antarctica that find the MWP warmer than today. Two Antarctic studies, for instance, concluded that current warming "is not yet as extreme in nature as the MWP" and that "the present state of reduced ice on the western Antarctic Peninsula is not unprecedented." A far smaller number of studies, such as one from Lake Tanganyika, found the MWP cooler than today.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352686132181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:08:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352686282905-27</Id><Title>Wahleee boy must be devestated</Title><Msg>Veterans to resurrect cross at Calif. desert site A war memorial cross that once stood on a rocky hilltop in a national park before being deemed unconstitutional and ordered removed will be resurrected on Veterans Day at the stunningly stark Mojave desert site, capping a landmark case for veterans fighting similar battles on public lands. Henry Sandoz, who cared for the original 1930s cross as part of a promise to a dying World War I veteran, will rededicate a new, 7-foot steel cross on the same hilltop. The site is now in private hands as part of a land swap with the National Park Service that ended the longstanding legal dispute, which had become entangled in the thorny issues of patriotism and religion. "Judges and lawyers may have played their roles, but it was the veterans who earned this memorial, and it is for them it rises once more," said attorney Hiram Sasser of the Texas-based Liberty Institute, which represented veterans in the legal fight. The settlement approved by a federal judge in April permitted the Park Service to turn over the acre of land known as Sunrise Rock to a Veteran of Foreign Wars post in Barstow and the Veterans Home of California-Barstow in exchange for five acres of donated property elsewhere in the 1.6 million acre preserve, about a four hour-drive east of Los Angeles. The donated land was owned by Sandoz and his wife, Wanda, of Yucca Valley. Sandoz has cared for the memorial as a promise to World War I veteran, Riley Bembry, who with other shell-shocked vets went to the desert to help heal and erected a wooden cross on Sunrise Rock in 1934. It was later replaced with a cross made of steel pipes. Then Sunrise Rock became part of the Mojave National Preserve in 1994, putting the Christian symbol on public land. The American Civil Liberties Union filed a lawsuit in 2001 on behalf of a retired Park Service employee who argued the cross was unconstitutional on government property because of the separation of church and state, and federal courts ordered it removed. Congress stepped in and ordered the land swap in 2003, but the courts rejected the transfer. The issue made its way to the U.S. Supreme Court, which in April 2010 refused to order the cross removed. The high court directed a federal judge to review the congressional land transfer plan. The decision was the latest on the issue by a Supreme Court that has signaled a greater willingness to allow religious symbols on public land amid a number of legal challenges in recent years by civil liberty activists and atheists. Weeks after the 2010 court decision, the cross _ which had been covered up to comply with court injunctions _ was stolen. The stolen cross turned up earlier this month in the San Francisco Bay area tied to a fence post. The San Mateo County Sheriff's Department plans to return the cross. But veterans plan to start fresh and dedicate its replacement in an official ceremony Sunday. The Park Service plans to fence the site, leaving entrances for visitors, and post signs noting it is private land. A plaque stating that the cross is a memorial for U.S. war veterans will be placed on the rock.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352686282905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:11:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352686402842-28</Id><Topic><Title>Election poetry</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1352506329746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:12:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You on the other hand appear to be beyond God's help. Satan waiting patiently for your arrival.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352686402842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:13:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352690534294-29</Id><Topic><Title>How long before infernal and invest croak ???????????</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1351812178848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 19:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long after you bully boy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352690534294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:22:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352693397603-30</Id><Topic><Title>Can Medieval Heat Cool Warming Worries?</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1352686132181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:08:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cyclically higher temperatures often occur around the peaks of sunspot activity, and trend up or down with the cycle peaks... The Sun is more influential than man - something many men cannot accept.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352693397603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:09:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>