<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-26"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348633776133-1</Id><Title>President Obama has Made America Great Again!</Title><Msg>Thank you Mr. President, you have saved America and gained the respect of the World. God Bless our Christian Brother, President Obama...President Obama has Made America Great Again!</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1348633776133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 00:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348634802749-2</Id><Title>Obama Weakling</Title><Msg>What a tragic performance at the UN....before he ran off to do "The View" - Yet more meaningless apologies. Iran slowly taking over Syria? Not a word.Kurdish independence.Not a word.Iran flying fighters and weapons into Syria over Iraqi air space? Not a word. And the incredible volume of hate speech and programming coming from arab and muslim mainstream media 24/7/365 for decades??? Not a word.Just more apologies for some laughable.meaningless middle school quality "film" shot in some guys backyard.Not ONE defense of free speech rights. The incompetence and weakness of this President is jaw dropping.He's literally doing everything possible to set the stage for a major war.He's openly inviting every aggressive,violent nutbag mullah and dictator to have at it! No worries dudes! The US isn't even a PAPER tiger.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348634802749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 00:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348636214774-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Weakling</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348634802749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 00:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"stage for a major war" ?? what does that mean to a lil stink diaper like you?? afraid of a war tax?? afraid of a draft??(daddy has no political connex to protect his lil coward??) a la "w" ??-- your ignorance is pathetic but the fear of a coward like you is disgusting. you should pray because you will stink yourself yellow from fear. you are a disgusting child playing war videos and listening to shizzle pants hannity.</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1348636214774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 01:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348638585491-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Weakling</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348634802749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 00:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic.In defense of Obama's ineptitude you've become a war hawk. Not really.You're just sloppy at expressing your tortured opinion.In reality anytime this country's influence is weakened in the world folks like you are satisfied.Like Doonsebury,for you the enemy is US.And if that ineptitude leads to major war,you're fine with it.That's another excuse to "blame america". Whatever goes wrong,it's not Obama's fault..it AMERICA'S fault. With that brilliant mindset america can never have enemies or even adversaries.Whatever goes wrong is just payback.Right? The only enemy is domestic - THE RED TEAM. Like football by other means. Some people hate the NY Yankees.Some people hate the Dallas Cowboys.And some peoople treat Democrats a dn Republicans like they're rooting for a sports team. MY TEAM right or wrong.Isn't it annoying how global politics won't cooperate with the rules of your chosen "sport"?</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348638585491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 01:49:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348640099339-5</Id><Topic><Title>Romney/Ryan is Bush/Chaney clone</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1348624822858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is doing his best to create the prefect situation for a regional war in the mid east.He is openly inviting every violent extremist to make their move.He's Neville Chamberlain.Anyone who thinks the US won't get dragged in is smokin' some badazz shizzle. It's not just Bush-Cheney.It's Reagan-Bush...Bush-Dole....it's hard power.Romney = Candi Rice.Back to hard power. There's only one alternative.Carter - Christopher as in Warren Christopher,the modern architect of soft power diplomacy...the one that lead to the Iran hostage crises.Clinton,operating in the post Reagan era, tried a little of both and got exactly what you'd expect...mixed results.Kicked Milosivic out of Bosnia but let Bin Laden get away. Obama is going the Warren Christopher route and it's done nothing but erode the situation in the mid east.In Libya he's been lucky.Because so many hated Ghaddafi many liked the US for occasionally kicking his butt.Too bad Egypt is the country that matters. N' that's it.Soft power vs. hard power.That's what the Prez has available.Accomodate and appease enemies and adversaries or,get in there and fight these fires in favor of america's interest before they flame into bigger problems.And accept the inevitable criticism for being 'too pushy" in the world. That's why it's called "Peace Through Strength".You may not like the process.But if you want to see how bad the results can be from "Peace Through Appeasement" look up a little affair known affectionately as 'World War II".And right now,that's appears to be Obama's approach.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348640099339</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 02:14:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348646868083-6</Id><Title>Trading at 92.89 on the Xetra Dax right now.</Title><Msg>It should open there</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1348646868083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 04:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348656140771-7</Id><Topic><Title>Romney/Ryan is Bush/Chaney clone</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1348624822858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Peace Through Strength" is preached by warmongers. The building of military power breeds the temptation to put that power to work. Funny how under Obama world conflict is at historic lows and you say would you do. You're an idiot torycoalition.</Msg><Username>lc298h</Username><Timestamp>1348656140771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 06:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348658819571-8</Id><Title>The 10% President : How 90% of the deficit becomes somebody else's fault.</Title><Msg>A question raised by President Obama's immortal line on CBS's "60 Minutes" on Sunday—"I think that, you know, as President, I bear responsibility for everything, to some degree"—is what that degree really is. Maybe 70% or 80% of the buck stops with him? Or is it halfsies? Nope. Now we know: It turns out the figure is 10%. The other 90% is somebody else's fault. This revelation came when Steve Kroft mentioned that the national debt has climbed 60% on the President's watch. "Well, first of all, Steve, I think it's important to understand the context here," Mr. Obama replied. Fair enough, so here's his context in full, with our own annotation and translation below: "When I came into office, I inherited the biggest deficit in our history.1 And over the last four years, the deficit has gone up, but 90% of that is as a consequence of two wars that weren't paid for,2 as a consequence of tax cuts that weren't paid for,3 a prescription drug plan that was not paid for,4 and then the worst economic crisis since the Great Depression.5 "Now we took some emergency actions, but that accounts for about 10% of this increase in the deficit,6 and we have actually seen the federal government grow at a slower pace than at any time since Dwight Eisenhower, in fact, substantially lower than the federal government grew under either Ronald Reagan or George Bush.7" *** Footnote No. 1: Either Mr. Obama inherited the largest deficit in American history or he won the 1944 election, but both can't be true. The biggest annual deficit the modern government has ever run was in 1943, equal to 30.3% of the economy, to mobilize for World War II. The next biggest years were the following two, at 22.7% and 21.5%, to win it. The deficit in fiscal 2008 was a mere 3.2% of GDP. The deficit in fiscal 2009, which began on October 1, 2008 and ran through September 2009, soared to 10.1%, the highest since 1945. Mr. Obama wants to blame all of that on his predecessor, and no doubt the recession that began in December 2007 reduced revenues and increased automatic spending "stabilizers" like jobless insurance. But Mr. Obama conveniently forgets a little event in February 2009 known as the "stimulus" that increased spending by a mere $830 billion above the normal baseline. The recession ended in June 2009, but spending has still kept rising. The President has presided over four years in a row of deficits in excess of $1 trillion, and the spending baseline going forward into his second term is nearly $1.1 trillion more than in fiscal 2007. Federal spending as a share of GDP will average 24.1% over his first term including 2013. Even if you throw out fiscal 2009 and blame that entirely on Mr. Bush, the Obama spending average will be 23.8% of GDP. That compares to a post-WWII average of a little under 20%. Spending under Mr. Bush averaged 20.1% including 2009, and 19.6% if that year is left out. Footnotes No. 2 through 4: Liberals continue to claim that the main causes of the current fiscal mess are tax rates established in, er, 2001 and 2003 and the post-9/11 wars on terror. But by 2006 and 2007, those tax rates were producing revenue of 18.2% and 18.5% of GDP, near historic norms. Another quandary for Mr. Obama's apologists is that he has endorsed nearly all of these policies. The 2003 Medicare drug benefit wasn't offset by tax hikes or spending cuts, but Democrats expanded the program as part of ObamaCare. The President also extended all the Bush tax rates in 2010 for two more years in the name of helping the economy, and he now wants to continue them for people earning under $200,000, which is where 71% of their "cost" resides. The Iraq campaign was won and beginning to be wound down when he took office, and he himself surged more troops in Afghanistan. Footnote No. 5: Mr. Obama keeps dining out on the excuse of the recession, but that ended halfway through his first year. The main deficit problems since 2009 are a permanently higher spending base (see Footnote No. 1) and the slowest economic recovery in modern history. Revenues have remained below 16% of the economy, compared to 18% to 19% in a normal expansion. The 2008 crisis is long over. The crisis now is Mr. Obama's non-recovery. Footnote No. 6: Even at face value, Mr. Obama's suggestion that he is "only" responsible for 10% of what the government does is ludicrous. Note that in addition to his stimulus, what he calls "emergency actions" include his new health-care entitlement that will cost taxpayers $200 billion per year when fully implemented and grow annually at 8%, even using low-ball assumptions. But the larger point concerns executive leadership. Every President "inherits" a government that was built over generations, which he chooses to change, or not to change, to suit his priorities. Mr. Obama chose to see the government he inherited and grow it faster than any President since LBJ. The pre-eminent political question now is whether to reform the government we have to make it affordable going forward, or to keep growing the government and raise taxes to finance it, if that is even possible. Mr. Obama favors the second option, though he pretends he can merely tax the rich to do it. Nobody who has looked honestly at the numbers believes that—not his own Simpson-Bowles commission and not the Congressional "super committee" he sanctioned but then worked to undermine. At every turn he has demagogued the Romney-Ryan proposals to modernize the entitlement state so it is affordable, and he personally blew up the "grand bargain" House Speaker John Boehner was willing to strike last summer. Footnote No. 7: Mr. Obama's posture as the tightest skinflint since Eisenhower is a tutorial in how to dissemble with statistics. The growth rate seems low because he's measuring from the end of fiscal 2009, after a one-year spending increase of $535 billion. That is the year of his stimulus and thus spending is growing off a much higher base. The real annual pace of government growth is closer to 5%, and that doesn't count ObamaCare. *** In another news-making bit with "60 Minutes," which the program decided not to air, Mr. Obama conceded that "Do we see sometimes us going overboard in our campaign, mistakes that are made, areas where there's no doubt that somebody could dispute how we are presenting things, that happens in politics." Note the passive voice, as if the President's re-election campaign is disembodied from the President. If Mr. Obama's campaign seems dishonest enough that even Mr. Obama is forced to admit it, this is because it's coming from the top.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348658819571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348658961155-9</Id><Topic><Title>Romney/Ryan is Bush/Chaney clone</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1348624822858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some day you should come visit this planet.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348658961155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348659961481-10</Id><Title>br plant in baton rouge ,we poll 250 union members and 63% said they are voting mitt romney</Title><Msg>wow</Msg><Username>gmman973</Username><Timestamp>1348659961481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348660523646-11</Id><Title>The Sad Reality of Harry Reid’s Senate</Title><Msg>Yesterday afternoon, Democratic Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid took to the Senate floor and offered the words that will—or at least should—define his tenure in the Senate. “The amendment days are over,” Reid somberly declared. He was referring to a specific bill—Rand Paul’s legislation that would remove foreign aid from Egypt, Libya, and Pakistan—but Reid could say those words at any time, because that sentiment hangs over the Senate day after day. The basic backstory is this: Paul has wanted a vote on this bill for quite some time, but since Republicans aren’t permitted to offer legislation or amendments in Reid’s Senate, he has been ignored. Paul decided he was going to hold up Senate business so he could get his floor vote. Liberals call this obstruction, but they are either uninformed or disingenuous; it’s actually a response to obstruction, which begins with Reid’s methodical deconstruction of basic Senate procedures. John McCain wanted to have a debate on the subject–something that is now foreign to Reid’s Senate as well–and to offer amendments to the bill. No, said Reid. Here is how the Hill framed it: Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid (D-Nev.) caved on Sen. Rand Paul’s (R-Ky.) demand for a vote on his bill to end aid to some Middle Eastern countries. It now constitutes “caving” for Reid to allow a vote in the Senate–and without amendments or debate. The amendment process is key to understanding why liberal commentators get it so wrong when they complain about the GOP’s insistence on being permitted to take part in the democratic process. Reid has perfected the art of “filling the amendment tree,” which is a device he employs to use up all allowable amendment space on a bill with his own so the GOP is unable to offer theirs. The best demonstration of how far from reality the GOP’s critics are, and the best refutation of it as well, actually came in Senator Marco Rubio’s full interview with Jon Stewart on the Daily Show in June. Stewart asked Rubio about GOP obstruction, and what he sees as a one-sided refusal to engage in bipartisanship. He asked Rubio: “can you explain to me why my reality is wrong?” Rubio was happy to. He explained to Stewart that in order to protect Democrats from having to take any votes—even votes they’ll win—Reid won’t let the GOP offer amendments or get votes on their legislation. Later on, Rubio gave a few examples of Reid’s obstruction. Rubio said he put forth a bill called the AGREE Act, because it was essentially a piece of legislation that incorporated the positions that Democrats and Republicans both agreed on. He said he offered a Jobs 2.0 bill that was bipartisan as well. He couldn’t get a vote on either one, he said. Though Rubio didn’t mention it, it’s worth here pointing out what exactly Reid was doing instead of passing bipartisan legislation. While the Senate still hasn’t passed a budget in three years, Reid was wasting Senate floor time on stunts like leveling unfounded accusations against Mitt Romney and possibly flouting ethics rules to campaign for Obama on the Senate floor–all instead of a jobs bill or a budget. Then Reid has the audacity to say that the time for amendments is over, because they have to get moving on temporary bills to fund the government, which shouldn’t be necessary in the first place if Reid were doing his job. The Stewart-Rubio debate on Senate procedure wrapped up with this exchange: Stewart: “There is an accountability issue within the Republican conference that I think is not a fantasy of mine, or has been made up. And in any conversation of it, it’s been ‘well those guys are mean too, and we’re not’.” Rubio: “But you’re talking about the filibuster. The filibuster basically is requiring 60 votes on a bill. That’s what the filibuster is. I’m saying we can’t even get the vote on the ideas that we’ve offered. And so when you don’t allow the minority party to get votes on legitimate ideas, the only tool the minority party has, the only leverage you have as the minority party in the Senate is the 60-vote threshold. That’s the counterreaction to it. And that’s what I’m trying to tell you.” Stewart: “So you don’t feel that you’ve overused your filibuster, it’s you’ve overprotected yourselves from the viciousness of the lack of voting you’re allowed?” Rubio: “No. I’m saying the Senate isn’t working the way it’s supposed to work. The Senate is supposed to be a place where any senator can offer amendments on any bill, you have a vote on it, [and] if they don’t like it you vote against it and we move on.” And with that, the conversation moved on as well, with Stewart duly educated and pronouncing the debate—which he was losing, badly—too technical for the show. I’ve written before about the various Senate traditions and procedures that Reid has destroyed in his ongoing quest for a debate-free, vote-free, budget-free Senate. The amendment process is a major one, however, and those mourning the end of the Senate we once knew can either continue their partisan venting by attacking Republicans or they can be honest and go right to the source. They can talk to Harry Reid.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348660523646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348660608309-12</Id><Topic><Title>The Sad Reality of Harry Reid’s Senate</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348660523646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a conference call with reporters, Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid said that his fellow Mormon, Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney, "is not the face of Mormonism." Reid added he agrees with Romney critics who claim Romney has "sullied" the faith of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints, the official name of the church. We've been down this theological road before. In the 1980s, liberal Christians who pretty much had the "faith" territory to themselves since Prohibition and the Scopes "monkey trial," claimed that evangelical and fundamentalist Christians were not "real Christians” when they began to exert their influence in the political arena. In recent weeks, Senator Reid has violated at least one of the Ten Commandments -- the one prohibiting the bearing of false witness -- as well as the command of Jesus to "Judge not, lest you be judged. For in the same way you judge others, you will be judged." (see Matthew 7:2-5). That doesn't mean Reid can't disagree with Romney's political positions, which is an entirely different matter and well within his theological and political rights, but to suggest that Romney's faith isn't as good as his own -- the apparent intent of his remark -- is to violate the command of the One Reid claims to follow. In the matter of "bearing false witness," Reid claimed that a "source," who he refused to name, told him that Romney had not paid any federal income taxes in a decade. Reid indicated he believed him and challenged Romney to release his tax returns. When Romney finally did, proving he has, indeed, paid millions of dollars in taxes, did Reid apologize and ask Romney to forgive him? He did not. Instead, Reid moved on to another accusation that Romney had "fudged" his charitable donations in order to live up to the percentage of his income he claimed to have given away in recent years. I'll leave it to the Mormon hierarchy and their flock to judge among themselves and not in public discourse who is the better face of Mormonism.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348660608309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348661448745-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Sad Reality of Harry Reid’s Senate</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348660523646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that Mitt Romney has released his taxes with proof that he’s paid taxes over the past ten years, it’s time for United States Senator Harry Reid of Nevada to “man up!” Harry Reid stood before his fellow senators on the nation’s United States’ senate floor and insisted that he had a reliable, confidential source which claimed GOP presidential candidate Mitt Romney didn’t pay taxes for ten years. Reid said that someone had contacted his office with the information, and Reid felt it necessary to face the American people via the press on the congressional floor and spread his rumor. When challenged, he reasserted his claim even more boldly. Harry Reid made a national spectacle of Mitt Romney – and himself – by repeating gossip that said Romney had not paid any taxes for the past ten years. Harry Reid has now been proven wrong – dead wrong. The logical question at this point is: Where’s the apology, Harry Reid? During the midterm election when Sharon Angle was challenging Harry Reid in the senate race in Nevada in 2010, she told Reid to “man up!” It’s apparent that Harry Reid still refuses to “man up” when he needs to do so for decency’s and dignity’s sake. Without a second thought, Harry Reid should have hit the press late Friday afternoon, the best time of the week for a politician to do something negative, politically, because it’s when most people have their minds on the weekend and news doesn’t stick like it does earlier in the doldrums of the work week. Reid could have gotten a totally justified apology out of the way – and in the future, people would have said, “He apologized but it didn’t get much press.” That would have been the smart and respectable way for Reid to have handled this latest embarrassment of his. But no, Reid lets Mitt Romney’s day of proof that Reid’s no-taxes-in-ten-years fiasco was nothing but “dirty politics” come and go without as much as a murmur of apology or regret for the misspeak – or lie – that he asserted for months. Those who may have had an ounce of respect remaining for Senator Harry Reid saw it evaporate on Friday. Romney lays all the tax information out on the table, makes Reid look like a gossiping fool, and Reid is mum. Reid should have been mum when he allegedly got the misinformation about Romney’s taxes – if, in fact, he ever got such information at all. If he really was really notified about Romney not paying taxes – knowing Washington, D.C. as we do – you would think the reference of the news would have been leaked from someone, somewhere by now. It makes one wonder if Reid ever even got such information at all and just made it up to help President Obama via “dirty politics”. That was my thought back when the Harry Reid’s allegations about Romney not paying taxes broke. I thought – and wrote – that the story was likely made up via “dirty politics” within the Democratic Party, and Reid was chosen to deliver the “dirty politicking” because a man with his years wouldn’t have that much time left in Congress anyway. One would assume he’s going to retire someday. Harry Reid has epitomized “dirty politics” in the 21st Century – pronounced most strongly by Reid during the presidential election of 2012 – and, unfortunately for him, he is making “Harry Reid’s dirty politicking” his legacy. Throughout American history, Harry Reid will be remembered as the American politician who (fill in the blank with one of Harry’s stunts here) – the man that the Democrats of this era idolized to iconic proportions. How sad. Incidentally, an informal online poll over the weekend shows that 79% of Americans believe Harry Reid should apologize to Mitt Romney, 10% believe that lying is expected of Harry Reid, and 9% have no opinion. 10% expect Harry Reid to lie – this percentage will likely increase greatly after this story settles in America’s minds. It may be too late for Harry Reid to “save face”, but it’s not too late for him to “man up” and apologize to Mitt Romney – as well as the American public for his misinformation or lies – like any decent human being would.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348661448745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 08:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348667443212-14</Id><Topic><Title>Romney/Ryan is Bush/Chaney clone</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1348624822858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't beieve they are a clone, but if they were we would be in much better shape than this leader has put the country in. bankrupt the country, no jobs, middle east in chaos, race and class warfare at all time lows. change???</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1348667443212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348667734605-15</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama has Made America Great Again!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1348633776133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 00:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too stupid for words.................................</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1348667734605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348668684419-16</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama has Made America Great Again!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1348633776133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 00:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obviously thinks Madonna has class too.</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1348668684419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348669903728-17</Id><Title>Inventories fell! Oil rising!</Title><Msg>..........</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1348669903728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:31:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348674781717-18</Id><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending September 21, 2012</Title><Msg>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending September 21, 2012 U.S. crude oil refinery inputs averaged 14.6 million barrels per day during the week ending September 21, 292 thousand barrels per day below the previous week’s average. Refineries operated at 87.4 percent of their operable capacity last week. Gasoline production decreased last week, averaging 8.9 million barrels per day. Distillate fuel production increased last week, averaging 4.6 million barrels per day. U.S. crude oil imports averaged 7.6 million barrels per day last week, down by 2.3 million barrels per day from the previous week. Over the last four weeks, crude oil imports have averaged 8.5 million barrels per day, 272 thousand barrels per day below the same four-week period last year. Total motor gasoline imports (including both finished gasoline and gasoline blending components) last week averaged 491 thousand barrels per day. Distillate fuel imports averaged 108 thousand barrels per day last week. U.S. commercial crude oil inventories (excluding those in the Strategic Petroleum Reserve) decreased by 2.4 million barrels from the previous week. At 365.2 million barrels, U.S. crude oil inventories are above the upper limit of the average range for this time of year. Total motor gasoline inventories decreased by 0.5 million barrels last week and are in the lower half of the average range. Finished gasoline inventories decreased while blending components inventories increased last week. Distillate fuel inventories decreased by 0.5 million barrels last week and are near the lower limit of the average range for this time of year. Propane/propylene inventories increased by 0.3 million barrels last week and are above the upper limit of the average range. Total commercial petroleum inventories decreased by 2.7 million barrels last week. Total products supplied over the last four-week period have averaged 18.4 million barrels per day, down by 3.4 percent compared to the similar period last year. Over the last four weeks, motor gasoline product supplied has averaged 8.8 million barrels per day, down by 1.0 percent from the same period last year. Distillate fuel product supplied has averaged about 3.5 million barrels per day over the last four weeks, down by 8.7 percent from the same period last year. Jet fuel product supplied is 0.2 percent lower over the last four weeks compared to the same four-week period last year. eia Data Overview (Combined Table 1 and Table 9) eia -------------------------------------- BLOOMBERG DOLLAR INDEX SPOT bloomberg -------------------------------------- Energy Futures Prices Below you may find all the futures prices &amp; quotes for: Crude Oil, Heating Oil, Gasoline RBOB, Natural Gas, ICE Brent Crude Oil, Ethanol (E) and more. Real Time Streaming Futures Quotes (CFDs) forexpros -------------------------------------- e85 prices e85prices -------------------------------------- Gas Buddy gasbuddy -------------------------------------- Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production (Usually updated late in the day on Thursday) ethanolrfa All of these URLs are available at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348674781717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 11:53:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348677377194-19</Id><Topic><Title>Place your bets</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348610347025</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:59:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can you refer to hate spewing mouths when that is all you do? Typical hypocrite.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348677377194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348678987215-20</Id><Topic><Title>The 10% President : How 90% of the deficit becomes somebody else's fault.</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348658819571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reagan and W Bush quadrupled the debt. Reagan gave Speaker of the House Tip O Neill massive increases in federal welfare spending and Bush doubled in his first four years federal social spending for Nancy Pelosi. Both parties have destoyed the USA. The system is broken beyond repair</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1348678987215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348681564465-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Sad Reality of Harry Reid’s Senate</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348660523646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Prince Harry has a lot of skeletons in his own closet. The messes he has been involved in Nevada, takes a lot of stupid guts for him to jump on Romney with lies or miss information.. He and Pelosi deserve each other.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1348681564465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348683087821-22</Id><Title>Dems push DOE for environmental analysis of natural gas exports</Title><Msg>Dems push DOE for environmental analysis of natural gas exports By Zack Colman - 09/26/12 12:33 PM ET A group of 20 Democrats told the Energy Department on Wednesday that it should complete environmental tests before approving liquefied natural gas (LNG) export deals. In a letter to Energy Secretary Steven Chu, the signatories expressed concern about the amount of hydraulic fracturing, known as fracking, needed to meet demand for natural gas exports. Led by Democratic Reps. Jared Polis (Colo.) and Maurice Hinchey (N.Y.), the lawmakers called on DOE to conduct an environmental impact statement, as outlined under the National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA), before approving more export deals or LNG terminal permits. “We are concerned that exporting more LNG would lead to greater hydraulic fracturing, or ‘fracking,’ activity thus threatening the health of local residents and jobs,” the letter said. “For instance, increased natural gas production in communities across the nation could negatively impact farmers, residents and local property values.” Fracking is the process of injecting a high-pressure mixture of water, sand and chemicals into tight rock formations to unlock natural gas. It has been linked to groundwater contamination and seismic activity. Many lawmakers and the gas industry say environmental fears about fracking are badly overstated and that the process is safe. Republicans, and some Democrats, have pushed the administration to expedite LNG export approval. They say the opportunity to sell cheap, domestic natural gas at higher prices abroad could be a financial boon that creates jobs and stabilizes the energy market. But some lawmakers, mainly Democrats, have urged caution on exporting LNG. They say it could raise electricity prices for consumers and the manufacturing industry, on top of the environmental concerns raised in the Wednesday letter. The letter signatories said LNG exports highlight the need for a review, citing NEPA language that said an environmental impact statement is triggered by “major Federal action significantly affecting the quality of the human environment.” The lawmakers said ramping up LNG exports would accelerate fracking. They cited a U.S. Energy Information Administration study that said 63 percent of export demand would come from increased production, 85 percent of which would come from unconventional methods such as fracking. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348683087821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348683341822-23</Id><Title>Report: Carbon tax could halve deficit</Title><Msg>Report: Carbon tax could halve deficit By Ben Geman - 09/26/12 12:38 PM ET Taxing carbon emissions could raise enough money to eventually cut the deficit in half, but policymakers would face tough questions about whether to use the cash to brighten the fiscal outlook or tackle other needs, a report finds. Carbon tax proposals to help battle climate change are politically dead in Congress right now. But the Congressional Research Service overview nonetheless arrives at a time of renewed interest in the idea from some policy wonks, Democrats, and former GOP lawmakers. The report finds that imposing an escalating fee that starts at $20 per metric ton could reduce the projected 10-year budget deficit by more than 50 percent, from $2.3 trillion to $1.1 trillion.That estimate relies on the Congressional Budget Office’s (CBO) “baseline” deficit projection. But the report notes that the same carbon tax would have a much smaller impact on the deficit — cutting it about 12 percent — under CBO’s “alternative” scenario that forecasts a much bigger shortfall. The report, relying on CBO analysis of carbon costs under a hypothetical cap-and-trade program, estimates that the escalating $20-per-ton tax could raise $88 billion in 2012, rising to $154 billion in 2021. However, deficit reduction is just one possible use for the cash. CRS notes that policymakers would face “key trade-offs” in weighing whether to minimize the costs of the tax on society overall “versus alleviating the costs borne by subgroups in the U.S. population or specific domestic industries.” “Economic studies indicate that using carbon tax revenues to offset reductions in existing taxes – labor, income and investment – could yield the greatest benefit to the economy overall. However, the approaches that yield the largest overall benefit often impose disproportionate costs on lower-income households,” the report finds. The report delves into other potential uses instead of devoting all carbon tax money to attacking the deficit. “If Congress were to consider a carbon tax system, a key debate would likely involve the degree to which carbon tax revenues would be returned to households to alleviate the expected financial burden imposed by the carbon tax,” it states. Also, the tax could hurt energy-intensive manufacturing and other industries that face competition from abroad, so they might need a piece of the pie. “Policymakers could alleviate this burden through carbon tax revenue distribution or through a border adjustment mechanism. Both approaches may entail trade concerns,” the report notes. The notion of a carbon tax also raises other tough questions, such as whether it’s levied on sources of fuel like oil production and coal mining, or other points, such as emissions from oil refineries and power plants that burn coal and natural gas, or “downstream” energy uses such as industrial plants and vehicles. For now, it’s an abstract debate as climate legislation remains frozen on Capitol Hill, where Republicans are seeking to roll back the Environmental Protection Agency’s existing power to regulate carbon emissions. Cap-and-trade or carbon tax bills face gigantic political hurdles in the current Congress and likely the next one, too. CRS notes — in somewhat clinical terms — that carbon tax proposals would face strong pushback from powerful industries. “Certain stakeholders are likely to exercise strong opposition to a carbon tax. These include energy-intensive manufacturers, farmers, and regional energy interests — especially those whose asset values may fall with expected impacts on profitability of owned or leased coal and oil resources,” the report states. However, there remains an undercurrent of interest in a carbon tax, which advocates call a more straightforward and efficient way to address carbon emissions than cap-and-trade proposals. Supporters and policy analysts have held a series of meetings to discuss the idea, which has support from some lawmakers. Rep. Jim McDermott (D-Wash.) introduced carbon tax legislation in August. Reps. Henry Waxman (D-Calif.) and Ed Markey (D-Mass.) joined with former GOP Reps. Sherwood Boehlert and Wayne Gilchrest in a February Washington Post op-ed that said, “We could slash our debt by making power plants and oil refineries pay for the carbon emissions that endanger our health and environment.” It called broadly for a “market mechanism such as the sale of carbon allowances or a fee on carbon pollution to lower emissions and increase revenue.” In addition, former GOP Rep. Bob Inglis (R-S.C.) is using a new role at George Mason University to advocate for his idea of a “revenue-neutral” carbon tax under which taxes on emissions would be offset by reductions in other rates. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348683341822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348683657074-24</Id><Title>Major energy firm speaks out against Arctic oil drilling</Title><Msg>Major energy firm speaks out against Arctic oil drilling By Zack Colman - 09/26/12 10:40 AM ET A major energy firm said Tuesday that the industry should avoid oil drilling in the Arctic, making it the first time an energy company making a play in the competitive region has spoken out against the practice. French oil-and-gas giant Total SA’s CEO Christophe de Margerie told the Financial Times that the environmental risk from Arctic oil drilling is too great. “Oil on Greenland would be a disaster,” he told the Financial Times in an interview. “A leak would do too much damage to the image of the company.” Though it is active in the Arctic, Total is only drilling for natural gas in Russian waters — an activity de Margerie justified as safer than oil drilling. Many of Total’s competitors — Royal Dutch Shell, ExxonMobil, Italy’s ENI and Norway’s Statoil — have Arctic oil drilling deals in place in Russian, Alaskan and Greenland waters. The dash for Arctic oil resources has already thrown some hurdles in the path of oil firms. The Financial Times noted United Kingdom-based Cairn Energy spent $1 billion looking for oil near Greenland, but found nothing in commercial volume. And in the United States, Shell tried to enter the Alaskan Arctic region first, but damaged safety equipment and a looming deadline to exit oil-bearing zone forced it to shelve its Arctic plans until 2013. That hiccup pushed Statoil to delay its Alaskan offshore drilling earlier this month by one year, pegging it for a 2015 start date. It said it would monitor Shell’s progress in the region before it enters the area. The Obama administration revamped oversight and strengthened drilling standards after the BP incident, saying that makeover was necessary to prevent a repeat. Republicans have said new red tape from the regulatory overhaul prevented Shell from entering the Arctic with enough time to perform its drilling operations. Environmentalists have applauded the new rules. They have pushed back against Arctic drilling, saying that an oil spill would be disastrous for the Arctic ecosystem. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348683657074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348683830919-25</Id><Topic><Title>Major energy firm speaks out against Arctic oil drilling</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348683657074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Top Senate Dem presses Interior to scrap Arctic oil lease sales By Ben Geman - 09/26/12 02:13 PM ET The Senate’s number two Democrat and five colleagues are urging the Obama administration to cancel planned oil-and-gas lease sales off Alaska’s Arctic shores in coming years. A letter from Senate Majority Whip Richard Durbin (D-Ill.) and others arrives shortly after Interior approved Royal Dutch Shell’s preliminary drilling on existing Arctic leases – a project that faces strong opposition from green groups. “Challenges with infrastructure and spill response are unprecedented in the Arctic’s remote, undeveloped region: the Arctic Ocean is characterized by hurricane-force storms, 20-foot swells, sea ice up to 25 feet thick, sub-zero temperatures and months-long darkness,” states the letter to Interior Secretary Ken Salazar from Durbin and Sens. Jeff Merkley (D-Ore.), Patrick Leahy (D-Vt.), Barbara Boxer (D-Calif.), Frank Lautenberg (D-N.J.) and Sheldon Whitehouse (D-R.I.). The senators’ Sept. 21 letter argues that new leasing off Alaska’s northern coast should be contingent on existence of a “comprehensive” scientific monitoring program, demonstration of oil spill response capacity and other conditions. Interior’s 2012-2017 offshore oil-and-gas lease sale schedule includes sales in Arctic waters in the final two years of the program, but the letter says they should be removed. The senators say they recognize that Interior’s five-year plan includes commitments to “mitigating and eliminating environmental and subsistence conflict,” but adds that the Arctic is a “unique environment with significant hurdles” that federal agencies still must address. The lawmakers also note that the Arctic has “extremely limited infrastructure” and that the nearest Coast Guard station is 1,000 miles away. “In the event of an oil spill the response may be too slow and irreversible damage to ecosystems and species could result. Consequently, we strongly disagree that leases in the Arctic Ocean should be included in the 2012-2017 program,” the letter states. Sales in the Arctic seas are currently planned for 2016 and 2017. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348683830919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:23:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348687000302-26</Id><Title>Infrastructure Investment and Job Training!</Title><Msg>A federal-State-private partnership must invest in the nation’s infrastructure: roads, bridges, airports, ports, and water systems, among others. Federal training programs have to be overhauled and made relevant for the workplace of the twenty-first century.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1348687000302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:16:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348688710575-27</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Ryan Always Frowning?</Title><Username>westsbest0304</Username><Timestamp>1348625656294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:14:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok but that frown is like a permanent feature of his face. He looks like a very unhappy person in general. It's really kinda weird. Maybe if he smiled more he'd be appealing but right now he kinda comes off as that angry young guy.</Msg><Username>westsbest0304</Username><Timestamp>1348688710575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348693860581-28</Id><Title>This Week In Petroleum September 26, 2012</Title><Msg>This Week In Petroleum September 26, 2012 Next Release: October 3, 2012 The Impact of U.S. Crude Oil Production on Gulf Coast Crude Imports Increased production of U.S. domestic crude oil, particularly light sweet crude from tight oil formations in Texas and North Dakota, has been replacing imports of foreign light crude oil processed by U.S. Gulf Coast refineries. With Gulf Coast imports of heavier crude oil remaining steady, this shift in light crude supply from imports to domestic production has changed the average quality of crude oil imported into the U.S. Gulf Coast (PADD 3). One of the primary characteristics that distinguishes different grades of crude oil is density, or how light or heavy the oil is. Crude oil density is typically measured as American Petroleum Institute (API) gravity, which is a scale expressing the specific gravity, or density, of liquid petroleum products in degrees; the higher the API gravity, the lighter the crude oil. Since 2007, as domestic production of light sweet crude has increased, overall crude imports have fallen and become, on average, heavier. The average API gravity of crude imports processed in PADD 3 has dropped from more than 28° API to less than 27° API (Figure 1). This move to a higher percentage of heavier oil imports accelerated in 2011 when volumes of domestic light sweet crude oil production increased significantly, reducing the need for imports. Going forward, the growing production of domestic light crude may strain the capability of refineries to balance crude slates by reducing light crude imports and may put downward pressure on light crude prices on the U.S. Gulf Coast. Normally, light crude warrants a premium over heavier crude. The volume of imported light crude oil (API gravity greater than 35°) (Figure 2) has decreased since 2010 to make room for the increasing volumes of light crudes from Eagle Ford (Texas) and Bakken (North Dakota) tight oil plays as well as for additional light sweet crude moving down the Seaway pipeline from Cushing, Oklahoma. While the absolute volume of imported heavy crude oil (API gravity less than 25°) has decreased since 2010 as well, the volume of heavy crude imports as a percentage of total PADD 3 imports has increased from 44 percent in 2010 to 47 percent in 2012. The increased light sweet crude oil production from the Eagle Ford and Bakken fields has primarily displaced foreign light crudes from Africa. In total, light crude imports processed in PADD 3 have decreased to less than 0.7 million barrels per day (bbl/d) for the first half of 2012 from an average of 1.2 million bbl/d in 2010 (lowering the light crude imports to PADD 3 to 15 percent from 22 percent). To maintain a balanced crude slate with increased light crude availability, refiners have reduced imports of light crude and replaced them with domestic production. Imports of heavy crude processed in PADD 3 have continued as much of the heavy crude is either under long-term contract, is processed in equity refineries, or is needed to blend with domestic light crudes to balance the refinery crude slate. The availability of domestic light crude to U.S. Gulf Coast refineries is expected to continue increasing as pipeline expansions allow more crude to move to the U.S. Gulf Coast. This increased light crude supply could exert downward pressure on Gulf Coast light crude prices. Light crude generally contains less sulfur than heavier crudes and is easier to process. As a result, it is normally priced at a premium to heavier crude oils. However, processing large amounts of light low-sulfur crude can unbalance refinery processing units. Refineries on the U.S. Gulf Coast in particular are designed to process heavy crude oils. Catalytic crackers, hydrocrackers, and coking units convert the very heavy compounds in the crude oil into lighter and more valuable products. Processing lighter crude oil could underload the cracking units that handle the heavier components and overload the units that process the lighter components, causing refineries to operate less economically than they would with a more balanced crude slate. To process more light sweet crude, PADD 3 refiners would need to readjust refinery crude runs, revamp refinery equipment to run a higher percent of light crude, or reduce the use of heavy crude upgrading equipment, which may have adverse impacts on operations. Each of these alternatives carries a cost and, as a result, refiners may not be willing to pay as much for light crude (compared to heavy crude), and light crude prices could decline. Gasoline and diesel fuel prices fall for the first time in 12 weeks The U.S. average retail price of regular gasoline decreased five cents last week to $3.83 per gallon, 32 cents per gallon higher than last year at this time. Prices decreased in all regions of the Nation except the Rocky Mountains, where the price was up less than a penny to remain at $3.77 per gallon. The West Coast price decreased less than a penny to remain at $4.07 per gallon. The largest decrease came in the Midwest, where the price is $3.81 per gallon, down eight cents from last week. The Gulf Coast price decreased six cents to $3.60 per gallon, while the East Coast price dropped a nickel to $3.83 per gallon. The national average diesel fuel price decreased a nickel to $4.09 per gallon, 30 cents per gallon higher than last year at this time. The largest decrease came on the West Coast, where the price is down eight cents to $4.32 per gallon. The Midwest price decreased six cents to $4.02 per gallon. The prices in the East Coast, Gulf Coast, and Rocky Mountain regions all decreased three cents to $4.09 per gallon, $4.00 per gallon, and $4.23 per gallon, respectively. Propane stocks edge up slightly Inventories of propane showed signs of leveling off last week, as the winter build season nears its end. Total U.S. inventories grew by 0.3 million barrels to end at 74.3 million barrels, 18 million barrels (32 percent) higher than a year ago. Midwest regional stocks were up by 0.3 million barrels, and East Coast stocks added 0.1 million barrels. Gulf Coast inventories dropped by 0.2 million barrels, and Rocky Mountain/West Coast regional stocks were up slightly. Propylene non-fuel-use inventories represented 6.1 percent of total propane inventories. eia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348693860581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348694682567-29</Id><Title>Power, gas groups press for Dodd-Frank delay</Title><Msg>Power, gas groups press for Dodd-Frank delay By Ben Geman - 09/26/12 04:48 PM ET Trade groups for power companies and natural-gas suppliers are pressing the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) to delay their industries’ compliance with reforms required under the 2010 Dodd-Frank law, warning that higher energy costs could result unless the leeway is provided. Three groups, in a detailed request to the CFTC, say more time is needed to adhere to the web of new controls on sprawling derivatives trading markets, which were seen as part of the reason the financial sector destabilized ahead of the 2008 economic crisis. “Careful and deliberate implementation is ... necessary so that uncertainty as to rules and regulations does not inadvertently disrupt the liquidity of the derivatives markets and the delivery of wholesale, non-financial commodities related to electric and gas operations, both of which could result in higher prices for consumers and commodity market participants,” states the Sept. 24 filing from the Edison Electric Institute, the American Gas Association and the Electric Power Supply Association. The Dodd-Frank law required a series of rules such as new position limits on trading in commodity markets; new reporting and margin requirements; clearer definitions of certain types of trading and market participants; and a number of others. A number of rules have been finalized while others are pending. With some compliance dates looming in October, the filing notes that the groups need more time to prepare for compliance with new and “still uncertain” record-keeping requirements, determine their status under the rules and make other preparations. The letter to the CFTC asks the regulators to defer compliance for “energy market participants” for a year after all the rules are finalized. “The rules are so interrelated that we are asking for a period of a year after the final rule is issued so that we can have a comprehensive look at all the rules and regulations that apply to us, so that we can develop a comprehensive compliance program,” said Lopa Parikh, the director of federal regulatory affairs for the Edison Electric Institute, which represents for-profit power companies. Energy trade groups have long expressed concern that their members using trading markets as a necessary hedge against price swings could be harmed by rules designed to prevent the kind of freewheeling, risky Wall Street trading that helped destabilize financial firms several years ago thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348694682567</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348695089544-30</Id><Title>Republicans are Amazing!</Title><Msg>Despite the GFC being unique, where no economist knows how long it will take to recover from a near complete shut-down of the banking system, let alone how to structure the recovery, republicans know what should have been done and how long it should have taken. Fact is, since real fears of a depression were evident, the recovery will take more then 8 years. Those they say less than 4 years are liars. But that's no surprise....republicans are liars. It would be amusing, but the republicans lied about conducting an unfunded war, where no WMD were found and many of our soldiers died. After this destruction of the US they offer us Romney. It should be hilarious but too much was spent and too many died.</Msg><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1348695089544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:31:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348699074263-31</Id><Title>Obammy---GETCHYO HANDS OUT MY POCKETS GAY BOY!!!!</Title><Msg>////////</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348699074263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 18:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348699286008-32</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are Amazing!</Title><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1348695089544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$, the potential for a real and complete meltdown of the financial system was addressed with TARP I and those concerns were over even long before Obama took office. TARP II, Auto bail out, Stimulus I, Stimulus II, Cash for Clunkers, etc were all (officially) about jobs creation and recovery. We largely recovered from the real depression in</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1348699286008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 18:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348699860191-33</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama has Made America Great Again!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1348633776133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 00:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us specifics on what he has done that makes us great again??? I mean what has he improved: International Affairs/Relations? No Domestic Affairs (relations, etc) No Economcy? No Unemplolyment? No Military (be that 'victories' or force reductions or getting them home)? No Federal Goverence? No Homeland Security? No Environment? No Infrastructure? No (Remember all them "shovel ready" projects?) Just exactly what has he ACCOMPLISHED (not words but deeds) that makes us great again? (Which presupposes we were not already/still great before.)</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1348699860191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 18:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348699970889-34</Id><Title>probably see a 10% drop in oil during correction</Title><Msg>and then kick back up in middle of earnings season</Msg><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1348699970889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 18:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348701159229-35</Id><Topic><Title>The 10% President : How 90% of the deficit becomes somebody else's fault.</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348658819571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sadly, the majority of the president's voters are (star struck) kids who will inherit his waste, lies, and, inefficiency. The other two components are illegal and union. Not to mention people who have made a profession of living with their hand out and, have become very practiced at doing so, including voting more than once. None of them know what they want and none of them understand how America got to be America. Most of them don't have a clue about the responsibilities of FREEDOM. I don't know where your collective heads are but, the reality does not bode well for our lawful and long suffering tax paying citizens. A vote for this administration is a vote for certain tyranny and, those mentioned above will be the first to pay the price of their ignorance. (For you obama voters, that means you have no idea what your are getting yourself into) Clear your head and consider those who will come behind you.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1348701159229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:12:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348701762473-36</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are Amazing!</Title><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1348695089544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The outstanding recovery led by Obama was of great monetary expense to the Gov., but not as much as the Republicans cried (lied). To reduce Gov. spending now, when big businesses are still sitting on their huge cash reserves would be irresponsible. The Republicans know it and are lying about the debt.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348701762473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348702742258-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obammy---GETCHYO HANDS OUT MY POCKETS GAY BOY!!!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348699074263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 18:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U SOUND LIKE AN ANGRY #$%$</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348702742258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:39:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348702975533-38</Id><Title>MAXWIZARD</Title><Msg>KEEP IN MIND ALL UR THREATS have already been reported to the JSO---they got your URL's #$%$</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348702975533</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348703234948-39</Id><Title>MAXWIZARD---u r not so smart anymore eh?</Title><Msg>......</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348703234948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348703481931-40</Id><Title>MAXWIZRD: advice---THINK BEFORE YOU POSE THREATS!!!</Title><Msg>have fun digging ur way out</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348703481931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348703999108-41</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are Amazing!</Title><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1348695089544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The recovery is underway. The debt was its tool. The republicans are lying and their lies are forwarded onto this board.</Msg><Username>mainst9</Username><Timestamp>1348703999108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348704351753-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obammy---GETCHYO HANDS OUT MY POCKETS GAY BOY!!!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348699074263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 18:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like i said</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348704351753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348705667812-43</Id><Topic><Title>MAXWIZARD</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348702975533</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 19:42:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if u r a lawyer u should know better shouldn't u?</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348705667812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348705822662-44</Id><Topic><Title>gcoffman is a cowardly racist</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348705721663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:28:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now u resort to name calling?</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348705822662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348706263741-45</Id><Title>I'm Glad We Give The Arab Countries Billions Of Dollars in Foreign Aid......</Title><Msg>Just think how much they would hate us if we didn't give them a thin dime:) PS. If it was up to this mean, cold eyed Yankee, I'd give them a kick in the behind instead of billions of American taxpayer dollars...... Boston, PMM</Msg><Username>boston_lawyaa</Username><Timestamp>1348706263741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:37:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348706366496-46</Id><Title>NOBODY BELIEVES THESE "POLLS"</Title><Msg>NOBODY</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348706366496</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348706616791-47</Id><Topic><Title>NOBODY BELIEVES THESE "POLLS"</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348706366496</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:39:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lie. I'm assuming you mean the ones that show Obama's lead, not the ones Fox shows. In which case the polls reflect everybody's belief that the hidden camera showed Romney's truth.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348706616791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:43:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348706743630-48</Id><Title>Carter lead Reagan by 17 points in the September</Title><Msg>preceding his ouster</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348706743630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348706744095-49</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are Amazing!</Title><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1348695089544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beating the Republican drum is like flogging a dead horse.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348706744095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:45:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348706756093-50</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's latest announcement..........</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348706067659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:34:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not even going to comment on this latest prattle. More importantly, kindly clue me in what vuk kind of lawyer are you? You did go law school right? Did you graduate? Did you pass the FL Bar? Do you work or do you just post this nonsense all day long. If you got all this time, how 'bout golf. That is certainly what I'd be doing down there.... Boston, PMM</Msg><Username>boston_lawyaa</Username><Timestamp>1348706756093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348706854437-51</Id><Topic><Title>Carter lead Reagan by 17 points in the September</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348706743630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like i said</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348706854437</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348707266031-52</Id><Topic><Title>Carter lead Reagan by 17 points in the September</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348706743630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like i said</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348707266031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348707362741-53</Id><Topic><Title>gcoffman is a cowardly racist</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348705721663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:28:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if u say so gay boy</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348707362741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348707456834-54</Id><Topic><Title>Step up, gcoffman</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348707372109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:56:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u must be gay</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348707456834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348707489679-55</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's latest announcement..........</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348706067659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:34:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>?????????? "Any other questions, jerk ????????" ?????????? Do you expect that I'm going to reply with some kind of juvenile name calling? I'd love to play Sawgrass especially that 17th hold. Have fun in your retirement. PMM</Msg><Username>boston_lawyaa</Username><Timestamp>1348707489679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348707588323-56</Id><Title>Maxwizard---u know all about teabagging don't you?</Title><Msg>......</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348707588323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348707687854-57</Id><Title>any "man" that supports the Muslim in Chief is either a terrorist, union thug or queer</Title><Msg>.......</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348707687854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348708411895-58</Id><Title>Greek Riots "Rage Against Austerity"</Title><Msg>This is where we're heading and Obama doesn't even pretend to have serious plan to prevent it.He's gonna drive the poor into the street and the middle class into the poor house.. 'We call on everyone to take part in the strike and resist the austerity measures that hurt Greek people and the economy," Despoina Spanou, of the ADEDY labor group, said. "This strike is only the beginning in our fight." 'It is virtually impossible to find a job': Brain drain is another Greek tragedy Much of the union's anger is directed at spending cuts worth nearly $15.55 billion over the next two years that Greece has promised the European Union and International Monetary Fund in an effort to unlock its next tranche of aid. The bulk of those cuts are expected from slashing wages, pensions and welfare benefits, heaping a new wave of misery on Greeks who say repeated rounds of austerity have pushed them to the brink and failed to transform the country for the better."</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348708411895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348708467170-59</Id><Topic><Title>Step up, gcoffman</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348707372109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:56:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry pal---i don't seek out people via the internet, that's what weirdos do</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1348708467170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348709257568-60</Id><Title>Spain's crisis turns middle-class into illegal squatters</Title><Msg>Re-elect Obama and we'll have this to look forward to - "During the protests in Spain Tuesday, people chanted outside the parliament, "Let us in, we want to evict you.” Evictions have soared in Spain as thousands of people have defaulted on bank loans. Protesters said they were fed up with cuts to public salaries and health and education. They are also angry that the state has poured funds into crumbled banks while it is cutting social benefits. "My annual salary has dropped by 8000 euros and if it falls much further I won't be able to make ends meet," Luis Rodriguez, 36, a firefighter who joined the protest, told Reuters. He said he is considering leaving Spain to find a better quality of life. "We're protesting against the cuts. I've had to give up my apartment," said Ondina, a 30-year-old fine arts graduate who is without a job. She said she can't survive on an unemployment benefit of $340 a month. Protesters said they were fed up with cuts to public salaries and health and education. They are also angry that the state has poured funds into crumbled banks while it is cutting social benefits. "My annual salary has dropped by 8000 euros and if it falls much further I won't be able to make ends meet," Luis Rodriguez, 36, a firefighter who joined the protest, told Reuters. He said he is considering leaving Spain to find a better quality of life. "We're protesting against the cuts. I've had to give up my apartment," said Ondina, a 30-year-old fine arts graduate who is without a job. She said she can't survive on an unemployment benefit of $340 a month. Spain, also badly hit by the euro zone debt crisis, has been hit by a second recession since 2009 that has put one in four workers out of a job.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348709257568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348712446402-61</Id><Topic><Title>gcoffman is a cowardly racist</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348705721663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:28:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The racist here always responds with what you just said.</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1348712446402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:20:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348712904840-62</Id><Title>Elitist Douchebag</Title><Msg>Usually we see these elitist douchebags' true sentiments AFTER the election! Its all over. Good riddance.</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1348712904840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>