<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346733625000-1</Id><Title>P(rinter)OTUS will drive WTI over $100 this week</Title><Msg>The Bernank is XOM's BFF!</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1346733625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 00:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346736276000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Infernal takes the Silver........</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1346199732000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh - the big bully who likes to threaten but won't back up his words. Bullies are cowards at heart which you , and a lot of libs, personify.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346736276000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 01:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346736452000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Romney-Ryan Labor Day</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346638888000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can continue to be jealous and aspire to be a moron wahleee boy, but you will never achieve that 'height'.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346736452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 01:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346736565000-4</Id><Topic><Title>How many of these czars will speak at the DNC?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1346676880000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:54:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for again demonstrating the effects of brain death wahleee boy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346736565000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 01:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346736735000-5</Id><Topic><Title>How many of these czars will speak at the DNC?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1346676880000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:54:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wahleee boy really bothered this weekend - using more than the usual number of aliases. But the same number of lies (all his posts). I love the desperation.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346736735000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 01:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346736985000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Kohn on Ryans Speech of Lies</Title><Username>bankhouseone</Username><Timestamp>1346727809000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:03:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since Obama does it every day, he must think it works in many more circumstances. Otherwise, why would the 'big lie' be such a critical part of the Dem party's strategy and platform?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346736985000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 01:36:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346750489135-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Needs Slick Willy</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1346680581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>95%+ of the Press is Democrat owned so they allow the Democrats to spew lie after lie without much challenge - accept recently it appears that some Democrat Press operatives are attempting to challenge some of the more outrages lies - like Wold Blitzer recently challenging Debbie Blabbermouth Shultz on one of her more outrageous lies.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1346750489135</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 05:21:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346750880761-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why Will The Seals Who</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1346686774000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 11:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has a disdain for our military whereas Romney does not, and the fighting personnel (not the seat warmers) know who has and does not have their back. The Democrats continually try to limit or void the overseas votes from our overseas military personnel.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1346750880761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 05:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346759462128-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Needs Slick Willy</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1346680581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>W had disdain for our military whereas Obama does not.</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1346759462128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 07:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346759695925-10</Id><Topic><Title>Dems to *livestream* Charlotte convention</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346606626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:23:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dems back global climate deal in platform By Ben Geman - 09/03/12 10:20 PM ET CHARLOTTE, N.C. – The Democrats’ official platform expected to be approved at the party's national convention on Tuesday calls for an international deal to limit greenhouse gas emissions. The platform says Democrats will pursue efforts to combat climate change through regulations and market solutions, setting up a continued battle with Republicans who argue such steps could hold back the economy. “Democrats pledge to continue showing international leadership on climate change, working toward an agreement to set emission limits in unison with other emerging powers,” states the platform. “Democrats will continue pursuing efforts to combat climate change at home as well, because reducing our emissions domestically – through regulation and market solutions – is necessary to continue being an international leader on this issue,” the platform continues. Still, the new version's language on an international agreement is..</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346759695925</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 07:54:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346759711397-11</Id><Topic><Title>EXXON UNION PRESIDENT SAYS HE THINK OVER 50% OF UNION MEMBER WILL VOTE FOR MITT ROMNEY</Title><Username>americafirst841</Username><Timestamp>1346708483000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 17:41:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MORE LIKE 60%</Msg><Username>usausa514</Username><Timestamp>1346759711397</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 07:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346759829225-12</Id><Title>Dems back global climate deal in platform</Title><Msg>Dems back global climate deal in platform By Ben Geman - 09/03/12 10:20 PM ET CHARLOTTE, N.C. – The Democrats’ official platform expected to be approved at the party's national convention on Tuesday calls for an international deal to limit greenhouse gas emissions. The platform says Democrats will pursue efforts to combat climate change through regulations and ..</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346759829225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 07:57:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346760745473-13</Id><Title>OBAMA RELEASE YOUR GRADES AND THESIS ! WHY ARE THEY SEALED!</Title><Msg>What don't you want us to know! That you came as a foreign student ............obama a fake a crook and a dumb #$%$ idiot president</Msg><Username>usausa514</Username><Timestamp>1346760745473</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 08:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346762612620-14</Id><Topic><Title>This alliance is gathering of Exxon Mobil Corpo (XOM) correct time to convene</Title><Username>padillagreer779</Username><Timestamp>1346683721000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:48:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a lot of potential sources of positive news releases in the coming.</Msg><Username>rigobertomorris300</Username><Timestamp>1346762612620</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 08:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346763508028-15</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Kohn on Ryans Speech of Lies</Title><Username>bankhouseone</Username><Timestamp>1346727809000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:03:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Janesville plant ceased operating in April of 2009. Obama took the oath of office before that. Get it?</Msg><Username>iggybiggies</Username><Timestamp>1346763508028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 08:58:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346770754581-16</Id><Title>Abramoff speaks at Convention</Title><Msg>Parties aren't what brought former influence peddler Jack Abramoff to the Republican National Convention. At what he jokingly called his "first post-incarceration convention," Abramoff said he was in Tampa mostly to tell the media what happens at the private receptions he once frequented as a lobbyist at Greenberg Traurig and Preston Gates &amp; Ellis (now K&amp;L Gates) before he pleaded guilty in 2006 to bribery, fraud and tax evasion charges. During the convention, Abramoff said he ran into old friends, who were "wonderfully kind." The former lobbyist said he only heard "a snipe here and there" from his detractors. Abramoff spent 3 1/2 years in prison before his release in 2010.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1346770754581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346771335023-17</Id><Topic><Title>Abramoff speaks at Convention</Title><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1346770754581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:59:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when will tommy delay be punished for his crimes??</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1346771335023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346774551439-18</Id><Topic><Title>XOM May be the Next BIG HOLE in ONE</Title><Username>wareskinner396</Username><Timestamp>1345895054000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 07:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just did with my 102k shares. great advice, thanks .</Msg><Username>mollycalderon30</Username><Timestamp>1346774551439</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:02:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346776753669-19</Id><Topic><Title>Abramoff speaks at Convention</Title><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1346770754581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:59:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Abramoff spent 3 1/2 years in prison before his release in 2010" Funny how the messiah made the tax evading turbo timmy part of his reign of incompetence while the Libocrits were supposedly draining the swamp ...</Msg><Username>squamish7b</Username><Timestamp>1346776753669</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346777919942-20</Id><Topic><Title>Who paid for obama trip to pakistan in 1985?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1346769588580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This message board is my litter box</Msg><Username>zevotor22</Username><Timestamp>1346777919942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:58:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346777920585-21</Id><Topic><Title>Who paid for obama trip to pakistan in 1985?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1346769588580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This message board is my litter box</Msg><Username>zevotor22</Username><Timestamp>1346777920585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346780037049-22</Id><Topic><Title>GOODBYE, friends and foes...Yahoo SUCKS !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1346768172955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:16:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well max if you are taking off--at least take the coalition steves and the 4skinyank with you--drop them on the side of the road and leave a case of pampers in case NOV goes wrong for them 1 other note--in Mescalero Apache the word "infernalq"--rough translation is "empty head with full diaper"</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1346780037049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 13:33:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346780795758-23</Id><Title>Enbridge defends Northern Gateway in final phase of public hearings</Title><Msg>Enbridge defends Northern Gateway in final phase of public hearings By Sheila Pratt, Edmonton Journal September 4, 2012 9:24 AM After a bumpy ride this summer, Enbridge will face a tough grilling this week on its $6 billion Northern Gateway project as public hearings enter their final phase in which interveners can challenge the company’s evidence. Enbridge will square off with unions and First Nations while big oilsands players, including MEG Energy, Cenovus, Suncor, Nexen and Total appear in a joint witness panel. The Alberta government is also prepared to appear for the “questioning” phase of the federal Joint Review Panel hearings to examine the economic benefits of the proposed $6-billion pipeline project to carry Alberta bitumen to Kitimat on the coast of British Columbia for export to China. Critics like the Alberta Federation of Labour will argue Canada’s refining industry will shrink — with a loss of 8,000 jobs expected — if the pipeline project goes ahead and diverts bitumen feedstock to China. Opponents will also argue there is plenty of room in existing pipelines to handle growing bitumen exports. Enbridge, however, is “ very confident” going into the hearings as it will finally have a chance to respond to critics, says spokesperson Ivan Giesbrecht, noting the company will speak Tuesday. “This is our first chance to speak; it’s going to be a rigorous questioning and we welcome that,” Giesbrecht said. “We really feel the project will benefit both provinces and... Complete article and URL posted on the XOM messgae board at ' stockhouse '.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346780795758</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 13:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346781477642-24</Id><Title>Gasoline Futures Rise on Speculation Isaac Tightened Inventories</Title><Msg>Gasoline Futures Rise on Speculation Isaac Tightened Inventories By Dan Murtaugh - Sep 4, 2012 7:48 AM MT Gasoline rose for a second straight day on speculation that Hurricane Isaac shrunk inventories and the Federal Reserve may add economic stimulus in the world’s largest oil-consuming country. Futures gained as after Isaac shut down 13 percent of Gulf Coast refining capacity last week, with several refineries still idled or at reduced rates. Federal Reserve Chairman Ben S. Bernanke said Aug. 31 he wouldn’t rule out further bond purchases to boost growth. “Despite the fact that Hurricane Isaac didn’t do any long- lasting damage, it sure did some short-term damage to supplies, and we’ll probably see some drawdowns because of that,” said Phil Flynn, senior market analyst at Price Futures Group in Chicago. “Add to that the talk of stimulus, and things seem to be getting off to a pretty good start today.” October-delivery gasoline rose 2.53 cents, or..</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346781477642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 13:57:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346782046269-25</Id><Title>Redeployments, Production Restarts Continue in Gulf Following Isaac</Title><Msg>Redeployments, Production Restarts Continue in Gulf Following Isaac by Karen Boman Rigzone Staff Tuesday, September 04, 2012 Offshore operators continued to redeploy workers and restart oil and gas production after evacuating personnel and halting Gulf of Mexico operations due to Hurricane Isaac. Lafayette, La.-based Stone Energy reported Tuesday that its major Gulf of Mexico facilities have been safely remanned, with damage from Hurricane Isaac to its facilities appearing to be minor. The company began shutting in production and evacuating workers on Aug. 26; by Aug. 28, virtually all of its Gulf production had been shut in, Stone said in a statement Tuesday. Stone's Gulf facilities were..</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346782046269</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 14:07:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346782823162-26</Id><Topic><Title>Every info about XOM traders are strengthening out huge profits up to 10-22%</Title><Username>brandybrandy73</Username><Timestamp>1346156568000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:22:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.when i came to know about the feture returns of the share's policy,i bacame more interested to invest my money on this.thanks for letting me know.have a good time ahead.</Msg><Username>lynda.guy74</Username><Timestamp>1346782823162</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 14:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346782823506-27</Id><Topic><Title>Every info about XOM traders are strengthening out huge profits up to 10-22%</Title><Username>brandybrandy73</Username><Timestamp>1346156568000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:22:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.when i came to know about the feture returns of the share's policy,i bacame more interested to invest my money on this.thanks for letting me know.have a good time ahead.</Msg><Username>lynda.guy74</Username><Timestamp>1346782823506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 14:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346785113148-28</Id><Topic><Title>Gasoline Futures Rise on Speculation Isaac Tightened Inventories</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346781477642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 13:57:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would seem to me that a hurricane is never good for oil and gas supply, and if refiners had to shut down, it would not be good for refined product inventory levels. all this is short term, and may be mitigated by macro economic concerns. Having said all that longer term we all know that oil and refined product costs are going higher, and one should add to this there is a limit to the downside on demand destruction. The final and not insignificant upside to all this is world demand is going to grow even if US demand continues to decline.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1346785113148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 14:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346785493190-29</Id><Topic><Title>Gasoline Futures Rise on Speculation Isaac Tightened Inventories</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1346781477642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 13:57:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While there is no real substitute for oil, natural gas looks to be the undervalued fuel, that could take some of the short range driving maket. The real problem still is the world economy, and i fear that the worst is not going to be revealed until after the election. next 12 to 24 mos could be tough. After Europe gets stable and world economies including US economy gets "reset" oil and oil stocks will resume their climb. Of course geopolitical issues could catapult oil prices at any time, so one should always stay invested to some extent.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1346785493190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 15:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346786290447-30</Id><Topic><Title>Abramoff speaks at Convention</Title><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1346770754581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:59:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe a confession is coming......</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1346786290447</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 15:18:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346789542235-31</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Kohn on Ryans Speech of Lies</Title><Username>bankhouseone</Username><Timestamp>1346727809000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:03:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Since Obama does it every day" Name those lies which Obama had said u MENTAL MIDGET !!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1346789542235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346790048275-32</Id><Title>Interesting signs that tell on the price of oil, and supply/demand</Title><Msg>First look at the nxy deal that China oil comapny wants to do. Why now especially when short term price of oil and nxy stock could weaken? One must conclude its about the future price of oil. Will Canada approve the takeover/acquistion? One could expect that as oil supply demand gets tighter again in the future Canada and other oil nations will be more lilkely to block takeover attempts by foreign firms, as they wont want to give up any control of stategic assets, so now is an opportune time for China. If China canto do the deal now they certainly wont be allowed to do the deal when suppy is tight and oil is $130. This also means oil is currently undervalued and Canadian oil perhaps more undervalued that most. bottom line is price of oil going higher for the patient long term people.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1346790048275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346790705325-33</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting signs that tell on the price of oil, and supply/demand</Title><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1346790048275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Second look at the recent news that the Kuwait national oil company wants to do a joint venture in a Canadian oil sands venture.(ath). Now one must conclude Kuwait knows something about oil, and they must see value in Canaidan oil. Other questions that follow include does Kuwait know something about the coming decline in production from elephant oil fields in the middle east. Perhaps its that Kuwait knows of the conflict risk to oil production in the midldle east, perhaps as a result of their experience with Iraq, and wants to diversify some oil investments outside of the unstable middle east. Its not hard to forsee a scenario where Iran gets into a hot war with some one and oil prices spike or the region becomes even more unstable. The Kuwait joint venture in Canada is a sign that shows Canadian oil is undervlued and oil is undervalued. It may also be that Kuwait has some sense that as oil supply demand gets tight in the future it might be difficult to get deals done in Canada and other nations as strategic asset concerns limit foreign ownership. When we hit a peak oil situation again governments are going to value oil assets as a matter of national security and may not want to allow even some control into foreign hands even at a premium. One can not rule out issues in Iraq or even Saudi Arabia with civil unrest that spills over from other nations in the middle east. bottom line is long term price of oil is going up.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1346790705325</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346802911132-34</Id><Topic><Title>Abramoff speaks at Convention</Title><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1346770754581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:59:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What crimes, meathead? When will Obamao be punished for his?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346802911132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 19:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346803177721-35</Id><Topic><Title>GOODBYE, friends and foes...Yahoo SUCKS !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1346768172955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:16:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your days are numbered you commie POS. War crimes starting and your a traitor to your country.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1346803177721</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 19:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346803913188-36</Id><Topic><Title>GOODBYE, friends and foes...Yahoo SUCKS !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1346768172955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:16:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're in such a hurry to leave you bumped your post? I figured you would find an excuse to run and hide. Good choice.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346803913188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346804168529-37</Id><Title>WAHLEEE IS DED!!!!!</Title><Msg>bye bye wahleeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee</Msg><Username>wahleee_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1346804168529</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346804342516-38</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Kohn on Ryans Speech of Lies</Title><Username>bankhouseone</Username><Timestamp>1346727809000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:03:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's start with: - I will cut the deficit in half in my first term - I will hold unemployment below 8% - I will stop the seas from rising - I have created over 4 million jobs (when in fact there are half a million fewer people employed today than the day he was inaugurated) - etc, etc. : Yahoo doesn't have enough storage to list all of Obamao's lies. No one does. So we now know who the mental midget is - just look in the mirror the next time you get confused.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346804342516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:19:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346809025414-39</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Kohn on Ryans Speech of Lies</Title><Username>bankhouseone</Username><Timestamp>1346727809000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:03:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please elaborate on how NOT raising debt limit would hurt credit rating. That is like saying I did not raise the limit on my credit card or did not get that second card and so my credit rating should drop. US credit rating was lowered because the deficit spending is growing fasterr than GDP so overall debt burden and thus ability to (eventual) pay it off is threatened. If we had kept the debt limit where it was, we have proven the ability to service that debt level. There certainly are other (some good, some bad) reasons we 'needed' to raise the limit, but to 'maintain the credit rating' is NOT one of them.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346809025414</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346809687197-40</Id><Topic><Title>Abramoff speaks at Convention</Title><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1346770754581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:59:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was he "invited" to the RNC by the GOP? no Was he attending as a delegate? No Was he there in any "official" GOP capacity? No No he was there as any private citizen who wanted to travel to Tampa could do. (Although he did need his parole officer's permission which most citizens do not). So what is the big deal? What if it had been the DNC where he chose to go and talk? What if he DOES go to Charlotte? It still would not matter and would not say any more about the Dems than his choice to go to Tampa did about the Reps. It is all a BFD with no real meaning or substance.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346809687197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346809957046-41</Id><Topic><Title>Romney-Ryan Labor Day</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346638888000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical wallboard post. Full of lies and vitriol.</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1346809957046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346814211611-42</Id><Title>!!!!!!!!!!! NOBAMA 2012 !!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>and good ridence to our "Great spender".....16 TRILLION as of today !!</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1346814211611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:03:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346816747382-43</Id><Title>HEY DEMS...I want my 16 TRILLION from YOU....LOSERS that ONLY want a HANDOUT !!!</Title><Msg>go get a job..or a better one LOSERS....</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1346816747382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346816773708-44</Id><Topic><Title>Flip Flopney and Lyin Ryan</Title><Username>walhieeeee</Username><Timestamp>1346816377161</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u know--it woulda been nice(approp) for Rmoney to have at least ONCE mentioned the military during his gop speech really just 1 time give a lil "thanks" or "never forget" or lets get em home just a mention mittens--please I know it is below the dignity of most of that group--but really you wanna be commander in chief c'mon</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1346816773708</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346816892921-45</Id><Topic><Title>HEY DEMS...I want my 16 TRILLION from YOU....LOSERS that ONLY want a HANDOUT !!!</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1346816747382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>check with the w and his gop congress--they made off with 7 of the 16 trillion and WE got nuttin to show for that 7 trillion--nuttin</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1346816892921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:48:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346816969740-46</Id><Topic><Title>!!!!!!!!!!! NOBAMA 2012 !!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1346814211611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:03:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's a "ridence" ??</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1346816969740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:49:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346817407393-47</Id><Topic><Title>HEY DEMS...I want my 16 TRILLION from YOU....LOSERS that ONLY want a HANDOUT !!!</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1346816747382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for again showing the board what brain death looks like. You're a great poster boy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1346817407393</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:56:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>