<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354079447664-1</Id><Topic><Title>The Best- and Worst-Run States in America</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354063744443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 19:49:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tiresome infernal. I believe the entire U.S. economy is headed for a major fall and am well positioned to profit from it as I've made quite clear. California did not get to be such a wealthy state by following your small government philosophy either. At no time since World War II has it been governed by such a philosophy, especially not by Reagan who governed it once, before he decided to call himself a neo-con. Urban economies do not function as you would like and never will. You will wait many lifetimes for a Manhattan to fail too, which is governed even more to your dislike. As for the greens - their agenda assures a depression to outrank them all. That I will enjoy, but I doubt you will...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354079447664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 00:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354105703241-2</Id><Title>California is the Precursor State of the US</Title><Msg>California is absolutely broke and yet the Demoncraps running the state continually increase taxes on the taxpaying citizens to increase spending initiatives on illegal immigrants, sexual deviants, killing unborn babies, union government "workers", and/or other near and dear Demoncrap policy initiatives. If it were not for the federal tax money help from the US, California would currently be in anarchy. Many rich taxpayers and taxpaying companies are leaving California for other States and international venues that tax less. At some point in the future, the US, in order to temporarily enable its continued existence, will have to stop bailing out the Demoncrap broke States like California. I think the US should sell California to Mexico in exchange for oil from Mexico since the illegal immigrants have almost taken over the state anyway.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354105703241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 07:28:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354106362384-3</Id><Topic><Title>Propose an "upstream" cap-and-trade system targeting oil refiners</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354072315603</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:11:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may be correct about the "Greens", but what specifically is bluecheese4u spreading that is rubbish? You, greedful_thing_s, need to get off your high horse and quit talking down to others. You may not intend, or even have to allow your standard of living to be reduced, but too many people already locked into a downward spiral of poverty will suffer with no way to profit. Lucky you, but you are winning the hearts of those you will be trampling upon.</Msg><Username>dogshitforbrains</Username><Timestamp>1354106362384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 07:39:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354111520557-4</Id><Topic><Title>API files suit against US EPA for 2013 biodiesel usage increase</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354074423435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 22:47:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...The latest attempt by the oil and gas industry to roll back the Renewable Fuel Standard came as no surprise to the biofuels industry. Monte Shaw, executive director of the Iowa Renewable Fuels Association, said the API has a “thin” track record in chipping away at the law, having lost each time it has challenged it in court, the White House and Congress. “You go back and look at every step, from when Congress was debating the law, to when the EPA was implementing the law, to every new annual implementation, they have challenged all of these. They have never supported it. They’ve always said the sky is falling,” Shaw said. “It’s not that the law isn’t working that bothers API, it’s the fact that the law is working that bothers API.”... financeDOTyahooDOTcom/mbview/threadview/?&amp;bn=bb63947c-75d4-3061-8743-a2ae53cc1787&amp;tid=1354111374019-3c13f458-5435-4507-ab0d-cbe14f2e018d&amp;tls=la%2Cd%2C0</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354111520557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 09:05:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354112410487-5</Id><Topic><Title>Read this now -Exxon Mobil Corporation. (XOM)</Title><Username>thomashazard94</Username><Timestamp>1354107540078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 07:59:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This just in j mc cain signs with norquist No mo O.</Msg><Username>orri1934</Username><Timestamp>1354112410487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 09:20:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354114603634-6</Id><Title>year end payout</Title><Msg>it would be nice if exxon payed a large yearend dividend</Msg><Username>donzi428</Username><Timestamp>1354114603634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 09:56:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354114616202-7</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT</Title><Username>soltradesrs</Username><Timestamp>1354110953175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 08:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very useful! good job</Msg><Username>vancelayne</Username><Timestamp>1354114616202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 09:56:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354118845856-8</Id><Topic><Title>PraPra Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354015228461</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 06:20:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone is Wahleee here, or wishes they were, Happy Birthday Wahlieee you great American!</Msg><Username>carl_cessman</Username><Timestamp>1354118845856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 11:07:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354119968085-9</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT</Title><Username>soltradesrs</Username><Timestamp>1354110953175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 08:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good alert</Msg><Username>johnsonsjohny</Username><Timestamp>1354119968085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 11:26:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354120308077-10</Id><Topic><Title>PraPra Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354015228461</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 06:20:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks wahleee boy for your continuing demonstration.l</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354120308077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 11:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354120843792-11</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT</Title><Username>soltradesrs</Username><Timestamp>1354110953175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 08:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good alert</Msg><Username>johnsonsjohny</Username><Timestamp>1354120843792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 11:40:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354121553123-12</Id><Topic><Title>Read this now -Exxon Mobil Corporation. (XOM)</Title><Username>thomashazard94</Username><Timestamp>1354107540078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 07:59:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Report love them....</Msg><Username>jessieriley78</Username><Timestamp>1354121553123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 11:52:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354123594752-13</Id><Topic><Title>PraPra Another Alias of Wahleee</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354015228461</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 06:20:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Carl! you're a great American!</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1354123594752</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 12:26:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354127787870-14</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT</Title><Username>soltradesrs</Username><Timestamp>1354110953175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 08:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it. Thanks</Msg><Username>laurenanderson409</Username><Timestamp>1354127787870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 13:36:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354129606229-15</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT</Title><Username>soltradesrs</Username><Timestamp>1354110953175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 08:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very useful</Msg><Username>johnnyandrews241</Username><Timestamp>1354129606229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:06:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354129608176-16</Id><Title>2014 F80 BMW M3 test mule refueled with E85 ethanol PHOTOS</Title><Msg>2014 F80 BMW M3 test mule refueled with E85 ethanol PHOTOS By Horatiu Boeriu. Read Bio November 27th, 2012 | BMW M3 | 2 comments Most likely filled under human error, but interesting enough that a photographer spent the time to snapped a shot. In the cold and snowy Sweden BMW is continuing the field testing of the upcoming 2014 F80 BMW M3 and a reader of Teknikensvarld caught the new BMW M3 when it stopped in Gothenburg to refuel the “wrong” fuel! Judging by these still shots, which may or may not capture the entire refueling process, the driver of the F80 M3 sedan grabbed the E85 ethanol pump to fill up the super-sporty sedan. As many of you know, ethanol fuel consists of 85% ethanol and 15% gasoline, a combination not recommended by BMW. The photos also point out that the pump handle for 95 unleaded fuel remains untouched. It remains unknown if the car was indeed refueled with the wrong combination as part of a testing process, or even if the driver actually went through with this idea. When coming to market in 2014 the F80 BMW M3 will be powered by an inline-six engine. The engine of choice is a newly developed 3.2 liter unit that is rated at 450 horsepower. The new M3 is expected to be slightly faster than the current E90 generation thanks to a lower weight. The engine is mated to a double-clutch transmission 7-speed transmission, but we expect to see a manual transmission for U.S. customers. bmwblogDOTcom/2012/11/27/2014-f80-bmw-m3-test-mule-refueled-with-e85-ethanol/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354129608176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:06:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354129702226-17</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT</Title><Username>soltradesrs</Username><Timestamp>1354110953175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 08:55:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very useful</Msg><Username>johnnyandrews241</Username><Timestamp>1354129702226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:08:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354130253242-18</Id><Title>Reinstate the Biodiesel Tax Incentive the biodiesel industry needs stability and a level energy playing field to continue growing</Title><Msg>Reinstate the Biodiesel Tax Incentive Posted by Joanna Schroeder – November 28th, 2012 The lame duck session is in full swing but no movement has yet been made on the tax extenders package that includes incentives for wind energy, advanced biofuels, including biodiesel, and cellulosic ethanol. Today, the Iowa Renewable Fuels Association (IRFA) sent letters to all the members of the Iowa Congressional delegation urging them to level the energy playing field and reinstate the biodiesel tax incentive. Iowa leads the county in biodiesel production. The letters stated: “The biodiesel industry’s recent progress is to be applauded, particularly in such a weak economy, but it should not cloud the fact that biodiesel remains a young and vulnerable industry. As the petroleum industry fights to preserve the tax advantages it has enjoyed continuously for the past century, the biodiesel industry has seen its growth stall since the tax incentive expired on Dec. 31, 2011. As a result, U.S. biodiesel production will likely be down from last year and the growth in Iowa biodiesel production will likely be less than expected. The projected decrease in U.S. biodiesel production in 2012 demonstrates that if the petroleum industry maintains its century-old tax advantages and the biodiesel tax incentive is not reinstated, then the RFS volumes will most likely be the ceiling for U.S. biodiesel production and use, not the floor. Now, as much as ever, the biodiesel industry needs stability and a level energy playing field to continue growing.” The letters were send to Senators Tom Harkin and Charles Grassley, and Representatives Dave Loebsack, Leonard Boswell, Steve King and Tom Latham. domesticfuelDOTcom/2012/11/28/reinstate-the-biodiesel-tax-incentive/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354130253242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:17:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354132207804-19</Id><Title>OVERNIGHT ENERGY: Lawmakers, veterans boost pressure for wind credit</Title><Msg>OVERNIGHT ENERGY: Lawmakers, veterans boost pressure for wind credit By Zack Colman and Ben Geman - 11/27/12 07:03 PM ET STATE OF PLAY: A bipartisan group of lawmakers will join military veterans at a Wednesday event pressing Congress to extend a wind energy incentive. Sens. Chuck Grassley (R-Iowa) and Mark Udall (D-Colo.), along with Reps. Jerry McNerney (D-Calif.) and Steve King (R-Iowa), will tout the wind industry as a job creator. The lawmakers also will present a petition signed by veterans across the country asking Congress to extend the credit. Many of the veterans attending the event are employed in the wind industry. They will meet with lawmakers Wednesday and Thursday to gain support for a one-year extension to the wind credit, which expires Dec. 31. The incentive pays wind power producers 2.2 cents per kilowatt-hour, and is seen as a vital tool for attracting investment. Planned installations for next year have dropped because of the incentive’s uncertain future. For now, the incentive’s fate waits on “fiscal cliff” negotiations between President Obama and Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio). Those automatic spending cuts and income tax increases are set to take effect Jan. 1 While its proponents contend the incentive leverages $15 billion of investment per year and would cost $5 billion, fiscal conservatives say it costs $12.1 billion and that it is too expensive to extend. Grassley said earlier this month that the Senate would wait to move the $205 billion tax extenders package that includes the wind incentive in order to give Obama and Boehner time to work on a deal. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/269679-overnight-energy-lawmakers-veterans-push-for-wind-incentive-extension</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354132207804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:50:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354132720522-20</Id><Title>John Boehner to GOP: Stick together on taxes VIDEO</Title><Msg>John Boehner to GOP: Stick together on taxes VIDEO By JAKE SHERMAN | 11/28/12 10:19 AM EST John Boehner had a message for House Republicans Wednesday morning: stick together or be left out. The Ohio Republican privately urged his House colleagues not to waver from their position to keep tax rates frozen, calling it a “principled position.” “It’s important that everyone in this room continue to be clear with our constituents about what that position is,” Boehner said in a closed meeting of the GOP Conference. The words come as President Barack Obama takes to the road to sell Americans on his plan to raise taxes on the wealthiest Americans. Boehner said his party should be “calling out the Democrats in Congress who are saying no to spending cuts, and saying we should go over the fiscal cliff.” The message that Boehner wants his Republican colleagues to deliver: “We’re fighting for spending cuts. We’re fighting against increases in tax rates that destroy jobs. And we’re fighting for pro-growth tax reform and entitlement reform, the keys to economic growth.” Boehner used a three-page slide show to prove his point, drawing on a recent poll by David Winston. The poll, displayed on blue pages and festooned by stars, displayed three statistics that bolstered the House Republican position on taxes: that tax rates shouldn’t go up on the rich, but the code should be reformed to eliminate loopholes and lower rates all while cutting spending. Boehner also brushed back on Rep. Tom Cole’s (R-Okla.) private comments — reported by POLITICO — that Congress should vote to extend middle class tax cuts before talking about tax rates on the wealthy. “I told Tom earlier in our conference meeting that I disagreed with him,” Boehner said to reporters after the meeting. “He’s a wonderful friend of mine, and great supporter of mine.” politicoDOTcom/news/stories/1112/84321.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354132720522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:58:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354133532047-21</Id><Title>Senate passes amendment keeping biofuel investments in defense bill</Title><Msg>Senate passes amendment keeping biofuel investments in defense bill By Zack Colman and Ramsey Cox - 11/28/12 02:33 PM ET The Senate approved an amendment to the defense bill Wednesday that would restore the military’s ability to invest in biofuels. Sen. Mark Udall’s (D-Colo.) amendment, 2985, strikes Section 313 of the National Defense Authorization Act, S. 3254, which bars the military from purchasing biofuels that cost more than petroleum and from spending money to scale up biofuel refineries. Those supporting the amendment, which passed on a 62-37 vote, said it would save lives and money. “This amendment would save lives and money and allows the Department of Defense to move forward on these new technologies,” Sen. Debbie Stabenow (D-Mich.), a co-sponsor of the amendment, said Wednesday before the vote. Sens. James Inhofe (R-Okla.) and John McCain (R-Ariz.) introduced the measures that blocked the Defense Department’s option to spend on biofuels when the Senate Armed Services Committee was considering the bill. The House defense spending bill contains similar language. The senators argued that biofuels are too expensive, with $500 billion of defense cuts slated for the next 10 years as part of sequestration. Inhofe and McCain oppose using military spending to commercialize energy technology, though several senators argued the Defense Department has a history of investing in less mature energy sectors. Still, Inhofe said biofuels are something the Department of Energy should be spending money on, not the Department of Defense. “This is something [the Department of Energy] should be doing if anybody is going to be doing it,” Inhofe said on the floor Wednesday. “This one amendment, more than any other, would take money away from readiness.” But the amendment's Senate proponents said biofuels could help keep military energy spending down by reducing the military's exposure to oil price shocks. The program has the support of Defense Secretary Leon Panetta and Navy Secretary Ray Mabus, who also contend it would stabilize energy costs. They call the program vital for energy security, saying it gives the military more fuel options and loosens it from foreign oil’s grip. Sen. Barbara Boxer (D-Calif.) asked if the Senate has to once again have a fight about oil. “Is big oil calling the shots here?” Boxer said Wednesday before the vote. “I would hope not, but I don’t understand why this section Sen. Udall is trying to strike is in this bill when the military says it’s critical to them.” Republican senators voting with Democrats to approve the amendment included Sens. Roy Blunt (Mo.), Thad Cochran (Miss.), Susan Collins (Maine), Chuck Grassley (Iowa), John Hoeven (N.D.), Dick Lugar (Ind.), Lisa Murkowski (Alaska), Olympia Snowe (Maine) and John Thune (S.D.). Democratic Sens. Joe Manchin (W.Va.) and Jim Webb (Va.) voted against the amendment. Collins, who serves on the Armed Services Committee, missed the May committee vote on the Inhofe and McCain amendments, each of which passed by one vote. thehillDOTcom/blogs/floor-action/senate/269897-senate-passes-amendment-keeping-biofuel-investments-in-defense-bill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354133532047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 15:12:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354133867715-22</Id><Title>Gulf lease sale today - Suit seeks cap and trade for transportation sector - Coal firm recalls laid off miners - Energy, climate get mentions during Nieto visit</Title><Msg>Gulf lease sale today - Suit seeks cap and trade for transportation sector - Coal firm recalls laid off miners - Energy, climate get mentions during Nieto visit By ALEX GUILLEN | 11/28/12 9:31 AM EDT with help from Andrew Restuccia and Darren Samuelsohn GULF LEASE SALE TODAY: The Bureau of Ocean Energy Management will hold an oil and gas lease sale today made up of more than 20 million acres in the Western Gulf of Mexico Planning Area. Building on two other sales in December and June, today’s is the first under the administration’s five-year plan. The 3,873 blocks up for grabs today range from depths of 16 feet to 10,975 feet (a little over two miles) and could yield 116 to 200 million barrels of oil and 538 to 938 billion cubic feet of natural gas, according to BOEM. The sale takes place at 9 a.m. CDT at the Mercedes-Benz Superdome in New Orleans. Sale as indicator of future: The National Ocean Industries Association expects the sale to be “interesting.” As the first sale under the five year plan, NOIA President Randall Luthi said in a statement, “the level of activity in this sale will be a good indicator of industry’s confidence not only in the remaining resources of the Western Gulf of Mexico, but also in the Administration’s willingness to allow those resources to be developed in a timely fashion.” Greens not happy: Several environmentalists took to Twitter yesterday to bash the sale. “Obama, endorsed by Sierra Club, LCV, NRDC, MoveOn, opens 20 million offshore acres in Gulf of Mexico for drilling,” Brad Johnson of Forecast the Facts wrote. “Black Fri., Cyber Mon., now All of the Above Wed.” blogger R.L. Miller wrote of the sale. politicoDOTcom/morningenergy/1112/morningenergy9555.html?hp=l6_b6</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354133867715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 15:17:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354139787405-23</Id><Title>A Triumph of Form Over Substance</Title><Msg>Obama's tax increase plan is far to small to make any difference to the trajectory of the Federal debt, even if the Republicans accept it. $80 billion/year is chump change, and does not even cover the interest on the debt run up since Bush took office. What little spending cuts he agrees to will be smoke and mirrors and gimmickry - totally irrelevant from a practical point of view. Hopes were high Obama would push for a more forceful tax plan, given his decisive victory over Romney. He is performing poorly, however, refraining again to concerns about what higher taxes would do to the economy - the same brand of hogwash that has been on sale since 1980, and increased the federal debt 1500% since then. What the economy will look like when the bond market refuses to loan more money to the U.S. government should be of greater concern but is not. Obama is going down as W-II, only worse as Obama has no energy plan.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354139787405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 16:56:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354141054469-24</Id><Topic><Title>Falling off the Fiscal Cliff would help the U. S. long term</Title><Username>bimmy.beoris</Username><Timestamp>1354060303029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 18:51:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The analogy of a limb needing amputation is better. That is what it will come to when the government's credit collapses. They may well fail to reach an agreement, but that will not stop them from passing a patch next year to abolish the tax increase and spend even more than they planned to fill in the gap left by the cliff... Obama has no real will to increase taxes, which is becoming obvious, except, that is, by the paltry amount he's mentioned already, or perhaps abolishing the odd loop hole for big oil. That's just not enough to get the job done. As the debt climbs it will squeeze out more and more of the world's savings leaving less and less for corporate investment or bidding stocks. As it is now it is consuming nearly 100% of U.S. private savings just to finance the deficit, to say nothing about financing other areas of the economy...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354141054469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 17:17:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354141756389-25</Id><Topic><Title>Heads Up Gentlemen ! Socialism is Moving Into High Gear !</Title><Username>disillusionedmale</Username><Timestamp>1354036230103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 12:10:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And if our Gov't would buy into Corporate ownership, that could work here too. Bad plan, Gov't should stay out of business and let the free enterprise system prevail.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1354141756389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 17:29:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354142218228-26</Id><Topic><Title>Heads Up Gentlemen ! Socialism is Moving Into High Gear !</Title><Username>disillusionedmale</Username><Timestamp>1354036230103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 12:10:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The left wing has been salivating over the thought of nationalizing the oil industry for years. Maybe the fear of Obama moving us into Socialism is the reason Black Friday had it's largest Gun Sales Day in history. Hugo Chavez made a terrible mess in Venezuela when he nationalized the oil business. Keep in mind that Obama and Pelosi have a big stick out for Exxon/Mobil and have stated their profits are too large and they intend to do something about it. Our Gov't should not try to poke their nose into corporations.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1354142218228</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 17:36:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354142668793-27</Id><Title>The Great Purification</Title><Msg>"liquidate labor, liquidate stocks, liquidate farmers, liquidate real estate… it will purge the rottenness out of the system. High costs of living and high living will come down. People will work harder, live a more moral life. Values will be adjusted, and enterprising people will pick up from less competent people." - Andrew Mellon after 1929 crash Basically that was done and the economy was able to put in a floor thanks to it. It has not been done today thanks to the U.S. government propping up price levels with all variety of entitlements, tax cuts, and freebies for the masses. Consequently, the trade deficit continues at a massive rate as industry flees the country to escape the high prices, the national debt spirals out of control, and the economy just slowly rots as it awaits the liquidation that will come. The only real difference in the outcome will be the government debt run up in the interim and the much higher tax bill that will be required to service it. There is also a new twist now: the government is actively engaging in a campaign to increase the cost of doing business in America with all manner of environmental regulations...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354142668793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 17:44:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354143760835-28</Id><Topic><Title>John Boehner to GOP: Stick together on taxes VIDEO</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354132720522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:58:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The attitude is absolutely amazing. This generation of Republican is totally worthless - reckless in the extreme, fiscally irresponsible in the extreme, and so deluded by charlatan economic advisers and self-interested lobbyists, they cannot even tell what is conservative and what is liberal. One word: clueless</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354143760835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 18:02:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354144969014-29</Id><Topic><Title>Heads Up Gentlemen ! Socialism is Moving Into High Gear !</Title><Username>disillusionedmale</Username><Timestamp>1354036230103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 12:10:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So is Fascism! Republicans can take pride in passing the Patriot Act, NDAA, Drones Over America, and getting rid of Habeous Corpus.</Msg><Username>shawn4golf</Username><Timestamp>1354144969014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 18:22:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354145321756-30</Id><Topic><Title>Heads Up Gentlemen ! Socialism is Moving Into High Gear !</Title><Username>disillusionedmale</Username><Timestamp>1354036230103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 12:10:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fascism is a form of socialism. The modern Republican is a fascist socialist. The modern Democrat is a socialist fascist. If you look at their method of paying for their programs, borrow &amp; spend, the approach is the same as the German and Italian fascists in their day. W or Obama, same thing...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354145321756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 18:28:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354146107439-31</Id><Title>Obergruppenführers &amp; Tsars</Title><Msg>one refers to the deputies of a despot and the other refers to a despot. The German word is much more fitting when you look at the duties of the officials involved. German is, of course, a much more precise language than English. lol</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354146107439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 18:41:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354146976883-32</Id><Title>Détente with China.</Title><Msg>Yes, indeed, that was the outcome of Obama's trip to Asia. Obama must have bowed low to his masters in Beijing and asked them to please, please keep buying T-bills and bonds. Of course all talk of Romney's ill advised comments about Chinese currency manipulation were dismissed and repudiated as revealed today to everyone. China can continue to destroy America's industrial base just as long is likes, provided it keeps loaning the U.S. government the money it earns in the process, money the U.S. government can continue to use to to prop up American price levels for as long and as well as it can, making the Chinese effort a success. It will end badly, as indeed it already has. It can get worse though, especially for the middle class on unemployment who will probably never see a real job again, or probably even unemployment when the extended program runs out in Jan</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354146976883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 18:56:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354156004669-33</Id><Topic><Title>John Boehner to GOP: Stick together on taxes VIDEO</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354132720522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 14:58:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your right, worthless when they spend more than they take in and still want to charge more on the China credit card. Watch what is going on in the stock market when our money is worth less. Irresponsible are those who will not cut what we spend or give away untill we find something to sell that is only made in the USA.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1354156004669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 21:26:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354162990357-34</Id><Topic><Title>Détente with China.</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354146976883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 18:56:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rick Perry noted in the debates that Romney's Bain was a "vulture capital" outfit that profited from exporting jobs to the Chicoms. Wall Streets desire to capitalze on 14 year olds working 80 hours a week in China will keep the GOP and Dems raping middle America of middle class manufacturing jobs. Fractional Reserve Banksters love socialism</Msg><Username>potterkimberly44</Username><Timestamp>1354162990357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 23:23:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354163841556-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obergruppenführers &amp; Tsars</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354146107439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 18:41:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deutschlander? Was Sagen Sie? Umlaut?</Msg><Username>iggybiggies</Username><Timestamp>1354163841556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 23:37:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>