<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344142168000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Strategy for China. What strategy?</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1344121448000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With a 17% increase in military spending each year how long until China reaches parity with the USA. The Chinese footprint in South America and Africa seems to be increasing significantly.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1344142168000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 00:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344148050000-2</Id><Title>New study links current events to climate change</Title><Msg>New study links current events to climate change By ASSOCIATED PRESS | 8/4/12 8:42 PM EDT WASHINGTON — The relentless, weather-gone-crazy type of heat that has blistered the United States and other parts of the world in recent years is so rare that it can't be anything but man-made global warming, says a new statistical analysis from a top government scientist. The research by a man often called the "godfather of global warming" says that the likelihood of such temperatures occurring from the 1950s through the 1980s was rarer than 1 in 300. Now, the odds are closer to 1 in 10, according to the study by NASA scientist James Hansen. He says that statistically what's happening is not random or normal, but pure and simple climate change. "This is not some scientific theory. We are now experiencing scientific fact," Hansen told The Associated Press in an interview. Hansen is a scientist at NASA's Goddard Institute for Space Studies in New York and a professor at Columbia University. But he is also a strident activist who has called for government action to curb greenhouse gases for years. While his study was published online Saturday in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Science, it is unlikely to sway opinion among the remaining climate change skeptics. White House science adviser John Holdren praised the paper's findings in a statement. But he also said it is true that scientists can't blame single events on global warming: "This work, which finds that extremely hot summers are over 10 times more common than they used to be, reinforces many other lines of evidence showing that climate change is occurring and that it is harmful." In a blunt departure from most climate research, Hansen's study — based on statistics, not the more typical climate modeling — blames these three heat waves purely on global warming: —Last year's devastating Texas-Oklahoma drought. —The 2010 heat waves in Russia and the Middle East, which led to thousands of deaths. —The 2003 European heat wave blamed for tens of thousands of deaths, especially among the elderly in France. The analysis was written before the current drought and record-breaking temperatures that have seared much of the United States this year. But Hansen believes this too is another prime example of global warming at its worst. The new research makes the case for the severity of global warming in a different way than most scientific studies and uses simple math instead of relying on complex climate models or an understanding of atmospheric physics. It also doesn't bother with the usual caveats about individual weather events having numerous causes. The increase in the chance of extreme heat, drought and heavy downpours in certain regions is so huge that scientists should stop hemming and hawing, Hansen said. "This is happening often enough, over a big enough area that people can see it happening," he said. Scientists have generally responded that it's impossible to say whether single events are caused by global warming, because of the influence of natural weather variability. However, that position has been shifting in recent months, as other studies too have concluded climate change is happening right before our eyes. Hansen hopes his new study will shift people's thinking about climate change and goad governments into action. He wrote an op-ed piece that appeared online Friday in the Washington Post. "There is still time to act and avoid a worsening climate, but we are wasting precious time," he wrote. http://www.politico.com/news/stories/0812/79378.html?hp=r10</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344148050000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 02:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344148061000-3</Id><Topic><Title>New study links current events to climate change</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344148050000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 02:27:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The science in Hansen's study is excellent "and reframes the question," said Andrew Weaver, a climate scientist at the University of Victoria in British Columbia who was a member of the Nobel Prize-winning international panel of climate scientists that issued a series of reports on global warming. "Rather than say, 'Is this because of climate change?' That's the wrong question. What you can say is, 'How likely is this to have occurred with the absence of global warming?' It's so extraordinarily unlikely that it has to be due to global warming," Weaver said. For years scientists have run complex computer models using combinations of various factors to see how likely a weather event would happen without global warming and with it. About 25 different aspects of climate change have been formally attributed to man-made greenhouse gases in dozens of formal studies. But these are generally broad and non-specific, such as more heat waves in some regions and heavy rainfall in others. Another upcoming study by Kevin Trenberth, climate analysis chief at the National Center for Atmospheric Research, links the 2010 Russian heat wave to global warming by looking at the underlying weather that caused the heat wave. He called Hansen's paper an important one that helps communicate the problem. But there is bound to be continued disagreement. Previous studies had been unable to link the two, and one by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration concluded that the Russian drought, which also led to devastating wildfires, was not related to global warming. Skeptical scientist John Christy of the University of Alabama at Huntsville said Hansen shouldn't have compared recent years to the 1950s-1980s time period because he said that was a quiet time for extremes. But Derek Arndt, director of climate monitoring for the federal government's National Climatic Data Center, said that range is a fair one and often used because it is the "golden era" for good statistics. Granger Morgan, head of engineering and public policy at Carnegie Mellon University, called Hansen's study "an important next step in what I expect will be a growing set of statistically-based arguments." In a landmark 1988 study, Hansen predicted that if greenhouse gas emissions continue, which they have, Washington, D.C., would have about nine days each year of 95 degrees or warmer in the decade of the 2010s. So far this year, with about four more weeks of summer, the city has had 23 days with 95 degrees or hotter temperatures. Hansen says now he underestimated how bad things would get. And while he hopes this will spur action including a tax on the burning of fossil fuels, which emit carbon dioxide, a key greenhouse gas, others doubt it. Science policy expert Roger Pielke Jr. of the University of Colorado said Hansen clearly doesn't understand social science, thinking a study like his could spur action. Just because something ought to happen, doesn't mean it will, he said. In an email, he wrote: "Hansen is pursuing a deeply flawed model of policy change, one that will prove ineffectual and with its most lasting consequence a further politicization of climate science (if that is possible!)."</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344148061000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 02:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344149827000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Strategy for China. What strategy?</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1344121448000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem with China is the billion people it has to feed. If prices go up exponentially, you won't have to worry about a military. People will be fighting for their food in the streets.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1344149827000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 02:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344165995000-5</Id><Title>How Republicans Think and Behave!</Title><Msg>http://kstp.com/news/stories/s2715484.shtml</Msg><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1344165995000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 07:26:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344175717000-6</Id><Topic><Title>How Republicans Think and Behave!</Title><Username>smithharry943</Username><Timestamp>1344165995000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 07:26:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumbocraps can do it why can't repubs.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1344175717000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344175833000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Strategy for China. What strategy?</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1344121448000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. The food bill should be added to the energy bill...China's economy faces utter collapse as food &amp; energy prices rise. They have substantially degraded their water resources, too, expanding their industry to pick up the slack created by Kyoto gutting Europe's industries. The cost of dealing with that problem, and the massive air pollution problem created by the power plants, should be added to the energy cost, as both are linked.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1344175833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344176832000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Strategy for China. What strategy?</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1344121448000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"With a 17% increase in military spending each year how long until China reaches parity with the USA. The Chinese footprint in South America and Africa seems to be increasing significantly." China will collapse under its own weight. The Chinese are trying to grow their economy by increasing energy use. The policy is deliberate and easily read from their 5-year plans which focus on electricity generation, and road construction to boost oil consumption. The policy can only work if the supply of energy can be increased without an increase in price. They are so big, though, they are increasing the price of coal and oil as they increase their use, reducing their net economic product, after energy, as they grow... China does not have a service economy capable of growing its economy on a low-energy intensity growth path. Their communist government prevents such an economy from forming... Europe's socialist economy makes growth via services difficult, too. High taxes and high regulation are death to services...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1344176832000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344190729000-9</Id><Title>Thou Shalt not covet thy neighbor's acheivments</Title><Msg>Great article: President Barack Obama’s notorious words: “If you’ve been successful, you didn’t get there on your own; If you have a business, you didn’t build that”, will follow him ‘Forward’ right up to Election Day and beyond. Small business owners, who are the backbone of America, know that the fateful words spoken by Obama on Friday, July 13th best describe Obama without his mask. They are words that show more than any others what Obama and the Democrats are all about. Obama’s words are rooted in jealousy and even the coveting of the achievement of thy neighbour.</Msg><Username>sirola1</Username><Timestamp>1344190729000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:18:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344197580000-10</Id><Title>Why did Obama sign war act with Israel</Title><Msg>All the baboons that believe Obama is against Israel. Well welcome to the lies and deceit from american media that the Obama is full support Israel 100 percent. They just use tactics try to make you think that Obama is against Israel because he is Islamic.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1344197580000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344200540000-11</Id><Title>Calling BS on Reid's Bain tax claims</Title><Msg>http://finance.fortune.cnn.com/2012/07/31/calling-bs-on-reids-bain-tax-claims/</Msg><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344200540000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344200605000-12</Id><Title>Why this month's good jobs news won't last</Title><Msg>http://finance.fortune.cnn.com/2012/08/03/july-jobs-employment-report/?google_editors_picks=true</Msg><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344200605000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:03:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344206875000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Calling BS on Reid's Bain tax claims</Title><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344200540000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The most effective move would be to release tax returns for the past decade and prove Reid's statement wrong. The lie would be useful in developing an anti-Democrat narrative...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1344206875000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344211168000-14</Id><Title>Lloyds Banking Group prepares to invest heavily in alternative energy</Title><Msg>Alternative energy gains a powerful ally in the UK By Stephen Vagus – August 5, 2012 Lloyds Banking Group prepares to invest heavily in alternative energy The United Kingdom’s Lloyds Banking Group, one of the world’s most influential financial institutions, has taken a keen interest in alternative energy. The organization is poised to make a large investment in several alternative energy projects. These projects include offshore wind farms, solar energy farms, biomass and hydrogen-based projects. The banking group has also allocated funds to the establishment of a hydrogen fuel infrastructure in the UK as part of the government’s Guarantees program. $1.57 billion allocated to alternative energy projects Lloyds is the latest multinational financial institution to announce its intentions of supporting alternative energy. The bank is prepared to invest a total of $1.57 billion in alternative energy projects over the coming years. A third of these funds will go to projects that are already taken root in the UK and elsewhere. The financial institution is looking to support 9 infrastructure projects and a total of 12 clean energy projects. UK continues to make progress in its alternative energy goals The United Kingdom has set ambitious energy goals for itself. The country aims to ensure that no less than 15% of all energy consumed by the UK comes from renewable sources by 2020. The government has identified infrastructure as one of the best ways to accomplish this goal, hoping that a comprehensive energy structure will make the transition away from fossil-fuels easier. The government’s Guarantees program is poised to make the establishment of a clean energy infrastructure possible, as it will allocate approximately $50 billion to such projects. Lloyds to release more information concerning investments in the coming months Lloyds Banking Group will examine the alternative energy projects that are currently taking place in the country and determine which of these to support. Thus far, solar, wind and hydrogen fuel have garnered a significant portion of the financial institution’s attention. The bank plans to release further information concerning the projects it is supporting when investment decisions have been made. Funds from Lloyds are expected to be issued at some point in 2013. http://www.hydrogenfuelnews.com/alternative-energy-gains-a-powerful-ally-in-the-uk/855061/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344211168000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344211523000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Lloyds Banking Group prepares to invest heavily in alternative energy</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344211168000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LYG - LLOYDS BANKING GROUP PLC 2012 HALF-YEAR RESULTS 26 July - Half-Year Results 2012</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1344211523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344214919000-16</Id><Title>The Two-Dimensional Barack Obama</Title><Msg>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2012/08/04/the_two-dimensional_barack_obama_114974.html?google_editors_picks=true</Msg><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344214919000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344215805000-17</Id><Title>Do as I say, not as I do.</Title><Msg>http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10000872396390443545504577567262487941198.html</Msg><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344215805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:16:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344215977000-18</Id><Title>Social Security not deal it once was for workers</Title><Msg>http://news.yahoo.com/social-security-not-deal-once-workers-165327268.html</Msg><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344215977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:19:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344218248000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Social Security not deal it once was for workers</Title><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344215977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better to do a B-I-G across the board and eliminate SS, unemployment benefits and welfare. http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_E/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=26534&amp;tid=457809&amp;mid=457856&amp;tof=105&amp;rt=1&amp;frt=2&amp;off=1</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1344218248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344218869000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Our Heartland and Our Warming Climate</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1344214607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:56:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's all that ethanol production in "our heartland" that Gawd is upset 'bout... thus why the historical drought and fires of brimstone... cause and effect... Gawd didn't want food prices for everyone to rise sooo much, making it tough, just to make ends meet... sooo, bring 'em drought and fires... makes sense... walhieee, y'all never cease to amaze us, with all of y'all's insight... have a nice day...</Msg><Username>be.pick</Username><Timestamp>1344218869000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:07:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344219404000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Social Security not deal it once was for workers</Title><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344215977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The way it is now, congress should raise the contribution and benefit base income limit to help fund the program. Maybe even put the SS and HI tax on capital gains. Why should the rich get another tax break? http://www.socialsecurity.gov/OACT/COLA/cbb.html</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1344219404000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:16:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344220034000-22</Id><Topic><Title>The last 93 days of the failure called obama</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1344219358000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:15:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is going to beat him?</Msg><Username>riskgrowswithprice</Username><Timestamp>1344220034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344220234000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Our Heartland and Our Warming Climate</Title><Username>walhieee12</Username><Timestamp>1344214607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:56:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.ocean-acidification.net/FAQeco.html The oceans will go to acid eventually too destroying a good portion of sea life. The race is on to find an alternative to fossil fuels. Sadly the effort is underfunded and has little prospect of success...</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1344220234000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344221599000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Oil futures UP 5%... not sure why</Title><Username>binnybozo</Username><Timestamp>1344218031000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:53:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every $10 it rises cost the Chinese economy nearly 1% of GDP is increase transportation costs, mining costs, and food costs. The Chinese economy will be the first to crack under the strain. Oil demand has been pared back in America and Europe and is concentrated on people with much more income at their disposal, getting much higher value per barrel. Price increases are manageable among such groups. The poor have already defaulted on their debts and most are out of work; whether they take to the bicycle will matter little to the economy.</Msg><Username>torycoalition</Username><Timestamp>1344221599000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344224592000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Social Security not deal it once was for workers</Title><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344215977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good bye coward</Msg><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1344224592000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 23:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>