<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356155401853-1</Id><Topic><Title>****** Split Announcement ******</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1356057886699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-20 21:44:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notice that Exxon was the weakest oil stock today and one of the weakest Dow stocks. Has badly trailed all averages for the last 4 years. Stock hurt by terrible XTO acquisition. Stock a real underperformer since Rex Tillerson became CEO.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1356155401853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 00:50:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356155753754-2</Id><Title>XTO</Title><Msg>At the time of the XTO acquisition CEO Rex Tillerson said over and over that the deal would be beneficial to shareholders despite poor reviews the deal received from analysts. Earlier this year in a speech, he said that Exxon was "losing its shirt on natural gas." How can one have confidence in this man and his management team. Wall Steet certainly doesn't.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1356155753754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 00:55:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356175306748-3</Id><Topic><Title>It Took Sleazy Republicans 4 Days To Promote More Gun Sales</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1355927636634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 09:33:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>walhieeeeeee - paranoid and delustional - our next mall shooter.</Msg><Username>xtromania</Username><Timestamp>1356175306748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 06:21:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356177192511-4</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncraps Rule!</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1356130389781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:53:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maxwizard sums it up best: Conservatives and Republicans have lost and the majority of the country has voted for Socialism and we will be like Cuba or Venezuela within the next decade or two. The majority in the USA apparently really wants this and i must be a relic since i do not understand why they want this versus what we have been. Anyway, it is reality and we must accept this whether we like it or not.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1356177192511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 06:53:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356181819682-5</Id><Title>Obama selects the richest american for Secretary</Title><Msg>John Kerry is the richest family in the US. The Forbes family is so wealthy that it makes your head spin. John Kerry family used the Chinese for cost of shipping goods during the Opium Wars of Britian. So I guess the democrats are for the little people. RIght? So If your ingnorant to your own history than look it up.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1356181819682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:10:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356182409771-6</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncraps Rule!</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1356130389781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:53:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ POS is all maxidopey will ever be.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1356182409771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:20:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356182500582-7</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncraps Rule!</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1356130389781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:53:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the poor are going to get alot poorer but this time they will go hungry. Maxidopey is a perfect example of eating out of dumpster.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1356182500582</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:21:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356182623341-8</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne Lapierre This Weeks Voice From He!!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356143892984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:38:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u r a complete #$%$ #$%$ and degenerate.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1356182623341</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:23:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356182803626-9</Id><Topic><Title>Gun tax ---</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356107274216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:27:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>greed u r an #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1356182803626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:26:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356190257924-10</Id><Topic><Title>reactionary fools</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356125649808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 16:34:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A course in German philosophy will leave you a good solid right winger. Hegel's Elements of the Philosophy of Right is a good place to start. No I don't have a website.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356190257924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 10:30:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356190762617-11</Id><Topic><Title>Gun tax ---</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356107274216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:27:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's wrong ref? You can't afford $10,000 for each gun and $5/round? I bet you like to pet and polish each gun, every night, along with your jack boots too. You've probably named them as well. Still haven't been practicing with the ladies, either, I shouldn't wonder...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356190762617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 10:39:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356194777692-12</Id><Title>Polls show wealthy want higher taxes</Title><Msg>The reason why is very simple: There are very few good investments in the world these days, which is why tens trillions of dollars, tens of trillions of euros, and trillions of pounds are squeezed into bank deposits and bonds earning nothing. Stocks earn nothing either, bid up to such lofty heights, although some dreamers hope they will. The stocks are bid there because corporations do not have investment opportunities for capital and could not put investor funds to work on projects even if they sold stock, making it impossible for the stock market to absorb the capital except with inflation of the stock prices. Worse still corporations are buying back stock with monies they cannot invest, which just compounds the glut of capital and extreme inflation of stock values. The solution is obvious: The government must invest the glut of capital in public goods, and the responsible way to go about financing that is higher taxes. Investments in infrastructure, education, energy research, military weapon systems with their associated spin-off technologies, medicine, genetic engineering, and other areas of public spending, offer far greater return than the near zero returns possible now the capital glutted private sector. Investing in basic education and cultural improvement projects to improve the productivity of minorities in cities and backward elements in rural areas promises good returns too. Nuclear fusion, superconductors, advanced alloys, nanotechnologies, artificial intelligence and military &amp; industrial robotics, cloaking technologies, space transportation, communications, and weapon systems are fields that could soak up capital. Then there is the idiocy of running the budget deficits when such vast income, income that far beyond the spending ability of individuals, is available. For those brainwashed by visions of small businesses earning lottery returns, or riding the next stock to a fortune such views probably seem strange. Such people lack perspective.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356194777692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 11:46:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356197511084-13</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncraps Rule!</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1356130389781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:53:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you believe that, you have been drunk for the last 4 years. I should have suspected that all along.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1356197511084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 12:31:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356198544584-14</Id><Topic><Title>Gun tax ---</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356107274216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:27:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should have background checks on purchasers and certain " lifestyle" people should be denied. That will never happen although it should. The full personality profile of the perpetrator in Conneticuit should be published, but parts of it would be deleted/covered up deemed irrelevant, so as to protect the sensetivity of a favored group.</Msg><Username>upsidetonograph</Username><Timestamp>1356198544584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 12:49:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356200820469-15</Id><Topic><Title>Barney Frank To Take Senator Kerry's Seat!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356144530095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:48:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You hare everyone, especially yourself - and with good reason.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1356200820469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 13:27:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356202927703-16</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne Lapierre This Weeks Voice From He!!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356143892984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:38:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>-- Mayan Palace Theater, San Antonio, Texas, this week: Jesus Manuel Garcia shoots at a movie theater, a police car and bystanders from the nearby China Garden restaurant; as he enters the movie theater, guns blazing, an armed off-duty cop shoots Garcia four times, stopping the attack. Total dead: Zero. -- Winnemucca, Nev., 2008: Ernesto Villagomez opens fire in a crowded restaurant; concealed carry permit-holder shoots him dead. Total dead: Two. (I'm excluding the shooters' deaths in these examples.) -- Appalachian School of Law, 2002: Crazed immigrant shoots the dean and a professor, then begins shooting students; as he goes for more ammunition, two armed students point their guns at him, allowing a third to tackle him. Total dead: Three. -- Santee, Calif., 2001: Student begins shooting his classmates -- as well as the "trained campus supervisor"; an off-duty cop who happened to be bringing his daughter to school that day points his gun at the shooter, holding him until more police arrive. Total dead: Two. -- Pearl High School, Mississippi, 1997: After shooting several people at his high school, student heads for the junior high school; assistant principal Joel Myrick retrieves a .45 pistol from his car and points it at the gunman's head, ending the murder spree. Total dead: Two. -- Edinboro, Pa., 1998: A student shoots up a junior high school dance being held at a restaurant; restaurant owner pulls out his shotgun and stops the gunman. Total dead: One. By contrast, the shootings in gun-free zones invariably result in far higher casualty figures -- Sikh temple, Oak Creek, Wis. (six dead); Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va. (32 dead); Columbine High School, Columbine, Colo. (12 dead); Amish school, Lancaster County, Pa. (five little girls killed); public school, Craighead County, Ark. (five killed, including four little girls). All these took place in gun-free zones, resulting in lots of people getting killed -- and thereby warranting inclusion in the Mother Jones study. If what we care about is saving the lives of innocent human beings by reducing the number of mass public shootings and the deaths they cause, only one policy has ever been shown to work: concealed-carry laws. On the other hand, if what we care about is self-indulgent grandstanding, and to hell with dozens of innocent children being murdered in cold blood, try the other policies.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1356202927703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 14:02:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356204145398-17</Id><Topic><Title>Gun tax ---</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356107274216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 11:27:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>greed u r a sick twisted #$%$ dik.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1356204145398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 14:22:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356204771300-18</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne Lapierre This Weeks Voice From He!!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1356143892984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 21:38:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Envision a fort under siege. Is this really the best place to be exchanging counter-battery fire with? If you must, you must... I'm sure Obama and his Grand Marshals are delighted at the opportunity...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356204771300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 14:32:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356206122539-19</Id><Topic><Title>XOM report.</Title><Username>robertklotz24</Username><Timestamp>1355765875748</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-17 12:37:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice stuff</Msg><Username>robertschan606</Username><Timestamp>1356206122539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 14:55:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356223334713-20</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncraps Rule!</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1356130389781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:53:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even a German should know that 2 out of 3 beats 1 out of 3. The House is powerless due to the Demoncrap controlled Senate and President. Also we have learned that Justice Roberts is actually a Demoncrap, so the Supreme Court if also controlled by the Demoncraps. Demoncraps 3 and RINOs 1. Game over for the RINOs. The RINO's best bet is just let the Demoncraps do what they want to do and the sheeple serfs will learn their lesson the hard way as we turn (at best) into another Socialist European country (which I know makes you feel better about Germany) or (at worst) Cuba or Venezuela. I actually believe the latter will be the eventual case since Obama will eventually turn into Hugo Chavez, or maybe even worse; Adolf Hitler.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1356223334713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 19:42:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356224082264-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama selects the richest american for Secretary</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1356181819682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:10:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see no contradiction. The Progressives have always been a group run by elitists. They were educated by German &amp; British elitists in Europe and German &amp; British elitist professors in American universities. The Socialist Party in Germany and the "Progressive" Party in Germany was run by elitist too - their objective was to introduce upper class culture to the German workers and negotiate the means for them to have at least a taste of the lifestyle. Really not that bad of a plan. They were not bearded revolutionaries...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356224082264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 19:54:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356224425935-22</Id><Topic><Title>Demoncraps Rule!</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1356130389781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-21 17:53:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republicans are under siege. When the siege is over, and the Democrats overrun them, I will invest in stocks. Not until. They can block the growth of government and key investments in infrastructure and technology, investments that are vital to America's future. Until they are out America and the world economy is no-go...2014 should be end for the GOP.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1356224425935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 20:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>