<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-16"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353043241278-1</Id><Title>This Week In Petroleum November 15, 2012</Title><Msg>This Week In Petroleum November 15, 2012 Next Release: November 21, 2012 Post-Sandy Look at Gasoline Data Shows Market Stresses in Affected Regions Petroleum data for the week ending November 9 released today by the U.S. Energy Information Administration (EIA) provide the second set of data to #$%$ the impacts of Hurricane Sandy on U.S. petroleum markets. The storm significantly disrupted electricity, natural gas, and petroleum product supply infrastructure in the Northeast and affected millions of consumers. However, the data from the first week following Hurricane Sandy showed falling gasoline inventories in the Northeast Petroleum Administration for Defense Districts (PADDs 1A and 1B) including the New England states, New York, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and Delaware, the region hit hardest by the storm (Figure 1), as reduced gasoline deliveries into the region and a drop in refinery production were likely partially offset by reduced demand. These data indicate that aggregate supplies of physical products across the broader Northeast region have been less of a problem than disruptions due to damage to terminals, ports, and pipelines serving the New York metropolitan area. These disruptions have especially stressed supply chains between the wholesale and retail segments. Refinery inputs have fallen sharply in the two weeks after the storm, lowering the production of gasoline in the Northeast. About 70 percent of the refining capacity in the Northeast is located along the lower Delaware River near Philadelphia. For precautionary reasons, these refineries either briefly shut down or reduced runs, but were largely back online relatively quickly after the storm. However, the 308,000 barrels per day (bbl/d) of refining capacity in the New York Harbor area were still inoperable through November 13. The major plant in the area, Phillips 66's 238,000-bbl/d refinery in Linden, New Jersey, suffered both power loss and flooding. Hess's plant in Port Reading, New Jersey, which has no crude distillation capacity, but produces gasoline and other petroleum products using units that process secondary feedstocks to produce gasoline, also lost power. The shutdowns at the New York Harbor facilities combined with the temporary reduction in runs in the Philadelphia area to lower gross inputs in PADD 1 by 290,000 bbl/d for the week ending November 2 compared to the previous week. PADD 1 gross refinery inputs for that week were 757,000 bbl/d, the lowest for any week since April 2011. The drop in inputs came on the heels of some of the highest levels of PADD 1 refinery inputs in almost a year following the early-October restart of Monroe Energy's 185,000-bbl/d refinery in Trainer, Pennsylvania. On November 5, Phillips 66 said it planned to have the Linden refinery return to production within three weeks. As of November 14, press reports indicated Hess's Port Reading facility was in the process of restarting. With some of the Philadelphia area refineries returning to more normal operations, PADD 1 gross refinery inputs increased by 101,000 bbl/d during the week ending November 9 to 858,000 bb/d. With New York Harbor closed for several days after the storm, the steady flow of gasoline imports into the region was also interrupted. Prior to Hurricane Sandy, PADD 1 had been importing an average of more than 600,000 bbl/d of gasoline in 2012, much of this going into the Northeast. However, for the week ending November 2, gasoline imports were just 217,000 bbl/d, the lowest total since EIA began tracking weekly PADD-level product imports in 2004. Imports rebounded to 525,000 bbl/d in the week ending November 9 as several major import-receiving terminals in the Northeast reopened. However, some of the reopened terminals still have damage that is impeding normal operations. As of November 13, five port terminals in the Northeast remained closed: in New Jersey, the Hess terminal in Bayonne and CITGO terminal in Linden; in New York, the Phillips 66 terminal in Tremley Point and Motiva's terminals in Brooklyn and on Long Island. These terminals are not only used for receiving imports, they are also used to receive waterborne oil products from major aggregating terminals in New York Harbor in order to move it into local distribution chains, particularly in the New York City area and on Long Island. While EIA does not collect weekly data on inter-PADD transfers of products, trade press reports and company statements indicate pipeline shipments of products from the Gulf Coast to the Northeast were significantly curtailed. With terminal capacity in the Northeast disrupted, many terminals in the region did not have the ability to take volumes off the Colonial Pipeline, the major link between the Gulf Coast and Northeast product markets. As a result, inventories built on the Gulf Coast as pipeline inputs were reduced on the southern portion of the line. On November 2, gasoline inventories on the Gulf Coast were 4.6 million barrels (7 percent) higher than a week earlier (Figure 2). This marked the largest weekly inventory build in the region since October 2008. Inventories continued to build during the week ending November 9, adding 900,000 barrels. The slowing inventory builds on the Gulf Coast reflected some easing of pipeline congestion in New York Harbor, allowing it to receive more volumes from the Gulf, along with the Jones Act waiver which temporarily allowed products to be sent to the Northeast on foreign-flagged vessels from the Gulf. It is likely that the disruption in supplies to the Northeast was at least somewhat offset by lower consumption. EIA does not collect weekly data on product supplied (a proxy for consumption) at the PADD level. However, EIA estimates that the Northeast consumes about 18 percent of the gasoline consumed nationally. For the week ending November 2, total product supplied of gasoline for the United States as a whole was 537,000 bbl/d lower than the previous week, and almost 300,000 bbl/d lower than the four-week average product supplied. However, product supplied recovered the week ending November 9, increasing by just over 600,000 bbl/d from the week before. Given its large share of the country's consumption and the supply chain disruptions, it is likely that a significant portion of the drop for the week ending November 2 occurred in the Northeast. As a result of the countervailing decreases in both supply and consumption, inventories were relatively flat for the week ending November 2. For both the weeks ending November 2 and November 9 gasoline inventories in the Northeast fell by 1.1 million barrels from the previous week, an amount within the fluctuations typically observed, and are now 4.5 million barrels (15 percent) below their five-year average levels for this time of year. Gasoline and diesel prices fall again The U.S. average retail price of regular gasoline decreased four cents last week to $3.45 per gallon, a penny per gallon higher than last year at this time. The largest decrease came on the West Coast, where the price has decreased 63 cents over the last five weeks, and 12 cents from last week, to $3.78 per gallon. The Gulf Coast price dropped seven cents to $3.21 per gallon, and the price in the Rocky Mountain region is now $3.56 per gallon, a nickel less than last week. On the East Coast the price decreased four cents to $3.49 per gallon. The only region where the price increased was the Midwest, where the price is up a penny to $3.33 per gallon. The national average diesel fuel price decreased three cents to $3.98 per gallon, a penny lower than last year at this time. The last time the national average diesel price was below the $4-per-gallon mark was August 13, 2012. The largest decrease came in the Rocky Mountain region, where the price fell six cents to $4.10 per gallon. The Midwest and Gulf Coast prices were each down a nickel, to $3.91 per gallon and $3.88 per gallon, respectively. On the West Coast the price is now $4.13 per gallon, a decrease of two cents from last week. The only region where the price increased was the East Coast, where the price increased less than a penny to $4.04 per gallon. Propane stocks continue seasonal drawdown Total U.S. inventories of propane dipped again last week, falling 0.4 million barrels to end at 73.2 million barrels, 13.6 million barrels (23 percent) higher than a year ago. Stocks in the East Coast region were drawn down by 0.3 million barrels, while Rocky Mountain/West Coast stocks fell 0.1 million barrels. Midwest stocks dropped slightly, and Gulf Coast inventories grew slightly. Propylene non-fuel-use inventories represented 5.7 percent of total propane inventories. Residential heating oil and propane prices hold steady Residential heating oil prices remained unchanged during the period ending November 12, 2012. The average residential heating oil price held firm last week at $3.98 per gallon, about 4 cents per gallon higher than the same time last year. Wholesale heating oil prices increased by more than 5 cents per gallon last week to reach $3.17 per gallon, almost 13 cents per gallon less than last year at this time. The average residential propane price remained the same last week at $2.40 per gallon, 42 cents per gallon lower than the same period last year. Wholesale propane prices decreased by over 4 cents to $0.96 per gallon for the week ending November 12, 2012, 54 cents per gallon lower than the November 14, 2011 price. eiaDOTgov/oog/info/twip/twip.asp</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353043241278</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 00:20:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353045772262-2</Id><Topic><Title>Anti-Tax Traitors</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353028266072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 20:11:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Additionally, liberals do not fight for anything and do not have anyone to fight for them.. So there won't be any problem, just a division where the homosexuals exist in their own states.</Msg><Username>wallstreetvet80</Username><Timestamp>1353045772262</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 01:02:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353072540053-3</Id><Title>He talks as though He STOLE the Election Hisself</Title><Msg>grotesque</Msg><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1353072540053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 08:29:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353076319444-4</Id><Topic><Title>Anti-Tax Traitors</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353028266072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 20:11:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can rant and rave all you like. It is irrelevant. You will be taxed more. It will be lawful and you will pay it. When the Republican Congress is swept away in two years you will be paying even more taxes too. The demographic trend makes the result inevitable. If you are unhappy about the bill and are looking for someone to blame look to Reagan and W: trillions in tax cuts, unfunded wars, etc compounding interest start to add up. As for the secessionist talk. That has been tried by countless rebel groups across the ages from England, to France, to the USA in the past. Catherine the Great had them drawn and quartered in Moscow. Washington sent in the army. Lincoln raised a million man army to deal with it etc, etc...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353076319444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:31:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353076372045-5</Id><Title>Cellulosic BioFuel Is Here - world’s first commercial-scale cellulosic ethanol plant, recently commissioned</Title><Msg>Cellulosic BioFuel Is Here Jim Ruen | November 15, 2012 Cellulosic biofuel is in production in one major plant, and more are on their way. The progress may be just in the nick of time. As commodity prices have risen, the old food versus fuel debate has morphed into fuel versus food and feed. When corn prices rose a few years ago, some in the corn ethanol industry demanded a grain reserve to protect ethanol producers. These days the industry is simply trying to hold on to the Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS) as fears of rising food prices provide fodder for a powerful triad of consumers, livestock feeders and anti-biofuel forces. PHOTO - The world’s first commercial-scale cellulosic ethanol plant, recently commissioned in Crescentino, Italy. The plant uses Beta Renewables’ PROESA technology and was built by Chemtex. Chemtex is developing a similar plant to produce cellulosic ethanol in North Carolina with a goal of completion in 2014. At the same time, the corn ethanol industry is in economic retreat as ethanol plants cut back and even close in the face of the recessionary impact on gasoline demand and negative margins due to high commodity prices. By contrast, cellulosic biofuel is a bright spot, one of several in the next generation of biofuels. "Between now and 2017 we will see a number of companies deploy and build cellulosic biofuel plants," said Mike McAdams, president, Advanced Biofuels Association (ABF). "There is every type of technology coming at this thing with a lot of major companies with significant investments in research and development. Some have begun engineering and permitting, others are building, and some are already operating." PRODUCING ETHANOL CHEAPER One of the companies that is making the investment is Chemtex Global S.A. with its collaborative partner Novozymes North America. "Cellulosic technology is real, and it is here today," said Dennis Leong, executive vice president, marketing and business development, Chemtex Global S.A. "It is commercially attractive and commercially viable. We believe we can produce ethanol at a lower cost per gallon than with corn or sugar cane." With one plant up and running in Italy and a second scheduled for North Carolina, Leong is confident of his claims. The company has been producing ethanol from cellulose at a pilot plant for four years. Both plants are designed to use biomass treated with enzymes from industry partner Novozyme. The enzymes turn the cellulose into sugar before it is fermented and ethanol is produced. "We can use tree crops, and we may in the short term, but we'll be transitioning to dedicated energy crops grown on low quality land not suitable for crop production," said Leong. "We are trying to make something from nothing on land that is just lying there." RENEWABLE CRUDE Kior, Inc. also will be making biofuel from cellulose, but it is a different breed of biofuel. By the time this article is in print, the company's new 11 million gallons per year plant in Mississippi should be producing what they call renewable crude, a drop-in hydrocarbon molecule that KiOR further processes to produce fungible gasoline and diesel components that drop-in to the existing petroleum transportation fuel infrastructure. While ethanol, regardless of its source, requires blender pumps and faces blending limits, gasoline and diesel from renewable crude has a host of potential homes and no limits. Kior isn't the first to make a drop-in biofuel commercially, though they will be the largest. What they won't be is the last. "An overwhelming number of our 51 members are making drop-in molecules that don't require blender’s pumps," said McAdams. "These are hydrocarbon molecules that behave exactly as if they came from a barrel of oil. They are fungible biofuels that can be mutually exchanged in gasoline, diesel or jet fuel." The efficacy of drop-in biofuels was recently demonstrated by the U.S. Navy off the coast of Hawaii. McAdams, representing the industry, was on board the USS Nimitz as a squadron of Navy jets took off, burning 50/50 biofuel based jet fuel. "When they landed, the pilots were debriefed," recalled McAdams. "They told us the planes flew great, and they wouldn't be using the fuel if they didn't believe in it." If the end product is equivalent to petroleum-based products, so, is the process for making it equivalent? Kior uses a proprietary process called Biomass Fluid Catalytic Cracking to convert biomass directly into a combination of renewable crude, water, light gasses and coke. Once separated, the renewable crude is refined into the desired product—gasoline, diesel, jet fuel or other. The gasses are burned to generate electricity. The process is "feedstock flexible" and can utilize a wide range of biomass materials. However, the location of the Mississippi plant is intended to utilize woody biomass, in this case, Southern Yellow Pine. The USDA Forest Service estimates enough surplus pine exists, beyond what is harvested each day for other uses, to supply 35 Kior-style plants using 1,500 dry tons per day. Best of all, pine is unlike other energy sources, such as corn, sugar, soy oil and even crude oil, which have fluctuated wildly in price over the past 12 years. Instead, its price has risen only slightly in that time period, giving Kior a feedstock in wide cultivation and available at a long-term stable price. ADJUSTING TO HIGH CORN PRICES Finding a stabler priced source of feedstock is the goal of many in the grain-based ethanol industry. Although most are focusing on post harvest corn biomass or corn stover, one is focusing on fiber in the grain. Quad County Corn Processors (QCCP) plans to be producing cellulosic ethanol along with its starch-based ethanol by fall of 2013. The change is going to make adjusting to higher corn prices easier, initially for QCCP and eventually for other corn processors. Thanks to a breakthrough in the fermentation process discovered by company engineer Travis Brotherson, ethanol production will increase by at least 6 percent and as much as 10 percent. Corn oil yield will more than triple from 0.5 lbs. per bushel to 1.6 lbs. per bushel. The only downside is that co-product tonnage, today known as distiller grains, will decrease by about 15 percent. On the plus side, the new co-product becomes a high-protein, low-fiber feed product that can be used in ruminant diets and is expected to be much more digestible by pigs, poultry and other monogastric animals. Brotherson expects demand will rise for the new byproduct as livestock producers get experience with it, much as happened with distillers grains. He also expects demand to rise for the process. "We will work on building the system here and letting people see the results," said Brotherson. "In the near time frame, we will be talking to other plants. Our plan is to commercialize it at other facilities in the future." BANKING ON RFS While cellulosic biofuel feedstocks and processing technologies differ across the board, one thing unites the advanced biofuels industry and the traditional grain-based industry. "The RFS is the keystone for where we are right now," said McAdams. "It is eminently important that it stay in place and that the federal government send a strong signal of support for it." He pointed to the billions of dollars being invested by private industry, as well as the grants, loans and loan guarantees already made by the U.S. government. The American Recovery and Reinvestment Act funded $800 million for advanced biofuels. As a result of those funds, private investors and creative new technologies, McAdams suggested that the country is well on its way to greater energy security, though there is a considerable way to go. "It's like we're in the second quarter of the game," said McAdams. "It's kind of hard if the rules are changed before we even reach the middle of the game." Leong agreed with McAdams, even though he pointed out there is a differentiation between corn-based biofuel and other feedstock-based biofuels. "Our position and that of a lot of others is that it isn't appropriate to touch the RFS," said Leong. "It has served the country well, and it is a policy that is important to our industry." agprofessionalDOTcom/agprofessional-magazine/Cellulosic-BioFuel-Is-Here-179555991.html?view=all</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353076372045</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:32:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353076485460-6</Id><Topic><Title>He talks as though He STOLE the Election Hisself</Title><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1353072540053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 08:29:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our Government has to borrow 40% to run our Entitlement state. Over 60% of our yearly budget goes to entitlements. Then there's the 1 Trillion dollar plus deficit every year. There is no wonder why the entitlement crowd (give me's) would vote for Obama and the Democratic socialist party. They appear to be very caring and generous while they use other people's money in order to appease and court the welfare herds.</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1353076485460</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:34:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353076923437-7</Id><Topic><Title>BUY MJNA - Medical Marijuana Inc ... There is a hope in recovering your losses !!!</Title><Username>mr_vopni</Username><Timestamp>1353037761193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 22:49:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They should legalize drugs and tax them. The "War on Drugs" has been a failure like Prohibition of alcohol and should be ended.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353076923437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:42:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353077184796-8</Id><Title>Supreme Court</Title><Msg>...Obama's victory ensures that it will be shifting squarely into the Progressive direction. So much for the abortion issue - time for a new campaign plank GOP So much for the war on porn - even the right wingers on the court abandoned that So much for trying to foist religion on the schools and government - DOA...new plank needed So much eccentric attitudes about guns rights and states rights shaped by farmers and backwoodsmen who have been dead for over 200 years...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353077184796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:46:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353077541854-9</Id><Title>When to buy market...</Title><Msg>Next year sometime, I should think, when Obama and the Democrat Party have demonstrated that they are in control of this situation, that they will start raising to taxes to fix the fiscal mess, and when the Wall Street speculators who have been betting on Republican tax polices for three decades have sold. Task #1 the Republican Congress needs to be thoroughly defeated on the Bush Tax Cuts battle...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353077541854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:52:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353082724339-10</Id><Title>Why is Exxon falling?</Title><Msg>This makes no sense. Exxon is supposed to be indestructible. October is the time to buy oil stocks, but apparently not this year. This year, in October, oil stocks hit all time highs practically. So what's the deal now?</Msg><Username>beepeeess</Username><Timestamp>1353082724339</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 11:18:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353082857678-11</Id><Title>Whose rig blew up in Gulf Mexico this morning?</Title><Msg>The USCG has annoounced a oil rig blew up this morning in the Gulf with a couple of deaths - anyone know who owned the rig?</Msg><Username>jspsaki</Username><Timestamp>1353082857678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 11:20:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353085677183-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Exxon falling?</Title><Username>beepeeess</Username><Timestamp>1353082724339</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 11:18:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Taxes. Most stocks are owned by the top 1% of income earners. The value of a stock is the present value of its projected dividend stream MINUS the projected taxes on that dividend stream. You should also keep in mind, too, that the $15+ trillion increase in the national debt, and the $10+ trillion in debt owed or insured by Fannie/Freddie, and all the FDIC backed deposits have value only based on the taxing power and credit of the U.S. government. That debt whoever is proposing higher taxes a natural constituency, and a constituency that includes some very wealthy and very powerful people. Then there are the usual suspects who are living off entitlements, and those obligations only have value based on the taxing power of the U.S. government. So you see there is good reason to expect taxes to be rising going forward, and stocks to be losing ground due to it. Stocks are not sound investments during times such as this this or that "October" or any other arbitrary month or day of the calendar aside...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353085677183</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 12:07:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353086062425-13</Id><Topic><Title>Whose rig blew up in Gulf Mexico this morning?</Title><Username>jspsaki</Username><Timestamp>1353082857678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 11:20:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure I don't know. You can rest assured, however, that most speculators in oil stocks are not taking the risk of explosions such as this into account. Of course they ignore the consequence these "mishaps" have around the world for their other businesses too: it is convenient for governments that have a desire to collect oil reserves into their state companies to have a track record of accidents, and criminal misconduct by major oil companies, ones like BP, to point to. You will find that the typical investor in such speculative business is just not a rational character, however... They typically are not diversified either and panic easily at the first whiff of real danger to their massively risky investment stance.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353086062425</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 12:14:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353088495254-14</Id><Topic><Title>Idiots giving away free money...</Title><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1352906396124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:19:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short selling campaign complete: No more trades until the debt/tax negotiations collapse.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353088495254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 12:54:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353092434217-15</Id><Title>NEW TAX</Title><Msg>How long will it take Boehner to cry and say OK to Obama, A week?</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1353092434217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:00:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353092889580-16</Id><Title>EPA denies appeal to waive US Renewable Fuels Standard</Title><Msg>EPA denies appeal to waive US Renewable Fuels Standard Jim Lane | November 16, 2012 The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) announced that the agency has not found evidence to support a finding of severe “economic harm” that would warrant granting a waiver of the Renewable Fuels Standard (RFS). The decision is based on economic analyses and modeling done in conjunction with the U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) and U.S. Department of Energy (DOE). “We recognize that this year’s drought has created hardship in some sectors of the economy, particularly for livestock producers,” said Gina McCarthy, assistant administrator for EPA’s Office of Air and Radiation. “But our extensive analysis makes clear that Congressional requirements for a waiver have not been met and that waiving the RFS will have little, if any, impact.” To support the waiver decision, EPA conducted several economic analyses. Economic analyses of impacts in the agricultural sector, conducted with USDA, showed that on average waiving the mandate would only reduce corn prices by approximately one percent. Economic analyses of impacts in the energy sector, conducted with DOE, showed that waiving the mandate would not impact household energy costs. EPA found that the evidence and information failed to support a determination that implementation of the RFS mandate during the 2012-2013 time period would severely harm the economy of a State, a region, or the United States, the standard established by Congress in the Energy Policy Act of 2005 (EPAct). EPAct required EPA to implement a renewable fuels standard to ensure that transportation fuel sold in the United States contains a minimum volume of renewable fuel. A waiver of the mandate requires EPA, working with USDA and DOE, to make a finding of “severe economic harm” from the RFS mandate itself. This is the second time that EPA has considered an RFS waiver request. In both cases, analysis concluded that that the mandate did not impose severe harm. In 2008, the state of Texas was denied a waiver. Reaction from the industry Brooke Coleman, Executive Director, AEC: “The advanced ethanol industry commends U.S. EPA for denying the RFS waiver petition. Waiving the RFS would have done little if anything to reduce grain prices, but would have hurt consumers at the pump and undercut investment in advanced biofuels. Congress was right to protect the RFS from specious and politically-motivated waiver arguments, and to include in the program explicit flexibility provisions that allow the standard to adjust to changing market conditions. The RFS is well-designed and is the primary reason why the United States has emerged as the global leader in the development of advanced biofuels. There will be other stalking horses advanced by the oil industry to weaken the RFS, but it is a step in the right direction to put this one behind us. The American Coalition for Ethanol (ACE) applauded the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) for denying a request from a handful of states to waive the Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS). “Despite millions of dollars spent by Big Oil and Big Food to shamelessly attack American-made ethanol, it comes as no surprise EPA denied the requests to waive the RFS because the facts are on our side,” said Brian Jennings, ACE Executive Vice President. “EPA considered the flexibility built-into the RFS, precedent established in 2008, and data which proved waiving the RFS wouldn’t remedy the harm of the drought in making the right decision.” Jennings says that comments submitted by ethanol supporters were a factor in the EPA’s decision. “In a strong demonstration of grassroots support for ethanol, more than 130 unique comments were submitted by ACE members from 15 different states making the case for the RFS,” said Jennings. “Given the battle we anticipate over the RFS in Congress next year, we encourage ethanol supporters to stay engaged. One way to remain actively involved is to join ACE for our annual ‘Biofuels Beltway March’ fly-in scheduled for March 13-14 on Capitol Hill.” Fuels America, a coalition of organizations representing a broad spectrum of renewable fuel stakeholders, released the following statement today after the EPA rejected requests to waive the Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS): “The multi-sector members of Fuels America are happy to see that the RFS, a policy that has driven job creation and investment in a time of economic distress, will remain intact. It has helped to attract billions in investment to an industry that supports over 400,000 jobs. “The economic facts support EPA’s decision. We commend the agency for recognizing the importance of the policy to lowering gas prices and reducing our dependence on foreign oil, and the role of the drought, not renewable fuels, in driving current commodity prices. “The certainty that this decision delivers will support continued investment and innovation in a range of diverse, efficient and advanced renewable fuel technologies.” The Fuels America coalition represents a diverse set of stakeholders – from industry, national security, agriculture and more – that support the RFS. Here’s what a few of its members said about today’s decision: Adam Monroe, President, Novozymes North America, said of EPA’s decision to deny the waiver: “With so much at stake for the economy, we need the Renewable Fuel Standard: Its stability has generated 400,000 careers, billions in private investment – and domestic, renewable fuel for America. Novozymes and other industry leaders have invested more than a billion dollars to commercialize advanced biofuels agricultural waste, household trash and more, in large part because of the RFS. “We appreciate the Administration’s decision to deny the waiver request based on the data – and are pleased the United States will continue becoming less dependent on foreign oil with domestic, renewable fuel for its cars and trucks.” Jan Koninckx, Global Business Director for Biofuels at DuPont: “We are pleased with the EPA ruling. The agency continues to demonstrate a commitment to US production of renewable fuels to reduce our dependence on imported oil. The careful analyses performed by USEPA and USDA show that the drought, and not the Renewable Fuels Standard, is the cause of the temporary situation,” said Jan Koninckx, Global Business Director for Biofuels at DuPont. “While we empathize with both livestock and ethanol producers that are struggling with higher corn prices, we are also confident that farmers will continue to expand corn production, and DuPont and others will continue to commercialize advanced biofuels – to serve both our feed and renewable fuels needs.” Jeff Lautt, CEO of POET “The EPA today made a sound decision in denying a waiver of the Renewable Fuel Standard. As studies have shown, a waiver would have likely had little to no impact on commodities prices in the aftermath of the recent drought. This effort was nothing more than the latest attempt by renewable fuel opponents to undermine policy that has helped make America stronger. “Today’s decision means the Renewable Fuel Standard remains strong and stable policy, and our industry can move forward with greater confidence, continuing to invest in new technology to make biofuels production even more efficient and commercializing fuel production from cellulosic feedstocks such as crop residue and other plant material. “POET-DSM Advanced Biofuels is moving forward with construction of the joint venture’s first commercial cellulosic biofuels plant that will use corn cobs, leaves, husk and some stalk to produce renewable fuel. Long term, there are ambitious plans for expansion of this technology to more plants in the POET network and to other companies through licensing agreements. By maintaining the integrity of the Renewable Fuel Standard, those expansion plans are much more feasible.” Bob Dinneen, CEO, Renewable Fuels Association “The EPA made the right decision today. We applaud the EPA for basing its decision on thoughtful analysis of the facts and not emotion or panic. The RFS is working as designed. The flexibility that is built into the RFS allows the marketplace to ration demand, not the government. Indeed, the ethanol industry has responded to the market by reducing output by approximately 12%. Other users of corn have responded to a lesser degree. Maintaining the RFS is in the best interest of both U.S. agriculture and American consumers. The RFS is resulting in greater energy independence and diversity, real job creation, lower gas prices, and a cleaner environment. Brent Erickson, executive vice-president of BIO’s Industrial &amp; Environmental, Section: “EPA has made the right decision and we thank them for making a careful and fully considered analysis. Earlier studies by researchers at Purdue University, Iowa State University and the University of Missouri’s Food and Agricultural Policy Research Institute showed clearly that a waiver of the RFS would not undo the economic harm caused by the drought. “However, a waiver of the RFS could have undercut ongoing investments in advanced biofuels. Renewable fuels are a significant contributor to our nation’s economy and energy security, creating jobs and directly reducing reliance on imported oil. This decision allows BIO member companies to continue to deliver innovative technologies to the market to expand our domestic production of biofuels, including fuels from agricultural residues, municipal solid waste, algae and purpose grown energy crops.” Tom Buis, CEO, Growth Energy: The announcement by the EPA is welcome news to the renewable fuels industry and those dedicated to reducing our dependence on foreign oil, spurring investment and creating jobs right here in America. “Growth Energy has continually advocated that the current conditions fall short of the threshold required to modify the RFS and that the market is working. Furthermore, granting a waiver on the evidence presented by the obligated parties would have sent the wrong signal the investment community, whose participation is vital to the reducing our dependence on foreign oil, creating jobs in the US that cannot be outsourced, improving our environment and saving consumers at the pump. “Today’s decision confirms what we knew all along – the petitioners were wrong in their belief that the RFS caused the economic harm. I commend the administration’s efforts to carefully review the facts and data in this matter. Their findings have echoed the comments of Growth Energy and we are pleased that the most successful energy policy enacted in the last forty years will not be modified. “I thank the EPA for their diligent work and applaud them for ensuring the win-win energy policy for America is not changed due to political pressure from an isolated event.” Reaction from critics Michal Rosenoer, biofuels policy campaigner at Friends of the Earth: “If the worst U.S. drought in more than 50 years and skyrocketing food prices are not enough to make EPA act, it falls to Congress to provide relief from our senseless federal support for corn ethanol. The RFS is a broken policy — rather than giving us clean energy, it’s incentivizing biofuels like corn ethanol that are exacerbating our economic and environmental problems. “Congress needs to cut corn ethanol from the RFS entirely to protect the economy and the environment from this destructive and dirty fuel.” Joint statement from Environmental Working Group, Friends of the Earth and ActionAid USA: “We are disappointed with EPA’s decision to deny relief for those who need it most. High corn prices have put enormous pressure on livestock producers, dairy farmers and consumers, as well as the environment. While Americans struggle to stay afloat and put food on their tables, more than 40 percent of the nation’s corn crop is being used to make ethanol – a result of the requirements of the federal Renewable Fuel Standard. “This decision should serve as a wake-up call to Congress and the White House that the Renewable Fuel Standard does not protect producers and consumers in times of hardship and must be reformed. Its reliance on mandates for food-based fuel – namely corn ethanol – exposes us to spiking prices whenever yields drop because of drought or other severe weather. “The skyrocketing cost of animal feed will force 100 of California’s dairies out of business by year’s end. Overall food prices are expected to rise by as much as 4 percent in the coming months, with even greater increases for meat, poultry, milk and eggs. These mandates have also spurred the conversion of 23 million acres of environmentally sensitive wetlands and grasslands – an area the size of Indiana – to row crops, mostly corn. “In order to stem further damage, we urge that lawmakers in Congress consider a responsible phase-out of the corn ethanol mandate. No amount of tinkering can substitute for the impact of real reform.” biofuelsdigestDOTcom/bdigest/2012/11/16/epa-denies-appeal-to-waive-us-renewable-fuels-standard/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353092889580</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:08:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353093219007-17</Id><Topic><Title>Whose rig blew up in Gulf Mexico this morning?</Title><Username>jspsaki</Username><Timestamp>1353082857678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 11:20:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Black Elk Petroleum and the rig did not blow up.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353093219007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:13:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353093269816-18</Id><Title>EPA rule puts Arizona plants on track to upgrade</Title><Msg>EPA rule puts Arizona plants on track to upgrade Updated: 11:43 a.m. Friday, Nov. 16, 2012 | Posted: 11:42 a.m. Friday, Nov. 16, 2012 By FELICIA FONSECA The Associated Press FLAGSTAFF, Ariz. — The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency had outlined a final plan for upgrades at three Arizona coal-fired power plants. The agency on Friday followed through with a proposal to partially reject Arizona's air quality plan. It came up with one of its own for nitrogen oxide emissions that impair visibility at 18 national parks and wilderness areas. Instead of sticking with technology such as low nitrogen-oxide burners, the Cholla, Coronado and Apache generating stations likely will have to install selective catalytic reduction technology to further reduce the emissions by 22,700 tons per year. The state Department of Environmental Quality was quick to denounce the EPA's decision, saying Arizona has a right to control pollutants within its borders. The department says visibility improvements from more than $500 million in upgrades will be imperceptible. kfoxtvDOTcom/news/ap/environment/epa-rule-puts-arizona-plants-on-track-to-upgrade/nS8B2/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353093269816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:14:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353094336683-19</Id><Title>Obama, leaders talk fiscal cliff compromise VIDEO</Title><Msg>Obama, leaders talk fiscal cliff compromise VIDEO By REID J. EPSTEIN | 11/16/12 11:10 AM EST Updated: 11/16/12 2:24 PM EST President Barack Obama and Congressional leaders Friday struck a conciliatory tone and appeared to point the way to compromise as they met face-to-face for the first time in the fiscal cliff negotiations. But the debate remains over the details, which neither House Speaker John Boehner nor Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell got into as they declared themselves open to raising new revenues after their meeting at the White House. Boehner told reporters he’s willing to deal and sent a message to House Republicans that they must appear that they are willing to consider a compromise. “To show our seriousness, we’ve put revenue on the table as long as its accompanied by significant spending cuts,” Boehner said. “While we’re going to continue to have revenue on the table, it’s incumbent for my colleagues to show the American people that we’re serious about cutting spending and solving our fiscal dilemma.” McConnell, who will be negotiating with more Republican senators in the lame duck than he’ll have come January, issued a stronger caveat about forcing spending cuts. “We’re prepared to put revenue on the table provided that we fix the real problem,” McConnell said, “even though most of my members without exception believe that we’re in the dilemma we’re in not because we tax too little but because we spend too much.” Increasing tax rates on the wealthy was a cornerstone of Obama’s reelection campaign, and he’s said several times since the election that he remains committed to allowing the Bush tax cuts to expire at year’s end on income greater than $200,000 for individuals and $250,000 for couples. Republicans have resisted, with an argument that’s taken shape around parsing the difference between raising rates and raising revenues. The meeting included discussion of topic that so far has been absent from the debate: revenue targets. Top lawmakers on Capitol Hill have been hesitant to discuss how much money should be raised from reforming the tax code — a key question that will guide the contours of the upcoming negotiations. To reach those targets, Boehner wants to “create simple mechanisms, in statute, that would achieve those revenue and spending goals. They would be in place unless or until more thoughtful policies replace them,” an aide to the speaker said. In essence, Boehner seems to be signaling he wants another legislative trigger to ensure Congress does its job. The last trigger Congress created was the dreaded sequester. Almost as if they were speaking from the same notes, Boehner, McConnell, Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid and House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi all pronounced the meeting “constructive” — a word that also appeared in a statement from the White House press secretary released later in the day. Obama kicked off the Friday meeting with a pledge to finally make the progress that’s been promised for months. “I think we’re all aware that we have some urgent business to do and we’ve got to make sure that taxes don’t go up on middle-class families, that our economy remains strong, that we’re creating jobs and that’s an agenda that Democrats and Republicans and independents, people all across the country share,” Obama said, with Boehner sitting beside him, as the meeting began. “So our challenge is to make sure that we are able to cooperate together, work together, find some common ground, make some tough compromises, build some consensus to do the people’s business.” Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid and House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi each focused on the urgency of reaching an agreement before year’s end. Reid said the congressional leaders would work through the Thanksgiving recess and are prepared to meet Obama again when they return. A White House official said Obama and congressional leaders will meet again during the last week of November. “We’re both going to have to give up some of the things that we know are a problem,” Reid said. “There’s no more, let’s do it some other time. We’re going to do it now. I think we feel very comfortable with each other and this isn’t something we’re going to wait until the last day of December to get it done.” Pelosi said the deadline to reaching a deal should be “before Christmas.” “We understand our responsibility there, we understand that it has to be about cuts,” she said. “It has to be about revenue. It has to be about growth. It has to be about the future. So as we cut investments and as we talk about revenue, we have to do so in a way that promotes growth and supports the future.” Obama was joined by Vice President Joe Biden, chief of staff Jack Lew and National Economic Council Director Gene Sperling. Republicans in the House and Senate are, to varying degrees, set against increasing tax rates, though some have signaled this week that they would be open to other means of collecting more revenue from the wealthy. Obama pledged action Friday. “What folks are looking for and I think all of us agree on this, is action,” the president said. “They want to see that we are focused on them, not focused on our politics here in Washington. So my hope is that this is going to be the beginning of a fruitful process where we’re able to come to an agreement that will reduce our deficit in a balanced way — that we will deal with some of these long-term impediments to growth, and we’re also going to be focusing on making sure that middle-class families are able to get ahead.” politicoDOTcom/news/stories/1112/83973.html?hp=l1</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353094336683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:32:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353095215196-20</Id><Title>God Bless The Socialist States of America</Title><Msg>and when exactly will the middle class MARCH ON DC, and PICKET THE W. H. ??? i pray for a Bloodless Revolution</Msg><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1353095215196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:46:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353100553835-21</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless The Socialist States of America</Title><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1353095215196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The voters had their chance this last election. It appears that alot of voters (both Republican and Democrat) did not vote, or voted for a 3rd party candidate. Plus the voters kept the Demoncraps in control of the Senate and the Republicans in control of the House. Accordingly, I think the majority of US voters are not to the point of voting the Demoncraps out of power and this is because a majority of voters are living off of taxpayer dollar funded welfare and other gifting programs provided by the Demoncraps. ObamaClause is alive and well this Obamas (I would call it Christmas but I don't want to tarnish Christ's name with Obama). Anyway, the USA is "stick a fork in it - it's done". What we weill all witness over the next 4 years will prove that the majority have voted their demise. Thanks Demoncraps! Hope you are accumulating lead and gold, because something bloody comes our way in the future.</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1353100553835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 16:15:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353105870790-22</Id><Title>Hoeven, Baucus Lead Senators in Calling for Keystone XL Meeting with President</Title><Msg>Hoeven, Baucus Lead Senators in Calling for Keystone XL Meeting with President Senators: The Election is Over, it's Time to Move forward with Keystone XL Jobs Nov 16 2012 WASHINGTON, D.C. – North Dakota Senator John Hoeven and Montana’s senior U.S. Senator Max Baucus led a bipartisan group of 18 senators today in calling for a meeting with President Obama to urge action on the Keystone XL Pipeline project. “The election is over, people want us to work together to create jobs, and one sure way we can create jobs right now is by moving forward with construction on the Keystone XL Pipeline,” Baucus said. “We’ve spent more than four years producing studies and addressing environmental and property concerns – there’s no excuse to keep Keystone jobs on hold any longer.” “The Keystone XL pipeline represents not only thousands of jobs and growth for the nation’s economy, but also a big step toward American energy independence,” Hoeven said. “We can become energy independent in America within five to seven years, but we must commit to moving forward with important projects like the Keystone XL pipeline.” Earlier this week, the International Energy Agency predicted the United States is on track to surpass Saudi Arabia as the world’s largest oil producer in about five years and will become self-sufficient in energy production by 2035. The Keystone XL Pipeline would carry Montana and North Dakota oil from the Bakken and other oil-bearing formations. The following Senators joined Baucus and Hoeven’s letter: Richard Lugar (R-Ind.), Republican Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.), Kent Conrad (D-N.D.), Kay Bailey Hutchison (R-Texas), Mary Landrieu (D-LA), Lisa Murkowski (R-Alaska), Mark Pryor (D-Ark.), David Vitter (R-La.), Jim Webb (D-VA), Jon Tester (D-Mont.), John Barrasso (R-Wyo.), Mike Johanns (R-Neb.), Kay Hagan (D-N.C.), Mark Begich (D-Alaska), Joe Manchin (D-W.V.), Rob Portman (R-Ohio). Complete text of the letter follows below. November 16, 2012 The Honorable Barack Obama President of the United States The White House 1600 Pennsylvania Ave NW Washington, District of Columbia 20500-0003 Dear Mr. President: With the elections of 2012 behind us, we write to remind you of the continuing importance of the Keystone XL Pipeline. We want to work together to keep creating jobs, and Keystone XL is one vital piece of the puzzle. We would like to meet with you in the near future to discuss this important project. Setting politics aside: Nothing has changed about the thousands of jobs that Keystone XL will create. Nothing has changed about the energy security to be gained through an important addition to the existing pipeline network built with sound environmental stewardship and the best modern technology. Nothing has changed about the security to be gained from using more fuel produced at home and by a close and stable ally. And nothing has changed about the need for America to remain a place where businesses can still build things. We hope that you will follow through on your directive of March 22, 2012, to federal agencies to move forward vital energy infrastructure like Keystone XL. The state of Nebraska is nearing completion of the new pipeline route within Nebraska. With that process near completion, we look forward to an affirmative determination of national interest soon. We then urge you to issue a Presidential Permit immediately afterward. Thank you for your consideration, and we look forward to your response. Sincerely, Max Baucus (D-Mont.) John Hoeven (R-N.D.) Richard Lugar (R-Ind.) Republican Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) Kent Conrad (D-N.D.) Kay Bailey Hutchison (R-Texas) Mary Landrieu (D-LA) Lisa Murkowski (R-Alaska) Mark Pryor (D-Ark.) David Vitter (R-La.) Jim Webb (D-VA) Jon Tester (D-Mont.) John Barrasso (R-Wyo.) Mike Johanns (R-Neb.) Kay Hagan (D-N.C.) Mark Begich (D-Alaska) Joe Manchin (D-W.V.) Rob Portman (R-Ohio) hoevenDOTsenateDOTgov/public/index.cfm/2012/11/hoeven-baucus-lead-senators-in-calling-for-keystone-xl-meeting-with-president</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353105870790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 17:44:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353106770544-23</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless The Socialist States of America</Title><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1353095215196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be a worthy prayer...............................</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1353106770544</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 17:59:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353107371669-24</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless The Socialist States of America</Title><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1353095215196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Voter fraud.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1353107371669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 18:09:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353107423481-25</Id><Topic><Title>God Bless The Socialist States of America</Title><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1353095215196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When america fails maxipad will be prosecuted.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1353107423481</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 18:10:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353107486134-26</Id><Topic><Title>It's So Nice To Be The Winner...</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1352943416616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 20:36:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This just in: What you won is your demise and, it has nothing to do with politics rather, a destructive idelogy that is engineered to to steal your meal ticket. Enjoy your victory! You deserve to win your loss.................................................</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1353107486134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 18:11:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353108694407-27</Id><Topic><Title>It's So Nice To Be The Winner...</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1352943416616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 20:36:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wahleee boy just wants his welfare so he can survive. The bondholders just want their debt paid back. The Treasury market is trading as if the government will collect the tax too as some point, which it can easily do in the years ahead with Democrat victory after Democrat victory. You have got the benefit of speculating and profiting off someone else's money in all your business dealings so far - now you will pay...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353108694407</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 18:31:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353109565642-28</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TAX</Title><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1353092434217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:00:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Saint" Grover has decreed that the GOP cannot make a deal - tax rates must be cut to increase revenues instead, something that Romney ran on, Romney lost on, and which Obama has said is a non-starter So, no I don't expect a deal to be reached. What I think will happen is the negotiations will collapse, Obama will tell Boehner the way it will be and not to return to the White House until he agrees to his terms... Boehner and the GOP can then have the rest of the year to pass as many balanced budget amendments as they want and as many GOP budget plans and tax cuts as they want, all the while the country heads off the Fiscal Cliff. In January when the taxes go up and the spending cuts come, Obama will be in a good position to ram his agenda through with the full wrath of the American people behind him - the crashing stock market, caused by the GOP, will be a good stick. Then comes the debt ceiling war. Humiliating the GOP on the Bush Tax Cuts will be the pre-show warmup to that,</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353109565642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 18:46:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353111429521-29</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TAX</Title><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1353092434217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:00:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without major cuts to entitlements, we are headed to 2nd world status. More taxes on the rich is only a drop in the budget deficit bucket. Even if they come to an agreement and make a deal to avoid the financial cliff, the next debt ceiling is coming up in early 2013..... plus another downgrade by moody's will be enough to bring growth to a stand still, Liberals are very generous, especially when they use other people money with their generosity. Entitlements are the real thorn in America's side.... not lack of taxes on the rich. The bottom feeder entitlement junkies are the ones crying the loudest about how the rich should pay more. Well *#@&amp;@% them and the horse they rode in on. If it was up to me, they wouldn't have the right to vote unless they paid taxes.....like the rest of us. If you don't like it move to Greece, Mexico or Cuba. EOM</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1353111429521</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 19:17:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353114139654-30</Id><Topic><Title>NEW TAX</Title><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1353092434217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:00:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is already more than a trillion dollar budget deficit even without the spending increases promises under Medicare. That will need to be closed by more taxes. The U.S. pays only about 1/2 as much tax per GDP as other developed countries. Then there is the matter of the $16 trillion in debt, plus other obligations like Fannie/Freddie, run up by year after year of paying only about 1/2 as much in taxes as other advanced countries. Quite simply, that is a revenue problem, solved by more taxes, GOP propaganda notwithstanding. Then there is the matter of the entitlements. It is unlikely the math will ever work for the current Healthcare System. The solution to that will be how they fixed the problem of rising prices for basic necessities during World War II: rationing, price controls, and government allocation of the resources. That approach will result in the nationalization of the health care system, as the only way doctors and other providers will be able to stay in business is to work for the government and let the government shield them from trial lawyers, and the welter of health plans and the waste of money, time, and overhead to negotiate the payment of bills, etc...</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353114139654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:02:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353114488370-31</Id><Title>Transmission project using area wind power set for completion in 2013 - “Power users will have more availability to renewable energy with this project,”</Title><Msg>Transmission project using area wind power set for completion in 2013 There are three transmission line projects in progress in the South Plains, including the Silverton to Cottonwood line running from Briscoe County to Dickens County east of Lubbock, according to a July progress report provided by the Public Utility Commission of Texas. Posted: October 9, 2012 - 5:46pm | Updated: October 10, 2012 - 11:17pm By Adam D. Young AVALANCHE-JOURNAL Hundreds of miles of high-voltage transmission lines are set to be placed and powered up next year as part of a $7 billion statewide project to transmit West Texas’ renewable energy to the state’s urban centers in the east. The transmission project is part of a statewide competitive renewable energy zone initiative approved by the Texas Legislature in 2005 and aimed to eventually transmit about 18,500 megawatts of wind power from wind farms across the Panhandle and West Texas to such metro areas as Dallas, Austin and San Antonio, said Bobbie Searcy, a spokeswoman for the Electric Reliability Council of Texas. The project will build about 2,400 miles of high-voltage transmission lines, including 200 miles crossing South Plains counties to create a grid expected to be completed by 2013. “Power users will have more availability to renewable energy with this project,” said Terry Hadley, a spokesman for the Texas Public Utility Commission. “Ultimately, it means more availability and access to a wider array of fuel generation for electricity.” The state currently has more than 10,000 megawatts of wind generation capacity, creating an opening for wind developers to provide an additional 8,500 megawatts to put the renewable energy zone grid to capacity, Hadley “There is room now to have more wind development in West Texas and the Panhandle,” he said. Construction of the transmission lines was bid out to private companies in 2010 and 2011, including Austin-based Wind Energy Transmission of Texas, which is expected to complete about 375 miles of line in West Texas. Wayne Morton, general manager of Wind Energy Transmission of Texas, said he expects his company’s West Texas lines, including a 74-mile stretch from Dickens County to Scurry County, to be finished by mid-2013. There are three transmission line projects in progress in the South Plains, including the Silverton to Cottonwood line running from Briscoe County to Dickens County east of Lubbock, according to a July progress report provided by the Public Utility Commission of Texas. Construction on the Silverton to Cottonwood line is about 27 percent complete, with about 20 of its 65 miles of high-voltage line installed. The project’s estimated cost is $113 million, with an estimated completion date in December. Other projects in the South Plains include the 74-mile Cottonwood to Dermott line from Dickens to Scurry County southeast of Lubbock, estimated at $142 million, and the 46-mile Nazareth to Silverton line from Castro County to Briscoe County. Both have no miles complete by July but were expected to be finished by December 2013. lubbockonlineDOTcom/local-news/2012-10-09/transmission-project-using-area-wind-power-set-completion-2013#.UKVcl2eG6So</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1353114488370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:08:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353116338183-32</Id><Title>More union payoffs</Title><Msg>The nation’s largest federal employee union has blocked the U.S. Air Force from implementing basic fitness standards for civilian police officers at Joint Base Andrews, home to Air Force One. The 1401 Chapter of the American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE) objected to new fitness standards ordered by the Department of Defense (DOD) in April 2012 because base officials did not consult the labor group before implementing the rule. The chapter comprises a small portion of the union’s 600,000 national members and represents police officers on the base. The union challenged the base in front of an arbitrator and claimed the new standards represented a “change in working conditions.” Such a change would subject the provision to collective bargaining. Base officials offered to take union proposals under consideration, but refused to bargain on the Pentagon order. “[The order] is a Department of Defense wide regulation which [is not] subject to bargaining with this [u]nion,” the Air Force said. The arbitrator affirmed that the Air Force’s 11th Wing, which manages base operations including security, did not have to consult the union before implementing orders that came from the Defense Department. The union appealed to the Federal Labor Relations Authority (FLRA), an independent arbiter akin to the National Labor Relations Board that attempts to settle labor disputes for federal employers and employees. FLRA Chairwoman Carol Waller Pope and former AFL-CIO attorney Ernest DuBester found in favor of the union and sent the issue back into arbitration. President Barack Obama appointed Pope and DuBester. “An agency violates the [Civil Service Law] when it expressly refuses to negotiate over a matter within the duty to bargain,” the FLRA ruling said. “An agency may not refuse to bargain merely because the matters…[are] subject to negotiations at a higher organizational level.” However, the Air Force appears to have consulted other federal employees unions before issuing the new standards. The Air Force negotiated the standards with the National Association of Government Employees (NAGE), which told its members that it had been able to work with the military to implement the standards. “Management has demonstrated a willingness to jointly work with Local Union Officials to develop, through Impact and Implementation Negotiations, a Fitness Program with Installation Fitness Personnel, if civilian Police Officers would like a more structured fitness program,” the union’s April newsletter said. NAGE is a branch of Service Employees International Union, which pumped more than $70 million into Democratic election efforts in in 2012. NAGE representatives did not return requests for comment. “The Obama administration is very tied to the union movement, particularly the more liberal groups like the SEIU, so it’s no surprise that he’d work with them [over other groups],” said Steven Allen, a labor expert at the Capital Research Center. The new plan will require police officers to perform 19 push-ups in two minutes—two fewer than its previous 21-push-up requirement—and eliminate the sit-up and 300-meter sprint examinations from the 2011 fitness test. The 17:30 cut-off for the mile-and-a-half run will remain unchanged. The unions are fighting to preserve the three paid hours of exercise that civilian security personnel can use each week despite the weaker standards. Several labor experts told the Washington Free Beacon the dispute is more about procedure than policy. “That is not an uncommon thing for the union to challenge,” said J. Justin Wilson, managing director of the labor watchdog Center for Union Facts. “When businesses unilaterally impose practices, even if they are reasonable, the union is going to demand negotiation even if they agree with it.” The issue is back in arbitration and it is unclear when the matter will be settled. A base spokesman declined to comment because of ongoing negotiations with the union. AFGE did not return multiple requests for comment.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353116338183</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:38:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353116390513-33</Id><Title>Debt Collection Service "Jobs"</Title><Msg>That is basically the role of those who work hard sitting on their couch and vote for politicians who will impose taxes to pay all of W's and Reagan's unpaid bills and debts. These hard working Americans collect a percentage of the take, called entitlements, food stamps, etc, derived from the Treasury's collection efforts. Really its best to think of the Treasury as a business - as indeed the Exchequer which it is based on was in the beginning... It started out as England Inc, about 1000 years ago, with the King as the CEO. His nobles helped collect the taxes from the real income producers - the peasants utilizing the power of Royal Sheriffs if need be. The Nobles and Sheriffs would sit back and cream off a share of the tax/rent for themselves - much like the couch potatoes of today. They devised nice titles to call themselves, and fancy armor and privileges too...lol Nobody can be expected to work for free either, that would not be just...Collecting taxes and supporting a government, and voting to keep it strong is hard work. LOL</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1353116390513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:39:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353116845356-34</Id><Title>More of the same</Title><Msg>A former West Virginia county commissioner was sentenced to 21 months in prison for his role in a 2010 voter fraud case, ABC Charleston reports. Thomas Ramey Jr. pleaded guilty in August to lying to a federal agent in an attempt to hide his part in a primary ballot scheme two years ago.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353116845356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:47:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353117074014-35</Id><Title>NYT Unsure if Rockets Fired at Israel Also not sure Hamas is a terrorist group</Title><Msg>New York Times Middle East correspondents Fares Akram and Isabel Kershner reported today that they are confused about current events in the Middle East. Despite the launching of more than 800 rockets from Gaza into Israel in 2012—including hundreds in the past week—the Times expressed uncertainty about whether any rockets have been fired at all. The Israeli military operation that commenced today is “in response to what Israel called repeated rocket attacks,” according to the Times. The Times is also uncertain about the nature of Hamas, a U.S.- and Israeli-designated terrorist organization. The Times reports that Hamas is a “militant organization regarded by Israel as a terrorist group sworn to Israel’s destruction.” The Times’ description is contradicted by Hamas, the leaders of which regard Hamas as a terrorist group sworn to Israel’s destruction. “This is a nation of martyrdom and martyrdom-seeking,” said Hamas’ leader Ismail Haniyah, who perhaps was chastising the New York Times for liberal bias. “A nation of jihad for the sake of Allah,” he affirmed. Hamas parliamentarian Ahmad Bahr added, “O Allah, vanquish the Jews and their supporters.” He concluded, “O Allah, vanquish the Americans and their supporters. O Allah, count their numbers, and kill them all, down to the very last one.” Abdallah Jardu, another Hamas official, also contradicted the New York Times. The Jews “want to present themselves to the world as if they have rights, but, in fact, they are foreign bacteria—a microbe unparalleled in the world,” he said. Jardu concluded, “May [Allah] annihilate this filthy people who have neither religion nor conscience.”</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353117074014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:51:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353117173674-36</Id><Topic><Title>More of the same</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353116845356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:47:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Former New York state assemblyman Jimmy K. Meng pleaded guilty in a bribery case Wednesday, according to the New York Times: Jimmy K. Meng, a former state legislator from Queens, admitted in court on Wednesday that he had solicited $80,000 from a friend facing criminal charges and falsely claimed that he could use that money to bribe prosecutors. Mr. Meng, 68, of Bayside, pleaded guilty to one count of wire fraud during a hearing before Judge Allyne R. Ross of Federal District Court in Brooklyn. Sentencing is set for March 12, and Mr. Meng’s lawyer, Todd D. Greenberg, said that he hoped the judge would spare Mr. Meng any jail time because this was the “first time in his 70 years that he had a lapse in judgment.” … In the courtroom, Mr. Meng was barely audible at times and occasionally turned to a Mandarin interpreter seated next to him to help explain the legal terminology. But when asked whether he had read the plea agreement, Mr. Meng, who had said during the hearing that he had a hearing problem and had relied on sleeping pills for 40 years, said in English: “Everything — two times,” before later stating, “I plead guilty.” Prosecutors will recommend he serve 12-18 months in jail. His daughter is Grace Meng. She was elected to the United States Congress last week and will be the first Asian-American representative from New York. Democratic Representative-elect Meng did not attend her father’s hearing.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353117173674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:52:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353117345254-37</Id><Topic><Title>NYT Unsure if Rockets Fired at Israel Also not sure Hamas is a terrorist group</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353117074014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:51:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Global media are portraying the terrorist group Hamas as the victim as Operation Pillar of Defense, the state of Israel’s attempt to stop rocket attacks from the Gaza Strip, gets underway. The Thursday cover of the Washington Post featured a picture of a Gaza man clutching the dead body of his infant son at a hospital, as the Post caption says, “after an Israeli airstrike in Gaza City.” However, the implication that the child died at the hands of Israelis has never been verified by credible sources. Hamas has fired hundreds of crude, unguided rockets from Gaza at Israel over the past 24 hours, and it is common for some of those rockets to land in Gaza. Hamas is also known for its “work accidents” in residential areas from mishandling weapons and explosives. The Palestinians in the Gaza Strip and West Bank are also known to have manipulated, and in some cases invented, accounts of civilian casualties because of the media sympathy such stories generate. It is unclear how the infant in the photo died. For the Washington Post, however, the verdict is in: Israel did it. Similarly, the New York Times‘ first story on the Israeli operation insinuated that Hamas rocket attacks had been simply made up by Israel as a pretext for attacking. The paper said that Hamas’ longstanding goal of destroying the Jewish State was merely an Israeli assertion. It called Israel’s long-delayed response to ceaseless rocket attacks on its civilians “a ferocious assault.” The BBC reported live from Gaza by filming a parade of “wounded” Palestinians who were obviously play-acting for the cameras. The practice has become so common practice that pro-Israel activists have made up a name for it: Pallywood. Honest Reporting, a media watchdog, shows one “wounded” man from the BBC broadcast walking around confidently only moments after he was carried through the streets, his body limp, by several helpers.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353117345254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:55:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353117459119-38</Id><Title>The most open administration in history</Title><Msg>Republican members of the House Committee on Science, Space, and Technology called for an investigation into the alleged use of secret email addresses by top Obama administration officials, including Environmental Protection Agency administrator Lisa Jackson, in letters released Friday. Members of the House Science Committee demanded information on the secret email addresses from Jackson and expressed concerns that conducting official business through such means may violate the Federal Records Act, Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), the Presidential Records Act, and other transparency laws. “The use of alias and private accounts that are hidden from staff responsible for retaining and providing access to records calls into question the fidelity of previous responses to not only the public through FOIA, but also to the Office of the Inspector General as well as Congress,” Republican committee members said in a statement. Chris Horner, an attorney and senior fellow at the Competitive Enterprise Institute (CEI), first alleged the use of secret email addresses by Jackson and other administration officials. Horner said top administration officials set up numerous secret email addresses to conduct official businesses in an effort to shield their communications from disclosure under the Freedom of Information Act. As previously reported by the Free Beacon, Horner and CEI have filed a FOIA lawsuit against the agency seeking disclosure of the email addresses and their content. The suit cites an internal EPA memo first revealed in a 2008 Government Accountability Office report which describes secondary email accounts known only to a “few EPA staff members, usually only high-level senior staff.” The Daily Caller later reported Horner had discovered that “Richard Windsor” was one of the aliases Jackson was using. The committee letters were sent to Jackson, the White House Counsel, the director of the White House’s Office of Science and Technology Policy, and the inspectors general of the EPA, Energy Department, and Commerce Department. The EPA did not respond to requests for comment.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353117459119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:57:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353117604731-39</Id><Topic><Title>The most open administration in history</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353117459119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 20:57:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden, White House pressured green energy loan, contrary to Obama’s statement, emails show Vice President Joe Biden and the White House pressured the Department of Energy to issue a loan guarantee in 2010 for a wind farm in Oregon, undermining the president’s claim of political neutrality in the loan process, according to emails released recently by a key congressional committee. The Department of Energy (DOE) issued numerous loans to support businesses as part of the 2009 stimulus. In an interview before the election, the president hailed the loans program for creating “jobs all across the country” and asserted that decisions about the loans are “made by the Department of Energy, they have nothing to do with politics.” Internal emails released on Oct. 31 by the House Oversight and Government Reform Committee suggest a different story, however. The Energy Department’s loan guarantee to Caithness Energy’s Shepherds Flat wind farm project in Oregon was approved after the application of significant pressure throughout the vetting process from high-level officials, including from the White House and the office of the vice president. “[The] emails indicate that senior administration officials—including those at the White House—were involved in approving specific projects, applying inappropriate pressure on career employees,” said Ali Ahmad, communications adviser to the Oversight and Government Reform Committee. If the Caithness Energy project were to go through, it would be one of the largest wind farms in the world—a fact that the Loan Program Office’s website prominently highlights now. The Obama administration trumpets its commitment to green energy projects but has few successes to tout thus far compared to the billions of taxpayer dollars spent. One of the earliest mentions of the Shepherds Flat wind farm in the released emails is an exchange dated July 27, 2010, between several Energy Department officials, including the Loan Program Office Executive Director Jonathan Silver. One email said: “We need to figure out how to properly characterize Shepherd’s [sic] Flat as WH is considering whether to have top principal involved.” The conditional guarantee of the loan was issued Oct. 8, 2010, just over two months later, according to Sustainable Business Oregon. It is unclear exactly who the White House’s “top principal” is and why the White House was getting involved in the loan so early in the process. DOE Loan Program Office Chief Credit Advisor Jim McCrea wrote on Sept. 2, 2010, “Shepherd’s [sic] Flat has been transmitted to OMB. I am starting transmittal to Treasury.” The Department of the Treasury played an advisory role in making the loan guarantees and the Office of Management and Budget ultimately approved them. There is no indication that they had received any information on the Shepherds Flat project before the beginning of September, raising further questions about why the White House was considering getting involved so early. McCrea sent an email time stamped 1:18 AM a week later indicating that Biden was applying pressure for the loan while it was still under consideration. McCrea wrote, in part, “Pressure is on real heavy on SF due to interest from VP.” An email later that day from McCrea confirmed the loan has not been approved and implied that there was pressure for the Shepherds Flat loan to proceed. McCrea wrote in an email later that morning: Also, as we go through the Shepherds Flat process with both OMB and Treasury, we will get a lot more questions as you know. We are going to have to be very fast in turning around responses and sending them to both. To do otherwise, will leave us firmly on the political path and give the agencies an opportunity to blame us when they are pressures [sic] to make decisions. As you all know, the pressures to make decisions on this transaction are high so speed is of the essence. McCrea does not indicate where the “pressures to make decisions” came from, but his earlier email indicates that the vice president was turning up the heat on the departments. An email dated Sept. 27, 2010, with the subject line “Calculations for Treasury—Shepherds Flat” indicated that a “big meeting” took place at the White House on Sept. 24, 2010 between the Departments of Energy and the Treasury, as well as the Office of Management and Budget. The Department of Treasury raised substantive questions about the loan, implying that the loan deal was still not completed when the departments convened at the White House. It is unclear why the meeting about an unfinished loan deal occurred at the White House, given President Barack Obama’s assurance that decisions about the loan were made by the Department of Energy. The Department of Energy did not return a request for comment. A later email reveals the White House had a special interest in this project and was directly encouraging the departments to complete the loan. Energy Secretary Steven Chu’s Chief of Staff Brandon Hurlbut wrote an email to Silver on Sept. 30, 2010: “Wh decided chu and geithner need to speak first thing in morning to make sf announcement happen.” Hurlbut requested that Silver draft some talking points for Chu. One of the talking points said, “We need to get the Shepherds Flat deal done so that the President can make it the centerpiece of his radio address on Saturday.” This email implies that political pressure at least sped up the completion of the loan. “The loan program set out to pick winners and losers using taxpayer funds,” Ahmad said. “Supposed safeguards for keeping politics out of decisions were repeatedly ignored.” “Politicization is the reason the loans are there in the first place,” said David Kreutzer, an energy economics expert at the Heritage Foundation. Kreutzer testified about the loan program before the House Subcommittee on Energy and Power earlier this year. He said the Department of Energy used two criteria for making the loans. “The first criterion was that projects should be commercially viable. The second was that those seeking funding must demonstrate that the projects cannot get private financing,” he said in testimony. “There’s no intersection there,” Kreutzer told the Washington Free Beacon. Commercially viable projects can receive private financing, he said. Caithness Energy’s political action committee has donated heavily to Democrats. It contributed $10,600 to campaigns in the 2008 cycle, all to Democrats; it donated $31,857 in 2012, 88 percent of which went to Democrats. “If the politics weren’t involved, we wouldn’t have the loans in the first place.”</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1353117604731</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 21:00:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353117848923-40</Id><Title>Past Quotes</Title><Msg>If you don't read the newspaper you are uninformed, if you do read the newspaper you are misinformed. A nation to try to tax itself into prosperity is like a man standing in a bucket and trying to lift himself up by the handle. A government which robs Peter to pay Paul can always depend on the support of Paul. A liberal is someone who feels a great debt to his fellow man, which debt he proposes to pay off with your money. Foreign aid might be defined as a transfer of money from poor people in rich countries to rich people in poor countries. Giving money and power to government is like giving whiskey and car keys to teenage boys. Government's view of the economy could be summed up in a few short phrases: If it moves, tax it. If it keeps moving, regulate it. And if it stops moving, subsidize it.</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1353117848923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 21:04:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353120019558-41</Id><Title>NYT = Propaganda Arm of Hamas</Title><Msg>Obama is supported by a propaganda apparatus similar to that found in the former Soviet Union.</Msg><Username>carrieanneamerica</Username><Timestamp>1353120019558</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 21:40:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353121451388-42</Id><Title>Wage Earners Suffer Badly Since Reagan But Especially Since Bush</Title><Msg>As wages remain stagnant since 2002, the past ten years have been effectively been a "lost decade for workers," says writer Kevin G. Hall. Wages for median working-age men have decreased 4 percent since 1970. (Photo by Official U.S. Navy Imagery via Flickr) Despite adequate coverage of the rise and fall of employment rates, little has been said about the actual rate of earnings, which—after adjusting for inflation—have reportedly declined across most industries and sectors since the Great Recession. "Equally troubling," Hall writes in the McClatchy report, is that "real wages are now about the same level as they were in December 2005." According to researchers at the Brookings Institute's Hamilton Project, the median working-age man with a job earns about 4 percent less, when adjusted for inflation, than he did in 1970. “A key thing is that from the 1970s up to 2000, middle income . . . families didn’t get their fair share, but they still saw some growth. Since 2000, nothing,” said Heidi Shierholz, a labor economist at the Economic Policy Institute. "This idea of a ‘lost decade,’ it’s already happened. We’re well into our next lost decade." McClatchy writes that there are a number of explanations for the declining earnings: One is that the Federal Reserve successfully tamed inflation, so wages aren’t racing to keep pace with rising prices. Another is the decline in labor unions, whose members enjoyed higher wages and better benefits. Yet another explanation is that productivity—a worker’s output per hour—has improved greatly thanks to computers, automation and other breakthroughs. Productivity’s role in falling real wages is a subject of debate in economic circles, partly because workers used to share in the benefits of rising productivity but have shared less so over the past decade. Regardless, it seems that real wages have been on a mostly downward slope for more than 40 years which—according to New York economist Martin Kohli—makes economic recovery more difficult "because without wage growth, it’s harder for Americans to pay down their debts."</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1353121451388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 22:04:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353122709786-43</Id><Topic><Title>BUY MJNA - Medical Marijuana Inc ... There is a hope in recovering your losses !!!</Title><Username>mr_vopni</Username><Timestamp>1353037761193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 22:49:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buy mjna</Msg><Username>mr_vopni</Username><Timestamp>1353122709786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 22:25:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>