<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343368927000-1</Id><Title>U.S. Auctioning Tracts Off East Coast To Wind Farm Developers</Title><Msg>U.S. Auctioning Tracts Off East Coast To Wind Farm Developers David Quilty | 26 July, 2012 | Wind Some Massachusetts residents may be busy dealing with the Cape Wind Project off their own coast, but residents up and down the eastern seaboard could soon have some new neighbors in the form of offshore wind farms. The U.S. government is planning to auction off an area encompassing 2,434 square miles in the Atlantic Ocean to developers of wind farms, opening up the continental shelf for the projects 10 miles offshore. The area encompasses a wide swath of the east coast, totaling 1.5 million acres of open ocean from Massachusetts to Virginia. The auction is scheduled to take place before year’s end and interested developers are doing what they can to avoid the angry divisions surrounding the Cape Wind Project, including studying wind farm effects on marine life and migratory birds. The American Wind and Wildlife Institute, a partnership between wildlife conservation groups and the wind industry, is working to make sure concerns from both sides are heeded. “Cape Wind really helped focus attention on what we didn’t know and what we needed to know for offshore wind in order to estimate risk,” said Taber Allison, director of research at the American Wind and Wildlife Institute. While the development and construction of any offshore wind turbines on the east coast is probably years away, the federal government is interested in pursuing the technology in order to meet the country’s energy needs. Wind farms in the Atlantic ocean could generate more than 1,000 GW of power per year, and we need to start now if we are to ever ween ourselves off fossil fuels and replace them with renewable energy sources. “We’re not a new technology — the offshore wind industry has been operating in Europe since 1991,” said Jim Lanard, president of the Offshore Wind Development Coalition. “The U.S. is two decades behind. To catch up, we have to make big investments, just like nuclear, oil, gas and coal had to make big investments at the start.” We definitely have a lot of catching up to do and while there is seemingly always some controversy surrounding offshore wind farms, this new plan could be just what the doctor ordered. At 10 miles off the coast, the turbines would be barely (if at all) visible to the naked eye and if the environmental studies pan out, I hope development starts sooner rather than later. http://revmodo.com/2012/07/26/u-s-auctioning-tracts-off-east-coast-to-offshore-wind-farms/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343368927000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 02:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343369075000-2</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Auctioning Tracts Off East Coast To Wind Farm Developers</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343368927000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 02:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bring on the offshore wind power, US enviros demand Posted on July 26, 2012 - 10:10 by Pete Danko, EarthTechling Keep the pressure on, Mr. President - that was the message recently from a broad coalition of US environmental movers and shakers hopeful of seeing wind turbines sending clean power ashore as soon as possible. "For the sake of our environment and the prospects of a vibrant clean energy economy in America, we must have numerous wind farms spinning off our shores within the next few years – and we need your continued leadership to make that vision a reality," some 217 environmental groups and stakeholders said in a letter to the president [PDF]. The coalition credited the Obama administration for finally putting offshore wind on the energy radar in the United States, but pointed to the striking contrast between Europe and the U.S.to make its point that more needs to be done here. The U.S. Department of Energy says the country could easily deploy 54 gigagwatts of offshore wind capacity by 2030, but so far, none has gone in. Meanwhile, Europe is going great guns on offshore wind: According to the European Wind Energy Association [PDF], as of the end of June, Europe had 1,503 grid-connected offshore wind turbines in 56 wind farms across 10 countries, for a total capacity of 4.3 GW. The U.S. Department of the Interior's "Smart from the Start" program is unfolding, and areas for wind development have been identified off Massachusetts, Rhode Island, New Jersey, Maryland, Delaware and Virginia, with the Carolinas next in line for assessment. The program's goal is tackle the daunting environmental and bureaucratic challenges in a systematic way that avoids the stop-start, lawsuit-ridden process that has characterized the Cape Wind project off Massachusetts. Earlier this month, the administration published an environmental assessment for commercial wind leases and site assessment off Rhode Island and Massachusetts that "puts Interior in position to offer this area as one of the nation's first offshore competitive lease sales before the end of the year," the Department of the Interior said. But even that won't ensure offshore wind power will soon be on its way. As Offshore Wind Wire reported recently, "If and when a lessee is prepared to propose wind energy generation on its lease, the lessee would submit a Construction and Operation Plan (COP) for Bureau of Ocean Energy Management approval. If a COP is submitted, BOEM would then prepare a separate site- and project-specific NEPA analysis to evaluate the potential environmental and socioeconomic consequences associated with the proposed project when considering whether to approve, approve with modification, or disapprove the COP." http://www.tgdaily.com/sustainability-features/64952-bring-on-the-offshore-wind-power-us-enviros-demand</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343369075000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 02:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343369087000-3</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. Auctioning Tracts Off East Coast To Wind Farm Developers</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343368927000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 02:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that doesn't even get into the financing side of the question, which only appears increasingly daunting given Congressional reluctance to maintain incentives for renewable energy development. While much attention has been focused on the expiring production tax credit for wind power, a key priority for the wind power industry ingeneral, the coalition said "offshore wind energy needs a long-term extension of its investment tax credit." Sens. Tom Carper (D-Del.) and Olympia Snowe (R-Maine) introduced just such a measure last year – it would continue the 30 percent tax credit for the first 3,000 megawatts of wind placed into service – but have failed to push the legislation to passage. Skepticism that this new call for action will have much impact is understandable, but at the very least it shows an environmental community united on the necessity to move forward on offshore wind. The range of groups behind the letter was impressive, including national heavyweights like the National Wildlife Federation, Greenpeace, the Sierra Club and the League of Conservation Voters, high-profile regional groups and leaders along the East Coast, and even the New Jersey group Grandmothers Mothers and More for Energy Safety.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343369087000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 02:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343378362000-4</Id><Title>Chinese corporations win this bid</Title><Msg>Chicoms leasing major ports and other key US properties as US debt translates into lost sovereignty to globalist cabal.</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1343378362000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 04:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343398463000-5</Id><Title>bp raising divy -bloomberg</Title><Msg>BP, Europe’s second-largest oil producer, might boost its payout to shareholders by 14 percent to 7 cents a share, according to Bloomberg Dividend Forecasts that factor in earnings and options prices. http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-07-27/bp-eni-may-increase-dividends-next-week-fresnillo-might-reduce.html</Msg><Username>tagthatstock</Username><Timestamp>1343398463000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 10:14:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343403378000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report July 26, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343324196000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 13:36:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending July 25, 2012 Release Date: July 26, 2012 | Next Release: August 2, 2012 In the News: U.S. Net Natural Gas Imports Through First Third of 2012 Lowest Since 1990Through the first four months of 2012, U.S. net imports (imports minus exports) of natural gas averaged just 4.5 billion cubic feet (Bcf) per day, down 26 percent from the corresponding period in 2011 and the lowest first third-of-year average since 1990. On an annual basis, U.S. net natural gas imports rose gradually from the late 1980s and peaked at over 10 Bcf per day in 2007. However, net imports have fallen sharply, the result of reduced imports and growing exports driven largely by significantly increasing domestic production associated primarily with shale gas development. Pipeline shipments from Canada are by far the leading source of U.S. natural gas imports. Liquefied natural gas (LNG) is an important secondary source, but higher natural gas prices in competing overseas markets are attracting spot LNG cargoes that can be delivered under flexible pricing terms. Overview: (For the Week Ending Wednesday, July 25, 2012)•Natural gas prices increased by double-digit amounts at most trading locations over the report week, with a few exceptions in the Northeast. The Henry Hub spot price rose from $2.84 per million British thermal units (MMBtu) at the beginning of the report week on July 18 to $3.19 per MMBtu on July 25. •At the New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), the near-month (August 2012) natural gas contract rose 9.7 cents to $3.07 per MMBtu. •Working natural gas in storage rose last week to 3,189 billion cubic feet (Bcf) as of Friday, July 20, according to the U.S. Energy Information Administration's (EIA) Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report (WNGSR). An implied storage build of 26 Bcf for the week positioned storage volumes 487 Bcf above year-ago levels. •The natural gas rotary rig count, as reported July 20 by Baker Hughes Incorporated, fell by 4 to 518. The oil rig count fell by 13 to 1,414. more summary data Prices: Natural gas prices rose over the report week at most spot market locations. The Henry Hub price increased from $2.84 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.19 per MMBtu yesterday. The largest price increases occurred in the Rocky Mountain area; for example, the spot price at the Opal Hub in Wyoming rose 51 cents from $2.48 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $2.99 yesterday. Various trade press and analysis reports have cited infrastructure issues in the price increases in the Rockies. A number of recent maintenance projects in the Rockies have limited outflow capacity, and recovery from maintenance provided support for prices. Prices at a few Northeast trading points, particularly Tennessee Pipeline's Zone 4, fell during the week, reflecting infrastructure constraints. This week, spot prices at Tennessee's Zone 4 in the Marcellus Shale dropped from $1.84 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $1.39 per MMBtu yesterday. Prices at this trading point have, in the past several months, diverged from Henry Hub prices as Marcellus natural gas production has outpaced available takeaway capacity. This report week marked the first time in 2012 that Henry Hub prices crossed the http://www.eia.gov/naturalgas/weekly/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343403378000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 11:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343403478000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report July 26, 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343324196000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 13:36:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weekly U.S. Coal Production Overview July 26, 2012 Report No.: DOE/EIA 0218/29 Report Released: July 26, 2012 http://www.eia.gov/cneaf/coal/weekly/weekly_html/wcpweek.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343403478000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 11:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343403742000-8</Id><Title>Low GDP = More Free Crack from Ben</Title><Msg>Ben is XOM's Best. Friend. Forever!</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1343403742000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 11:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343416795000-9</Id><Title>$100 per share</Title><Msg>It's coming... $$$ :) XOM!</Msg><Username>jorgey54</Username><Timestamp>1343416795000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 15:19:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343424095000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Should the American taxpayer keep subsidizing the richest company on the planet?</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1343421507000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 16:38:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What subsidies are you refering to? I bet you haven't the first clue. It's just political propaganda that you blindly buy in to.</Msg><Username>poutywouty</Username><Timestamp>1343424095000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 17:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343427045000-11</Id><Title>Groups battle over request from ranchers to ease ethanol rule</Title><Msg>Groups battle over request from ranchers to ease ethanol rule By Zack Colman - 07/27/12 12:44 PM ET Interest groups on both sides of the corn ethanol debate are stepping up their messaging on an Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) rule that lawmakers have targeted in recent weeks. The groups are battling over the renewable fuel standard (RFS), which requires http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_D/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=5067&amp;tid=20231&amp;mid=20231&amp;tof=1&amp;frt=2</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343427045000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 18:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343430995000-12</Id><Topic><Title>$100 per share</Title><Username>jorgey54</Username><Timestamp>1343416795000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 15:19:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it will split before $100.</Msg><Username>merisland2000</Username><Timestamp>1343430995000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 19:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343431750000-13</Id><Title>Enbridge gets OK to reverse pipeline flow east</Title><Msg>Enbridge gets OK to reverse pipeline flow east National Energy Board approves change with safety conditions attached CBC News Posted: Jul 27, 2012 7:12 PM AT Last Updated: Jul 27, 2012 8:16 PM AT Read 11 comments11 Pipeline giant Enbridge Pipelines Inc. will be allowed to reverse the flow on a portion of its Line 9 pipeline between Sarnia and Hamilton to flow east, the National Energy Board has decided. Enbridge applied last August to reverse approximately 194 kilometres of pipeline between the Sarnia Terminal (at Sarnia, Ont.) and the North Westover Pump Station (near Hamilton, Ont.) to flow in an eastward direction. Federal Labour Minister Lisa Raitt welcomed the board's decision saying it would bring more Western Canadian crude to eastern markets and reduce dependence on imported oil. "Energy is a matter of national importance and our government welcomes efforts to better utilize our immense energy assets for the benefit of all Canadians," the former natural resources minister said in a written statement Friday. "Energy is key to supporting the standard of living and quality of life for all Canadians. Over the past five years, the oil and gas industry has contributed an average of $22 billion a year to government revenues ... to help pay for everything, from education and health care to roads and bridges," added Raitt, who was speaking on behalf of Natural Resources Minister Joe Oliver. The board agreed to the pipeline reversal with 15 conditions, most having to do with pipeline integrity. Landowners, environmental and aboriginal groups had the opportunity to express their views with respect to the safety of the pipeline and possible impacts resulting from any possible accident or malfunction during public hearings which took place in London, Ont., in May. The project involves infrastructure additions and modifications at four existing sites along the pipeline segment. The reversal is expected to cost $16.9 million. Premiers talk pipelines, national energy strategy Earlier in the week, P.E.I. Premier Robert Ghiz and New Brunswick Premier David Alward said they would push for a west-to-east pipeline that could carry unrefined bitumen to refineries in eastern Canada. "New Brunswick is very open to seeing a pipeline come from Alberta to Saint John and the refinery there," Alward said, speaking from a premier's conference in Halifax. "We're open for business and we're looking forward, if there is a business case, to seeing that come here." The premiers have started to work on a national energy strategy led by Alberta Premier Alison Redford, but B.C. Premier Christy Clark said she's not interested in discussing a national strategy until Redford and the federal government sit down with her to address her conditions for the Northern Gateway pipeline project. The Northern Gateway project is a proposal by Enbridge to build two pipelines stretching 1,177 kilometres between the Alberta oilsands and Kitimat on B.C.'s west coast. http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/prince-edward-island/story/2012/07/27/pol-enbridge-pipeline.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343431750000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 19:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343433749000-14</Id><Title>XOM: It's close to a 52 week high. Good time to sell? YES/NO? I have a boatload of it.</Title><Msg>Thanks</Msg><Username>readyforwhat7</Username><Timestamp>1343433749000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 20:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343437583000-15</Id><Title>B.C. premier won't sign national energy strategy until pipeline dispute resolved</Title><Msg>B.C. premier won't sign national energy strategy until pipeline dispute resolved By Alison Auld, The Canadian Press July 27, 2012 7:30 PM HALIFAX - British Columbia Premier Christy Clark refused Friday to join her provincial counterparts in crafting a national energy strategy, insisting that a public feud over the Northern Gateway pipeline has to be resolved before she can proceed. Clark stepped out of meetings at the Council of the Federation in Halifax to make the announcement as premiers tried to cobble together a pan-Canadian strategy on energy and before they broke for their final news conference. She said she wouldn't endorse a deal before discussions take place with Ottawa and Alberta over how B.C. would be compensated for allowing the $6-billion pipeline to carry heavy oil to the B.C. coast to be loaded onto tankers bound for Asia. "British Columbia will not be participating in any of those discussions until after we've seen some progress that our requirements for the shipment of heavy oil will be met," she told a hastily called news conference. "It's not a national energy strategy if British Columbia hasn't signed on." Clark and Alberta Premier Alison Redford have been locked in an intractable dispute over economic benefits associated with the megaproject proposed by Enbridge (TSX:ENB), with Clark saying the sides must talk before there can be any movement. She said the two had a "very frank discussion" about it Friday morning, but didn't reveal details or if they planned on holding further talks on the matter. Redford has said she sees no point in talking since the pipeline project is a private venture and British Columbia has to decide on its own how to proceed with trying to secure more revenue from it. At the closing news conference, Redford said the lack of unanimity on a national energy plan wasn't something that concerned her. "I don't think we should lament the fact that we're not all the way there yet," Redford said. "I think we should actually celebrate a tremendous amount of success in that we had almost every premier in the country talking about the fact that we need to come together and talk about how to grow Canada's energy economy." But after much talk going into the meeting of co-operation and the evolution of a pan-Canadian energy strategy, the premiers appeared to leave with little more than the creation of a working group of premiers that will build on a 2007 plan. Still, the host of the annual meeting, Nova Scotia Premier Darrell Dexter, said he wasn't disappointed in the results of the gathering, which addressed health care, transfer payments, changes to employment insurance and aboriginal issues. He said the work of the council can continue despite the tussle between Alberta and B.C. "I would like to see that work that we're doing as a bridge over any kind of division," he said. Clark has said she decided to ask for an unspecified share of benefits from the Northern Gateway after doing analysis on the development, which will move bitumen from Alberta to the B.C. coast for shipment to Asia. Her government has released five conditions she says need to be met before she can move forward with the pipeline. In addition to the demand for a greater portion of the economic benefits, they include the completion of an environmental review now underway, assurances that the "best" responses will be available for potential spills on land and at sea, and that aboriginal rights will be recognized. http://www.thestarphoenix.com/news/Premier+Christy+Clark+derails+forge+national+energy+strategy/7000373/story.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343437583000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 21:06:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343437594000-16</Id><Topic><Title>B.C. premier won't sign national energy strategy until pipeline dispute resolved</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343437583000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 21:06:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clark repeated her position that the province bears too much risk from oil spills at sea or on land, while receiving only eight per cent in tax benefits. She added another wrinkle to the feud when she called on Ottawa on Wednesday to sit down with her and Redford to hash out the issue. Foreign Affairs Minister John Baird responded bluntly by questioning Clark's stance and reiterating the federal government's support for the project. Redford has flatly dismissed Clark's position as one that would "fundamentally change Confederation" because it would mean new negotiations for projects throughout the country. According to research in an application filed by Enbridge, 8.2 per cent of the Northern Gateway's projected $81 billion tax revenue would flow to B.C. over a 30-year period. That equates to $6.7 billion for B.C., while Ottawa is expected to receive $36 billion and Alberta would earn $32 billion. Saskatchewan is expected to top the remainder of the provinces in terms of tax benefit, receiving about $4 billion. Enbridge's proposed 1,177-kilometre twin line would carry heavy oil from Alberta across a vast swath of pristine B.C. wilderness and First Nations territory to a port at Kitimat, B.C., for shipment to Asia. Last week, the company announced it will shore up $500 million in safety improvements. Next year's Council of the Federation meeting will be held in Niagara-on-the-Lake, Ont.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1343437594000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 21:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343446422000-17</Id><Title>GM: Still $42B in the Hole</Title><Msg>Taxpayers on the hook for billions despite Obama’s claims to the contrary http://freebeacon.com/gm-still-42b-in-the-hole/</Msg><Username>infernal.equinox</Username><Timestamp>1343446422000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 23:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>