<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-07"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354856439186-1</Id><Title>DECEMEMBER 7, 1941--PEARL HARBOR, HAWAII!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>PASS THE WORD, PLEASE REMEMBER?</Msg><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1354856439186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:00:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354856530482-2</Id><Title>Feds may weigh in soon on Keystone XL</Title><Msg>Feds may weigh in soon on Keystone XL Published: Dec. 6, 2012 at 6:51 AM LINCOLN, Neb., Dec. 6 (UPI) -- A preliminary decision on the planned Keystone XL oil pipeline is expected from the U.S. State Department relatively soon, an official said. Nebraskans this week expressed opinions regarding the latest route proposal through the state from TransCanada, the company planning the pipeline. Nebraska regulators last month published a draft evaluation report for the pipeline, saying a route proposed by TransCanada avoids the ecologically sensitive Sand Hills. A State Department official was quoted by the Omaha (Neb.) World-Herald as saying a federal environmental impact statement on the route was expected "in the near future." Nebraska Gov. Dave Heineman has authority over pipeline decisions in his state. The State Department makes the final decision, however, because the pipeline would cross the U.S. border with Canada. Jane Kleeb, executive director of project opponent Bold Nebraska, said the new route is "no better" than TransCanada's previous proposals. "TransCanada is still risking our aquifer and still risking the fragile sandy soils of our state," she said in a statement. Supporters of the project say it would support U.S. energy security and the economy. Opponents have expressed concern over a series of pipeline spills and the environmental consequences of exploiting tar sands oil, the type of crude designated from Keystone XL. upiDOTcom/Business_News/Energy-Resources/2012/12/06/Feds-may-weigh-in-soon-on-Keystone-XL/UPI-15921354794673/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354856530482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:02:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354856789106-3</Id><Title>Oregon considering 'clean fuel' rules; critics say gas prices would rise</Title><Msg>Oregon considering 'clean fuel' rules; critics say gas prices would rise By Scott Learn, The Oregonian on December 06, 2012 at 5:29 PM, updated December 06, 2012 at 5:31 PM Oregon's Environmental Quality Commission gets to deal with two hot-button issues --global warming and gas prices -- in one package today, as commissioners take their first swing at setting new rules for "clean fuels." Authorized by the 2009 Legislature, the clean fuel standards would require suppliers and distributors to cut the carbon in car and truck fuels 10 percent a gallon by 2025. Supporters include the Oregon Environmental Council, the state's ethanol and biodiesel producers and the Oregon chapter of the American Lung Association. They say the program would foster home-grown biofuels, reduce dependence on foreign oil and address climate change. But opponents say the mandates ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354856789106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:06:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354856882636-4</Id><Topic><Title>dr Demento does a Palin</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1354850932063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 22:28:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt it--she would have to resign guv/then the lt guv would have to appoint her to the position the lt guv is not her guy as her lt guv got booted on ethics violations (S Carolina gop--shock) and there is notta lotta love between nikki and lt guv mcconnel -- he could appoint 1 of his buds instead of her so other than that risk she is very unpopular and will have tough relection for guv she knows there is no way can win senate race. but all that aside--in 2014 there will be 2 senate races and guv race in S Car--the politicals hacks like rove will move there--its their dream come true</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1354856882636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:08:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354857186665-5</Id><Title>Offshore Wind Developer May Set Up Shop in New Jersey</Title><Msg>Offshore Wind Developer May Set Up Shop in New Jersey Move could nudge dream of Jersey dominance of offshore wind closer to reality By Tom Johnson, December 6, 2012 in Energy &amp; Environment|2 Comments The developer of a proposed offshore wind transmission backbone is looking at putting a manufacturing facility in the port of Paulsboro, a move that might bolster New Jersey’s efforts to become the hub of the offshore wind sector along the Eastern Seaboard. “We’re committed to working in New Jersey,’’ said Bill Wall, director of marine operations for Atlantic Wind Connection. The Google-backed proposal intends to establish a 300-mile-long transmission system to serve offshore wind farms. “We’re going to build an industry in New Jersey,’’ he added. There are a lot of big "ifs" associated with the proposal, including whether the state can come up with a workable funding mechanism to help offshore wind developers line up financing for their projects. Still, the AWC statement is the first time anyone has publically vowed to build a manufacturing facility for offshore wind in New Jersey. The Christie administration and lawmakers have proposed developing 1,100 megawatts of generating capacity from wind farms off the Jersey coast, but the efforts have been mired in bureaucratic delays at both state and federal levels. The delays have drawn criticism from clean energy advocates and even raised questions privately among offshore wind developers as to whether the state’s commitment to the technology is real. But Wall remains bullish about the sector, speaking at a conference on renewable energy in New Brunswick. The gathering was sponsored by the New Jersey Institute for Continuing Legal Education, a division of the State Bar Association, “It’s the perfect landing for offshore wind,’’ Wall said, referring to plans to begin the backbone off the coast of Jersey. There are great wind resources offshore; plenty of people to use the power the wind farms generate; a gently sloping ocean floor to anchor the wind turbines; and high energy costs in the region, according to Wall. Atlantic Wind Connection is looking at locating a facility in Paulsboro, where New Jersey is trying to convert a former oil refinery into a port serving the offshore wind sector. If the Paulsboro proposal goes forward, AWC would hire a contractor to manufacture and assemble the equipment it would need at hub platforms, where electricity from the offshore farms would be converted from AC into DC. The conversion is necessary to reduce loss when transmitting power to New Jersey and elsewhere, according to Wall. AWC plans to invest $2 billlion in New Jersey, including the Paulsboro project. “There’s going to be a lot of people employed in New Jersey,’’ Wall said, noting that the technology used to deploy submarine cables to bring the electricity to shore; to build wind turbines; and to establish offshore energy platforms is at least 50 years old or older. “This is not rocket science.’’ None of that will happen, however, unless the state can establish a program to direct subsidies from New Jersey ratepayers to the offshore wind farms. This would help finance the projects by awarding so-called Offshore Renewable Energy Credits (ORECs) for the electricity they produce. If Atlantic Wind Connection can show it will bring thousands of jobs to New Jersey, then hopefully the state will move forward with the OREC program, Wall said. The state has not been the only bottleneck blocking the developing offshore wind. Just last week, a bureau in the U.S. Department of Interior announced it would hold lease sales off the coasts of Massachusetts, Rhode Island, and New Jersey. State officials have said New Jersey was not included in the sales, primarily because more developers are seeking to bid on the same tracts off the Jersey coast. The sale of leases off the Jersey coast is not expected to happen until next spring, at the earliest. Others were more optimistic about the development of offshore wind. Peter Fursaro, chairman of Global Change Associates, a New York-based energy and environmental consulting firm, said wind is now cost-competitive with more conventional technologies, and investment in the sector is growing -- despite all ‘’the noise’’ in Washington. “You will see offshore wind off of Long Island and New Jersey,’’ he said. “If you don’t believe in climate change, you’ve got your head in the sand.’’ njspotlightDOTcom/stories/12/12/05/offshore-wind-developer-may-set-up-shop-in-new-jersey/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354857186665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:13:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354857708180-6</Id><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high-speed rail plan</Title><Msg>Obama pushes ahead with high-speed rail plan Washington Post Published 11:05 p.m., Thursday, December 6, 2012 WASHINGTON — Undaunted by the looming fiscal crisis, the Obama administration said Thursday that it plans to forge ahead with its signature transportation project, investing billions of dollars in a long-term effort to build a high-speed rail network. “We're not giving up on high-speed rail,” Transportation Secretary Ray LaHood said in testimony that was welcomed by a majority of members who attended the House Transportation and Infrastructure Committee hearing. “The president will include funding in his budget. I think we'll get there with public money, but in the absence of that we'll get there with private money.” mysanantonioDOTcom/news/article/Obama-pushes-ahead-with-high-peed-rail-plan-4098381.php</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354857708180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:21:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354863360170-7</Id><Title>CRUDE REALITYS</Title><Msg>We have all heard the lies of the big oil hucksters, oil is becomming harder ,and harder to find, oil will only go higher, Demand will only increase, But my favorite lie they spew is that Brent crude will reach 150 a barrel by 2014! LOL Sure and Santa claus will buy me a new Mercedes Benz by Xmas lol Fact, more and more oil is being discovered and captured in never before though of places such as Afrika Russia, Brazil, Canada, which i still believe contains the most crude in the world, and finally in the good ole USA Shale oil will be retrieved worldwide, technology has surpassed demand expectations. Witness the massive contents of the Bakken formation in the US ! Canadien oil sands up north alone could provide 40 years or more of US demand alone! Do not forget the capacity of offshore drilling as well. Beyond 10.000 ft of ocean is now obtainable. Demand you ask? Oh yes, the hucksters other big lie, China buying and India, will provide demand for 150 crude LOL Please, purchasing a new SUV, or midsize vehicle is a pipedream for 90 percent of the population of China or India. 4 dollars a day buys you what they can afford now, a new or slightly used bicycle LOL The fortunate 10 percent purchase 30 mpg vehicles or more. And guess what? The weekend trip to the sea is financially out of the question for them, I been to China. Spent 2 weeks theyre last year. Just because demand is theyre for new vehicles does not equate for purchases, they can only dream about. Finally, here in the USA, what many energy companies do not want you to know is this, WTI prices are hugely inflated at current prices. 88 WTI price? Give me a break, Demand continues to go down, 2013 will see another 3 to 5 percent decline in oil demand. Largely driven by 30 mpg vehicles or more. Nat gas vehicles are now being designed, yes nat gas, Chrysler plans to sell them in 2014. two of them as i speak will be available in 2014. Yet WTI at 88? HMM we have heard the rumours of price collusion at the Nymex, we have heard the reasons WTI goes up 2 dollars or more in a day, Middle East concerns are the reason the media claims LOL But my favorite reason they give is the economy is getting better in the US LOL 30mpg vehicles and more being sold but they jack up the price anyway on nonsense. I guess if your allowed like the Nymex boys to order millions of barrels of oil, then cancel within 30 days of delivery to hike the price, ANYTHING and Everything goes. Mark my words here people who doubt me on this , if the Obama administration were to make regulations stating that if you must take delivery of ordered oil at the Nymex, without having the option of cancelling you would see a 10 to 20 percent decline in WTI within a month! Whos kidding who here? Remember 2009? i do i remember WTI at 30 a barrel lol Yes 3 yrs ago WTI was at 30 a barrel, LOL Credit was stopped orseverly witheld for many many Americans. Fear of the great depression descended upon us, Nymex boys didnt have the credit, or a nicer term margin if you prefer to bid up oil/ Now in 2012 economy better and banks need interest on theyre money so up and up goes WTI From30 a barrel to 88 a barrel in 2012. LOL Big oil will say its the demand LOL Finally those of you in xom are fortunate for now, hedging, purchasing of politicians, lol and i must confess more shareholder friendly than past mgmt have given you great returns, But the future may not be as kind to you, good luck to all of you</Msg><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1354863360170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 01:56:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354864664112-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high-speed rail plan</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354857708180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bravo, greatnews, more jobs</Msg><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1354864664112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 02:17:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354864931837-9</Id><Topic><Title>Feds may weigh in soon on Keystone XL</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354856530482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:02:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a matter of time, politicians want theyre donors happy! Will only add to oil glut, but American consumers should see lower prices. Bakken producers of crude will be in for a crude AWAKENING when the pipeline gets approval. They NEED 70 WTI price of oil to make any money. LOL</Msg><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1354864931837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 02:22:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354866288971-10</Id><Topic><Title>DECEMEMBER 7, 1941--PEARL HARBOR, HAWAII!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1354856439186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:00:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i will dont worry</Msg><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1354866288971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 02:44:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354877570675-11</Id><Topic><Title>DECEMEMBER 7, 1941--PEARL HARBOR, HAWAII!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1354856439186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:00:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can you forget, roosevelt set them poor souls up to get us into the war. Seems like someone else in the WH doing the same.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354877570675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 05:52:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354877616665-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high-speed rail plan</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354857708180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354877616665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 05:53:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354877754355-13</Id><Topic><Title>Serves them right</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354821035350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:10:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ #$%$ POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354877754355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 05:55:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354877817750-14</Id><Topic><Title>Serves them right</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354821035350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 14:10:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a #$%$ big mouth. He will go hungry in his cardboard box.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354877817750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 05:56:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354880340503-15</Id><Title>Bundesbank Sees the Future</Title><Msg>and it doesn't look good for Germany and Europe. But I believe Germany could fair better than the USA because they have a better politicians leading their country and an overall better work ethic than does the USA. Below is from a Reuters article this morning. I believe the referenced "widespread uncertainty" is not knowing what will Obama and the Demoncraps do next to harm the economic conditions in the USA, and therefore the world. "Germany's Bundesbank cut its growth outlook on Friday and now expects the euro zone's largest economy to barely grow in 2013, while it also pointed to risks of a recession as the euro zone debt crisis takes its toll. The Bundesbank expects Germany's economy to grow just 0.4 percent next year, down from an earlier forecast in June of 1.6 percent. The move comes a day after the European Central Bank cut its forecasts for next year, pointing to weaker growth prospects for the bloc's core countries such as Germany, France and the Netherlands. Germany has been a key growth driver of the euro zone, now in its second recession since 2009, but the country's resilience to the crisis is wearing thin and the central bank's new projections reflect this. "Given the difficult economic situation in some euro-area countries and widespread uncertainty, economic growth will be lower than previously assumed," the Bundesbank said."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354880340503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 06:39:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354883192423-16</Id><Topic><Title>Bundesbank Sees the Future</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354880340503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 06:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zieg Hiel! You are a good little fascist..</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1354883192423</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 07:26:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354885531758-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high-speed rail plan</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354857708180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's meant to save energy for a greener planet, especially here in California.</Msg><Username>sugar4u2see</Username><Timestamp>1354885531758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 08:05:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354886087753-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high-speed rail plan</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354857708180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The price of the California bullet train continues to rise according to the Los Angeles Times. Prior to project revisions, a high-speed train in California was supposed to cost an estimated $43 billion with an end date in 2020. However, according to recent reports, the revised plan, which is supposed to be unveiled later today, would quote the cost at $98.5 billion with an end date in 2033".</Msg><Username>commishfree1</Username><Timestamp>1354886087753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 08:14:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354888396124-19</Id><Topic><Title>CRUDE REALITYS</Title><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1354863360170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 01:56:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see new developments in energy, especially natural gas a problem for some investments with oil companies. I am long XOM &amp; COP and both are big players in the natural gas game. I am really not worried about either company for the long term and I wouldn't be too worried about the other major oil &amp; gas companies for the foreseeable future either, at least in my opinion.</Msg><Username>johnh834</Username><Timestamp>1354888396124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 08:53:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354890679575-20</Id><Topic><Title>CRUDE REALITYS</Title><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1354863360170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 01:56:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reality is, is that it costs a pile of Dineros to drill safely, possibly frack, pipeline (if you can get it permitted), and deliver it to your doorstep, in a Refined state. I would say that 50 bucks is the new floor for Oil, and if the Middle East doesn't settle down in the next year or two, 75 will be a cheap price to pay. China is taking every Bbl they can buy from Saudi and Iraq forward at 85/bbl. Buy XOM on dips</Msg><Username>cmontx</Username><Timestamp>1354890679575</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:31:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354891693779-21</Id><Topic><Title>Composite Indicators Signal</Title><Username>geniesulsgcz</Username><Timestamp>1300639590000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-03-20 12:46:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks.</Msg><Username>wglimberd</Username><Timestamp>1354891693779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:48:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354891949925-22</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement for XOM. **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>hilton.steinhoff</Username><Timestamp>1354711843447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 07:50:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trusting.</Msg><Username>stanleysanchez83</Username><Timestamp>1354891949925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:52:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354891975075-23</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement for XOM. **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>hilton.steinhoff</Username><Timestamp>1354711843447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 07:50:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trusting.</Msg><Username>stanleysanchez83</Username><Timestamp>1354891975075</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:52:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354892151893-24</Id><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high speed rail plan</Title><Msg>Obama pushes ahead with high speed rail plan Ashley Halsey III , The Washington Post Washington Friday 07 December 2012 Undaunted by the looming fiscal crisis, the Obama administration said Thursday that it plans to forge ahead with its signature transportation project, investing billions of dollars in a long-term effort to build a high-speed rail network. "We're not giving up on high-speed rail," Transportation Secretary Ray LaHood testified before a congressional committee. "The president will include funding in his budget. I think we'll get there with public money, but in the absence of that we'll get there with private money." LaHood's testimony was welcomed by a majority of members who attended the House Transportation and Infrastructure Committee hearing, including a number of Republicans who have expressed varying degrees of skepticism about high-speed rail in the past. Rep. John Mica, R.-Fla., who will step down as committee chairman next month, cautioned that money is tight. "I have been one of the strongest proponents in Congress of transportation and passenger rail, but in these days of trillion-dollar deficits, we have a responsibility to ensure that the taxpayers' money is wisely invested and that we move forward responsibly with any transportation improvements," Mica said. GOP support fell short of unanimous, however, with two California Republicans whose districts would be crisscrossed with the first proposed line speaking out against it. "Maybe it's time to cut our losses and pay down our debt," Rep. Kevin McCarthy told the committee. "I have real doubts about the viability and the cost. Just because we've [already] invested money doesn't mean we have to invest more." Rep. Jeff Denham, who in June pushed through the House legislation to ban federal spending on high-speed rail in California, questioned the price tag for the concept, in his state and nationwide. "It would be a fun thing to have," he said, "but can we afford something that would be a fun thing?" The Obama administration launched the high-speed rail program using about $8 billion in economic stimulus funding. The first project — a $68 billion link between San Francisco and Los Angeles — has yet to break ground. It is projected to take 15 years to complete the 520-mile line. More than 150 proposals related to the creation of a high-speed rail system have been funded, most of them to link major population areas on the two coasts and in the Midwest. Concern over whether their states would be left holding the bag if federal funding dried up, Republican governors in Florida, Ohio and Wisconsin rejected federal funding for high-speed rail plans for their states last year. Bringing that service to the Northeast expeditiously was supported Thursday by two Washington area Democrats — Del. Eleanor Holmes Norton, D.C., and Rep. Donna Edwards, Md., — who said the administration's long-term goals would benefit if the public saw more immediate progress. Norton suggested launching a pilot program to garner public support. "I'm not convinced that we know how to do it because we haven't done it," Norton said. "There will be huge criticism of the administration for having nothing to show for its efforts in five years." "We need to get started," Edwards said. "I know when the interstates were being built there were areas that didn't want them. Who doesn't want a highway now?" independentDOTcoDOTuk/news/world/americas/obama-pushes-ahead-with-high-speed-rail-plan-8392373.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354892151893</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:55:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354894139983-25</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>Dow up 50-XOM down again. Company starting 5th year of drastic underperformance. Management very skilled at destroying shareholder wealth (XTO, terrible exploration and production results under Tillerson's management.)</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1354894139983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:28:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354894308851-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high speed rail plan</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354892151893</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 09:55:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course we will forge ahead and with taxpayer money. After all, who is the largest railroad owner these days that stands to benefit? Warren Buffet and wasn't he one of Obumers biggest campaign contributers. Also can't leave out the railroad unions.</Msg><Username>jake.legge</Username><Timestamp>1354894308851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354894542682-27</Id><Topic><Title>Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1354894139983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:28:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>think what it would look like if its price reflected the American net national savings rate of about -$450 billion/year, instead of the Chinese savings rate of +$2,500 billion/year. The Chinese are bidding long term bonds, and all variety of dollar assets pushing money into the tulip mania as they attempt to save each year what Americans took two decades in the past to save. Eventually the bubble will collapse as they drive down the price level in the goods market they sell in, and inflation up in China with money printing to sustain their undervalued currency and +$2,500 billion savings rate..</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354894542682</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:35:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354895223990-28</Id><Title>Gold Crash Coming</Title><Msg>The China and the Arabs have a net national savings rate of nearly $4 trillion/year between them (about 60% of that is China and 40% oil profits created by Chinese demand). Much of that is being vented into the world market as both the Chinese and Arabs use it to buy financial assets. They are certainly buy stocks and bonds hand over fist running those markets into a massive bubble, but they are buying gold too... There is not enough liquidity in the stock market, or even in the bond market, to absorb that many buy orders. So they are buying gold. If you are a gold bug or stock tulip junkie you had better hope China can keep saving so much. In the past they were unable to save even a tenth of what they are saving now, and the peculiar mix of circumstances that allow them to save so much now will not last forever</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354895223990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 10:47:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354896624667-29</Id><Topic><Title>Bundesbank Sees the Future</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354880340503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 06:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Germany is saving about 300 billion euros/year on net basis after depreciation. There is very little unemployment. In Austria and Switzerland there is effectively no unemployment. The budget is balanced. Germany's wealth is being invested mostly domestically, and used to improve future growth prospects. Other countries are riding the wave of the Chinese Dragon, the one created by the Chinese trying to save half their GDP and put as much of it as possible into dollar bonds, stocks, and gold. The USA is blowing through around half a trillion/year of its capital stock as it saves nothing and runs down its assets. Even with the tulip mania running full force under the influence of the Chinese Dragon chasing it and the Fed pumping it, it is still not enough to create any real capital in America... The UK is a huge capital deficit too, along with Greece, Portugal, Yemem, and various other spendthrift lands.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354896624667</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:10:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354896825462-30</Id><Topic><Title>Bundesbank Sees the Future</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354880340503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 06:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obscene, wahleee boy, as always... I've got some other things to attend to... Enjoy the tulips.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354896825462</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:13:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354897557043-31</Id><Topic><Title>Bundesbank Sees the Future</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1354880340503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 06:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tulip mania, wahleee boy, like that insanely agitated little mind of yours...</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354897557043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 11:25:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354901453760-32</Id><Topic><Title>Serious Advancement for XOM. **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>hilton.steinhoff</Username><Timestamp>1354711843447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-05 07:50:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who else is?</Msg><Username>antoniogreen12</Username><Timestamp>1354901453760</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:30:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354903649914-33</Id><Topic><Title>CRUDE REALITYS</Title><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1354863360170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 01:56:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>China was saving around $300 billion/year back in 1998 when oil was about $12/bbl and they are saving over $2500 billion/year now that oil is over $100/bbl. Where did all that new savings come from? From Gobi/inner Mongolia coal, transported south to make manufactured goods, around 90 quadrillion BTUs worth/year at this point, more then 4 times the annual U.S. coal demand. The Chinese used their new coal driven industry to wipe out much of the energy intensive industry of the United States, and Europe. To prevent the money they earned going to U.S. and European goods purchases they manipulated their currency by printing yuan and imposed currency controls. They sowed the profits they earned in the process buying stocks, mortgage bonds, treasury bonds, and gold. That pushed interest rates from around 7% down to about 2-3%, and stocks like Apple up to around $700 (now down to around $500) and gold from around $300 to over $1700. Speculators just ran oil up with everything else. That is where the demand for the mortgages that run up the housing bubble came from too. The Chinese demand has simple concentrated itself more sharply into gold, stocks, and U.S. government debt now that real estate has crashed... The Chinese cannot keep this up forever. They longer they keep their currency undervalued the more inflation they will get in China, and there will be a revolution there if inflation increases food &amp; energy prices as it surely will... If they allow their currency to rise in value their export surplus will evaporate, and their savings rate will plummet, and the markets they have been bidding with their savings from gold, to oil, to bonds will collapse...</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354903649914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:07:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354904987176-34</Id><Topic><Title>CRUDE REALITYS</Title><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1354863360170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 01:56:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"if the Obama administration were to make regulations stating that if you must take delivery of ordered oil at the Nymex, without having the option of cancelling you would see a 10 to 20 percent decline in WTI within a month!"--that is prob true but not possible (WAY too much rules/regs involved and to single out 1 futures/commodity from others prob won't happen. what could easily be done with a lot/maybe same effect is to raise margin req for crude oil futures (this gets the nonsense out of the mkt and back to the people that are involved/not speculators)--I think what you want/stated but a very easy approach. I have read that the big boys are now req to only put up 10% on the dollar--dunno if that is true but if margin reqs were put back to 50% + it would end the nonsense. You can see where that was done with silver--marg reqs and the result. exactly what should be done with crude. Tillerson said oil price is about 25-30 $/bbl speculation--that is ridiculous .</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1354904987176</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:29:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354906530236-35</Id><Title>FCX short squeeze to 34s</Title><Msg>load up gang</Msg><Username>jjohns8181</Username><Timestamp>1354906530236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:55:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354907828945-36</Id><Topic><Title>CRUDE REALITYS</Title><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1354863360170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 01:56:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EXCELLENT ANALYSIS</Msg><Username>michaelkosanovichkosanovich</Username><Timestamp>1354907828945</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 14:17:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354908831592-37</Id><Topic><Title>FCX short squeeze to 34s</Title><Username>jjohns8181</Username><Timestamp>1354906530236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 13:55:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The price of that stock mirrors the price of Guangdong bound seaborne coal almost perfectly from 1998 to 2012. In other words it reflect the commodity/asset price bubble being created by China's communist government. The China story presents many difficulties going forward. One is the impossibility of them increasing their coal demand and savings much, as there is simply not enough good markets left to saturate, plus it is a geologic impossibility for the Chinese to keep increasing coal extraction at such a pace. Second, the bigger the asset price bubble builds across the stock, bond, mortgage, gold, copper, oil, and other markets being influenced by China the harder it is to sustain it. The inflated asset prices discourage savings which reduces demand for assets over time, and the cheap money encourages more production of basic commodities and other goods which will utterly wreck the markets China is inflating, and the markets China is selling into to fuel the bubble. The terms of trade are not on the side of the Chinese; their success actively undermines them. Don't think this happened happened before in the past either...Although the Chinese are the biggest example to date.</Msg><Username>romanismrules</Username><Timestamp>1354908831592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 14:33:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354909795554-38</Id><Topic><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high-speed rail plan</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354857708180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who will be there to use it? With a high tax rate and the new Panama Canal expansion things like the port strike (and UNIONS ) will be a thing of the past. China and the Port of Antwerp are funding the expansion so ships with 12,000 containers each will go around the US. To bad Mr Buffett and your RR's.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1354909795554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 14:49:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354917509788-39</Id><Title>Deflation Steamroller</Title><Msg>Elements: 1) Surge in coal, natural gas, and industrial energy production &amp; consumption worldwide 2) Surge in world capital stock and productivity driven by rising industrial energy consumption 3) Very low labor costs in areas with the biggest leaps in industrial energy consumption and price convergence caused by trade 4) Rising population densities in urban areas, at the expense of rural &amp; suburban areas, lowering the resource use, and goods use, of societies... 5) High oil prices which speed the urbanization rate, making spatially diffuse, and resource intensive, suburban and rural living uneconomic. Crashing land values in rural &amp; suburban areas are just the start. 6) Technological growth driven along resource use reducing paths by high commodity prices. 7) Rise of Big Business worldwide which promises to increase both the rate of technological growth, and the deployment of the abundant capital to the production of goods and services. 8) The defeat of the pro-rural, pro-small business, anti-tax, anti-government coalition in America promises to bring further improvements to education, and public service provision, the practical effect of which will be to encourage big business dominance across the economy, reduce waste and duplication of services, and improve productivity. China has placed itself on an enormous treadmill where it must extract coal even more quickly just to sustain its economic momentum. Worsening terms of trade from falling manufactured goods prices and other industrial goods prices will force them to produce more and more at lower and lower prices, going forward. By tying their currency to the dollar they effectively make themselves the 51st U.S. state too as far as dollar based savings, dollar strength and prices is concerned. They will have to invest more and more in new technology to keep up with the technological arms race they are encouraging around the world with the cheap capital costs they are causing... There was a similar phenomenon in the 19th century, which hit a world already awash in capital, and reduced prices quite considerably over time.</Msg><Username>greedful_thing_s</Username><Timestamp>1354917509788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 16:58:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354919439492-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high-speed rail plan</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354857708180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And who is going to pay for that, certainly not wacko california.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354919439492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 17:30:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354919525504-41</Id><Topic><Title>Election poetry</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1352506329746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:12:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will see who gets the last laugh especially when you go hungry and there are no scraps in the dumpster.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354919525504</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 17:32:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354925549641-42</Id><Topic><Title>Election poetry</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1352506329746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:12:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raul is also your buddy wahlee stupid. BTW you sound like a c--t.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1354925549641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 19:12:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354927903075-43</Id><Title>O’Malley Reaches Out To Obama For Offshore Wind Support</Title><Msg>O’Malley Reaches Out To Obama For Offshore Wind Support 12/07/2012 | By News Editor, Shawn J. Soper OCEAN CITY -- With another General Assembly session looming, and likely another battle over proposed offshore wind farms off the coast of Ocean City, Gov. Martin O’Malley last week appealed to a higher authority for support for his proposed alternative energy agenda. In each of the last three years, O’Malley has pushed legislation aimed at fostering the development of offshore wind farms off the coast of Ocean City in order to meet Maryland’s long-term energy diversification goals and each year the bill has not been approved for a variety of reasons. Last year, the Maryland Offshore Wind Energy Act of 2012 was passed by the House by an 88-47 vote, but never came to a vote in the Senate. O’Malley has already said he will introduce similar legislation in the upcoming 2013 General Assembly session and battle lines are already being drawn on both sides of the aisle. In advance of the 2013 session, O’Malley is already attempting to line up support from some heavyweights. In a letter to President Obama last week outlining Maryland’s commitment to addressing global warming and climate change, O’Malley took the opportunity to make a plug for continued federal support for the state’s budding offshore wind energy program. “As an example of how smart policy can incent economic development and reduce our carbon footprint, Maryland has chosen to aggressively develop our vast offshore wind resources,” the letter reads. “My administration has introduced legislation to make offshore wind power a reality off Maryland’s coast.” In the letter to the president, O’Malley suggests Maryland is poised to be a leader in developing its offshore wind resources with a wind farm consisting of as many as 100 turbines just 10 miles off the coast. “This has the potential to foster a $10 billion industry in our state, providing a significant benefit to the region’s economy,” the letter reads. “And offshore wind will confront climate change head-on, generating up to 1 GW of renewable electricity from a designated lease area off Maryland’s coast, enough to power nearly 400,000 homes.” Finding a way to partner private investment with a commitment of public dollars continues to be a challenge for offshore wind in Maryland and in states up and down the coast. One of the casualties of the much-debated “fiscal cliff” the nation may be headed toward could be tax incentives for private investment in offshore wind set to expire Dec. 31. O’Malley’s letter encourages the president to intercede to ensure those tax incentives for private investment in offshore wind don’t expire as expected, and for the administration to continue to be a partner in developing the resource off the coast of Maryland and beyond. “The federal government has been a strong partner in developing this resource and we look forward to further collaboration,” the letter reads. “In particular, we encourage your administration’s continuing support for favorable renewable energy incentive policies and ask for your assistance in encouraging purchasing of offshore wind power by federal agencies and our armed forces.” O’Malley’s comments about developing offshore wind energy in Maryland came as part of a larger appeal to the president to continue to focus on climate change and global warming, particularly after the staggering effects of Hurricane, and later Super Storm, Sandy in late October. The governor pointed to Maryland as a shining example on the front lines of those efforts. “Maryland has adopted policies that leverage the strength of our people to build a brighter future,” the letter reads. “As your administration works to create jobs and protect the climate, we urge you to look to Maryland as an example or smart policy choices that help push our country forward.” O’Malley said in the letter the destruction suffered in the wake of Sandy made climate change and extreme weather more pertinent now more than ever. “The need and timeliness of preparing for the impacts of climate change, particularly those associated with extreme storms, has become more heightened following the devastation caused by Super Storm Sandy,” the letter reads. “While we were very fortunate to be spared the brunt of the storm, science tells us that we must continue to work hard to plan and prepare for the very likely possibility of more storms like Sandy in the future.” The governor said in the letter to the president Maryland has been proactive on the issues of climate change and renewable energy alternatives even prior to Sandy in late October. “To that end, I created a task force which issued a report entitled ‘Weathering the Storm’ in September 2012 that focused on specific steps that utilities, governments and other stakeholders could take to improve the resiliency of the state’s electric distribution system and emergency response,” the letter reads. “Federal, state and local government leadership is imperative if we are to adapt to the impacts of climate change.” mdcoastdispatchDOTcom/articles/2012/12/07/Top-Stories/OMalley-Reaches-Out-To-Obama-For-Offshore-Wind-Support</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354927903075</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 19:51:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354928784935-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high-speed rail plan</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354857708180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the time it's completed, if it ever is, it will only cost taxpayers a subsidy of about $500 per ticket. Another Obamao contribution to deficit reduction.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1354928784935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 20:06:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354929408710-45</Id><Title>AEO2013 Early Release Overview</Title><Msg>AEO2013 Early Release Overview Executive summary Projections in the Annual Energy Outlook 2013 (AEO2013) Reference case focus on the factors that shape U.S. energy markets through 2040, under the assumption that current laws and regulations remain generally unchanged throughout the projection period. This early release focuses on the AEO2013 Reference case, which provides the basis for examination and discussion of energy market trends and serves as a starting point for analysis of potential changes in U.S. energy policies, rules, or regulations or potential technology breakthroughs. Readers are encouraged to review the full range of cases that will be presented when the complete AEO2013 is released in early 2013, exploring key uncertainties in the Reference case. Major highlights in the AEO2013 Reference case include: Crude oil production, particularly from tight oil plays, rises sharply over the next decade The advent and continuing improvement of advanced crude oil production technologies continue to lift projected domestic supply. Domestic production of crude oil increases sharply in AEO2013, with annual growth averaging 234 thousand barrels per day (bpd) through 2019, when production reaches 7.5 million bpd (Figure 1). The growth results largely from a significant increase in onshore crude oil production, particularly from shale and other tight formations. After about 2020, production begins declining gradually to 6.1 million bpd in 2040 as producers develop sweet spots first and then move to less productive or less profitable drilling areas. Natural gas production is higher throughout the AEO2013 Reference case projection than it was in AEO2012, with natural gas increasingly serving the industrial and electric power sectors, as well as an expanding export market Relatively low natural gas prices, facilitated by growing shale gas production, spur increased use in the industrial and electric power sectors, particularly over the next 15 years. Natural gas use (excluding lease and plant fuel) in the industrial sector increases by 16 percent, from 6.8 trillion cubic feet per year in 2011 to 7.8 trillion cubic feet per year in 2025. Although natural gas also continues to capture a growing share of total electricity generation, natural gas consumption by power plants does not increase as sharply as generation because new plants are very efficient. After accounting for 16 percent of total generation in 2000, the natural gas share of generation rose to 24 percent in 2010 and is expected to continue increasing, to 27 percent in 2020 and 30 percent in 2040. In the AEO2013 Reference case, natural gas also reaches other new markets, such as exports, as a fuel for heavy-duty freight transportation (trucking), and as a feedstock for producing diesel and other fuels. Motor gasoline consumption is lower in AEO2013 relative to the level in AEO2012, reflecting the introduction of more stringent corporate average fuel economy standards; growth in diesel fuel consumption is moderated by increased use of natural gas in heavy-duty vehicles AEO2013 incorporates the greenhouse gas (GHG) and eiaDOTgov/forecasts/aeo/er/pdf/0383er(2013).pdf</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354929408710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 20:16:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354932026415-46</Id><Topic><Title>Obama pushes ahead with high-speed rail plan</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1354857708180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 00:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>taxpayer subsidy to get 1 (one) gallon of gasoline (thank you halliburton) to a army tank in the mountains of Afghanistan only 50$ but hey that punishes saddam and his nuclear weapons(did they find those YET??) AND puts cash in dick cheney pocket the inferno cheers the army waste in another country maybe the inferno will move there since he said he was leaving USA if Obama won election !!</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1354932026415</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 21:00:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354935446629-47</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Party Of Stupid Brings Nothing But Destruction to USA</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1354852507844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 22:55:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>walhieeeeeeeeee.......maybe you should refine STUPID, kind of close to home isn't it! To call anybody a filthy rat really shows your ignorance. Pity....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1354935446629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 21:57:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354936173527-48</Id><Topic><Title>The Gig Is Up At Fox</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1354675156682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 21:39:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>walhieeeeeee.....you apparently never have any idea of what you think you are talking about. Do you have any idea of what Socialism really is? I doubt it very much. If you possibly are a Christian, you better pray this doesn't happen and our freedoms are taken away. Without corporations providing jobs, wealth, and benefits, this country would go down the toilet.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1354936173527</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 22:09:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>