<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348725071300-1</Id><Title>Christy Clark writes Alberta premier Alison Redford over Northern Gateway pipeline - Clark will be in Calgary next Tuesday for private meetings</Title><Msg>Christy Clark writes Alberta premier Alison Redford over Northern Gateway pipeline By Jonathan Fowlie, Vancouver Sun September 26, 2012 6:26 PM VICTORIA — Premier Christy Clark opened the door Wednesday to restarting discussions with Alberta Premier Alison Redford over the controversial Northern Gateway pipeline. “I expect to be in Calgary early next week should you wish to discuss this issue further,” Clark wrote in a three-page letter sent Wednesday. Clark will be in Calgary next Tuesday for private meetings, her office said, and as well will speak to students at the University of Calgary’s master of public policy program. An official with the university said Clark’s office called about two weeks ago to ask if the premier could speak at the public policy school’s luncheon series, adding he expects about 40 students to attend. Clark was not available for comment Wednesday, but her spokesman said he expects about 150 students, faculty and media at the luncheon event, and that the premier hopes to use it as a platform to discuss B.C.’s interests in the project. “The primary purpose is to go and speak to Albertans about British Columbia’s position regarding Northern Gateway,” said Michael Morton. Ken Boessenkool, Clark’s former chief of staff who resigned Sunday, is a former executive fellow at the School of Public Policy at the University of Calgary. It is not clear if he was directly involved in setting up the talk. Morton added that Clark’s letter to Redford was not a formal request for a meeting, but that “if Premier Redford would like to meet, we would be happy to meet.” “It was simply a letter of protocol advising — as one head of government would do to another head of government — that I’m going to be in your province, I’m going to be in your city, and if the opportunity avails itself we would still like to discuss British Columbia’s position,” he added, saying it would be up to Redford to make the next move. Clark and Redford got into a war of words this past July over the Northern Gateway pipeline, with Clark saying she wanted to see B.C. get more of the economic benefits from the project. In her letter Wednesday, Clark reiterated the five conditions her government has set out before it will give the $6 billion pipeline its blessing. She also wrote “there are a significant number of permits required for any pipeline project to proceed in British Columbia,” a seeming suggestion that B.C. can block the project if it wants. But Clark also suggested she is open to a discussion about how the two provinces may be able to bridge the gap. “With respect to fiscal and economic benefits, it is important to note that my government has not placed any conditions on these discussions,” Clark wrote. “While others may have characterized this conversation as somehow sharing Alberta’s royalty payments, we have been careful to avoid discussing the source of any benefit-sharing, or indeed the very nature of any increased benefits to British Columbia,” she added. “I look forward to continuing a dialogue with you about opportunities to address British Columbia’s five conditions,” Clark continued. Redford’s press secretary, Kim Misik, said the offices of the two premiers had been in contact late Wednesday afternoon and Redford was willing to sit down with Clark if her schedule allowed. “That being said, our position hasn’t changed, and the talk of Alberta resource revenues are not a part of this discussion,” Misik said. “If Premier Clark wants to bring a different position to the table, if she wants to clarify a couple things, obviously that would be something we would be willing to talk to her about.” New Democratic Party house leader John Horgan said he was surprised by Clark’s approach. “The juvenile nature of it is quite surprising,” he said, adding he thought Clark’s letter was a clumsy way of communicating. “Ms. Clark is the premier of British Columbia. If she has issues with the province of Alberta and the premier of Alberta, surely to goodness adults can communicate with each other directly, rather than in a sort-of obtuse way,” he continued. “‘I’m prepared to talk to you if you’re prepared to talk to me’: It literally sounds like middle school, not like intergovernmental relations.” vancouversun</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348725071300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 01:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348736274175-2</Id><Topic><Title>Place your bets</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348610347025</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:59:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The more you "wanna bet" the younger you sound. Obama isn't winning nearly as much as Romney is losing,for the moment at least. Like you,nobody supports Obama based on his accomplishments or brilliant plans.Greece and Spain in torment thanks to austerity.Obama is cruising in the same direction.He has no serious plan to avert default and the consequences it would have the poor and middle income. And that's just one reason Obama's support is weak.A LOT of voters WANT a CHANGE IN DIRECTION.If Romney holds his own in the debates and presents a plan americans can understand those poll numbers will start shifting....fast.Obama's strategy? We already know it.Keep telling the public everything is fine and rely on Romney's image problems.And yes,I'm "betting" Romney turns the tide.In the end weather or not one puts up money will be meaningless.Like recommending a stock on these boards,all that matters is the call - it's proven right or wrong. And the day after election day winners will crow,weather they made money or not.</Msg><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348736274175</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 04:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348737968857-3</Id><Title>MITT ROMNEY WIN BY 5 POINTS ! XOM PLANT POLL 250 UNION MEMBERS AND 63% SAID THEY WILL VOTE FOR MITT ROMNEY</Title><Msg>1) romney for jobs 2) romney will protect america 3)will be a real american president</Msg><Username>usgovernment890</Username><Timestamp>1348737968857</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 05:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348742074603-4</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY WIN BY 5 POINTS ! XOM PLANT POLL 250 UNION MEMBERS AND 63% SAID THEY WILL VOTE FOR MITT ROMNEY</Title><Username>usgovernment890</Username><Timestamp>1348737968857</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 05:26:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You stupid idiot. Presidential candidates don't win by points. You prove that looneys support Romney.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1348742074603</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 06:34:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348747188663-5</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Glad We Give The Arab Countries Billions Of Dollars in Foreign Aid......</Title><Username>boston_lawyaa</Username><Timestamp>1348706263741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:37:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Slumlord Ambulance chaser you can rest knowing that we pay billions more to fly unmanned aircraft which launch missiles that murder innocent arab women and children. That must make you sooo happy. And it looks like that filthy liar Scott Brown is in trouble. He's slinging the mud like the water rat he is. He's a one term wonder.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348747188663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 07:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348749254506-6</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Glad We Give The Arab Countries Billions Of Dollars in Foreign Aid......</Title><Username>boston_lawyaa</Username><Timestamp>1348706263741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:37:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time for the nation to demand, no more f--kin $.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348749254506</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348749303705-7</Id><Topic><Title>Place your bets</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348610347025</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:59:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ you commie traitor POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348749303705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348749388369-8</Id><Topic><Title>gcoffman is a cowardly racist</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348705721663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:28:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maxidopey is a traitor and coward. He will run the other way if confronted. He is a true commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348749388369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348749492161-9</Id><Topic><Title>Step up, gcoffman</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348707372109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:56:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont worry the little sissy maxipad will run the other way like the true commie coward. But after the election I am going to kick his commie #$%$ out of america, that is if he can be found.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348749492161</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:38:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348749555898-10</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's latest announcement..........</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348706067659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:34:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listen to the commie #$%$ talk. Maxipad dosnt know his #$%$ from his face.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1348749555898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348755954800-11</Id><Title>Gas Prices Soar After Refinery Blast</Title><Msg>Gas Prices Soar After Refinery Blast Updated September 26, 2012, 3:41 p.m. ET By JERRY A. DICOLO NEW YORK—U.S. gasoline futures jumped 3.8% while crude-oil prices declined, after an explosion at a major refinery in Canada focused attention on low U.S. fuel supplies. Gasoline futures surged as high as $3.0874 a gallon on the New York Mercantile Exchange midday Wednesday after a blast at Irving Oil's 300,000-barrel-a-day Saint John Refinery in New Brunswick, Canada. The refiner said damage was minimal and operations would resume later Wednesday, but the accident highlighted the increasingly tenuous gasoline-supply situation in parts of the U.S. Fuel stockpiles in the Northeast U.S. are at their lowest level since November 1990, according to the latest Energy Department figures. "It's a reminder that gas supplies are low for this time of year, and a reminder that you have very thin margins for error," said Phil Flynn, an energy analyst at Price Futures Group. "When that story came across, it got everyone nervous, and you buy first and ask questions later." Stockpiles are at a nearly four-year low nationally, having dropped 14.2 million barrels in the past nine weeks, though demand also has fallen. Light, sweet crude for November delivery settled $1.39, or 1.5%, lower at $89.98 a barrel on Nymex, the first close below $90 since early August. Brent crude on the ICE futures exchange was 62 cents lower at $109.81 a barrel. October reformulated gasoline blendstock, or RBOB, settled 11.4 cents higher at $3.0811 a gallon, while the more actively-traded November contract rose 5.14 cents to $2.8738 a gallon. Heating oil settled near flat, down 0.18 cent at $3.1068 a gallon. The surge in gasoline prices wasn't enough to lift crude-oil futures, which were snagged by concerns about Europe's debt crisis and data that showed weak U.S. fuel demand. Oil fell after data released by the U.S. Energy Information Administration showed four-week demand for fuel products fell to the lowest level since April 6. Bob Yawger, director of energy futures at Mizuho, said he was surprised that oil prices continued to fall despite the climb in gasoline. But with U.S. stockpiles of crude oil still high, traders aren't as nervous about supplies, particularly as the broader economy shows signs of weakness. Weaker data on U.S. fuel usage arrived along with new worries about Europe. Spain roiled markets following calls for early elections in Catalonia and a decision by the Spanish prime minister to restrict early-retirement programs. Meanwhile, unions in Greece began a general strike over austerity measures, and street protests there turned violent. After surging toward $100 a barrel earlier this month on optimism about new stimulus measures from the Federal Reserve, oil prices have slumped over the past two weeks as investors grow uneasy about slowing global growth. wsj</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348755954800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348755963499-12</Id><Title>Brent Crude Surges Toward $112 on Mideast Tensions</Title><Msg>Oil leapt towards $112 a barrel on Thursday on renewed worries over potential supply disruptions from the Middle East as a war of words escalated between Israel and Iran. Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is due to issue an ultimatum to Iran when he speaks later today at the United Nations: halt a disputed nuclear drive or risk coming under military attack. Comments from Iran about "neutralizing" all efforts to sabotage its nuclear facilities had already pushed oil higher in earlier trade. "Nothing has improved in the relationship between Iran and Israel and there is unpleasantness throughout the Middle East," said David Morrison, analyst at GFT Global. "The danger is that we have a nasty flare-up." Brent crude [LCOCV1 111.47 1.43 (+1.3%) ] was trading at $111.75, up $1.71, while U.S. light, sweet crude oil [CLCV1 90.89 0.91 (+1.01%) ] gained $1.15 to trade at $91.13. Iranian President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad said in a speech before the U.N. General Assembly that Iran is under threat of military action from "uncivilized Zionists", a clear reference to Israel. Oil also gained support from data that showed crude and refined product stockpiles in the United States, the world's biggest oil consumer, fell unexpectedly last week as crude imports plunged. Domestic crude stocks declined by 2.45 million barrels to 365.18 million barrels, the Energy Information Administration said, against a forecast increase of 900,000 barrels. Gasoline inventories dropped by 481,000 barrels to 195.83 million barrels, against expectations of an increase of 200,000 barrels. That in part helped U.S. RBOB gasoline futures[RBCV1 3.142 0.0609 (+1.98%) ] jump 11.40 cents, or 3.8 percent, on Wednesday.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1348755963499</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348756088399-13</Id><Title>Oil inventories causing rise in Oil, THIS SHOULD BE UP</Title><Msg>..........</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1348756088399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348756481484-14</Id><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report September 27, 2012</Title><Msg>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report September 27, 2012 Notes and Definitions Beginning with the report period for the week ending March 16, 2012, EIA is including salt dome and nonsalt facility subtotals for the Producing Region in the Summary section. The sum of the components may not equal the total for the Producing Region, because of independent rounding. Summary Working gas in storage was 3,576 Bcf as of Friday, September 21, 2012, according to EIA estimates. This represents a net increase of 80 Bcf from the previous week. Stocks were 296 Bcf higher than last year at this time and 282 Bcf above the 5-year average of 3,294 Bcf. In the East Region, stocks were 75 Bcf above the 5-year average following net injections of 46 Bcf. Stocks in the Producing Region were 159 Bcf above the 5-year average of 994 Bcf after a net injection of 29 Bcf. Stocks in the West Region were 48 Bcf above the 5-year average after a net addition of 5 Bcf. At 3,576 Bcf, total working gas is above the 5-year historical range. Working gas stocks in the Producing Region, for the week ending September 21, 2012, totaled 1,153 Bcf, with 232 Bcf in salt cavern facilities and 921 Bcf in nonsalt cavern facilities. Working gas stocks increased 15 Bcf in the salt cavern facilities and increased 14 Bcf in the nonsalt cavern facilities since September 14. An historical series of the salt and nonsalt subtotals of the Producing Region is available for download at eia This URL is available at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348756481484</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348757606946-15</Id><Title>LPH is now largest Non State Owned Petroleum Facility in China</Title><Msg>LPH just put the hammer down today, tripling it's reserves with no shareholder dilution, BAMMM!!!!</Msg><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1348757606946</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348761738538-16</Id><Topic><Title>LPH is now largest Non State Owned Petroleum Facility in China</Title><Username>edwarddpeters</Username><Timestamp>1348757606946</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:53:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Acquisition of their third storage facility which adds 80% or 100,000 metric tons to their existing capacity. The new facility was paid for 100% from internal profits, without ANY shareholder dilution. LPH auditors recently published a comprehensive reconciliation of SAIC tax filings to SEC filings to prove that earnings over the period from 2009 to 2012 were accurately reported, based on direct verification from state computers. The new facility is turnkey, operational, and has a dedicated rail spur. Management and sales staff hired a while back have been on the ground, so that management states that tanks will be able to sell oil within 2 weeks. EPS is expected to increase from TTM EPS = 0.61 to TTM EPS = 0.80 by FYE 6/30/13, and to a TTM EPS of $1 by calendar year ending 12/31/13. Sentiment improvement from the current P/E will occur as a result from doing this acquistion without dilution, combined with the credibility increase because LPH is one of only a couple China stocks to pass with flying colors an audit of 2009 to 2012 SAIC tax filings versus SEC filings. The combined effecct should increase P/E much greater than the current 2.4 P/E. I expect P/E to rise to 5 or 6 by early next year on sentiment shift and new facility earnings. A P/E increase factor of 5 divided by 2.4 multiplied by an EPS increase of 1.0 divided by 0.61 yields an overall upside of 240 percent, which equates to PPS multipleid by a factor of 3.4.</Msg><Username>globaltrader7</Username><Timestamp>1348761738538</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:02:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348763682832-17</Id><Topic><Title>gcoffman is a cowardly racist</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1348705721663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 20:28:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you are in the courtroom, do you usually threaten to beat up the judge, the opposing attorneys or both? Is that now standard lib strategy?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348763682832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348765458949-18</Id><Title>White House; Today’s Economic Data</Title><Msg>White House; Today’s Economic Data Alan Krueger September 27, 2012 11:57 AM EDT More than the usual amount of economic statistics were released this morning. As a whole, today’s economic news shows that while we are still fighting back from the worst economic crisis since the Great Depression, we are making progress. We lost more than 8 million jobs and GDP contracted by almost 5 percent as a result of the Great Recession. We have more work to do, but incorporating today’s preliminary benchmark revision to the employment figures released by the Bureau of Labor Statistics with their earlier data indicates that the economy has added nearly 5.1 million private sector jobs, on net, over the past 30 months. BLS announced that total employment likely grew by 386,000 more jobs than previously announced during the 12 months from March 2011 to March 2012, and by 453,000 more private sector jobs in that same time period. In the past decade, the absolute difference between the preliminary and final benchmark revision has averaged 37,000 jobs. We also saw revised data released today showing that real GDP grew in the second quarter of 2012 by 1.3 percent at an annual rate. Real GDP growth in the second quarter was revised down due, in part, to a downward revision to agriculture inventories as a result of the devastating drought our nation faced this summer. The Obama Administration continues to take all available steps to mitigate the impacts of the drought, and has called on Congress to pass a farm bill that would spur growth and provide rural Americans with the certainty they deserve. We also learned today that the advance report of durable goods orders declined in August, largely as a result of a decline in orders for transportation equipment. Excluding the volatile transportation category, durable goods orders fell by 1.6 percent. Today’s news shows that we must do more to strengthen our economy and promote job creation. Over a year ago, President Obama proposed the American Jobs Act – a plan that independent economists have said would create up to 2 million jobs. The President will continue to push policies that will continue this progress we have made, including incentives to strengthen the American manufacturing industry, investments in our nation’s infrastructure, and the extension of the tax cuts for 98 percent of Americans and 97 percent of small businesses. While we are still rebuilding our economy and working to recover from the worst crisis since the Great Depression, we are making progress and the last thing we should do is return to the economic policies that failed us in the past. The revisions announced in today’s reports are a reminder that economic data are subject to large revisions. As a whole the pattern of revisions suggest that the recession that began at the end of 2007 was deeper than initially reported, and the jobs recovery over the last 2.5 years has been a bit stronger than initially reported, although much work remains to be done to return to full employment. whitehouse</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348765458949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:04:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348766195403-19</Id><Title>Biofuels industry fights back with media blitz</Title><Msg>Biofuels industry fights back with media blitz By Zack Colman - 09/27/12 10:00 AM ET The biofuels industry is undertaking an aggressive messaging campaign aimed at building public support for a fuel requirement that is increasingly under attack on Capitol Hill. The sector is partnering up with national security groups, think tanks and clean energy companies to make the case for a renewable fuel standard (RFS), which has been credited with creating a national biofuels market. “We believe that it’s not as well-known as it should be, the renewable fuel standard, and that what it supports is a really good thing for the economy, energy security, the environment,” Adam Monroe, president of biofuels firm Novozymes North America, told The Hill in an interview. “We just need to get that better understood by the policymakers and the public.” Historically a regional issue, fiscally conservative lawmakers have begun to view the fuel standard as an example of needless government intervention in the energy market. On top of that, the summer’s devastating drought has both Republicans and Democrats arguing that the biofuels requirements exacerbate food shortages. Biofuels backers have responded aggressively, holding a series of meetings with lawmakers this month to try and shore up congressional support for the fuel standard. The new media campaign announced Thursday morning will try to put a face on the biofuels industry by telling stories from rural communities, entrepreneurs and others who benefit from it, organizers said. National security groups — some of which support biofuels as a way to reduce dependence on foreign oil — think tanks and other potential industries will also lend support. Industry groups would not elaborate on how much would be spent on the new campaign or what media would be used, but said the effort would continue indefinitely. They said the initial effort would focus on stories from Colorado, Delaware, Montana and Ohio, though it could include more states in the future. One of the areas showcased in the first phase of the campaign is Marion, a rural town of about 66,000 people in central Ohio. It landed a $130 million biofuels facility that Pam Hall, the president of the Marion Chamber of Commerce, said revitalized the community. “It doesn’t seem that this particular issue is divided by party, and I think it is refreshing it is not,” Hall told The Hill. “What I can speak to is the health of our community and the very positive impact this industry has had, and we need to help people understand that both at the national and at the local level.” The campaign’s primary aim is to fight off attacks on the renewable fuel standard, which industry groups said is necessary to maintain investment in more “advanced” biofuels that are just now starting to come online. The standard requires refiners to blend 36 billion gallons of biofuels into traditional transportation fuel by 2022. Of those 36 billion gallons, 21 must come from “advanced” biofuels — those made from non-edible sources — with the rest coming mainly from corn. Currently, corn-based ethanol constitutes a majority of the biofuels market. Refiners must blend 13.2 billion gallons of corn-based ethanol into traditional fuel this year, a target that industry says will be met easily. The most immediate threat to the fuel standard is a waiver request that would exempt refiners from blending corn ethanol into traditional gasoline. Governors from a handful of states say that requirement has choked off corn supplies, making it difficult for livestock and poultry groups to find affordable feed during the drought. That pressure has helped unite the oft-disjointed biofuels industry, Monroe said. He explained that the fuel standard sparked new technologies that went in separate directions, but all owe their origins to it. The idea of that ending has brought them back together, he said. “I think the reason is, ironically, is there’s been so much technology that’s been advanced that a huge wave of different interests has come into this space,” Monroe said. “I think out of all that wave of innovation, possibly policymakers have gotten lost.” thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348766195403</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348766781532-20</Id><Title>Don't raise the dead, heal the sick or make little girls talk out of their head.</Title><Msg>Raise the dividend!!! Who's with me??</Msg><Username>chance_pocketwatch</Username><Timestamp>1348766781532</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348767184616-21</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are Amazing!</Title><Username>westward969</Username><Timestamp>1348695089544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the recovery is so great, then WHY are 'big business' sitting on their "huge cash reserves"?</Msg><Username>fore6996</Username><Timestamp>1348767184616</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348767850037-22</Id><Title>The Bernack isn't even cutting the Free Crack</Title><Msg>Ben is XOM's Best. Friend. Ever!</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1348767850037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348768222560-23</Id><Title>Weekly Coal Production Data for week ended September 22, 2012</Title><Msg>Weekly Coal Production Data for week ended September 22, 2012 Release Date: September 27, 2012 | Next Release: October 04, 2012 For the week ended September 22, 2012: •U.S. coal production totaled approximately 19.3 million short tons (mmst) •This production estimate is 4.2 percent lower than last week's estimate and 10.7 percent lower than the production estimate in the comparable week in 2011 •Coal production east of the Mississippi River totaled 8.2 mmst •Coal production west of the Mississippi River totaled 11.2 mmst •U.S. year-to-date coal production totaled 745.8 mmst, 5.2 percent lower than the comparable year-to-date coal production in 2011 •All of 2011 production has been revised to match the Mine Safety and Health Administration (MSHA) final 2011 production. Second quarter 2012 production has been revised to match MSHA production. These changes are present in the Revisions/Archives section, and are also reflected in the "Current Weekly Estimates" and "Current Monthly Estimates" tables in the year to date and 52 weeks ended totals. These changes are not reflected in the two Original Estimates tables. Weekly U.S. coal production overview eia Current Weekly Estimates eia URLs available at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348768222560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348768957256-24</Id><Title>Window dressing has begun,</Title><Msg>92.50? today</Msg><Username>greenlight_cap</Username><Timestamp>1348768957256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348769023569-25</Id><Title>92.50 by close,</Title><Msg>possible</Msg><Username>greenlight_cap</Username><Timestamp>1348769023569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348770090295-26</Id><Title>Buy it now, or pay more later,</Title><Msg>......</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets17</Username><Timestamp>1348770090295</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348773116331-27</Id><Title>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending September 26, 2012</Title><Msg>Natural Gas Weekly Update for Week Ending September 26, 2012 Release Date: September 27, 2012 In the News: Although Storage Injections Are Below Historical Levels, Inventories Remain HighWorking natural gas levels as of September 21 were at 3,576 Bcf, representing an implied net injection of 80 Bcf from the previous week, the highest storage build of the 2012 injection season. This injection season, additions to working natural gas inventories have been below the five-year (2007-2011) average injections as well as below last year’s injection levels, for all but three weeks, including the most current week. Despite lower injections, overall inventory levels remain at historical highs and are expected to hit a new record at the end of October, when the traditional injection season ends. The U.S. Energy Information Administration’s (EIA) Short-Term Energy Outlook (STEO) expects that inventory levels will end the heating season at 3,950 billion cubic feet (Bcf), a new end-of-October record. The STEO projects record high levels—despite the low injections this season—because inventories began the season at a very high level. This injection season began with 2,477 Bcf of working natural gas in storage, coming out of a warm winter that required low withdrawals to meet depressed heating demand. (In 2011, the injection season began with 1,581 Bcf in storage.) While EIA expects inventory levels will end the injection season at a record high, the projected increase of 1,473 Bcf in working gas inventory during the 2012 injection season would be the smallest build since 1991. Overview: (For the Week Ending Wednesday, September 26, 2012)•Natural gas prices generally registered overall increases for the report week (Wednesday to Wednesday) at many of the country’s trading locations. The Henry Hub price rose steadily through much of the reporting period to close at $2.92 per million British thermal units (MMBtu) yesterday (up 22 cents per MMBtu for the week). •The natural gas futures market trended higher over most of the week. At the New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), the October 2012 natural gas contract gained 26.1 cents per MMBtu to close at $3.023 per MMBtu yesterday. •Working natural gas in storage rose last week to 3,576 Bcf as of Friday, September 21, according to the EIA’s Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report (WNGSR). An implied storage build of 80 Bcf for the week positioned storage volumes 296 Bcf above year-ago levels. •The natural gas rotary rig count, as reported by Baker Hughes Incorporated on September 21, increased by 6 to 454 active units. Meanwhile, oil-directed rigs dropped by 11 to 1,402 units. more summary data Prices: The Henry Hub day-ahead price registered a generally steady increase for the week, stalling briefly on Friday before resuming an upward track for the balance of the reporting period, closing at $2.92 per MMBtu yesterday, up 8.1 percent. Prices at many downstream trading locations recorded overall increases, generally dipping somewhat before rebounding toward the end of the reporting week. For example, the Southern California Border Average price ended higher as temperatures remained relatively warm for much of the period (reaching 94 degrees in Los Angeles over the weekend); prices started the report week at $2.98 per MMBtu and finished yesterday at $3.21 per MMBtu, up 7.7 percent. Prices at the Transcontinental Pipeline’s Zone 6 trading point (which serves New York City markets) declined from $2.91 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $2.83 per MMBtu on Friday, then rebounded to $3.07 per MMBtu by week’s end (up 5.5 percent). Certain locations in the Northeast saw prices trending considerably lower following completion of pipeline maintenance on Algonquin Gas Transmission’s system. At the Algonquin Citygate trading point (for delivery into Boston), spot prices started the current reporting week at $3.72 per MMBtu, but continued last week’s steady decline, dipping to $3.06 per MMBtu on Monday before regaining some ground on Tuesday and yesterday, closing at $3.18 per MMBtu (down 14.5 percent for the week). Algonquin Citygate prices had reached $4.52 per MMBtu during the previous reporting week. At the NYMEX, the October 2012 contract, which expired yesterday, ended the week significantly higher, rising from $2.762 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.023 per MMBtu yesterday, an increase of 9.4 percent. Prices rose Thursday and Friday, and then again after falling on Monday to close yesterday up 26.1 cents per MMBtu overall. The November contract, which moves into the near-month position today, rose from $2.945 per MMBtu last Wednesday to $3.215 per MMBtu yesterday. The 12-Month Strip (average of September 2012 to August 2013 contracts) rose through much of the reporting week, closing at $3.215 per MMBtu, up 27 cents per MMBtu (9.2 percent). Total consumption for the report week registered an overall increase, with higher residential/commercial and industrial sector demand offsetting a modest decrease in power burn. According to estimates from BENTEK Energy LLC (Bentek), domestic natural gas consumption rose by 2.6 percent from last week, driven by increases of 11.7 percent and 1.4 percent, respectively, in residential/commercial and industrial sector consumption. For the power sector, consumption dipped by 1.0 percent, yet still exceeded levels for the same week last year by 13.6 percent. Total supply for the week registered an overall increase of just 0.3 percent, reflecting unchanged dry gas production for the reporting period relative to last week. According to Bentek estimates, domestic weekly dry gas production averaged 64.3 Bcf per day, virtually identical to the previous reporting week (although 1.2 percent above the same time last year). Imports from Canada rose 4.6 percent, as increases in shipments to the Northeast and Midwest offset declines in the West. For the week, imports from Canada stand 1.9 percent above year-ago volumes. Liquefied natural gas (LNG) sendout dropped significantly, down 13.5 percent from last week; sendout volumes remain well below (57.4 percent) year-ago levels. more price data Storage Working natural gas in storage increased to 3,576 Bcf as of Friday, September 21, according to EIA’s WNGSR. This represents an implied net injection of 80 Bcf from the previous week. This week’s injection was 4 Bcf above the 5-year (2007-2011) average injection of 76 Bcf, and 24 Bcf below last year’s injection of 104 Bcf. Inventories are currently 296 Bcf (9.0 percent) greater than last year at this time and 282 Bcf (8.6 percent) greater than the 5-year average. All three storage regions posted increases this week. Inventories in the East, West, and Producing regions increased by 46 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 47 Bcf), 5 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 9 Bcf), and 29 Bcf (the 5-year average net injection is 20 Bcf), respectively. In the Producing region, working natural gas inventories increased 15 Bcf (6.9 percent) in salt cavern facilities and increased 14 Bcf (1.5 percent) in nonsalt cavern facilities. Temperatures during the storage report week were 0.9 degrees cooler than the 30-year normal temperature and 2.0 degrees warmer than the same period last year. Temperatures in the lower 48 States averaged 66.0 degrees, compared to 64.0 last year and the 30-year normal of 66.9 degrees. While overall temperatures were about a degree cooler than normal, temperatures varied somewhat across Census divisions. The Pacific Census division in the West was particularly warm, averaging 5.0 degrees warmer than the 30-year normal. In the Midwest, temperatures in the East North Central and West North Central Census divisions were cool, averaging 4.1 and 3.7 degrees cooler, respectively, than the 30-year normal. eia URL provided at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348773116331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348776798157-28</Id><Topic><Title>White House; Today’s Economic Data</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348765458949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:04:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Complete White House bull as usual. Today's statistics were horrible and showed even more how Obamao is leading us from recession into depression. A loser beyond compare.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348776798157</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348776918464-29</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels industry fights back with media blitz</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348766195403</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:16:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We don't need biofuels for energy independence. Just open up drilling, fracking and build the Keystone pipeline. Well be there.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348776918464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348777980768-30</Id><Title>At least they admit it</Title><Msg>Obamao wants to redistribute the wealth worldwide! Hillary Clinton: Raise Taxes on Rich Everywhere (CNBC) It's no secret that the foreign policy of the United States tends to reflect the world views of the occupant of the White House. Sure, there used to be some homage paid to the notion that "politics stops at the water's edge," but that hasn't really been true for generations. Particularly if you are out to improve the world, you are going to wind up exporting your own ideas about world improvement. Free-market types will urge freer markets, even when these take the form of the kind of corrupt privatization that gave rise to Russia's oligarchs. And the Obama administration, well, it thinks the wealthy need to be taxed more - everywhere. "One of the issues that I have been preaching about around the world is collecting taxes in an equitable manner - especially from the elites in every country," Secretary of State Hillary Clinton said in her speech at the Clinton Global Initiative Monday. Although Clinton noted that she is "out of politics" domestically, the audience was already chuckling at her clear reference to the debate over tax policy in the presidential contest. "It is a fact that the elites in every country are making money. There are rich people everywhere, and yet they do not contribute to the growth of their own countries," Clinton said. What Clinton meant by "contribute to growth" was revealing. She listed contributing to building schools and hospitals rather than domestic business investment, which is the conventional meaning of contributing to growth. This is something that I hadn't realized was a part of the goals of U.S. foreign policy: higher taxes around the world on the wealthy. But now we know it straight from the mouth of Madam Secretary Clinton herself.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348777980768</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348783503803-31</Id><Title>Obamao caught in yet another lie</Title><Msg>White House knew Benghazi attack was a terrorist act from day one From day one, the Obama administration was aware that the September 11 assault on the US consulate in Benghazi was a pre-planned terrorist attack, despite offering up conflicting explanations in the weeks since. Unnamed officials confirm to Fox News that the White House knew that al-Qaeda-linked terrorists were behind the murder of four Americans in Libya, but only today did US Defense Secretary Leon Panetta publicly acknowledge the truth. Secretary Panetta now admits that the Pentagon knew within hours of the assault on America’s Benghazi consulate that left Ambassador Chris Stevens and three others dead that it was an act of terrorism. The Obama administration has altered their explanation repeatedly in the weeks since Mr. Stevens and three others were killed on September 11, 2012 while on assignment in Libya. On Thursday, the Defense Department confirmed the attack as having been hatched by terrorists, despite earlier statements made by the White House that suggested an anti-American film produced in the US had triggered a spontaneous assault. "The reason I think it pretty clearly was a terrorist attack is because a group of terrorists obviously conducted that attack on the consulate and against our individuals," Defense Secretary Leon Panetta said Thursday alongside Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff Gen. Martin Dempsey. "What terrorists were involved I think still remains to be determined by the investigation. But it clearly was a group of terrorists who conducted that attack against that facility." US Secretary of State Hillary Clinton suggested earlier in the week that the attack in Benghazi may have been hatched by an al-Qaeda affiliate, yet another drastic change of heart from an Obama appointee this week. In New York City on Wednesday, Secretary Clinton told attendees at a special United Nations meeting that the September 11 assault first thought by the White House to be a spontaneous response to an Anti-Islam film made in America could have been orchestrated by extremists in North Africa, specifically those subscribed to an off-shoot of al-Qaeda. “For some time, al-Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb and other groups have launched attacks and kidnappings from northern Mali into neighboring countries,” Clinton told the crowd this week. “Now, with a larger safe haven and increased freedom to maneuver, terrorists are seeking to extend their reach and their networks in multiple directions. And they are working with other violent extremists to undermine the democratic transitions underway in North Africa, as we tragically saw in Benghazi.” Secretary Clinton’s address was delivered at a United Nations meeting on instability in the Sahel, the region of Africa that includes Mali and, apparently, terrorist operatives conducting assaults on Americans for al-Qaeda. Immediately following the September 11 attack in Benghazi, Libya, the Obama administration all but confirmed their suspicious than “Innocence of Muslims,” an America-made film that mocked Islamic prophet Mohammed, was likely to blame for the violence. The movie was believed to have sparked protests in Cairo earlier in the day, which the White House then suggested spread to Libya and elsewhere in the Muslim world. Both the State Department and the White House initially hinted that the film was to blame for the Benghazi raid, and on September 16 Susan E. Rice, US ambassador to the United Nations, directly linked the movie with the mayhem. Days later, what was once a “spontaneous” response was reconsidered by many as something more. “I would say yes, they were killed in the course of a terrorist attack on our embassy,” National Counterterrorism Center Director Matthew Olsen told Congress on September 19. The next day, White House Press Secretary Jay Carney said it’s “self-evident that what happened in Benghazi was a terrorist attack.” Nearly a week later on September 26, Carney altered the official explanation to say, “it is certainly the case that it is our view as an administration, the President’s view, that it was a terrorist attack.” Carney’s reluctance to identify the assault as the act of terrorists could easily be explained as the White House’s unwillingness to admit a defeat in their War in Terror, not just on the anniversary of the September 11, 2001 attacks but so close to the November presidential elections. The United States has so far invested a substantial amount of men and money into efforts to allegedly free the Libyan people from the regime of fallen former leader Muammar Gaddafi, but now it appears as a man considered a ruthless dictator by Washington has only been replaced by rampant terrorism courtesy of al-Qaeda affiliates. Now Secretary Clinton says that the assault was more than just an act of violent extremism and that the men behind the mob attack may have ties to America’s most notorious foe: al-Qaeda. "We’re working with the Libyan government and other partners to find those responsible for the attack on our diplomatic post in Benghazi and bring them to justice.But we are also expanding our counterterrorism partnerships to help countries meet their own growing threats,” she added at the UN meeting. “ We’re taking aim at the support structure of al-Qaida and its affiliates – closing safe havens, cutting off finances, countering their ideology and denying them recruits." Earlier in the week, US President Barack Obama told the UN General Assembly, “I have made it clear that the United States government had nothing to do with this video, and I believe its message must be rejected by all who respect our common humanity.”</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348783503803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348786712531-32</Id><Title>Blow Em Off The Map</Title><Msg>BB. Too bad we don't have any real leaders like Israel does. Time to exterminate the radical MZLM roaches. Maybe a good time and place to exterminate them is when they all go to Mecca and spew their hatred. "Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, in a dramatic speech to the United Nations, employed a simple diagram to hammer home his plea that the international community set a "clear red line" over Iran's nuclear program -- warning that a nuclear-armed Iran would be tantamount to a nuclear-armed Al Qaeda."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348786712531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348787170261-33</Id><Title>Obama Lies Americans Die</Title><Msg>The Fraud in Chief should be impeached for all of his continuing lies, some of which kill Americans "Imagine the uproar if, barely a month before Election Day, the Bush Administration had responded to a terrorist strike—on Sept. 11 no less—in this fashion. Obfuscating about what happened. Refusing to acknowledge that clear security warnings were apparently ignored. Then trying to shoot the messengers who bring these inconvenient truths to light in order to talk about anything but a stunning and deadly attack on U.S. sovereign territory. Four Americans lost their lives in Benghazi in a terrorist attack that evidence suggests should have been anticipated and might have been stopped. Rather than accept responsibility, the Administration has tried to stonewall and blame others. Congress should call hearings to hold someone accountable for this debacle."</Msg><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348787170261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:06:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348787833699-34</Id><Topic><Title>Blow Em Off The Map</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348786712531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PEACE through STRENGTH. Make no mistake, this administration wants to cut our STRENGTH. Is anyone on this board going to challenge the neighborhood bully (who has a gun) with a screw driver? Our world is no different!</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1348787833699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:17:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348788453311-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Lies Americans Die</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348787170261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:06:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any one who does not know this is living under a liberal umbrella of absoulute ignorance. Surprising to me because, you punks will be the first to go down.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1348788453311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348790482688-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Lies Americans Die</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348787170261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:06:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But wait - it's Bush's fault (isn't it?).</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348790482688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 20:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348790590429-37</Id><Topic><Title>Blow Em Off The Map</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348786712531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually it's you who are fing stupid - and too stupid to realize it.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348790590429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 20:03:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348794374877-38</Id><Title>Biomass to Biodiesel for $2 A Gallon: Incitor Stepping Up Production</Title><Msg>Biomass to Biodiesel for $2 A Gallon: Incitor Stepping Up Production Sep 27, 2012 04:43 PM EDT (Photo : Reuters) What could be better than an inexpensive, environmentally friendly process for converting plants into fuel ? On September 10th, Biofuels Digest reported that Incitor Inc., an Albuquerque-based start-up was successful in attracting another round of venture capital investments totaling $1 million for its conversion technology that turns biomass into biodiesel for $2 a gallon. According to Biofuels Digest, "The company has signed a letter of intent to build its facility in Milan, and has since attracted investment from the New Mexico Angels and the Sun Mountain Capital of Santa Fe." Like Us on Facebook Over the summer, Cottonwood Technology Fund, an early-stage technology fund that targets the entrepreneurial communities along the Rio Grande, invested $1.5 million in Incitor. An Incitor press release states that Incitor's "patent-pending low-temperature chemical process breaks down almost any biomass from agricultural, solid, woody or algal waste to create commodity petrochemical replacements, specialty bio-based chemicals, and Alestron(TM), a novel third generation biofuel compatible with both gasoline and diesel." Another release from the company quoted Cottonwood Managing Director David Blivin as saying, "We believe Incitor's unique low-cost chemistry brings new economics to the biofuels and biochemical industries," It's new chemistry that's potentially disruptive." According to Incitor Vice President for Business Development Jacob Berman, the new venture funding is being put to use to rapidly scale biofuel production to about 30,000 gallons per year, as a pilot project. The goal is to reach between 4 million and 10 million gallons annually in a few years. However, government certification will be required before Incitor can commercially produce and sell a new type of biofuel. The technology was developed under a $2 million Army Corps of Engineers' Construction Engineering Research Laboratory contract and another $1.6 million was also obtained from individual investors, including Incitor CEO, Dr. John Elling. ivcpost</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348794374877</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:06:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348794718793-39</Id><Title>Virginia seeks to survey ocean floor, research offshore winds for wind farm development</Title><Msg>Virginia seeks to survey ocean floor, research offshore winds for wind farm development STEVE SZKOTAK Associated Press September 26, 2012 - 10:36 am EDT RICHMOND, Va. — Virginia is seeking to survey a vast expanse of the ocean floor and document wind, waves and wildlife offshore to smooth the way for development of wind turbines by energy companies. The proposed exploration 27 miles off Virginia Beach encompasses 113,000 acres, or 133 square miles, in the federally designated wind development area. Eight companies have expressed an interest in building towering turbines there to capture wind for energy. The eight include Dominion Virginia Power, the state's largest utility, as well as international interests. The Department of Mines, Minerals and Energy is proposing two initiatives. One seeks proposals by Oct. 17 to survey the ocean bottom to determine if it can hold massive support structures for wind turbines, which would rise hundreds of feet above the surface. The other involves building platforms along the edges of the commercial lease area. The so-called metocean platforms would use instruments and human observers to map and measure wind speeds and direction, water levels, and bird and bat activity. The initiatives are intended to spare developers the preliminary steps needed to create wind farms in offshore tracts overseen by the U.S. Department of the Interior and to create an environment for energy companies to move forward with wind energy plans, state officials said. Companies already face daunting costs to develop wind energy in an ocean environment, such as the design and manufacture of turbine and blade components and ships to deliver and install them. "If you don't know what is on the ocean floor, then your risk is exacerbated by that lack of knowledge," said Maureen Matsen, Gov. Bob McDonnell's top energy adviser and a member of a state authority promoting offshore development. "That's what this is really about. It's about eliminating the uncertainty and reducing the risk." Matsen said the ocean bottom survey would be the first ever in those waters. While the U.S. lags the rest of the world in offshore wind development, the industry has seen some promising signs. No commercial wind power is produced in waters off the U.S., although a project off Cape Cod, Mass., could begin producing electricity in 2014. A project known as the Atlantic Wind Connection, backed by Internet giant Google and other investors, is moving forward with the construction of a 380-mile power line that would enable up to 7,000 megawatts of electricity to be produced at offshore wind farms from Virginia to New Jersey. Wind power advocates have said Virginia is uniquely positioned to nurture the industry because of the relatively shallow waters offshore and strong winds. It also has the coastal infrastructure — a shipbuilding industry and a deepwater port — to allow for building and delivering turbines. Studies have forecast the creation of thousands of jobs as an offshore wind industry is developed. "I think everyone in the industry has recognized the high cost is the real barrier right now," Matsen said. "Everyone is looking for ways to bring costs down." Dominion's senior vice president for alternative energy solutions, Mary C. Doswell, said the research will help companies seeking a stake in offshore wind energy. "The survey will expedite the evaluation of the sea floor under the development area and will reduce the cost for whichever company is chosen to develop a wind farm," she said. Matsen said the geological survey would be financed by $300,000 in state funds and matched by the Interior Department. The state is seeking to secure leases from the agency to record environmental data on the north and south ends of the leasing area. Nine teams have put forth proposals on the research platforms. Funding has not been secured yet. Al Christopher, director of the division of energy with the state DMME, echoed Matsen's comments — that public-private partnerships can help move forward offshore development. He wrote in an email that the data gathered will help the industry more quickly develop. therepublic</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348794718793</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348796513805-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obamao caught in yet another lie</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348783503803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those in charge are #$%$ looking for the #$%$ vote. No doubt, they will get it. Eventually they will recognize the complete lunacy of their blind ignorance or, maybe not. It does not matter. Things will be what they are. History teaches lessions. Listen or, not!</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1348796513805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348796613005-41</Id><Topic><Title>Blow Em Off The Map</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348786712531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you can't read either. You must be great in the courtroom: not. So answer the question: who do you threaten to beat up when you are in court?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348796613005</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348796922495-42</Id><Topic><Title>Blow Em Off The Map</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1348786712531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Punk, you don;t have any idea of what "typical" is.................</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1348796922495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348797244285-43</Id><Topic><Title>This Board Shows Why Obama's In Trouble</Title><Username>kyleusa1</Username><Timestamp>1348532680926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:24:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have made that claim before. I offered you the chance to back it up with $$$$$$ and you ran away. Remember? Offer is still open if you have the guts big mouth bully.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1348797244285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348800953975-44</Id><Title>Chicken Draft Dodger Romney Afraid To Talk About Afganistan</Title><Msg>he won't even mention it. Nothing. No plan, no nothin. I think he'll just outsource US foreign policy to the Likudniks.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348800953975</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 22:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348801144765-45</Id><Title>Republican Senator Blocks COLA Payments to Deceased Soldiers Children</Title><Msg>And that senator is too scared to reveal himself. As I have always said, Republicans HATE Veterans. A dead Veteran is their favorite kind of Veteran. And once that Veteran is dead they simply screw the family left behind. I hate Republicans.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1348801144765</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 22:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348804257305-46</Id><Title>US DoD to Spend $1.8 Billion on Clean Energy by 2025</Title><Msg>US DoD to Spend $1.8 Billion on Clean Energy by 2025 September 27, 2012 By Mridul Chadha 3 Comments According to the latest report published by Colarado-based Pike Research, the US Department of Defense is expected to spend $1.8 billion on clean energy by 2025. The clean energy programs also include conservation measures which are expected to increase steadily over the next 12 years. The various branches of the U.S. Department of Defense (DoD) combine to become one of the largest consumers of energy in the world, with consumption of around 3.8 billion kWh of electricity and 120 million barrels of oil annually, totalling $20 billion spent on energy directly per year. “Changes in energy policy have provided countless opportunities throughout all operations of the DoD, with examples of renewable energy projects that include targets of 1 gigawatt of renewable energy installed capacity each for the Army, Navy, and Air Force by 2025, a target of 25 percent of all energy produced or procured from renewable energy sources by 2025, and development of the Navy’s Great Green Fleet Strike Group powered by biofuel, nuclear power, synthetic fuels, and hybrid propulsion systems,” says research analyst Dexter Gauntlett. “Most of these initiatives have gained considerable momentum and many of the targets will be achieved.” The report predicts that the DoD is one of the most important drivers of renewable energy in the United States, with an official annual budget of about $800 billion. But, according to the Pike Research, the actual budget is much higher. Pike predicts that DoD expenditures include the procurement of technology, vehicles, aircrafts, and vessels running on cleantech and energy efficient components, and about $75 billion spent on research and development programs. This Pike Research report, “Renewable Energy for Military Applications,” apart from forecasting the DoD expenditures on renewable energy by 2025, also analyses the present status and future plans of renewable energy at DoD and military bases. The report also examines the near- and long-term plans of DoD in research and development, primary drivers of renewable energy for each branch of the military. Analysis of renewable energy programs by technology (including solar, wind, geothermal, biomass, waste to energy, hydrokinetic and ocean energy, and fuel cells) is also covered in the report. Earlier this year, the Obama administration had confirmed the establishment of a new army laboratory aimed at focussing on improving energy efficiency in combat vehicles. Also, a memorandum of understanding was signed between Defense Secretary Leon Panetta and the Interior Secretary Ken Salazar to work together on promoting the renewable energy generation on 16 million acres of DoD land. Clean Technica</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1348804257305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>