<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373259252004-1</Id><Title>BREAKING: Germany Sets Solar Power Record (Again) — 23.9 GW</Title><Msg>BREAKING: Germany Sets Solar Power Record (Again) — 23.9 GW July 7, 2013 Zachary Shahan It has been a very sunny day here in western Poland, so I knew it was basically the same in Germany (it always is) and that there was a good chance Germany would break its previous solar power output record. So, I’ve been keeping an eye on SMA Solar Technology’s live solar power output tool for the country. Sure enough, a few hours ago, solar output climbed above the 22.68 GW solar power output record Germany set in April. Not long after, it climbed above the 23.4 GW solar power output record set in June. At its peak at about 1:45pm local time (one hour ago), the output got up to 23.9 GW. (Actually, I thought I saw it reach 24 GW at that time, but the replay isn’t showing it go above 23.9 GW.) I’m sure an official number still needs to be confirmed, but a full 0.5 GW increase according to SMA’s site makes for a very safe conclusion that we have a new record. It is an estimate based on the output of thousands of SMA solar power systems spread across the country. Germany’s peak electricity demand at midday is about 60 GW, so at 1:45pm or so, solar power was providing about 40% of the country’s electricity demand. Impressive. Approximately 1.3–1.4 million solar power systems were involved in creating that massive electricity output, our German solar expert Thomas tells me. And about 8.5 million people live in buildings where solar power systems are used to produce electricity or heat. As we’ve reported many times before, Germany is the clear solar power world leader at the moment. (Though, Bulgaria and the Czech Republic actually beat it on solar power per GDP). Despite what Fox News or Fox &amp; Friends might want to tell you, it’s not because of Germany’s “excellent” solar resources — its solar resources are comparable to Alaska’s. Rather, it’s because the country has h</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373259252004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:54:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373281271342-2</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Germany Sets Solar Power Record (Again) — 23.9 GW</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373259252004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:54:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is largely irrelevant to XOM. Solar power will never be good enough to replace fossil fuels.</Msg><Username>goldbug34</Username><Timestamp>1373281271342</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 07:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373289897603-3</Id><Topic><Title>Yankeedom USA</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369925701757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 10:55:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Perhaps we could hold a séance and I could ask the ghosts of dead Yankees for their advice on these pressing matters. I think this house is haunted by the way.” More $$$ from USA to fund war on fossil fuels investments. The estate has been settled and my share has been deposited and invested. None of it is invested in the US either. New England money thus returns to Old England. I could put in Germany if I wanted but I want a little diversification. The British government’s war effort on fossil fuels is far superior to the USA, and its government is better in every respect than the US government. So long as a cultural Marxist such as Obama sits in the White House I will never invest anything in the USA. Sales of $ for € @1.4905 $/£ &amp; purchase of 5 Year UK Government Bonds at 1.44% ytm War on Fossil Fuels Allocations (%): German Real Estate {urban upper/middle class, large city}: 78.5% United Kingdom 5 Year Government Bonds: 12.5% German t-bills: 9.0%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373289897603</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 09:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373291785660-4</Id><Title>Breaking News BISU -- DIABETES CURE!!</Title><Msg>MONSTER</Msg><Username>tedsmith912</Username><Timestamp>1373291785660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 09:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373294054689-5</Id><Title>Devastated Lac-Mégantic waits for word of its missing: 5 declared dead, about 40 missing after runaway train cars explode in Quebec town</Title><Msg>Investigators in the Quebec town devastated by a massive tanker-train explosion are expanding their search for the 40 people still missing two days later. Quebec provincial police said the official death toll, which stands at five, and missing persons list didn't change overnight. The area surrounding the derailed tanker cars has remained largely off limits to anyone other than fire crews as they tried to bring the flames under control and prevent further explosions. Watch: Town pharmacist describes tight-knit community Watch: Resident was getting ready for bed when she felt the ground shake "There’s a been a lot of work that has been done on the scene during the night, and hopefully we’ll get some more areas that we can search during the day — but of course, that is the firefighters responsibility," Quebec provincial police Sgt. Benoît Richard said Monday morning. 5 confirmed dead, 40 missing after explosion early Saturday Air quality tests show no risk to public Police search for victims expanding 30 buildings destroyed, including popular bar Rail company says shutdown may have caused release of air brakes</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1373294054689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373295265082-6</Id><Title>socialist climate Kommando</Title><Msg>New England is the Koenigsberg of America. I am sure Immanuel K would be happy there in the frigid home of Emerson and Thoreau. Personally I prefer Verrmont to Connecticut as it boasts a smart economist by the name of Bernie Sanders who is anti fossil fuel and probably a student of your Freddy Engels.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1373295265082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373295310112-7</Id><Topic><Title>socialist climate Kommando</Title><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1373295265082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This was in reply to steelyard</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1373295310112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373299006654-8</Id><Topic><Title>Yankeedom USA</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369925701757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 10:55:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New England is the Koenigsberg of America. I am sure Immanuel K would be happy there in the frigid home of Emerson and Thoreau. Personally I prefer Verrmont to Connecticut as it boasts a smart economist by the name of Bernie Sanders who is anti fossil fuel and probably a student of your Freddy Engels</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1373299006654</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:56:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373301954924-9</Id><Title>@BarackObama: The threat of #climate change is real and is not going away. If Congress won't act, President Obama will:</Title><Msg>TWITTER... @BarackObama: The threat of #climate change is real and is not going away. If Congress won't act, President Obama will:</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373301954924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:45:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373302784418-10</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Germany Sets Solar Power Record (Again) — 23.9 GW</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373259252004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:54:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine how the LNG market will almost vanish in the near term! Germany is at latitudes similar to much of Canada. The American solar market will boom.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373302784418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:59:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373308673182-11</Id><Topic><Title>stock splits are good</Title><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1369765772412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the dividend remains unchanged, which it usually does, and with a traditional 2 for 1 split, the dividend effectively doubles. Simple stuff.</Msg><Username>hopalong_hooha</Username><Timestamp>1373308673182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373330112089-12</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're seriously obsessive/compulsive........seek help</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373330112089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373330196576-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bluecheese: All his posts are "absolutely worthless" !</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371752941651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you and refsteve and foul-mouthed punks ! And cowards.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373330196576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>