<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371733139801-1</Id><Title>BP defends renewable-fuel rule other oil companies oppose</Title><Msg>BP defends renewable-fuel rule other oil companies oppose June 20, 2013 at 6:45 am by Bloomberg As Congress considers scaling back or abolishing U.S. rules that mandate the use of renewable fuels, it has the full-throated support of the petroleum industry — with one major exception. BP Plc (BP/) (BP/), one of the world’s biggest oil companies by revenue, is part of a joint venture with DuPont Co. (DD) that is set to start producing a new alternative fuel by the end of the year. In order to preserve a market for that fuel, its officials are busy in Washington trying to convince lawmakers that the current system doesn’t need an overhaul. “They don’t need to change the law,” Paul Beckwith, the chief executive of the venture, Butamax Advanced Biofuels LLC (0031863D) of Wilmington, Delaware, said in an interview. The program “as it’s currently configured is working, and there are good opportunities for increasing renewable levels beyond where they are today.” The Renewable Fuel Standard, or RFS, dates in its current form to 2007, when concerns about dependence on overseas oil and a desire to curb the use of fossil fuels induced Congress to set quotas for the use of alternatives to gasoline or diesel, such as ethanol and biodiesel. Under the law, refiners such as Exxon Mobil Corp. (XOM) must blend a certain amount of renewable fuels into their gasoline each year, with their contribution determined by their share of the fuel market. The Environmental Protection Agency and renewable-fuel producers say the mandate spurs production of American-made fuels, helps corn farmers and cuts carbon emissions by replacing gasoline. Lobbying Costs The efforts of BP and Wilmington, Delaware-based DuPont, which together spent $13.8 million on lobbying in 2012, show the fissures in the business community over the future of the rules, and the difficult path any overhaul must tread. A panel of the House Energy and Commerce Committee is set to hold a hearing on the progra</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371733139801</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 08:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371733574534-2</Id><Title>Obama kissed the ring of our fair Chancellor with style.</Title><Msg>He should come to Berlin more often. We could set up a special chair for him and he could take notes. When the inspiration for an Executive Order strikes him, such as pursuing the war on fossil fuels with more interest, the note can be dispatched to DC quickly.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371733574534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 09:06:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371734113717-3</Id><Title>Pipe waits on the prairie as Keystone XL debate rages almost 5 years</Title><Msg>Pipe waits on the prairie as Keystone XL debate rages almost 5 years By Deena Winter / June 19, 2013 / 15 Comments LIMBO: Some 230 miles of pipe has been sitting in this pasture near Gascoyne, N.D., since 2011 as the debate rages over the Keystone XL oil pipeline. By Deena Winter | Nebraska Watchdog LINCOLN – South Dakota rancher Bret Clanton heard a Canadian oil pipeline company, TransCanada, was stockpiling pipe across the border in North Dakota. In 2011 he drove from his ranch to take a look. At the top of a hill east of Scranton, N.D. — near a ghost town named Gascoyne — trucks unloaded pipe into a pasture. That field is now filled with rows and rows of mostly aqua-green pipe, some stamped with the words “made in Canada.” It’s where the pipe has sat ever since, waiting for the Obama administration to give the green light so it can be buried in American soil, filled with oil from Alberta, Canada and sent to Texas refineries. The future of the 230 or so miles of unused pipe in rural North Dakota has caused consternation for environmentalists, libertarians, union workers, oil companies, farmers, ranchers, governors and politicians — from the lowliest county commissioner to the president. Should a Canadian company be allowed to put 1,179 miles of this pipe in the ground and run 830,000 barrels of oil per day through it? The question has vexed America since TransCanada applied for its permits in September 2008. Clanton is deeply interested in the outcome, since three miles of the pipeline would cross his cattle ranch near Buffalo, S.D. Clanton occasionally visits the pipe yard and takes pictures of the pipe – a pile so big he can’t fit it in one frame. He figures TransCanada chose Gascoyne as a storage spot because it has a railroad spur once used for a coal mine. The few times Clanton visited the pipe yard and taken photos, a little white pickup stopped by to keep watch. “You could drive right in the middle of it if you wanted,” Clanton said. “I don</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371734113717</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 09:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371734928366-4</Id><Title>Rep. Jeff Duncan Denies He Voted For Big Oil Subsidies, Then Gets Flustered Trying To Justify The Money VIDEO</Title><Msg>Rep. Jeff Duncan Denies He Voted For Big Oil Subsidies, Then Gets Flustered Trying To Justify The Money VIDEO By Lee Fang on May 10, 2011 at 5:20 pm Although Republicans hinted for months that they may reverse course and end billions in subsidies to big oil companies, they voted in lockstep last week to protect them. Before the Silver Elephant Dinner last week in Columbia, SC, ThinkProgress spoke to freshman Rep. Jeff Duncan (R-SC) about the vote. At first, Duncan claimed that he “did not” vote to preserve billions in subsidies to oil companies. Second later, he backtracked and told us that he opposed an amendment, offered by Democrats, which would have killed the subsidies. Finally, after some prodding, Duncan told us he stands by companies like Exxon and BP, but had “no comment” on why they deserve special subsidies: FANG: What do you think about oil subsidies? I know Democrats have brought this up this week and there was a vote on Thursday or maybe Wednesday on ending billions of dollars in tax subsidies to very profitable oil companies like Exxon, Shell, Chevron, etc. Do you think it’s necessary that the government borrows money to give to already very profitable oil companies? DUNCAN: Well look at all the money we borrow to give to countries that hate us in foreign aid. I think we gotta look at every bit of expenditure, every tax line, and really work on reining in government spending more. FANG: Did you vote to extend those subsidies? DUNCAN: I did not. FANG: Okay. DUNCAN: Or I didn’t vote for the Democrat amendment that you were talking about. I support American energy production, and it will be produced by companies, Exxon, BP, Shell, and continue to support American energy. FANG: Even if they made $35 billion in the last quarter, you think that it’s still necessary that the taxpayer subsidize them? DUNCAN: I’m not going to comment on that. Watch it: VIDEO Taxpayers will be forced to hand over some $70 billion in oil subsidies over the next</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371734928366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 09:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371735111840-5</Id><Topic><Title>Can't beat free</Title><Username>gbutler668</Username><Timestamp>1371057349042</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:15:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks man, greatly appreciated</Msg><Username>omcconnell977</Username><Timestamp>1371735111840</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 09:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371735472002-6</Id><Title>Ben sent the bond funds to Israel !!!!</Title><Msg>Yep. There will be an investigation.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1371735472002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 09:37:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371743089220-7</Id><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report for week ending June 14, 2013</Title><Msg>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report for week ending June 14, 2013 Released: June 20, 2013 at 10:30 a.m. Summary Working gas in storage was 2,438 Bcf as of Friday, June 14, 2013, according to EIA estimates. This represents a net increase of 91 Bcf from the previous week. Stocks were 559 Bcf less than last year at this time and 47 Bcf below the 5-year average of 2,485 Bcf. In the East Region, stocks were 94 Bcf below the 5-year average following net injections of 60 Bcf. Stocks in the Producing Region were 3 Bcf above the 5-year average of 930 Bcf after a net injection of 20 Bcf. Stocks in the West Region were 44 Bcf above the 5-year average after a net addition of 11 Bcf. At 2,438 Bcf, total working gas is within the 5-year historical range. eia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371743089220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371743236615-8</Id><Topic><Title>Unreal</Title><Username>calebhaley159</Username><Timestamp>1371129732346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 09:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getting good benefit?</Msg><Username>austinjeremiah838</Username><Timestamp>1371743236615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:47:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371743451330-9</Id><Title>Billionaire Steyer Rejects Trade With Obama on Keystone</Title><Msg>Billionaire Steyer Rejects Trade With Obama on Keystone 20 June 2013 June 20 (Bloomberg) — Billionaire Tom Steyer, a donor to President Barack Obama’s re-election campaign and a foe of the Keystone XL pipeline, said no offer of action to combat climate change can offset the president’s approval of the project. Steyer, who is set to unveil today a social-media drive to stop the pipeline modeled on the Obama campaign’s online efforts, said he keeps hearing suggestions the president will act to curb greenhouse-gas emissions as a way to assuage environmentalists for approving a project they say will add to global warming. “I understand the idea of a trade, but you have to tell me, who is the trade with?” Steyer, a co-founder of hedge fund Farallon Capital Management LLC, said at a Bloomberg Government breakfast. “They would like this to go away, but it can’t go away.” Obama in coming weeks will outline steps his administration will take to deal with climate change, including pursuing Environmental Protection Agency regulation of emissions from power plants, establishing energy-efficiency standards for appliances and approving more clean energy on public lands, Heather Zichal, his energy aide, said yesterday. In a speech yesterday in Berlin, Obama said the U.S. “will do more” to cut carbon emissions. “The effort to slow climate change requires bold action,” Obama said, warning that more severe storms, famines and floods will affect all nations. “This is the global threat of our time.” ‘Big Thing’ None of the actions Zichal suggested can compensate for approving TransCanada Corp.’s $5.3 billion the pipeline, Steyer said. On Keystone, “the downside for him is making a big mistake,” Steyer said. “I know this is something they consider to be a red herring, but I think substantively it’s a very big thing.” “Everyday the likelihood he approves the pipeline goes down,” he said. The pipeline would carry about 830,000 barrels a day from the oil sands of Alber</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371743451330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371747436883-10</Id><Title>Today shows just how FAKE high oil prices are.... !!</Title><Msg>Big Oil is allowed to pump up prices as far as possible, rip off the consumer and throw the economy into recession while padding their balance sheets. What a rip off. Exxon is criminal. Unfortunately, they run the country.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1371747436883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371750397751-11</Id><Title>Murkowski, Wyden weigh path forward for US-Mexico drilling agreement</Title><Msg>Murkowski, Wyden weigh path forward for US-Mexico drilling agreement By Ben Geman - 06/20/13 10:53 AM ET A House-Senate collision over competing bills to implement a 2012 U.S.-Mexico pact on Gulf of Mexico drilling cooperation is getting closer to coming to a head. Sen. Lisa Murkowski (R-Alaska) said she spoke Wednesday with Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee Chairman Ron Wyden (D-Ore.) about the path forward for their bill to implement the Transboundary Hydrocarbon Agreement. “I think both of us share the desire to help advance that and as with everything it is figuring out when we do it,” she told The Hill in the Capitol on Wednesday. Rep. Jeff Duncan (R-S.C.), a lead sponsor of the House version of the bill, said it could come to the House floor next week, according to a report Wednesday in Environment and Energy Daily. But there's a huge difference between the bills. The Senate bill does not contain a House provision that exempts oil companies operating under the pact from controversial Dodd-Frank rules that force energy producers to disclose their payments to foreign governments. “We are kind of looking at it and saying, ‘that is a provision that really doesn’t need to be in the bill,’ ” Murkowski said. Click here for much more about the House version of the bill to implement the U.S.-Mexico pact. The 2012 agreement the Obama administration reached with Mexico, which has support from Republicans, is aimed at fostering oil-and-gas development along a maritime boundary in the Gulf of Mexico. Murkowski said she wants to learn from House lawmakers whether the exemption from the Dodd-Frank rules is a “must have” for them, or instead a “nice to have.” House Republicans and oil industry representatives say the Dodd-Frank disclosure exemption is needed to prevent a collision with confidentiality provisions in the U.S.-Mexico accord. But backers of the Dodd-Frank rules dispute the claims and have expressed concern that the House provision</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371750397751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371750575400-12</Id><Title>Boehner: Obama climate proposal 'absolutely crazy'</Title><Msg>Boehner: Obama climate proposal 'absolutely crazy' By Molly K. Hooper - 06/20/13 12:34 PM ET President Obama's soon-to-be-revealed second-term climate change proposal is “absolutely crazy,” Speaker John Boehner said Thursday. The Ohio Republican was incredulous when asked to react to reports that the White House plans to regulate carbon emissions from power plants as part of its climate change strategy. “I think this is absolutely crazy,” Boehner said at his weekly press conference. “Why would you want to increase the cost of energy and kill more American jobs at a time when American people are asking, 'Where are the jobs.' " Obama's top climate adviser on Wednesday vowed that “meaningful” action on global warming was coming soon. Heather Zichal, the deputy assistant to the president on energy and climate change, spoke of bolstering energy efficiency, expanding clean energy on public lands and using various “tools” — including the Clean Air Act — to address climate change. Obama in his State of the Union address though vowed to act on climate change if Congress does not, saying it would be a second-term priority. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371750575400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371750710023-13</Id><Topic><Title>Ben sent the bond funds to Israel !!!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1371735472002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 09:37:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does this relate to XOM?</Msg><Username>trend_investor</Username><Timestamp>1371750710023</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371752941651-14</Id><Title>Bluecheese: All his posts are "absolutely worthless" !</Title><Msg>'nuff said..............What's your point, idiot ?</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371752941651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371755827308-15</Id><Topic><Title>Ben sent the bond funds to Israel !!!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1371735472002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 09:37:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the proceeds did not go into the US in total. Ben skimmed. Ben has been fired. The result is that QE was a scam, and only Ben's buddies prospered. XOM will face higher rates. Historically, when rates rise, XOM falls. It trades like a bond.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1371755827308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371762014682-16</Id><Topic><Title>Today shows just how FAKE high oil prices are.... !!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1371747436883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Binney, 90% of the price you pay now, are taxes....Go speak to your politicians.</Msg><Username>boilerroommanager</Username><Timestamp>1371762014682</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 17:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371772519801-17</Id><Title>Houston to buy half its power from renewable sources</Title><Msg>Houston to buy half its power from renewable sources Posted on June 20, 2013 at 1:51 pm by Jeannie Kever Comments(3) The city of Houston has agreed to purchase half its electricity from renewable sources. That will make Houston the largest municipal purchaser of renewable energy in the nation, according to the city, which cited estimates from the Environmental Protection Agency. “Houston is already known as the energy capital of the world, but we are committed to becoming the alternative energy capital of the world as well,” Mayor Annise Parker said in a written statement Thursday. “Purchasing green power reduces the environmental impacts of electricity use, decreases the cost of renewable power over time and supports the development of new renewable generation,” she added. Photos: Asia’s largest solar-thermal power plant launches (photos) The move comes as renewable energy is getting a boost from all quarters. The Electric Reliability Council of Texas reported this spring that generation from renewable sources grew by 7 percent in 2012. On Thursday, the city announced that it had signed an agreement with Reliant Energy to purchase 140 megawatts of renewable power between July 1 and June 30, 2015, accounting for half of its annual electricity demand. The transaction is done through the purchase of renewable energy credits. According to the announcement, the city committed $2 million for the two-year agreement. New York: Solar-powered phone-charging stations make debut Environmentalists praised the move. “From promoting electric vehicles to adopting some of the strongest energy efficiency standards in the country, Houston is a rising star among clean energy cities,” said Luke Metzger, director of Environment Texas. He cited a November 2011 report by the Environment Texas Research and Policy Center that calculated by 2030, improvements in energy efficiency and expanded solar power in the Houston metro area could reduce demand for e</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371772519801</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 19:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371773048802-18</Id><Title>Sen. Feinstein plans power plant carbon bill</Title><Msg>Sen. Feinstein plans power plant carbon bill By Ben Geman - 06/20/13 01:55 PM ET Sen. Dianne Feinstein (D-Calif.) said Thursday that she’s planning legislation that would impose a fee on carbon emissions from power plants, a measure that’s narrower than carbon bills circulated by other Democrats. Feinstein told reporters that her bill would assess a $10-per-ton fee on emissions “just for the utility industry,” and that she plans to float the measure in a couple of weeks. It would add to other carbon tax bills that are piling up even as the concept faces long odds on Capitol Hill. Sens. Barbara Boxer (D-Calif.) and Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) have introduced a plan, and Sen. Sheldon Whitehouse (D-R.I.) and Rep. Henry Waxman (D-Calif.) have floated a draft bill, too. Feinstein’s plan would cover a smaller range of industries than the other measures, and launching the fee at $10-per-ton is less aggressive than the other bills too. The Center for Climate and Energy Solutions has a handy chart here that compares the Boxer and Whitehouse plans, which differ substantially in structure. Boxer, chairwoman of the Environment and Public Works Committee, told reporters Wednesday that she will have a climate change hearing some time in July that will include discussion of legislative proposals. Climate legislation faces remote prospects of passage in the current Congress. President Obama, within weeks, is expected to announce plans for executive-level actions on global warming, including power plant regulations. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371773048802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371775570562-19</Id><Title>If Bernake is right, people will travel with lower gas prices.</Title><Msg>Then you will have hotels, leisure trips and and the economy will be pumped…They will neeed more oil. I have a little company that just started to pump oil Texas,,,1200 bbls since end on May and possibly an outcome will be posted if they hit oil in Belize within possibly 2 weeks.. If that happens lookout..JMHO, but lookup TECO on investor hangout..TECO.</Msg><Username>stevek454</Username><Timestamp>1371775570562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371776637392-20</Id><Topic><Title>Unreal</Title><Username>calebhaley159</Username><Timestamp>1371129732346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 09:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Key Logger site...........enjoy. Now try to get rid of it.</Msg><Username>dai_gul_dai</Username><Timestamp>1371776637392</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:03:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371782095353-21</Id><Topic><Title>Bluecheese: All his posts are "absolutely worthless" !</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371752941651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take a hint cheesebreath..........no one is reading your cut and paste junk.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371782095353</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 22:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371785240166-22</Id><Topic><Title>Bluecheese: All his posts are "absolutely worthless" !</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371752941651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently, YOU are!</Msg><Username>gyrogearcrunch</Username><Timestamp>1371785240166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 23:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371785250737-23</Id><Title>Deutschland Fuel Cells Proceedings</Title><Msg>More bad news for Big Oil from Germany, the world’s leader in fuel cell technology: German Scientists at Berlin and Jülich recently discovered a way to reduce the platinum requirement for fuel cells by 90%. The cost of platinum has been the main impediment to the economic use of fuel cells so this very significant. Nanotechnological science aided by supercomputing analytical techniques contributed to the advance. Economic fuel cells will make the internal combustion engine obsolete, a development that will eventually bankrupt the oil industry. The article is in Nature Materials 16 June 2013. The German fuel cell R&amp;D effort is broad based. There are at least 4,000 scientists and engineers working on the programs around Germany, plus supporting staff. ZBT GmbH, a non-profit R&amp;D company owned by the University of Duisburg-Essen and funded by various government entities, is representative. There are at least a dozen such organizations around Germany. The German Aerospace Center is a source of funding for fuel cell programs, and the Fraunhofer Society has many institutes working on fuel cells. Besides Berlin and the Ruhr, Stuttgart and Munich, both major automotive R&amp;D and super-computing centers, are fuel cell development areas. The death warrant for Big Oil has been issued and the German government is paying people to hunt it down. The wolves are circling the prey.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371785250737</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 23:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>