<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-12"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365744126439-1</Id><Title>California Carbon Advances After Governor Approves Quebec Link</Title><Msg>By Lynn Doan - Apr 9, 2013 4:56 PM MT California carbon futures rose to the highest price in almost three weeks after Governor Jerry Brown approved a proposal to link the state’s greenhouse-gas program with one in Quebec. The regulation behind carbon markets in Quebec and California are “similar or identical” enough to be linked, Brown said in a letter posted on his website late yesterday. State law requires the governor’s approval before the state Air Resources Board links carbon systems with any jurisdiction. The board is scheduled to consider regulation April 19 to join systems with Quebec beginning Jan. 1, 2014. Futures based on California carbon allowances for 2014 gained for the first time in three days, rising 15 cents to $14.70 a metric ton, the highest since March 21, according to data compiled by Chicago-based CME Group Inc. (CME) Prices have fallen 8.7 percent this year. “The announcement could be mildly bullish due to the fundamental upside a linkage would provide,” Thomas Marcello, a Bloomberg New Energy Finance analyst, said in a research note today. “We do not expect speculators to take long-term positions based on the announcement. Instead, price reaction is likely to be both short-lived and limited in scale.” The air board’s staff has said a link with Quebec would improve market liquidity for carbon allowances by increasing the pool of both permits and companies trading them. The reduction in greenhouse-gas emissions achieved by combining the two programs would also be larger than cuts through a California- only system, the agency said in a report last year. Quebec Link The link to Quebec may raise California carbon allowance prices from 2013 to 2020, depending on how many offset credits the Canadian province is able to generate, said Marcello, based in New York. Should Quebec supply less than 23 million tons of bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-04-09/california-carbon-advances-after-governor-approves-quebec-link.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365744126439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 01:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365745005351-2</Id><Title>Low Carbon Fuel Standard: Consumer choice is key to California success</Title><Msg>Low Carbon Fuel Standard: Consumer choice is key to California success By Matt Horton Special to the Mercury News Posted: 04/04/2013 10:22:52 AM PDT April 11, 2013 1:57 AM GMTUpdated: 04/10/2013 06:57:44 PM PDT "You can have any color Ford you want, as long as it's black," Henry Ford is famously credited with saying in the early years of the U.S. automobile industry, when Fords came in only one color. Why so many color options today? Consumers. Consumers are one of the most powerful drivers of change on the planet. We vote with our wallets, and we vote with our values. And we have the power to make changes far greater than a car's color. Yet at the fuel pump, consumers still have no power. We all know our dependence on fossil fuels weakens our economy and security while threatening our environment. We simply feel powerless to address it because there is no true alternative. Rather than being able to choose fuels made in the U.S. or from renewable sources or from local businesses, the choices remain regular, super and premium unleaded. Even if you are one of the 1 million California drivers with a flex fuel or diesel vehicle, alternative fuels are rare and very hard to find despite domestic alternative fuel production reaching 14 billion gallons annually. In our state, that's starting to change. In 2010, voters defeated an attempt to repeal the state's Low Carbon Fuel Standard, California's landmark clean-energy law, and committed to cleaner fuels by a 23-point margin. Today, as a consequence, the standard and new technologies are helping consumers and businesses access a brand-new competitive market with a full spectrum of fueling options. Whether by blending alternative fuels into gasoline or developing entirely new fuel types, the low carbon standard is driving the development of clean alternatives to oil. Demand for them will accelerate innovation and create jobs right here in California.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365745005351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 01:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365746679468-3</Id><Title>THE DOLLAR IS DEAD FOLKS,,, GET READY !!!</Title><Msg>WE need to get our families ready for inflation and a crash</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1365746679468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 02:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365746793174-4</Id><Title>CHANGE THE TWO PARTY SYSTEM AND GET RID OF THE BANKSTERS!!</Title><Msg>The corporation are hurting the world debt is slavery</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1365746793174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 02:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365766192110-5</Id><Topic><Title>MAXIPAD MAXIPAD</Title><Username>max_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1365730262552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He does, the commie POS. He dont need knee pads he is used to it and has hardened skin on his knees. Must be his job and I bet he dos'nt pay tax's.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1365766192110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 07:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365772801435-6</Id><Title>Fracking rule is ‘imminent’</Title><Msg>Fracking rule is ‘imminent’ By Ben Geman and Zack Colman - 04/11/13 06:39 PM ET GET READY: The Interior Department is on the cusp of releasing a controversial, heavily lobbied proposal to regulate oil-and-gas “fracking” on public lands. Outgoing Interior Secretary Ken Salazar told a House subcommittee Thursday that the draft regulations will surface soon. “The rule is imminent,” Salazar told an Appropriations Committee subpanel. “I expect that my successor will be announcing it in the very near future.” It’s Interior’s second swing at the plan after pulling back an earlier version in January. The measure will require disclosure of chemicals used in the hydraulic fracturing process, and also includes provisions on well integrity and management of “flowback” water. The rule faces pushback from industry groups who fear new costs and say state-level regulation is protective enough, while green groups are in favor of new federal requirements. Industry lobbyists, environmentalists and others have held around a dozen meetings with the White House Office of Management and Budget on the plan this year. The latest one listed was on March 28, when Exxon representatives met with OMB. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/293479-overnight-energy-fracking-rule-is-imminent-outgoing-interior-chief-says</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365772801435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 09:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365778020508-7</Id><Title>EU policy: nearly eliminate fossil fuels by 2050</Title><Msg>Sweden has targeted 0 carbon emissions by that date. Oil &amp; gas will be eliminated by bio-fuels, and nuclear by solar &amp; wind. Germany has set similar objectives. European scientific institutions, education, and industry do not function as American ones either. Government led industrial policy and educational policy has been an ongoing part of European economic development for nearly 400 years. It certainly works. Whether it be in the area of theological indoctrination, militaristic and patriotic indoctrination, or the fostering of environmental and scientific ethos such policies do work. Germanic Europe leads the world in scientists and engineers per capita and possesses an education system none can surpass. The combined industrial power is awesome and growing. China cannot compete with it, and routinely runs trade deficits with the region. This did not happen by accident. The technology that has been decreed will not remain bottled up in Europe either, although Germanic Europe will certainly profit most from its sale... Such a future has no place for companies whose business model is based around fossil fuels.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365778020508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365781707564-8</Id><Title>The desperation of China...</Title><Msg>They will become very desperate as their fossil fuel based economy falters in the years ahead. The enormous expansion of automobile use they have encouraged by subsidized highway construction and fuel use will devastate their trade balance and ultimately their economy. Their industry is not technologically competitive and will face major problems competing against (European) industrial systems they do not understand. They do well against American industry mainly because of the stupidity of the US government and its tradition of free markets and liberalism, but such methods do not work when they are matched against Masters of an art they are only just learning. China's desperation will be vented by savage reductions in prices in the low tech industrial fields they specialize in which will be strongly deflationary, mainly for the US economy which is a key dumping ground for their exports. They will certainly be forced to slam the breaks on their oil imports, by setting quotas when their economy moves into a trade deficit. This will crash the oil price and create still more deflation.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365781707564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 11:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365783178595-9</Id><Topic><Title>MAXIPAD MAXIPAD</Title><Username>max_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1365730262552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He does, the commie POS. He dont need knee pads he is used to it and has hardened skin on his knees. Must be his job and I bet he dos'nt pay tax's. ref_steve Grow up and stop this BS. You are just as bad as Maxi fueling the fire. Nothing either of you post has anything to do with XOM so bug off. Dismissed.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1365783178595</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365785632924-10</Id><Topic><Title>MAXIPAD MAXIPAD</Title><Username>max_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1365730262552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ its just entertainment. Its worse in hollywood dim.</Msg><Username>bluemax19</Username><Timestamp>1365785632924</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 12:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365787305721-11</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like XOM Is On The Verge Of A Massive Up Trend</Title><Username>mcknightgertrude537</Username><Timestamp>1365787074721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 13:17:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I already knew this...Good job.</Msg><Username>terrirusso425</Username><Timestamp>1365787305721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 13:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365789881564-12</Id><Title>Biofuels are not the problem</Title><Msg>By Jeff Lautt, CEO, POET - 04/12/13 10:15 AM ET You’re paying more for gasoline. The oil industry’s pocketing the profits. And they don’t want you to know it. Complaints about biofuels this year are the latest shiny ball for the oil industry, meant to distract the public from what’s really biting into their household budgets. Refining margins this year have been at record levels. Oil companies are making more money, even as gas prices for February and March were the highest in history. If you want to know why you’re paying more at the pump, look no further than oil executives’ pockets. How they keep a straight face while espousing concern for American drivers is beyond me. I have no problem with an industry making money. Oil is a business, and they have every right to profits. What I object to is them pretending their substantial profits don’t exist while they point the finger at renewable fuel as the cause of higher prices. They need to own up to where our extra money spent at the pump is going. Expect to see more of the same misdirection from the oil industry through the rest of 2013. This year is pivotal for that industry because starting in 2014, they will have to begin offering consumers the option of ethanol blends such as E15 (15 percent ethanol) in order to meet the country’s renewable fuel targets. Rather than help America make a transition, they have spent their money on lobbying, press conferences, lawsuits, “research” and similar tactics to block consumer choice. In much of America, drivers can choose between 90 percent gasoline or 100 percent gasoline. And that’s how the oil industry wants to keep it. E15 offers an additional option, one that threatens to further erode oil companies’ gasoline market share as it ushers in a new kind of biofuel from sources such as crop residue, grasses and wood waste. Those opposed to E15 do not have to use it. But those who want to use it should be allowed to do so. The time to start offering it has come.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365789881564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 14:04:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365791176684-13</Id><Title>Bill to ban E15 gas is introduced in the U.S. House</Title><Msg>Bill to ban E15 gas is introduced in the U.S. House April 12, 2013 HR 1462, a bill to reform the Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS) to eliminate ethanol requirements, has been introduced in the U.S. House of Representatives. HR 1462 aims to reform the RFS by eliminating its corn-based ethanol requirements, reducing the requirements of cellulosic ethanol and banning E15 in the marketplace. The Specialty Equipment Market Association (SEMA) says the current RFS mandates that an increasing amount of ethanol or other biofuels be blended into gasoline each year -- levels that are now becoming unattainable in a free marketplace. Congress enacted the RFS in 2005 and then dramatically expanded the volume of renewables to be blended each year, from 9 billion gallons in 2008 to 36 billion gallons by 2022. The RFS has been the driving force behind a decision by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) to allow the content of ethanol in gasoline to rise from 10% (E10) to 15% (E15) ethanol. E15 will then become the way refiners meet RFS mandates. In addition, the RFS requires fuel producers to meet unattainable mandates for other types of biofuels, such as cellulosic ethanol (wood, grasses and other agricultural byproducts) that have not yet been developed. SEMA supports other proposed legislation (HR 875 and S. 344) to halt E15 sales. moderntiredealerDOTcom/news/story/2013/04/bill-to-ban-e15-gas-is-introduced-in-the-u-s-houseDOTaspx?prestitial=1</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365791176684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 14:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365795212364-14</Id><Topic><Title>Plan Your Next Move For XOM</Title><Username>amyvincent99</Username><Timestamp>1365794143137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 15:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful information</Msg><Username>josalas22</Username><Timestamp>1365795212364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 15:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365802171856-15</Id><Topic><Title>Plan Your Next Move For XOM</Title><Username>amyvincent99</Username><Timestamp>1365794143137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 15:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Key logger site from India see the .in ? Better get your computer fixed before doing any financial Banking/Brokerage trading.</Msg><Username>basherbuste_r</Username><Timestamp>1365802171856</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 17:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365803500845-16</Id><Topic><Title>The desperation of China...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365781707564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 11:48:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you think they're building up their Military/Navy/etc. Currency wars, trade wars, food wars, fuel wars, water wars......you name it. We are living in a dangerous world my friend....an it's going to get worse...faster.</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1365803500845</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 17:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365803905123-17</Id><Topic><Title>Plan Your Next Move For XOM</Title><Username>amyvincent99</Username><Timestamp>1365794143137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 15:15:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you should be happy the markets going up...if the market just went down...you wouldnt be able to trade it anymore.</Msg><Username>coffeyg74</Username><Timestamp>1365803905123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 17:58:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365813203086-18</Id><Title>Solar = 100% Of New US Power Capacity In March, Renewables = 82% In 1st Quarter</Title><Msg>Solar = 100% Of New US Power Capacity In March, Renewables = 82% In 1st Quarter by Tim on April 12, 2013 Renewables are leading again. The Federal Energy Regulatory Commission’s Office of Energy Projects has just released a report for the first three months of 2013. The report is called the “Energy Infrastructure Update” and it shows that renewable energy sources (biomass, geothermal, solar, water, wind) have accounted for 82% of all new domestic electrical generating capacity installed for the first quarter of 2013. The total amount of the combined renewables came in at 1,546 MW. So far this year, coal, nuclear, and oil have provided no new generating capacity, which is good news to say the least. Natural gas came in with 340 MW of electrical generating capacity installed for the first quarter of 2013. The breakdown of the report put wind energy in the lead for quarter one, with 6 new “units” totaling 958 MW. Second place went to solar, with 38 units totaling 537 MW accounting for over 28% of new power capacity in Q1. (Obviously, this doesn’t include small- or medium-scale solar installations, which account for about half of all US solar power capacity.) During the first quarter of 2012, solar only installed 264 MW, so this year solar has more than doubled its newly installed capacity (537 MW). The big winner in renewables for the month of March was solar, which produced 100% of the new electrical generation capacity, with 7 new units with a combined capacity of 44 MW in California, Nevada, New Jersey, Hawaii, Arizona, and North Carolina. In the past couple of years, the installed price of solar has dropped about 40%. This has certainly spurred on a good portion of the growth, but the price is projected to fall much more in the coming years. So what lies ahead? One of the other key players in the renewable mix in quarter one was biomass, with... solarloveDOTorg/renewables-provide-82-of-new-us-electrical-generating-capacity-in-1q2013/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365813203086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 20:33:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365813728700-19</Id><Topic><Title>Solar = 100% Of New US Power Capacity In March, Renewables = 82% In 1st Quarter</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365813203086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 20:33:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... with 28 units that totaled 46 MW. And even water was in the picture for the first quarter, with 4 new units with an installed capacity of 5.4 MW. Geothermal is lagging behind so far this year with no new capacity reported. Here’s a full table: Nearly 16% of total installed US generating capacity now goes to renewable energy sources. Here’s a break down of the current installed generating capacity from the report: Water — 8.53% Wind — 5.18% Biomass — 1.3% Solar — 0.44% Geothermal — 0.32% For a comparison, that is more than these combined: Nuclear — 9.15% Oil — 3.54% According to the US Energy Information Administration, the actual net electrical generation from renewable energy sources in the United States now totals a bit more than 13%. (Just a note since generating capacity is not the same as actual generation.) It is clear, however, that renewable energy sources continue to dominate the new electrical generating capacity being brought on-line in the United States. It seems like with every one of these reports it becomes clearer that coal is slowly fading away and a cleaner future is on its way with renewables.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365813728700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 20:42:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365819298881-20</Id><Title>Court sides with Iowa solar installer in dispute with utility</Title><Msg>Posted on 04/12/2013 by Kari Lydersen Solar panels installed by Eagle Point Solar atop Dubuque’s municipal building. (Photo courtesy Eagle Point Solar) Editor’s note: This story was updated to include a response from Alliant Energy. An Iowa district court ruling March 29 could be a “landmark decision” for solar development in the state, in Eagle Point Solar President Barry Shear’s words, by allowing the company to sell electricity directly to the Dubuque city government to power the municipal building where the panels are located. Previously, the Iowa Utility Board had prohibited Eagle Point from selling electricity to Dubuque from the rooftop installation. The utility board ruling came after the local utility, Alliant Energy, had complained to the Dubuque City Council in summer 2011 that the then-in-the-works project violated their exclusive right to provide electricity to the city. The utility argued that Eagle Point would be acting as a utility and encroaching on Alliant’s monopoly territory by selling electricity from its panels to power the building. The Utility Board agreed with Alliant in a March 2012 ruling. But the Polk County District Court found that Eagle Point would not be acting as a utility, so the company can sign what is known as a third-party power purchase agreement (PPA) with Dubuque to sell the city electricity from the panels, which are owned by an investor and managed by Eagle Point. Experts consider the ruling crucial to the development of solar installations on the rooftops or grounds of city buildings, universities, churches, hospitals and other non-profit institutions in Iowa. That’s because non-profit institutions can’t take advantage of the tax breaks considered key to making solar financially viable for many property owners. However, a for-profit solar developer can install panels on a.. midwestenergynewsDOTcom/2013/04/12/court-sides-with-iowa-solar-installer-in-dispute-with-utility/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365819298881</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 22:14:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365819762596-21</Id><Title>E.P.A. Will Delay Rule Limiting Carbon Emissions at New Power Plants</Title><Msg>By JOHN M. BRODER Published: April 12, 2013 WASHINGTON – The Environmental Protection Agency said Friday that it would delay issuance of a new rule limiting emissions of carbon dioxide and other greenhouse gases from new power plants after the electric power industry objected on legal and technical grounds. The rule, proposed a year ago and scheduled to be finalized on Saturday, would have put in place the first restrictions on climate-altering gases from the power sector in the United States. Agency officials said it would be rewritten to address the concerns raised by the industry, which said that strict new carbon standards could not be met using existing technology. An E.P.A. spokeswoman said the agency had received more than two million comments on the proposed rule. She would not speculate on when a revised standard would be issued. “We are continuing to work on the rule,” said Alisha Johnson, the E.P.A. press secretary. “No timetable has been set.” The draft rule, introduced last March by Lisa P. Jackson, then the E.P.A. administrator, would have limited carbon dioxide emissions from new power plants to 1,000 pounds per megawatt-hour. Gina McCarthy, the head of the agency’s air and radiation office that wrote the rule, has been tapped to head the E.P.A. Her nomination is currently before the Senate. Newer power plants burning natural gas already easily meet the new standards, so the rule presents little obstacle for new gas plants. But the rule would have effectively killed any new coal-fired plants, because they emit nearly twice as much carbon per unit of electricity as natural gas plants and there is currently no available technology to bring their emissions under the limit. Coal today provides about 40 percent of electricity generation in the United States and is the single-largest source of emissions associated with global warming. The... nytimesDOTcom/2013/04/13/science/earth/epa-to-delay-emissions-rule-at-new-power-plants.html?_r=0</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365819762596</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 22:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365819899798-22</Id><Topic><Title>E.P.A. Will Delay Rule Limiting Carbon Emissions at New Power Plants</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365819762596</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 22:22:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EPA official: Carbon rules for existing power plants ‘on the table’ in 2014 Posted on 04/12/2013 by Environment and Energy Daily midwestenergynewsDOTcom/2013/04/12/epa-official-carbon-rules-for-existing-power-plants-on-the-table-in-2014/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365819899798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 22:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365820753289-23</Id><Title>State May Start Funding Energy-Storage Projects for Solar and Wind</Title><Msg>Proposal comes at a time when New Jersey is slashing funds for most sources of renewable energy By Tom Johnson, April 10, 2013 in Energy &amp; Environment|7 Comments For the first time, New Jersey’s clean energy program is proposing that it hand out money to energy-storage projects, which are viewed by many experts as a crucial element in helping technologies like solar and wind become more successful. In a straw proposal developed in the Office of Clean Energy at the New Jersey Board of Public Utilities, the staff is suggesting that the state allocate between $5 million and $10 million over the next four years for energy storage. The proposal says it may award up to $2.5 million in state fiscal year 2014. Over four years, the total could rise to $10 million. Because the sun doesn’t always shine and the wind doesn't always blow, energy storage is viewed as key to promoting cleaner ways of producing electricity. Energy storage is still under development. Given the intermittent nature of solar and wind, it is viewed as crucial to making clean energy competitive with conventional technologies like natural gas and coal-fired plants. The proposal comes at a time when the state is slashing funding for renewable energy, proposing just $7.5 million in the 2014 budget to finance solar, biomass, onshore wind, and water energy. Nevertheless, the state has aggressive goals to have 22.5 percent of its electricity produced from renewable energy sources by 2020, a target many environmental groups think should be more ambitious. New Jersey has been a leader in promoting the development of solar installations, ranking only behind California and Arizona in the number of systems it has installed. The state is also aggressively trying to promote the development of offshore wind, establishing a goal of 1,100 megawatts by 2020. Both goals would be bolstered by the... njspotlightDOcom/stories/13/04/09/state-may-start-funding-energy-storage-projects-for-solar-and-wind-power/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365820753289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 22:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365821296286-24</Id><Topic><Title>Bill to ban E15 gas is introduced in the U.S. House</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365791176684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 14:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The senate won't even consider a HOUSE BILL to ban E15 and President Obama wouldn't sign it if it ever reached the oval office. American farmers are extremely busy planting the largest corn crop in history. A massive corn suplus and an inexpensive flood of ethanol is just months away!</Msg><Username>moooooooooooooooooooooooo4u</Username><Timestamp>1365821296286</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 22:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>