<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359091312441-1</Id><Topic><Title>Bills seek to reduce or remove ethanol from Maine gas</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359087820802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:23:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not that related to XOM, but thank God someone wants to get rid of ethanol fuel. Atrocious idea. Irving? Huh, odd.</Msg><Username>rwilson31781</Username><Timestamp>1359091312441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 00:21:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359092143041-2</Id><Topic><Title>Trek back to $80 begins soon</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359065370898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:09:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The P/E is</Msg><Username>rwilson31781</Username><Timestamp>1359092143041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 00:35:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359092353409-3</Id><Topic><Title>Trek back to $80 begins soon</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359065370898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:09:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It cut off my message, sorry - long story short, P/E is less than 10 not 12. EPS is 12. Oil is a good sector. Buy on weakness (low oil prices) in the summer. CVX, COP, BP, RDS, BP, TOT are all nice examples of the sector if you don't want to pay the market cap/stability premium for XOM. Share buybacks are better than dividends because they do the same thing, but SB are only taxed once, on sale and dividends are taxed if you DRIP and taxed again when you sell.</Msg><Username>rwilson31781</Username><Timestamp>1359092353409</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 00:39:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359112802077-4</Id><Topic><Title>Where's that arrogant little nut Maxwiz?</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359057863003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:04:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxipad never had 2 nickels to rub together and maybe some redneck gave him an attitude adjustment. The commie POS might have gotten himself deported.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1359112802077</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 06:20:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359119264736-5</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation UPDATED CHARTS!</Title><Username>rosalselawendy</Username><Timestamp>1359044946110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 11:29:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for great articles. Nice to be here.</Msg><Username>lowry1genevieve</Username><Timestamp>1359119264736</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:07:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359122079762-6</Id><Topic><Title>Trek back to $80 begins soon</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359065370898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:09:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see FY2012 EPS to be $7.91 if they meet quarterly estimates when they report next week. Slap your PE of 10 on it and what do you have? EPS is 12? On what planet?</Msg><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359122079762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:54:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359122964985-7</Id><Title>State Sponsored Elitism</Title><Msg>The cornerstone of the German technological excellence for the past 200 years has been state subsidized education. It may seem that such a system helps "spread the wealth," to use a very crude and ignorant phrase from a notable American, but the reality is it does not, and it is precisely because it does not that it works well for the economy and society. The way the system works is the state pays for the education, but system is designed to prevent most people from reaching the top. All one need do to ensure that outcome is to measure people objectively and one will find that most people simply do not measure up - in other words all people are not created equal, and they are not endowed with some magical inalienable "right" to succeed. Most people are just stupid or lazy or both. To get to University you need to pass your Abitur which is designed to fail most people. To get the right to take the Abitur you need to get through Gymnasium. To get to Gymnasium you need to be gifted, and the vast majority of people fall short. There are ways for people who failed on the Gymnasium path to get into University but they are time consuming and require many steps, and easily filter out people of low ability or commitment. When the state collects taxes from all the people who fail to reach the upper echelons to pay the way for those that do that is subsidizing success and taxing failure. The system is by definition elitist, which is precisely the intent, and the power of the approach is evident in the results... Once someone has emerged at the pinnacle of such a system they are in a very powerful position in society, indeed. State employment opportunities and opportunities in the private sector are engineered to favor them or quite often just mandated by regulation as a sort of entitlement. In any event the assumption is that if the state has spent so much money and effort educating someone, that they are qualified for certain jobs. The system is also designed to tailor the outcomes for those who cannot reach the top - through education applicable to their station in society. Wasting money trying to elevate people who simply cannot be elevated is not useful to society, and doesn't help the prospects of the failures either... That is collectivism German style... Many other countries follow a very similar program. America would do well to adopt the approach.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359122964985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:09:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359125950673-8</Id><Title>HUSA HUOUSTON AMERICAN ENERGY</Title><Msg>HUSA</Msg><Username>aenadeona</Username><Timestamp>1359125950673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:59:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359127621714-9</Id><Topic><Title>XOM might be the next SEFE!</Title><Username>williamhardin10</Username><Timestamp>1359119742570</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:15:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>listen to the masters</Msg><Username>haydenjeremy942</Username><Timestamp>1359127621714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:27:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359128247755-10</Id><Title>Congressional Democrats Form Climate Change Task Force</Title><Msg>Congressional Democrats Form Climate Change Task Force Posted by News Editor in Air/Climate, Gov/Politics, Latest News, RSS on January 24, 2013 4:32 WASHINGTON, DC, January 24, 2013 (ENS) – Climate change is getting renewed attention in Congress. Representative Henry Waxman of California and Senator Sheldon Whitehouse of Rhode Island, both Democrats, today announced the formation of a Task Force on Climate Change that will be active in both the House and the Senate. Inspired by President Barack Obama’s statement in his inaugural address that failing to respond to the threat of climate change would “betray our children and future generations,” the task force aims to focus Congressional and public attention on developing effective policy responses, and will be open to all Members of Congress interested in collaborating on this issue. Senator Sheldon Whitehouse, left, and Representative Henry Waxman announce the Climate Change Task Force, January 24, 2013 (Image from video courtesy Rep. Waxman) The Task Force will be co-chaired by Waxman, who serves as the Ranking Member of the House Energy and Commerce Committee, and Whitehouse, who chairs the Subcommittee on Oversight for the Senate Environment and Public Works Committee. “Congress and the public need to understand that climate change impacts are turning out worse than expected and our window to act is closing,” said Waxman. “This threat is not waiting until we are ready to deal with it. That is why I am pleased to join with Senator Whitehouse to work to educate our colleagues and all Americans about the magnitude of the problem and the urgency of the threat we are confronting.” “I’m honored to join Representative Waxman in this effort,” said Whitehouse. “Carbon pollution is wreaking havoc on our atmosphere and on our oceans, and it’s time to bring all hands on deck as we seek to meet that challenge.” “We intend this new group to bring the attention and energy to the issue necessary to get something done,” he said. “I look forward to working with President Obama, Chairman [Barbara] Boxer in the Senate, and any of our other colleagues who wish to join us.” Senator Boxer, who chairs the Senate Environment and Public Works Committee, said, “Dangerous climate change poses an urgent threat and we have a responsibility to address that threat.” On January 11, Boxer announced that environmental attorney Joe Mendelson will join her EPW team as chief climate counsel. Previously, Mendelson served as the policy director of the Climate and Energy Program at the National Wildlife Federation. He played a key role in a landmark 2007 U.S. Supreme Court decision that established that the Environmental Protection Agency has jurisdiction over reducing carbon pollution from motor vehicles. As a first order of business in the new task force, Waxman, Whitehouse and Congressman Ed Markey of Massachusetts, the Ranking Member of the House Committee on Natural Resources, today sent a letter to President Obama. They applauded his recognition of climate change in his inaugural address, pledged to help him address this issue, and urged him to quickly develop a comprehensive climate change plan. Petersburg coal-fired power plant operated by Indianaopolis Power &amp; Light emits greenhouse gases. (Photo by IP&amp;L) “The window to deal effectively with a warming planet and to mitigate long-term risks is quickly closing,” they wrote. “Meanwhile, oil and coal industries continue to spend hundreds of millions of dollars denying the science, exaggerating the costs, and confusing the public. As a result, too few Americans fully appreciate the magnitude of the problem or the urgency of the threat we are confronting.” The lawmakers ask for “presidential leadership” to “forge together a national consensus that insists on addressing climate change.” They ask the President not to wait for Congress to act, but to use his administration’s “broad authorities” to lower heat-trapping emissions, to encourage clean energy research and development and develop adaptive strategies. “We in Congress need your leadership most of all,” the Democratic lawmakers wrote. “Virtually all Republicans in Congress opposed comprehensive climate legislation in the 11th Congress, and they voted to strip EPA of regulatory authority in the last one.” “Progress in Congress may be so difficult or protracted that you should not hesitate to act,” they wrote. “Congress will benefit from knowing what actions you will take administratively to meet your climate pledge and protect our nation. And we will benefit even more from a concerted effort between your administration and your allies in Congress to marshal the latent public support into a political force.” Environmentalists greeted the climate task force with enthusiasm. Environmental Defense Fund President Fred Krupp said, “I’m very happy to hear that Senator Sheldon Whitehouse and Congressman Henry Waxman are creating a new task force to fight climate change. In his inaugural address, President Obama called on all of us to protect our children and future generations from the dangers of climate change.” “At EDF, we’re grateful to these lawmakers for their ongoing leadership on this critical issue, and we stand ready to help the task force however we can.” Krupp said the task force, along with Senator Barbara Boxer’s recently announced “climate clearinghouse,” are steps towards “reducing the pollution that endangers us.” Boxer said in December that this year she will hold weekly “open forums” on climate change, and she hopes both Republicans and Democrats will participate in the “climate change clearinghouse” to discuss potential global warming legislation. “We are going to review the latest information, we are going to work on supporting a major bill, we are also going to work on various smaller provisions that we think will move us forward and focus on green jobs, energy efficiency and making sure that we get the carbon out of the air, and work with the administration on some executive stuff,” Boxer told “The Hill.” Boxer said a major climate change bill would cap carbon emissions and find ways to “harden our infrastructure to protect our people against extreme weather.” ens-newswireDOTcom/2013/01/24/congressional-democrats-form-climate-change-task-force/ We</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359128247755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 10:37:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359130380974-11</Id><Topic><Title>SQUAWK BOX to feature XOM CEO!</Title><Username>rex.kenneth</Username><Timestamp>1359122035521</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:53:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report , thanks !</Msg><Username>april_simpson</Username><Timestamp>1359130380974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:13:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359130508344-12</Id><Topic><Title>Secret XOM Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>ashley.haggerty</Username><Timestamp>1359055637792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:27:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report , thanks !</Msg><Username>april_simpson</Username><Timestamp>1359130508344</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:15:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359130808287-13</Id><Title>Michigan officials to study future energy needs</Title><Msg>Michigan officials to study future energy needs By JOHN FLESHER AP Environmental Writer Posted: Thursday, 01/24/13 09:49 pm TRAVERSE CITY (AP) — Gov. Rick Snyder’s administration is kicking off a year-long study to help set future energy policies for Michigan, including whether to require expanded use of wind, the sun and other renewable electricity sources. The Republican governor promised to dig into the issue last fall after voters soundly rejected a ballot proposal that would have ordered the state’s utilities to generate 25 percent of their power from alternatives to coal, natural gas and other fossil fuels by 2025. Existing law sets a 10 percent minimum that must be met by 2015. The study is designed to provide Snyder and the state Legislature with information they’ll need to devise a new energy strategy as the deadline arrives, said John Quackenbush, chairman of the Michigan Public Service Commission. Quackenbush is leading the project with Steven Bakkal, director of the Michigan Energy Office. It will begin with seven public meetings around the state, starting Feb. 14 in Lansing and ending April 22 in Traverse City. The meetings will give people a chance to provide information for reports that will be submitted to the governor and lawmakers. “What we’re interested in at this point is gathering information — studies and data that will guide policymakers and help them make good decisions,” Quackenbush said this week. A law enacted in 2008 established the 10 percent renewable energy standard. It also required electric utilities to reduce power usage by 5.5 percent and gas providers to achieve a 3.85 percent cut by 2015. Another provision guarantees that one-tenth of the electricity sold in Michigan will come from suppliers other than regulated utilities. The study will deal with all those topics, Bakkal said. Environmental groups, contending the renewable standard was insufficient, gathered enough petition signatures to force the statewide vote on a 25 percent minimum, contending it would help Michigan keep pace with competing states in clean energy development and create jobs. Utilities said it would hit customers with higher electric bills and make supplies less reliable. When releasing a special message on energy and the environment last November, Snyder made no commitment to strengthening the standard but told The Associated Press he favored increased use of renewables. “The real question is at what pace should that happen,” he said. Bakkal said the study would examine the best available data showing how well Michigan energy providers have lived up to existing requirements. Another question to be explored is the relative costs of generating and transmitting renewable energy as opposed to energy from conventional sources, he said. “The governor is interested in benchmarking — how we compare to other states,” Bakkal said. The Michigan Environmental Council, which campaigned for the unsuccessful ballot initiative, will attend the public meetings and submit reports it commissioned that deal with costs and pollution, spokesman Hugh McDiarmid Jr. said. “We believe that if the governor is looking at this from a data-driven perspective ... we’ll come up with a better energy plan than we have now,” McDiarmid said Thursday. Consumers Energy also will provide information, spokesman Jeff Holyfield said. “Michigan should have an informed discussion about what’s the best path forward after 2015,” he said. “We’ll be participating and talking about the benefits that the 2008 energy law has brought to Michigan families and businesses.” macombdailyDOTcom/article/20130124/NEWS03/130129634/michigan-officials-to-study-future-energy-needs?mobredirect=true</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359130808287</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 11:20:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359133901431-14</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation UPDATED CHARTS!</Title><Username>rosalselawendy</Username><Timestamp>1359044946110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 11:29:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I followed your reports since last week. Nice work.</Msg><Username>knowledgesondra</Username><Timestamp>1359133901431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:11:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359134596666-15</Id><Topic><Title>State Sponsored Elitism</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359122964985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 09:09:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this approach sounds very right wing there is a reason for that. It was invented by Prussian administrators, intent on replicating the elitism of the Prussian officer class but on the level of an entire society. Of course it worked. The fundamental inequality flowing from genetic and behavior traits is systematically reinforced with the resources of the state. The inequality of wealth that the Prussian aristocrats tried to enforce with special privileges, apart and parallel to this system, has long since been abolished. Such things as income "redistribution" to elevate those of low ability becomes quite impossible when the system is focusing the opportunity to accumulate income and wealth into the hands of an aristocracy of merit. It could well be possible to redistribute wealth away from some lazy #$%$ who somehow came into wealth, but then that is a good outcome. This is government by the Philosophy of Right, of by and for the "Universal Class."</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359134596666</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:23:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359134773745-16</Id><Topic><Title>XOM might be the next SEFE!</Title><Username>williamhardin10</Username><Timestamp>1359119742570</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 08:15:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are amazing fact</Msg><Username>francisco.wright</Username><Timestamp>1359134773745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:26:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359135228434-17</Id><Title>GREEDINNESS MADE ME LLOOOOK STUPPIDD!</Title><Msg>DID NOT SELL APPLE @700.</Msg><Username>mlg4044</Username><Timestamp>1359135228434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:33:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359136415394-18</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359039485760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:58:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh BTW is sold the bonds this morning while you Yanks were probably sleeping @3.244% ytm...+0.20%... 100% £ short term at 0.5%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359136415394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:53:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359136641668-19</Id><Title>IWEA welcomes Ireland-UK wind energy agreement</Title><Msg>IWEA welcomes Ireland-UK wind energy agreement Robin WhitlockFriday, 25 January 2013 The agreement between the two countries can give Ireland a framework to become a renewable electricity exporter of scale before 2020 says the Irish Wind Energy Association A Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) has been signed by the Irish Minister for Communications, Energy and Natural Resources, Pat Rabitte TD and the UK’s Secretary of State for Energy, Edward Davey. This will in turn lead to a full inter-governmental agreement to allow Ireland to export some of its wind-generated electricity to Britain. “We welcome this hugely important initial step in delivering an energy trade agreement and we commend both the Irish and British governments for their work and commitment in continuing to advance this important opportunity for both countries” said Kenneth Matthews, CEO of the Irish Wind Energy Association (IWEA). “This agreement, as highlighted in IWEA’s document, “Export Policy - A renewables development policy framework for Ireland” could have enormous benefits for Ireland. For example, up to 30,000 indigenous jobs could be created countrywide, coupled with investments of over €18bn by 2020 if the required enablers along with this agreement are put in place. In addition to this, it has the potential to directly assist local authorities by increasing current annual commercial rates from €11.5 Million in 2012 to €70 Million by 2020. All these benefits will provide a huge boost to both the local and national economy which will be driven by a sustainable industry that only keeps expanding in terms of ambition and scope.” Mr Matthews went on to state that the electricity sector in Ireland is on the cusp of transformational change with renewables, and wind energy in particular, at the heart of it. The efficient use of existing and new interconnectors to increase Ireland’s ability to integrate wind energy and to export surplus wind-generated electricity will be central to this transition. The new agreement will also provide further confidence and assurance to investors and energy companies alike and is something that the IWEA has worked towards consistently and diligently for many years. Mr Matthews added that the IWEA continues to call on the Irish government to establish a Government and Industry Implementation Group which would seek to maximise the opportunities available to Ireland from exporting renewable energy, thereby positioning the country as one of the premier destinations for investment in the sector. “Today’s announcement is great news for Ireland Inc. and a major boon for developers” commented Feilim O’Caoimh, Head of Commercial and Renewable Energy Units at McDowell Purcell. “While the two governments must now work together to develop a full intergovernmental agreement between the two jurisdictions and agree a competitive tender for the right to construct the interconnectors – it is important to note that it will be for developers rather than government to acquire and develop the wind farm sites themselves.” According to Mr O’Caoimh a number of substantial developers have been acquiring land rights for the purposes of servicing the interconnectors but a myriad of legal issues lie in wait, including the securing of foreshore licenses on either side of the Irish Sea and establishing a regime for purchasing the electricity in the UK or accommodating it within the existing regime. “Undoubtedly, planning for projects of this scale is going to be a significant issue” he said, “and it will be interesting to see if the Irish government has any appetite to modify the existing planning regime.” Further information: Irish Wind Energy Association (IWEA) renewableenergymagazineDOTcom/article/iwea-welcomes-irelanduk-wind-energy-agreement-20130125</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359136641668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:57:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359136678498-20</Id><Topic><Title>GREEDINNESS MADE ME LLOOOOK STUPPIDD!</Title><Username>mlg4044</Username><Timestamp>1359135228434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:33:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is unfortunate... Try harder next time. Wouldn't it be better if the state made it possible for you to accumulate wealth more easily without troubling yourself with speculations you don't seem very good at? --- of course you would have to be intelligent for that to work. That's the German way... Perhaps your children will be able to enjoy such opportunities. One can only hope it comes to Amerika soon enough.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359136678498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:57:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359136940137-21</Id><Title>XOM</Title><Msg>Like Rodney Dangerfield, Exxon gets no respect. But, once again they are #1. That and a dollar will get them a cup of coffee.</Msg><Username>ploddingalong98</Username><Timestamp>1359136940137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:02:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359138848569-22</Id><Title>where is stenchcloud with splitz predictions now?</Title><Msg>now that it is a real probablity? lol stench, where are you buddy??</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1359138848569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:34:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359139120279-23</Id><Topic><Title>XOM</Title><Username>ploddingalong98</Username><Timestamp>1359136940137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:02:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over the past 5 years it's averaged only 4%/year. 30 Year U.S. Treasuries which have a duration nearly identical to the implied duration of this company's investments returned over 8%/year over that period from falling interest rates... You are pleased with that miserable performance? You should realize that per rational mathematical analysis the stock will most certainly decline in value if interest rates rise back to the Jan 2008 level, all else equal...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359139120279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:38:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359139132625-24</Id><Topic><Title>where is stenchcloud with splitz predictions now?</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1359138848569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:34:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>up some ones #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1359139132625</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:38:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359141323919-25</Id><Title>Federal Reserve System losses</Title><Msg>They have most certainly sustained losses on their program of buying long term US bonds and mortgages the past year. All you need do is look at the interest rates they have been buying the bonds to prove that... The market is moving against them, and it is far larger and more powerful than they are... If they sustain their monetary policy and try to fight the combined power of the global market, they will sustain severe losses and eventually their assets will be insufficient to match the money they have borrowed from the US banks. When that happens they will have to ask that the US Treasury somehow recapitalizes them. That would require an Act of Congress. Treasury could print the money or borrow, but either way it would cause interest rates to be permanently higher...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359141323919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 14:15:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359143098171-26</Id><Topic><Title>GREEDINNESS MADE ME LLOOOOK STUPPIDD!</Title><Username>mlg4044</Username><Timestamp>1359135228434</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 12:33:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i can do better than that, i sold $2000 worth of Apple JUST before it began it's rocket to the moon. like $24 share :)</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1359143098171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 14:44:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359146591336-27</Id><Topic><Title>Where's that arrogant little nut Maxwiz?</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359057863003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:04:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359146591336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 15:43:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359148590849-28</Id><Title>Daimler has good taste...</Title><Msg>Kate Upton framed the car very nicely. I hope they gave her plenty of money - the world could use lots more genes like that...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359148590849</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 16:16:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359152150936-29</Id><Topic><Title>Where's that arrogant little nut Maxwiz?</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359057863003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:04:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxipad never got thumbs up rating mostly thumbs down. He took another name. The #$%$ sewer rat traitor could'nt handle the truth.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1359152150936</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:15:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359152757852-30</Id><Topic><Title>Where's that arrogant little nut Maxwiz?</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359057863003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:04:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxipad#$%$ coward c-nt</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1359152757852</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:25:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359154432309-31</Id><Topic><Title>where is stenchcloud with splitz predictions now?</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1359138848569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:34:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>playing hide the salami with karl rove--another great prognosticator landslide--momentum--polls--karl knows</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1359154432309</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 17:53:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359162356709-32</Id><Title>Court delivers blow to biofuel industry in ruling against EPA</Title><Msg>Court delivers blow to biofuel industry in ruling against EPA By Zack Colman - 01/25/13 12:10 PM ET A federal court delivered a blow to the biofuel industry Friday when it ruled the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) must lower certain targets in a key biofuel-blending rule. The U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit sided with the American Petroleum Institute (API), saying the EPA cannot set forward-leaning blending projections for cellulosic biofuel when supplies aren't available to meet the requirements. “[W]e agree with API that EPA’s 2012 projection of cellulosic biofuel production was in excess of the agency’s statutory authority. We accordingly vacate that aspect of the 2012 RFS (renewable fuel standard) rule and remand for further proceedings consistent with this opinion,” the court said in its decision. A biofuel trade group official familiar with the case told The Hill that the court decision creates uncertainty for investment in cellulosic biofuels, a type of “advanced” biofuel made from non-edible feedstock. The cellulosic portion is one component of the renewable fuel standard, the linchpin for the domestic biofuel industry. The petroleum trade group is trying to get Congress to repeal the rule while also fighting it on the legal front. The Friday court decision on the cellulosic portion amounts to the oil-and-gas lobby's first major victory in that effort. The rule requires refiners to blend 36 billion gallons of biofuel into traditional transportation fuel by 2022. Of that total, the EPA had called for refiners to blend 10.45 million ethanol equivalent gallons last year — but producers pumped out just 22,000. API said refiners were forced to buy credits for phantom gallons of cellulosic biofuel to meet the EPA’s targets. It said the EPA should bring its projections in line with actual production levels. The court agreed with that opinion on Friday. "We’re hopeful Congress will take note of this decision and recognizes the way the RFS is constructed encourages this behavior," Bob Greco, API downstream director, told The Hill on Friday. The aggressive blending projections were meant to drive investment into cellulosic biofuels. The biofuel industry has vigorously defended the blending targets, saying any alterations would #$%$ investment. The biofuel industry source said it is too early to tell how investors will respond. The source added that API also has challenged the EPA’s cellulosic production targets for 2011, and that the agency’s projections for this year have not yet been released. The source noted, however, that the court upheld the EPA’s projection of 2 billion gallons of overall advanced biofuels. "[A]lthough we disagree with the court's decision vacating the 2012 cellulosic volumes, today's decision once again rejects broad-brushed attempts to effectively roll back the federal Renewable Fuel Standard," biofuel trade groups said Friday in a join statement. API had contested the advanced biofuel mark as well. But the court said the EPA’s practice of allowing imports of Brazilian sugarcane ethanol and other advanced biofuels was acceptable for meeting the 2 billion gallon threshold. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/279329-court-decision-on-key-rule-delivers-setback-to-biofuel-industry</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359162356709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 20:05:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359162878599-33</Id><Title>Rep. Waxman: Keystone pipeline remarks were ‘misinterpreted’</Title><Msg>Rep. Waxman: Keystone pipeline remarks were ‘misinterpreted’ By Ben Geman - 01/25/13 04:12 PM ET Rep. Henry Waxman (D-Calif.) is “clarifying” comments he made Thursday that appeared to downplay the significance of the Keystone XL oil sands pipeline in battles over climate change. Waxman, a senior Democrat and key ally of green groups, opposes the proposed pipeline but on Thursday called it a “small issue compared to the overall objective” of fighting global warming. “While I was quoted accurately, what I meant to say has been misinterpreted,” Waxman said Friday in a statement clarifying his remarks Thursday. His Friday statement adds: What I was trying to say is that our climate policy must be much bigger and more ambitious than just rejecting the Keystone pipeline. EPA should issue emission standards that reduce carbon pollution from both new and old power plants, as well as other major sources of carbon pollution. The Department of Energy should tighten energy efficiency standards. The State Department should negotiate a phase-out of HFCs as part of the Montreal Protocol. Many other steps are also necessary. Waxman’s Thursday remarks, made at the announcement of a new bicameral climate task force, and Friday clarification arrive in the middle of an intense political and lobbying battle over Keystone. TransCanada Corp.’s proposed pipeline would bring oil from Alberta’s massive oil sands projects to Gulf Coast refineries. Major business groups and a number of unions are pressing the White House to allow construction, while environmentalists have made stopping the pipeline a priority. “My views on the Keystone XL tar sands pipeline have not changed. In fact, my opposition to the pipeline has intensified as the scientific evidence mounts that the impacts of both climate change and the pipeline itself are likely to be even worse than we have expected,” Waxman, the top Democrat on the Energy and Commerce Committee, said Friday. He added: Using tar sands produces far more carbon pollution than conventional oil. That means a massive expansion of tar sands production is a huge step backwards on climate when the imperative of moving forward on climate has never been clearer. Just last week, a new report from the Pembina Institute, based in part on analyses by Canadian banks, confirmed that Keystone XL is critical to expanding tar sands production, which the oil companies plan to almost triple. I have opposed this reckless project from the beginning and I continue to strongly urge the president to reject it. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/279411-rep-waxman-keystone-pipeline-remarks-were-misinterpreted</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359162878599</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 20:14:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359164148701-34</Id><Topic><Title>Money Flowing Out Of Apple Into Exxon Today!</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1359037369599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:22:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You heard vit first from The StenchMan! Now,all the rags are talking about Exxon taking the # 1 spot.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1359164148701</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 20:35:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359169246084-35</Id><Topic><Title>XOM</Title><Username>ploddingalong98</Username><Timestamp>1359136940137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:02:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xom closed the the 2010 year end at(stock price)73.12 up 7.2%,for 2010.xom close the year end for 2011 at 84.76 up 15.9% for the year.i have the Houston chronicle buss. page in front of me.i always save the yr. end buss. pg.its all about your time horizon.i still have a good bit of 14,15 and 28.$ xom.they pay you to hold.lol all</Msg><Username>wdsjr22949</Username><Timestamp>1359169246084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:00:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359172510732-36</Id><Title>Energy Department Weighs Loan to Wind Farm Project</Title><Msg>Energy Department Weighs Loan to Wind Farm Project January 25, 2013, 6:47 p.m. ET By JENNIFER LEVITZ And RYAN TRACY The U.S. Department of Energy is again considering a loan to Cape Wind, the planned Massachusetts offshore wind farm whose request for federal aid was shelved in 2011. In a sign of fresh activity in the Obama administration's loan program to jumpstart renewable-energy production, despite the fallout from government loans to failed solar-panel company Solyndra LLC, Cape Wind's application for a government loan is again under "active review," said a representative for Cape Wind developer Energy Management Inc. of Boston. Cape Wind, which would be the U.S.'s first offshore wind farm, had previously applied to the federal government for a nearly $2 billion guaranteed loan, but is now being considered for a "considerably" smaller loan, with a decision possible by spring, according to a person familiar with the loan application. The Department of Energy currently has the authority to back about $1.5 billion in renewable-energy loans. The federal financing would be an important development for Cape Wind, which for a decade has been trying to build a 468-megawatt, 130-turbine wind farm in Nantucket Sound, off the coast of Cape Cod—provoking an all-encompassing political and environmental debate in the process. The company is also working with BarclaysBARC.LN +0.23% PLC to secure private funding and expects to begin construction by the end of the year. "The Department of Energy loan program was created with bipartisan support to promote energy projects that will reduce greenhouse-gas emissions, create jobs, and help launch new clean-energy industries in America—Cape Wind does all three," Cape Wind spokesman Mark Rodgers said Friday. Republicans have attacked the Department of Energy loan program as an example of wasted taxpayer dollars. Solyndra filed for bankruptcy protection in 2011, after receiving about $528 million in U.S. government loans. The Obama administration has pointed to other successful loans in the program. President Barack Obama prominently addressed climate change and the need for the U.S. to lead a "path towards sustainable energy sources" in his second inaugural address last week. On Friday, Republican U.S. Reps. Paul Broun and James Lankford signed a letter to Energy Secretary Steven Chu expressing concern "that the Department is moving forward with this loan guarantee despite the extensive controversy surrounding departmental management and decision-making associated with this program." Mr. Broun, of Georgia, and Mr. Lankford, of Oklahoma, chair separate House subcommittees that oversee the department. Department of Energy spokesman Bill Gibbons said the more than 30 projects in the department's loan portfolio "have helped us double America's renewable energy capacity in the last four years and are generating $55 billion in economic investment." "As we review applications for the remaining funding, we want to continue to support cutting-edge clean-energy technologies that will help America win the global race for the jobs of the future," he said. In May 2011, the Department of Energy told Cape Wind its loan request was being put on hold, "not terminated," while federal loans were distributed to projects that were more ready to proceed. Since then, the Federal Aviation Administration has given its approval to the wind farm; Cape Wind said the approval meant it had received all required regulatory permits to proceed. Still, several opponents have pending lawsuits in federal court, citing environmental, safety, and historical concerns. Massachusetts political leaders, including Sen. John Kerry and Gov. Deval Patrick, have been vocal supporters of Cape Wind, saying the project would bring jobs and help the nation achieve energy-independence goals. Opponents have included Cape Cod homeowners, from the late Sen. Edward M. Kennedy to Republican donor and energy businessman William Koch. onlineDOTwsjDOTcom/article/SB10001424127887323539804578264173972072866.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359172510732</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:55:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359172711604-37</Id><Topic><Title>OVERPRICED LOOK</Title><Username>voxguitarplayer</Username><Timestamp>1359080072628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 21:14:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we need a 2/1 split to keep up this momentum!</Msg><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1359172711604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 22:58:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359174145412-38</Id><Title>Poet Halts Output at Missouri Ethanol Plant on Corn Shortage</Title><Msg>Poet Halts Output at Missouri Ethanol Plant on Corn Shortage By Mario Parker - Jan 25, 2013 2:00 PM MT 0 Comments Poet LLC, the second-biggest U.S. ethanol producer, said it will idle a plant in Macon, Missouri, because there isn’t enough corn available. The plant, which has the capacity to produce 44 million gallons of the fuel annually, is in one of the areas hardest hit by the worst drought since the 1930s, Sioux Falls, South Dakota- based Poet said in an e-mailed statement. “Macon will temporarily suspend plant operations effective Feb. 1 due primarily to a lack of available local corn,” the company said. Poet said it doen’t have a date for when it will resume output. The company will spend $14.5 million to upgrade the mill while it’s closed. Denatured ethanol for February delivery fell 0.6 cent, or 0.3 percent, to $2.376 a gallon on the Chicago Board of Trade. Prices have gained 8.5 percent this year. Corn for March delivery fell 3.5 cents, or 0.5 percent, to $7.2075 a bushel in Chicago. One bushel makes at least 2.75 gallons of ethanol. Based on March contracts for corn and ethanol, producers are losing 23 cents on each gallon of the fuel made, unchanged from yesterday, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. The figures exclude the revenue that can be made from the sale of dried distillers’ grains, a byproduct of ethanol production that can be fed to livestock. Plants Close Aemetis Inc. (AMTX), another U.S. ethanol producer, idled production at a plant in Keyes, California, on Jan. 15, citing “unprofitable market conditions for corn ethanol,” and will upgrade the operation to make fuel from sorghum as well, it said in a Jan. 17 regulatory filing. Abengoa SA (ABG), a Spanish engineering and renewable energy company, said Jan. 16 it halted output at ethanol mills in York and Ravenna, Nebraska, until market conditions improve. Ethanol production in the week ended Jan. 18 rose 1 percent to 792,000 barrels a day, the U.S. Energy Information Administration said yesterday, rebounding from the lowest level since the Energy Department’s statistical agency began tracking weekly data for the fuel in June 2010. Archer Daniels Midland Co. (ADM), in Decatur, Illinois, is the largest U.S. ethanol producer, according to data from the Renewable Fuels Association, a Washington-based trade group. bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-01-25/poet-halts-output-at-missouri-ethanol-plant-on-corn-shortage-1-.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359174145412</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 23:22:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359174501581-39</Id><Title>California Remains On Track To Reach Aggressive Renewable Energy Goals</Title><Msg>California Remains On Track To Reach Aggressive Renewable Energy Goals by SI Staff on Friday 25 January 2013 comments: 0 California is making steady progress in deploying solar power and other forms of renewable energy, according to remarks by Gov. Jerry Brown, D-Calif., during his state of the state address. "We are…meeting our renewable energy goals - more than 20 percent renewable energy this year," Brown said, according to a transcript posted on his website. "By 2020, we will get at least a third of our electricity from the sun and the wind and other renewable sources - and probably more." The Solar Energy Industries Association (SEIA) praised Brown for reiterating his support for the state's 33% renewable portfolio standard (RPS). "With this stepped-up commitment, additional solar firms throughout California will be in a position to further their growth," SEIA noted in a statement. "Fast-growing solar companies throughout the state have greatly expanded their presence since 2001." A total of approximately 43,700 solar professionals are working at 1,505 California solar companies in California. SEIA noted that the California Solar Initiative and net metering provisions have been key in allowing solar power to flourish in California. The state is currently ranked first in installed solar capacity, according to SEIA data. solarindustrymagDOTcom/e107_plugins/content/contentDOTphp?content.11979</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359174501581</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 23:28:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359176334177-40</Id><Title>GE touts efficiency of latest turbine technology VIDEOS</Title><Msg>GE touts efficiency of latest turbine technology VIDEOS Posted on January 25, 2013 at 4:05 pm by Zain Shauk in Electricity Comments(0) GE gave Houston power executives a presentation Friday on its latest power plant technology, meant to help increase reliance on renewable forms of power. But the GE systems runs on natural gas. The systems help improve the use of renewable energy sources, however, because they can start up quickly and generate a lot of power, almost on demand. That makes them a reliable backup option to solar and wind generators at times when the sun stops shining and the wind stops blowing, said Jonas Seyppel, a senior product marketing manager for GE Energy. One type of plant design could go from operating at a low level, with a capacity of 105 megawatts, to a high rate of 750 megawatts within 30 minutes, he said. Seyppel and other GE representatives toured interested customers through an 88-foot-long truck trailer display filled with models and video screens. The trailer, which expanded to a width of 22 feet, was parked at Minute Maid Park on Friday for the presentations. GE’s latest natural gas combined-cycle power plant design is more efficient than any other plant of its kind, according to the company. The design uses natural gas turbines, which each have a capacity of 250 megawatts. The exhaust heat from those turbines is used to produce steam, which can power steam turbines. Those steam turbines have a capacity of 250 megawatts as well, Seyppel said, while describing a plant concept. That gives the plant an efficiency level of more than 61 percent, he said. See more about the GE plant and turbine technology here: fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/01/25/ge-touts-efficiency-of-latest-natural-gas-turbine-technology/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359176334177</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 23:58:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>