<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-13"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368423425783-1</Id><Title>It may be green, but it's probably not local</Title><Msg>It may be green, but it's probably not local May 13, 2013 Illinois law requires that, if possible, renewable energy should come from Illinois or surrounding states. However, unless a municipality or business explicitly has stated it wants local renewable power, the power it receives is probably from outside Illinois, where energy credits are cheaper. For instance, McCormick Place officials last week announced a deal to offset 100 percent of the convention center's power with renewable wind energy credits. Most likely those credits won't support Illinois wind farms, but wind farms in Iowa, Nebraska and the Dakotas, according to Mel Jones, president and CEO of Sterling Planet. In total, McCormick Place will purchase an estimated 130 million kilowatt-hours of wind power annually in a three-year renewable energy credit purchase program from Sterling Planet. Jones said the contract allows the company to source renewable energy credits from anywhere. He said most Illinois-based energy credits are tied up with firms and utilities attempting to meet Illinois' renewable energy mandates, which makes them more expensive. Even if McCormick Place isn't supporting Illinois wind, Jones said, it's supporting wind power somewhere, which helps drive up demand for renewable energy. The McCormick Place deal was announced at the American Wind Energy Association conference attended by thousands of people involved in the wind energy industry. Gov. Pat Quinn and Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel touted the deal. "Moving to 100 percent wind energy will increase job opportunities and economic development, while moving toward a sustainable future for the city of Chicago," Emanuel said. "It is also clear proof that sustainability can go hand in hand with the creating of a vibrant, thriving business environment." chicagotribuneDOTcom/business/ct-biz-0513-renewables-side-20130513,0,769124DOTstory</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368423425783</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 01:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368423743241-2</Id><Title>Wisconsin gets 8 new E15 pumps</Title><Msg>Wisconsin gets 8 new E15 pumps Wisconsin Ethanol Coalition | May 07, 2013 The Wisconsin Ethanol Coalition is excited to announce eight pumps offering E15 as a choice to consumers. The pumps are located at the SmartStation, 1290 Business Highway 151, Platteville, Wis., a wholly owned subsidiary of Badger State Ethanol. E15 is a new high-octane fuel made up of 15 percent ethanol and 85 percent gasoline. In January 2011, the EPA approved E15 for use in model year 2001 and newer cars, light-duty trucks, SUVs, and flex-fuel vehicles. “We congratulate Badger State Ethanol and Wisconsin’s ethanol industry for working together to bring E15 to the Wisconsin market,” said Joshua Morby of the Wisconsin Ethanol Coalition. “We are honored to be Wisconsin’s first retailer to offer E15 to our customers who have been asking for it,” said Erik Hushitt of Badger State Ethanol. “We hope other retailers follow our lead so that consumers around the state have an opportunity to gain access to a cleaner burning fuel that contributes directly to the billion dollar ethanol industry in Wisconsin.” E15 can be used by more than 75 percent of light duty vehicles on the road today, representing more than 85 percent of the unleaded fuel sold. "E15 offers retailers a chance to set themselves apart by offering a new, exciting fuel to their station that not only confirms their commitment to domestic renewable fuels but also offers them a competitive advantage," Morby said. “We expect retailers around the state to take notice of the demand by consumers for cheaper, cleaner, more homegrown E15.” Consumers wishing to have access to this less expensive option should contact the Wisconsin Ethanol Coalition. ethanolproducerDOTcom/articles/9823/wisconsin-gets-8-new-e15-pumps</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368423743241</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 01:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368424639515-3</Id><Title>£20 million wind farm is opened in Co Antrim</Title><Msg>£20 million wind farm is opened in Co Antrim By Linda Stewart– 08 May 2013 Eighty-six wind farms across Northern Ireland have now been given the go-ahead as part of our drive towards renewables - not to mention many more single turbine planning applications. The latest wind farm to open will generate enough power to meet the electricity demand of nearly 8,000 homes a year. The £20 million Carn Hill development in Newtownabbey, launched by the First and Deputy First Ministers, will use six turbines to produce 13.8MW of power. It’s the first development in Gaelectric’s Northern Ireland portfolio to get up and running. The company is also planning a 15MW windfarm at Inishative near Pomeroy in Co Tyrone which received planning permission in 2010. To date, 46 large wind farms and 40 small windfarms across Northern Ireland have been granted the go-ahead by planning authorities. Environment Minister Alex Attwood told the Belfast Telegraph that there are enough renewable energy applications in the planning system to meet the target of generating 40% of electricity from renewables by 2020. belfasttelegraphDOTcoDOTuk/news/local-national/northern-ireland/20-million-wind-farm-in-opened-in-co-antrim-29252590.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368424639515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 01:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368430048431-4</Id><Topic><Title>£20 million wind farm is opened in Co Antrim</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368424639515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 01:57:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The latest wind farm to open will generate enough power to meet the electricity demand of nearly 8,000 homes a year. " A very small blip on the radar for big oil.</Msg><Username>gold_speculator</Username><Timestamp>1368430048431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 03:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368434641919-5</Id><Topic><Title>racist exxon gas station owners</Title><Username>demsenate4obama</Username><Timestamp>1368372248164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 11:24:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amen to that.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1368434641919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 04:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368447320964-6</Id><Topic><Title>oil &amp; gold crash....</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366032873167</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 09:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368447320964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 08:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368448194700-7</Id><Topic><Title>The Land of the Uneducated</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368365905130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:38:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO. My mother was born in Stamford, Connecticut though, and I'm fairly certain I can speak English better than most Americans, including you and the lunatic above. I would not live in the USA if someone paid me. I endured it for a while because I had to find myself a deutsche amerikanische Gräfin (maybe princess sometimes), someone who would appreciate the beauty and richness of a true Germanic country unpolluted by filth - the sort allowed in under your banner of tired, poor, hungry masses yearning to be free... free to indulge the fantasy of Republican business interests and Democrat electoral machines. I</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368448194700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 08:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368449745560-8</Id><Title>Utilities drop plan for new Ohio natural gas power plant</Title><Msg>Utilities drop plan for new Ohio natural gas power plant</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368449745560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 08:55:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368450179907-9</Id><Title>Natural Gas Export Plans Stir Debate</Title><Msg>Natural Gas Export Plans Stir Debate by The Associated Press May 13, 2013 3:21 AM WASHINGTON (AP) — A domestic natural gas boom already has lowered U.S. energy prices while stoking fears of environmental disaster. Now U.S. producers are poised to ship vast quantities of gas overseas as energy companies seek permits for proposed export projects that could set off a renewed frenzy of fracking. Expanded drilling is unlocking enormous reserves of crude oil and natural gas, offering the potential of moving the country closer to its decades-long quest for energy independence. Yet as the industry looks to profit from foreign markets, there is the specter of higher prices at home and increased manufacturing costs for products from plastics to fertilizers. Companies such as Exxon Mobil and Sempra Energy are seeking federal permits for more than 20 export projects that could handle as much as 29 billion cubic feet of natural gas a day. If approved, the resulting export boom could lead to further increases in hydraulic fracturing, a drilling technique also known as fracking. It has allowed companies to gain access to huge stores of natural gas underneath states from Colorado to New York, but raised widespread concerns about alleged groundwater contamination and even earthquakes. The drilling boom has helped boost U.S. natural gas production by one-third since 2005, with production reaching an all-time high of 25.3 trillion cubic feet last year, according to the U.S. Energy Information Administration. In recent months, however, production has begun to level off as the glut of natural gas keeps U.S. prices down. In response, producers have begun pushing to export the fuel to Europe and Asia, where prices are far higher. Approval of all the projects currently under review by the nprDOTorg/templates/story/story.php?storyId=183534455</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368450179907</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 09:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368450430698-10</Id><Title>Is Canada’s Oil Too Dirty for Europe?</Title><Msg>Is Canada’s Oil Too Dirty for Europe?</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368450430698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 09:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368451632858-11</Id><Title>More than 25,000 megawatts of new gas plants are under construction, in the works or announced through 2017</Title><Msg>... More than 25,000 megawatts of new gas plants are under construction, in the works or announced through 2017, ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368451632858</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 09:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368455060572-12</Id><Topic><Title>The Land of the Uneducated</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368365905130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:38:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cannot for the life of me detect any anti American hatred in Han's posts and I believe he is just critiquing some of our ideas while at the same time waving "die Faune hoch". I also am fond of the new Germany but in a cultural sense but I have nothing good to say about the #$%$ past.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1368455060572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 10:24:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368465440940-13</Id><Title>see massive oil sell-off here</Title><Msg>No real demand here. Too many other alternatives.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368465440940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368467642964-14</Id><Title>UK’s Cameron wants ‘global standard’ on energy payments disclosure</Title><Msg>Ben Geman - 05/13/13 11:19 AM ET British Prime Minister David Cameron wants a global standard under which petroleum and mining companies will report their payments to governments, calling it a way to curb corruption in resource-rich nations. Cameron, who is meeting with President Obama at the White House on Monday, called for the Group of Eight leading industrial nations to work on the effort at its June gathering in Ireland. The prime minister, in a broader Wall Street Journal column backing free trade, said greater “transparency” must accompany more open global markets. “[W]e must lift the veil of secrecy that too often lets corrupt corporations and officials in some countries run rings around the law. The G8 must move toward a global common standard for resource-extracting companies to report all payments to governments, and in turn for governments to report those revenues,” Cameron writes. “This will encourage more investment in resource-rich countries and level the playing field for business,” he writes. The column arrives as European officials are completing standards that will require oil-and-gas, mining and logging companies to report payments to foreign governments. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has already finalized a U.S. version of the rules that apply to SEC-listed oil-and-gas and mining companies, but they remain under legal challenge by oil industry and business groups. The SEC has also completed separate rules to force manufacturers to disclose whether they rely on minerals – tantalum, tin, gold and tungsten – from war-stricken parts of Africa. But those are also under court review. “We ... need to make sure that mineral wealth in developing countries becomes a blessing, not a curse. It is to the shame of the whole world that a lack of transparency allowed the illicit diamond trade to thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/299285-uks-cameron-wants-global-standard-on-energy-payments-disclosure</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368467642964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368468784453-15</Id><Title>Wind, Solar, &amp; Natural Gas Up In Europe — Coal &amp; Nuclear Down</Title><Msg>May 13, 2013 Zachary Shahan Following up on the report I just published regarding EPIA’s 2012–2017 European and global solar PV report, below are some really interesting charts I wanted to highlight. Basically, they show that solar PV, wind power, and natural gas capacity has grown substantially in the EU while coal, nuclear, and oil capacity has fallen. Image Credit: EPIA. Click to enlarge. Image Credit: EPIA. Click to enlarge. Naturally, more capacity means more electricity production, and less capacity means less electricity production. Image Credit: EPIA. Click to enlarge. In other words, despite what some may have you think, increasing of solar and wind power in the EU has not been leading to a surge in coal power capacity due to the nuclear phaseouts taking place in several countries. Rather, coal power capacity has also declined. The only fossil fuel that saw an increase in capacity in 2012 was natural gas. If you look at 2011 statistics, you can see that coal power capacity also increased (along with solar, wind, and natural gas) as nuclear power capacity dropped. However, with such power plants taking a long time to permit, build, and connect to the grid, this was really due to years of work preceding Fukushima and the strong nuclear phaseout plans that resulted from that. Image Credit: European Wind Energy Association (EWEA) Furthermore, the same trend has occurred in the US – wind, solar, and natural gas have been increasing; coal and nuclear power have been decreasing. Compared to 2011, a shift has also occurred within the top three. More wind power came online in 2012 than in 2011, while the net increase in natural gas capacity was much smaller. (Notably, I noted back in December 2011 that wind power was pricing natural gas out of the market in Germany. I imagine the same thing was happening in other countries.) cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/05/13/wind-solar-natural-gas-up-in-europe-coal-nuclear-down/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368468784453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 14:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368469187102-16</Id><Title>With Record Sales, Tesla Turns A Profit As Consumer Reports Says It ‘Comes Close’ To Being ‘The Best Car Ever’!</Title><Msg>Adam Peck and Ryan Koronowski on May 13, 2013 at 11:50 am Tesla Motors Company is coming off a very good week. On Wednesday, the company reported that it had sold more electric vehicles than any other automaker during the first quarter of the year, and turned a profit for the first time in its 10 year history. On Thursday, Consumer Reports — the famously austere purveyors of customer satisfaction surveys and product testing for all manner of consumer goods — announced that Tesla’s Model S roadster outperformed every other commercially-available vehicle in their annual battery of stress tests, scoring a 99 out of a possible 100: The Tesla Model S outscores every other car in our test Ratings. It does so even though it’s an electric car. In fact, it does so because it is electric. Built from the ground up as an EV, this car’s overall balance benefits from mounting the battery under the floor and in the lowest part of the body. That gives the car a rock-bottom center of gravity that enables excellent handling, a comfortable ride, and lots of room inside. The reviewers didn’t stop there. So thorough was the performance of Tesla’s flagship car, the magazine went on to describe the Model S as one of the best cars they’ve ever tested in its nearly 80 year history: “So is the Tesla Model S the best car ever? We wrestled with that question long and hard. It comes close.” Tesla’s score of 99 is the highest for any hybrid or electric vehicle, and tied for the highest rating awarded to any car in the history of the magazine. The market for 100 percent electric cars has lagged behind the rest of the industry, hindered in part from the perception that the cars weren’t reliable or practical for everyday use. But coupled with the quickening expansion of high-speed charging stations in the most highly trafficked parts thinkprogressDOTorg/climate/2013/05/13/1991311/with-record-sales-tesla-turns-a-profit-as-consumer-reports-says-it-comes-close-to-being-the-best-car-ever/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368469187102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 14:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368475272484-17</Id><Topic><Title>With Record Sales, Tesla Turns A Profit As Consumer Reports Says It ‘Comes Close’ To Being ‘The Best Car Ever’!</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368469187102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 14:19:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blue; maybe you can explain to me the allure of electric cars. My understanding is that the range of today's electric car is around 200 miles. I think people want more freedom than that. I'm thinking natural gas and not electric is the way to go for furture automobiles. Paul</Msg><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1368475272484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368491204661-18</Id><Title>Environmentalists praise fed ruling on San Onofre</Title><Msg>May 13, 2013 at 6:08 pm Associated Press By Michael R. Blood Associated Press LOS ANGELES (AP) — Environmentalists celebrated a federal order Monday that they said opened the way for a more detailed review of a plan to restart the shuttered San Onofre nuclear power plant in California. The ruling by the Nuclear Regulatory Commission’s Atomic Safety and Licensing board had the potential to lead to further delays in a possible restart. The twin-reactor plant between San Diego and Los Angeles hasn’t produced power since January 2012, after a small radiation leak led to the discovery of unusual damage to hundreds of tubes that carry radioactive water. Friends of the Earth, an advocacy group critical of the nuclear power industry, had argued that the federal process set up to consider a restart of the plant’s Unit 2 reactor was in fact a change to the plant’s operating license that would require a court-like hearing. The board agreed. However, there were conflicting assessments on the meaning of the ruling. Environmentalists said the decision was a watershed moment that would force operator Southern California Edison to face a new, extensive review of the restart plan. Edison had no immediate comment. An NRC statement characterized the ruling as a partial win for the environmental group. NRC spokesman Scott Burnell said the board found the group hadn’t provided enough information for the three-member panel to consider in a lengthy hearing. Accordingly, they ended the case. “They didn’t give enough meat for the board to chew on,” said NRC spokesman Scott Burnell. “At the same time the board says, ‘Yes, there should be a hearing,’ … they said the hearing is terminated.” But the group will have the opportunity to submit additional materials in an appeal. Edison wants to run the Unit 2 reactor at reduced power for five months, which it projects will stop damage to tubing fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/13/environmentalists-praise-fed-ruling-on-san-onofre/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368491204661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 20:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368491691668-19</Id><Topic><Title>Maine votes to ban ethanol in gasoline, takes stand against E15</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368317268968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 20:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LePage wants wind energy goals out of Maine law By Matthew Stone, BDN Staff Posted May 09, 2013, at 5:53 p.m. AUGUSTA, Maine — Gov. Paul LePage wants to strip from state law goals for increasing the state’s wind energy capacity over the next two decades. LePage’s energy director, Patrick Woodcock, made recommendations Thursday to rewrite the state’s 2008 Wind Energy Act, shifting focus from growing wind energy capacity to lowering electricity costs and making sure Maine sees an economic return on its wind energy investments. The Maine Wind Energy Act, a priority of LePage’s predecessor, Democratic Gov. John Baldacci, sought to expedite wind energy development in Maine. The law zoned much of Maine’s Unorganized Territory as suitable for wind development and set goals for the state to have 2,000 megawatts of wind energy capacity by 2015, 3,000 by 2020 and 8,000 by 2030. Maine’s wind energy capacity today is about 435 megawatts, according to the Maine Renewable Energy Association. “We are not going to be meeting that goal,” Woodcock said of the 2,000-megawatt threshold by 2015. “I think that it’s an unrealistic goal, and there should be consideration beyond that of whether megawatt capacity installed is really the best metric of our wind energy policies.” The recommendation from Woodcock to the Legislature’s Energy and Utilities Committee came the same day the Energy Committee heard testimony on a number of bills meant to roll back portions of the 2008 wind energy law, including one measure to temporarily suspend permitting for certain wind developments and another that would eliminate the same wind energy goals LePage favors eliminating. Both of those measures are sponsored by Democrats. “The intention of our wind energy act was not only to increase wind energy, but to lower electricity costs,” Woodcock said. Rather than setting energy bangordailynewsDOTcom/2013/05/09/news/state/lepage-wants-wind-energy-goals-out-of-maine-law/?ref=inline</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368491691668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 20:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368492860234-20</Id><Topic><Title>Maine votes to ban ethanol in gasoline, takes stand against E15</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368317268968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 20:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gov. Scott should sign bill to repeal ethanol mandate Sun Sentinel Editorial Board May 13, 2013 Florida lawmakers this year voted to repeal a five-year-old law that forces consumers to buy ethanol-blended fuel at most gas stations across the state. Gov. Rick Scott need only add his signature to set things right. Encouraging the use of corn-based fuel seemed like a good idea years ago, but the policy has instead created an oppressive mandate amid widespread reports about ethanol causing damage to boat motors and car engines. A legal reversal would be a win for a free-market economy, though a blow to big agribusiness. Both the Florida House and Senate voted to repeal the Florida Renewable Fuel Standards Act by wide margins; 77-39 and 33-1, respectively. The bill would end the requirement that gasoline contain up to 10 percent ethanol or another alternative fuel. Exceptions were carved out for fuel sold for boats, small motors and collector vehicles. Nonetheless, the law left a majority of motorists with little choice at the pump. sun-sentinelDOTcom/news/opinion/editorials/fl-ethanol-bill-repeal-dv-20130513,0,1738399DOTstory</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368492860234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 20:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368494776010-21</Id><Title>☛☛☛CNBC=Certainily Not Buying Nonsense ! Manhatten DEM Propaganda tool</Title><Msg>sell asap or get BURNED</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1368494776010</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 21:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368503367785-22</Id><Title>PROVENGE® (sipuleucel-T) is approved by the FDA as an autologous cellular immunotherapy for the treatment of asymptomatic or minimally symptomatic metastatic castrate resistant (hormone refractory) prostate cancer.</Title><Msg>dndn</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1368503367785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 23:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>