<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361337527941-1</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know, inferno, I don't think wahleee boy likes you very much. I don't care either. What you need is a mistress - then you can make more infernos. You appear to be wealthy enough to support many more too. A real man would step up.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361337527941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:18:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361337606890-2</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fraunhofer-Gesellschaft zur Förderung der angewandten Forschung is working on projects that might interest you. I cannot give you details... Find them yourself if you can.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361337606890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:20:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361365719176-3</Id><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Msg>30 Year UK Gilts @ 3.487% --- 50% allocation. 50% @0.50% LIBOR (£) --- for UK rentals</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361365719176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:08:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361367191224-4</Id><Title>Italy to become laughing stock of Europe</Title><Msg>A comedian is now the media's and mob's darling candidate in the upcoming elections. They are hoping for a big upset. The Italian mob is a shameful thing. The Italian media is just as bad. Their debt is shameful too and of course they would like more of it - with German money to keep their rates low. The situation is similar to the US where the mob picks their favorite and uses a Park Avenue credit card to spend wildly.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361367191224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:33:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361369094710-5</Id><Topic><Title>Real Estate in the Scepter'd Isle</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359217500199</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 11:25:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump.... It would be very symmetrical if the mob in Italy elects a government on an anti-euro, anti-EU plank, or at least enough dissidents to make governing there impossible. Personally I despise the currency and the EU. The UK is already picking up many skilled University graduates from southern Europe seeking work. The numbers will only grow.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361369094710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:04:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361371196992-6</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update forExxon Mobil Corporation **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>alvinsoto80</Username><Timestamp>1361369026300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hear the picks usually go up 10.81%</Msg><Username>paris.olivarez</Username><Timestamp>1361371196992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:39:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361371883515-7</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be interesting to hear her views on gtl plants to make fuel oil from coal and nat gas. Perhaps it takes $150 oil and or cheap nat gas to make that process attractive. So just now we have cheap coal and in north america cheap nat gas, the last thing necessary is a bit more expensive crude and perhaps gtl takes off.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1361371883515</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:51:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361371924072-8</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update forExxon Mobil Corporation **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>alvinsoto80</Username><Timestamp>1361369026300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cant resist</Msg><Username>scottdon644</Username><Timestamp>1361371924072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:52:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361372610166-9</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update forExxon Mobil Corporation **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>alvinsoto80</Username><Timestamp>1361369026300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes they are</Msg><Username>jacksonjeffrey746</Username><Timestamp>1361372610166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:03:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361373191513-10</Id><Title>Split Headlinez Nearing !!!</Title><Msg>The Q2 suprise Announcement could also bring with it the largest Dividend hikez in history,and an abrupt end to share buybackz.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1361373191513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:13:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361373924485-11</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The German advanced energy programs and industry work in an alliance with government and will proceed no matter what the price for oil, gas, or coal is. Using American notions of economics and organization to judge Germany is flawed. Germany's contempt for free markets goes back to the Prussians and their use of education and noble led government to force the economy down paths they preferred. It worked better than the free market too. German education, scientific, and industrial resources can be commanded by the Chancellor, just as in the past the Kaiser's government could command them or the Führer when he wanted rockets and jet planes. It is not the same as it is for Obama making statements and having no real buttons to push at his Oval Office desk.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361373924485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:25:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361375042630-12</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update forExxon Mobil Corporation **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>alvinsoto80</Username><Timestamp>1361369026300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>give me a winner now</Msg><Username>emerywarren149</Username><Timestamp>1361375042630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:44:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361376076172-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361365719176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:08:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold 30 Year UK Gilts @3.475% yield to maturity. gain in price +0.22% 100% £, LIBOR @ 0.50%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361376076172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:01:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361376917506-14</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES XOM.</Title><Username>lambertdavid169</Username><Timestamp>1361376296080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:04:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks a lot!</Msg><Username>andrewbrudny</Username><Timestamp>1361376917506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:15:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361378020392-15</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES XOM.</Title><Username>lambertdavid169</Username><Timestamp>1361376296080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:04:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spam</Msg><Username>radcardude</Username><Timestamp>1361378020392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:33:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361378957478-16</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES XOM.</Title><Username>lambertdavid169</Username><Timestamp>1361376296080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:04:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>excellent report! thank U</Msg><Username>dieseljosh370</Username><Timestamp>1361378957478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:49:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361380112972-17</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES XOM.</Title><Username>lambertdavid169</Username><Timestamp>1361376296080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:04:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks!</Msg><Username>brown_nadya</Username><Timestamp>1361380112972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:08:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361380245218-18</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update forExxon Mobil Corporation **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>alvinsoto80</Username><Timestamp>1361369026300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>meat riders lol</Msg><Username>guzmanandrew658</Username><Timestamp>1361380245218</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:10:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361380509852-19</Id><Topic><Title>Split Headlinez Nearing !!!</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1361373191513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:13:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think they will up the divy a little but will not stop the buybacks.</Msg><Username>christophmil</Username><Timestamp>1361380509852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:15:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361381380791-20</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update forExxon Mobil Corporation **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>alvinsoto80</Username><Timestamp>1361369026300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow another winner!</Msg><Username>mitchelljuan314</Username><Timestamp>1361381380791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:29:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361381577490-21</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES XOM.</Title><Username>lambertdavid169</Username><Timestamp>1361376296080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:04:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report!</Msg><Username>aquinodavid252</Username><Timestamp>1361381577490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:32:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361382194176-22</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES XOM.</Title><Username>lambertdavid169</Username><Timestamp>1361376296080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:04:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice one</Msg><Username>whiteed14</Username><Timestamp>1361382194176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:43:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361383443587-23</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES XOM.</Title><Username>lambertdavid169</Username><Timestamp>1361376296080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:04:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful report. thanks a lot!</Msg><Username>sjeff53</Username><Timestamp>1361383443587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:04:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361385232599-24</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update forExxon Mobil Corporation **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>alvinsoto80</Username><Timestamp>1361369026300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dont lose man</Msg><Username>rollingdarren</Username><Timestamp>1361385232599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:33:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361387575140-25</Id><Title>Renewables constitute all new US electricity capacity added in January</Title><Msg>Renewables constitute all new US electricity capacity added in January By Zack Colman - 02/20/13 12:46 PM ET Renewable energy accounted for all new electric capacity added in the United States last month, according to the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission. In all, 1,231 megawatts of new generating capacity were installed in January. Of that total, wind provided 958 megawatts, solar chipped in 267 megawatts and biomass contributed 6 megawatts. That's a marked difference from January 2012, when coal led the way with 808 megawatts of the 1,693 megawatts added. Natural gas followed with 445 megawatts, and wind tossed in 276 megawatts to take the pole for renewables. On Wednesday, President Obama sought to expand promotion of renewable energy by reviving the Commerce Department’s Renewable Energy and Energy Efficiency Advisory Committee. Deputy Commerce Secretary Rebecca Blank appointed 37 private-sector members to the committee on Wednesday. It will feature members from trade associations, private firms and nonprofit organizations from a range of energy industries. The panel, originally formed in 2010, had previously worked on strengthening the renewable and energy efficiency’s industry’s export competitiveness. “The renewable energy and energy efficiency sector holds tremendous growth potential, and transitioning to cleaner, safer, and affordable sources of energy is a high priority for the Department of Commerce and for President Obama," Blank said in a statement. The committee’s relaunch comes one week after Obama pledged during his State of the Union address to double electricity generating capacity from renewable energy by 2020. The U.S. already doubled its electric generating capacity from renewable sources between 2008 and 2012, according to a Bloomberg New Energy Finance and Business Council for Sustainable Energy report released last month. To double it again, Obama called on Congress to make the renewable energy production tax credit permanent. Currently, Congress must renew that credit — which pays wind, biomass, geothermal and other energy producers on a per-kilowatt-hour basis — every couple of years. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/284011-renewables-comprise-all-new-us-electricity-capacity-added-in-january</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361387575140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:12:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361387637718-26</Id><Topic><Title>★★★ GALE @ 1.68 ★★★★★ ANX @ .70 ★★★★★ APPY @ 2.11 ★★★★★ DARA @ 1.02 ★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★</Title><Username>clearwire_soonover325</Username><Timestamp>1359647821891</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 10:57:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>private placement for 52 million shares in that 1 biotech, and a few insider and index fund purchases in the others. Nice finds.</Msg><Username>rimm_since7dollars</Username><Timestamp>1361387637718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:13:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361388597801-27</Id><Title>TransCanada downplays Keystone XL protests</Title><Msg>TransCanada downplays Keystone XL protests TransCanada's Alex Pourbaix says the opposition to the project is 'not a surprise.' Close By TALIA BUFORD | 2/20/13 4:41 AM EST Two days after climate activists rallied on the National Mall, supporters of the Keystone XL pipeline were back on the offensive Tuesday. They downplayed the opposition and reinforced the message that the pipeline is the best course for the both the U.S. and Canada. “We always are concerned when there’s opposition to our projects, but it’s not a surprise,” said Alex Pourbaix, president of oil pipelines and energy at TransCanada, during a reporter roundtable Tuesday at the National Association of Manufacturers’ headquarters in Washington. “My experience is the events over the weekend are not getting nearly the coverage in the media they would have a year, year and a half ago. So I’m of the view that the temperature is going down on this issue.” Sierra Club Executive Director Michael Brune scoffed at that statement. “That TransCanada would say ‘the temperature is going down’ on dirty and dangerous tar sands that would only cause global temperatures to rise shows just how out of touch they are with reality,” Brune said. “Whether they’re denying that Keystone XL is an export pipeline or ignoring the significant international news created by the nearly 50,000 Americans who stood up for climate solutions, it’s clear that no fact or truth is sacred to TransCanada.” Organizers originally estimated that 35,000 people participated in Sunday’s rally against Keystone but now say that “more than 40,000” attended the event. Either way, they billed it as the... 2 pages... politicoDOTcom/story/2013/02/transcanada-counterpunches-on-xl-pipeline-87813.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361388597801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:29:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361390061701-28</Id><Title>Sen. Wyden wants nuclear cleanup commitment from next Energy secretary</Title><Msg>Sen. Wyden wants nuclear cleanup commitment from next Energy secretary By Zack Colman - 02/20/13 11:02 AM ET The Senate Energy Committee chairman said Tuesday that any Energy secretary nominee must agree to clean up high-level nuclear waste at a Washington facility to get his support. Leaks reported last week at the Hanford nuclear reservation require immediate attention, Energy Committee Chairman Ron Wyden (D-Ore.) said. He also expressed concern that a waste treatment plant is behind schedule and over budget. As Energy Committee Chairman, Wyden will oversee the confirmation hearing for outgoing Energy Secretary Steven Chu's replacement. He said he would ask nominees to commit to treating and disposing of waste at the Hanford nuclear reservation. “This should represent an unacceptable threat to the Pacific Northwest for everybody,” Wyden said after touring the site, according to The Associated Press. “There are problems that have to be solved, and right now the Department of Energy cannot say what changes are needed, when they will be completed and what they will cost.” DOE manages the nation’s waste from nuclear weapons and energy research. Of its $6 billion annual cleanup budget, it spends $2 billion on maintaining Hanford, which straddles Oregon’s border along the Columbia River. Wyden said he would hold a hearing on the Hanford situation, though he did not offer a specific date. The attention to Hanford — with which Wyden has a long history — comes as the chairman and three other senators are hammering out legislation on nuclear waste management. Wyden, Energy Committee ranking member Sen. Lisa Murkowski (R-Alaska) and Sens. Dianne Feinstein (D-Calif.) and Lamar Alexander (R-Tenn.) are working on that bill. Wyden has said he is willing to separate military spent fuel — the kind at Hanford — from civilian, and has explored the idea of sending that military waste to the Waste Isolation Pilot Project, located near Carlsbad, N.M. He also says he is willing to move some waste near risky areas — such as fault lines — to interim storage sites, even without identifying a permanent waste repository. That take is more aligned with Murkowski than the position held by now-retired Sen. Jeff Bingaman (D-N.M.), who chaired the Energy Committee last Congress and was involved in nuclear waste legislation negotiations. Some senators involved in the talks disagreed with Bingaman’s insistence that moving waste to intermediate sites required having an application for a permanent repository filed with DOE. Wyden’s openness to moving at least some nuclear waste to intermediate sites, therefore, could yield progress for the foursome working on the bill. Still, what works in the Senate might not be true of the House. The Senate framework would allow states that want to host a</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361390061701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:54:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361392346653-29</Id><Title>Reports: Shale Gas Bubble Looms, Aided by Wall Street</Title><Msg>Reports: Shale Gas Bubble Looms, Aided by Wall Street Tue, 2013-02-19 09:00STEVE HORN Two long-awaited reports were published today at ShaleBubble # by the Post Carbon Institute (PCI) and the Energy Policy Forum (EPF). Together, the reports conclude that the hydraulic fracturing ("fracking") boom could lead to a "bubble burst" akin to the housing bubble burst of 2008. While most media attention towards fracking has focused on the threats to drinking water and health in communities throughout North America and the world, there is an even larger threat looming. The fracking industry has the ability - paralleling the housing bubble burst that served as a precursor to the 2008 economic crisis - to tank the global economy. Playing the role of Cassandra, the reports conclude that "the so-called shale revolution is nothing more than a bubble, driven by record levels of drilling, speculative lease &amp; flip practices on the part of shale energy companies, fee-driven promotion by the same investment banks that fomented the housing bubble..." a summary details. "Geological and economic constraints – not to mention the very serious environmental and health impacts of drilling – mean that shale gas and shale oil (tight oil) are far from the solution to our energy woes." PCI's report is titled "Drill Baby, Drill," authored by PCI Fellow and former oil and gas industry geoscientist J. Dave Hughes, while EPF's report is titled "Shale Gas and Wall Street," authored by EPF Director and former Wall Street financial analyst Deborah Rogers. "100 Years of Natural Gas"? Uh huh... desmogblogDOTcom/2013/02/19/fracking-wall-street-housing-bubble</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361392346653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:32:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361419005530-30</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They should install some "placebo' buttons in the oval office so the president can believe he is actually in control of some of the things people think he can control. World leaders of the consumer nations can cartel together to push price of oil down for a while, but its like pushing on a spring and its going to rebound perhaps more than expected. Thats okay if it gets us over a depression and gets america and other nations working. Thinking the future is not so bright, more expensive oil, and cheaper labor. glta</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1361419005530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:56:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361420554574-31</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quantum is a great academic curiosity. Just like Quantum computers. when Intel, Ibm, or Dell offers a quantum desk top i be a believer, not before. I would say that the world oil reserves like the Saudi reserve for example are like Schrodinger's cat we really dont know if the resevoir is full or not since we cant really see inside the box.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1361420554574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:22:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361422032920-32</Id><Title>Gina McCarthy emerging as likely pick for EPA chief</Title><Msg>Gina McCarthy emerging as likely pick for EPA chief By Ben Wolfgang The Washington Times Wednesday, February 20, 2013 While no official announcement has been made, speculation is swirling around Gina McCarthy as the White House’s pick to head the Environmental Protection Agency. Multiple media reports have in recent days portrayed Ms. McCarthy, currently assistant administrator for EPA's Office of Air and Radiation, as the clear front-runner to be the next EPA administrator. She would replace Lisa Jackson, who held the post for the last four years but oversaw a period when the agency’s scientific credibility hit an all-time low among congressional Republicans and many in the oil, gas and coal industries. Filling the EPA job is especially important for the Obama administration after the president’s recent pledge to confront climate change in his second term. The agency has played a key role in previous White House efforts to reduce greenhouse gas emissions, most notably taking the lead in dramatically raising auto fuel efficiency standards. EPA regulations also have resulted in an effective ban on, among other things, new coal-fired power plants. Critics do not expect anything to change under a McCarthy-led agency. “The EPA will continue it’s anti-fossil fuel crusade undeterred, and the administration will continue to avoid normal democratic means to legislate the president’s climate change agenda through the regulatory agencies,” said Benjamin Cole, spokesman for the American Energy Alliance, a conservative energy think tank. But environmental groups likely would applaud the pick, as it would signal that the White House will make air pollution and carbon emissions a high priority over the next four years. Before coming to the EPA, Ms. McCarthy served as commissioner of Connecticut’s Department of Environmental Protection. washingtontimesDOTcom/news/2013/feb/20/gina-mccarthy-emerging-likely-pick-epa-chief/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361422032920</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:47:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361422721303-33</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Blocks Increased Ethanol Blend for Gasoline</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360994964537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 01:09:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's very unlikely to ever reach the oval office and if the legislation does, President Obama will veto it making it invalid until at least 2017.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361422721303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:58:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>