<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357362207601-1</Id><Topic><Title>The End of the World As We Know It :)</Title><Username>biggatorhear</Username><Timestamp>1357316970724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 11:29:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I japan they are paying $1,760,000 for one tuna fish. The food supply is running out global warming will cause mass starvation:)</Msg><Username>biggatorhear</Username><Timestamp>1357362207601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 00:03:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357362953080-2</Id><Title>I must of struck or chord.</Title><Msg>Haha! Easy peazy!</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1357362953080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 00:15:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357362977140-3</Id><Topic><Title>I must of struck or chord.</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1357362953080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 00:15:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talk about whimpy!</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1357362977140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 00:16:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357363077847-4</Id><Topic><Title>More Dem hypocrisy</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1357257961790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 19:06:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So far you have missed on many of your 'predictions' and I believe you will be proven wrong on a lot more" this from the loon that said healthcare law was unconstitutional ?? the guy that said romney would win and rove was bushs' brain ?? the same guy that said the teaparty would lead the congress ?? the same guy that said he would leave USA if Obama won again ?? you are off the rails with allen west,sarah palin,trump and bachmann--loon on the loose</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1357363077847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 00:17:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357364361963-5</Id><Title>Mrsuerte demonstrates how brain death and lying go together</Title><Msg>Right wahleee boy? "this from the loon that said healthcare law was unconstitutional ?? the guy that said romney would win and rove was bushs' brain ?? the same guy that said the teaparty would lead the congress ?? the same guy that said he would leave USA if Obama won again ??" Try pointing out a post in which I said any of those things? It might be a bit difficult since they don't exist. But thanks for proving again what a lying sleazebag you are.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1357364361963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 00:39:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357371696008-6</Id><Topic><Title>More Dem hypocrisy</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1357257961790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 19:06:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ja, ja…You are a speculator no matter how you want to frame it, and you are pushing your interests, which is understandable but not necessarily commendable. I’ve been in Munich all December and for this month as well. I’m treating my fiancée and then we go back to the US. Maybe someday you can visit Germany, although you will sadly be paying your own way. Maybe one of those speculations you’ve been salting away for years will cover it. You could see first how well a society run counter to your ideology really works. As for the currency trades you seem so interested in. Don’t expect more. I wouldn’t want someone to try to copy one, seeing they always make money. That would annoy me. If you are so skilled at predictions you should try your hand at some trades and see if you can do better.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357371696008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 02:41:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357387069971-7</Id><Topic><Title>Mrsuerte demonstrates how brain death and lying go together</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1357364361963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 00:39:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mr luck sounds like the wahlee boy #$%$ POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357387069971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 06:57:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357394228875-8</Id><Title>Remarks of President Barack Obama The Weekly Address</Title><Msg>Remarks of President Barack Obama The Weekly Address Honolulu, Hawaii January 4, 2013 Hi, everybody. Over the past year, as I traveled across the country campaigning for this office, I told you that if I was fortunate enough to be re-elected, I’d work to change a tax code that too often benefited the wealthy at the expense of the middle class. This week, we did that. For the first time in two decades, we raised taxes on the wealthiest 2% of Americans in a bipartisan way, while preventing a middle-class tax hike that could have thrown our economy back into recession. Under this law, more than 98% of Americans and 97% of small business will not see their income taxes go up one dime. We also made sure that millions of families will continue to receive tax credits to help raise their children and send them to college. Companies will continue to receive tax credits for the research they do, the investments they make, and the clean energy jobs they create. And two million Americans who are out of work will continue to receive unemployment benefits so long as they are actively looking for a job. But all this was just one more step in the broader effort to grow our economy and shrink our deficits. We still need to do more to put Americans back to work while also putting this country on a path to pay down its debt. And our economy can’t afford more protracted showdowns or manufactured crises along the way. Because even as our businesses created 2 million new jobs last year – including 168,000 new jobs last month – the messy brinksmanship in Congress made business owners more uncertain and consumers less confident. We know there’s a path forward. Last year, I signed into law $1.7 trillion in deficit reduction. This week’s action further reduces the deficit by $737 billion, making it one of the largest deficit reduction bills passed by Congress in over a decade. And I’m willing to do more. I believe we can find more places to cut spending without shortchanging things like education, job training, research and technology all which are critical to our prosperity in a 21st century economy. But spending cuts must be balanced with more reforms to our tax code. The wealthiest individuals and the biggest corporations shouldn’t be able to take advantage of loopholes and deductions that aren’t available to most Americans. And as I said earlier this week, one thing I will not compromise over is whether or not Congress should pay the tab for a bill they’ve already racked up. If Congress refuses to give the United States the ability to pay its bills on time, the consequences for the entire global economy could be catastrophic. The last time Congress threatened this course of action, our entire economy suffered for it. Our families and our businesses cannot afford that dangerous game again. I congratulate the newly sworn-in Members of Congress, and I look forward to working with the new Congress in a bipartisan way. If we focus on the interests of our country above the interests of party, I’m convinced we can cut spending and raise revenue in a manner that reduces our deficit and protects the middle class. And we can step up to meet the important business that awaits us this year. Creating jobs and boosting incomes. Fixing our infrastructure and our immigration system. Promoting our energy independence while protecting our planet from the harmful effects of climate change. Educating our children and shielding them from the horrors of gun violence. These aren’t just things we should do – they’re things we must do. And in this New Year, I’ll fight as hard as I know how to get them done. Happy New Year, everybody. whitehouseDOTgov/the-press-office/2013/01/05/weekly-address-working-together-new-year-grow-our-economy-and-shrink-our</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357394228875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:57:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357395171808-9</Id><Title>Iowa’s second E15 retail station opens in Fredericksburg</Title><Msg>Iowa’s second E15 retail station opens in Fredericksburg By Iowa Renewable Fuels Association | January 04, 2013 The Iowa Renewable Fuels Association has announced that Fredericksburg Coop in Fredericksburg, Iowa now offers E15 as a registered fuel to 2001 and newer vehicles, joining Linn Coop Oil in Marion, to become Iowa’s second fuel retailer offering E15 to 2001 and newer vehicles. “We’re excited to get the ball rolling again for E15 in Iowa,” said IRFA Executive Director Monte Shaw. “After the first round of retailer approvals the EPA essentially shut down the system for three months. Now the EPA is apparently back on track and Fredericksburg Coop was the first station approved. IRFA believes that Fredericksburg Coop will be the first of many stations to add the option of cheaper, cleaner E15 in 2013.” Fredericksburg Coop is located in Northeast Iowa on Highway 18 West in Fredericksburg. E15, a blend of gasoline and 15 percent ethanol, can be used by all 2001 and newer passenger vehicles and all flexible fuel vehicles (FFVs). Those vehicles account for 85 percent of fuel use in the United States. In order to offer E15 to the non-FFVs, a retailer must register with the EPA. IRFA works with retailers to ensure they follow all federal and state E15 regulations. “I believe retailers see great value in offering a less expensive, cleaner, more American-made fuel option like E15 to their consumers,” stated Fredericksburg Coop Petroleum Manager Steve Neuendorf. “Fredericksburg Coop is thrilled to be Iowa’s second retail station to offer E15. We see the option of E15 as a win for our customers—both motorists and farmers. And that is a win for us.” Iowa is the leader in renewable fuels production. Iowa has 41 ethanol refineries capable of producing over 3.7 billion gallons annually, with one wet mill and two cellulosic ethanol facilities currently under construction. In addition, Iowa has 12 biodiesel facilities with the capacity to produce 315 million gallons annually The Iowa Renewable Fuels Association was formed in 2002 to represent the state’s liquid renewable fuels industry. The trade group fosters the development and growth of the renewable fuels industry in Iowa through education, promotion, legislation and infrastructure development. ethanolproducerDOTcom/articles/9423/iowaundefineds-second-e15-retail-station-opens-in-fredericksburg</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357395171808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 09:12:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357395553101-10</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Ownership, institutional ownership</Title><Username>roxiewiltzxwlii9768</Username><Timestamp>1302018056000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-04-05 11:40:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brilliant analysis</Msg><Username>williamkatz43</Username><Timestamp>1357395553101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 09:19:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357400785732-11</Id><Title>hansesteelyard / greedful</Title><Msg>"Ja, ja…You are a speculator no matter how you want to frame it, and you are pushing your interests, which is understandable but not necessarily commendable. I’ve been in Munich all December and for this month as well. I’m treating my fiancée and then we go back to the US. Maybe someday you can visit Germany, although you will sadly be paying your own way. Maybe one of those speculations you’ve been salting away for years will cover it. You could see first how well a society run counter to your ideology really works. As for the currency trades you seem so interested in. Don’t expect more. I wouldn’t want someone to try to copy one, seeing they always make money. That would annoy me. If you are so skilled at predictions you should try your hand at some trades and see if you can do better." More blather as is your typical, and more assumptions as always that are untrue or irrelevant or both. Pushing one's interests is not necessarily commendable? - interesting since that's what you do a lot of the time. Maybe someday I can visit Germany? I have lived in Europe for a number of years, and my parents lived in Germany as well when I was in college. I also regularly traveled to Europe throughout my career. So I do believe I have some understanding of Europe. You seem to have a lot of notions that make no sense but that you are strangely committed to. I have no desire nor need to engage in currency trades. I don't even know if you do them despite your statements. And your predictions have and will speak for themselves over time.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1357400785732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 10:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357404344901-12</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard / greedful</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1357400785732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 10:46:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another cynical post, but it is much wordier than the others – you really outdid yourself. Your opinions about Europe do not concern me. Your attempt to be cosmopolitan falls flat as well, considering your much more typical persona here. There is a reason you do not post anything verifiable or useful – like a single real time prediction someone could make money on let alone a dozen. You cannot do it. It is beyond your depth. Lying and claiming you would not pick up such easy money if you could is just ridiculous too. Why did I deign to demonstrate it here with pounds, euros, and shorting your silly stock on occasion, and shorting the bloated Fed-pumped monstrosity of a stock market on occasion too? It’s entertaining to me. Your endless defense against the other prediction, the one on oil prices and failure here, just shows how desperate you are becoming, and will continue to become, as it unfolds. Your conversation has grown tiresome at this point. Find someone else to be cynical and obnoxious with.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357404344901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 11:45:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357406571498-13</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard / greedful</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1357400785732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 10:46:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My pleasure - your self-centered prognostications and garbage assumptions are even more tiresome. As I said, we will see over time.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1357406571498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:22:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357407073329-14</Id><Title>new, fully automated, skid-mounted enzymatic biodiesel processing system</Title><Msg>new, fully automated, skid-mounted enzymatic biodiesel processing system. After two years of development work to hone the process and build the first unit, the firm is now working to fill orders from customers around the globe. “This is the first completely automated enzymatic system in the world,” said Ernie DeMartino, president and CEO of Pearland, Texas-based Biodiesel Experts International. The systems can be ordered in various sizes, or production volumes, depending on the</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357407073329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:31:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357407797855-15</Id><Title>Townships readying for wind</Title><Msg>Townships readying for wind Posted by Compmanager on January 5, 2013 PHOTO As farmers work in the field to harvest crops, NextEra Energy Resources LLC have cranes in the fields to put up turbines to harvest the wind in Blumfield and Gilford townships. (Right) Tuscola County’s first wind farm is taking shape one turbine at a time. Some of them are expected to be generating power any day. By Mary Drier Staff Writer TUSCOLA COUNTY — With one wind farm project up and running in Tuscola County, more townships are clearing the way for wind development in their area. At their Dec. 17, 2012 meeting, the Columbia Township Board approved their wind zoning ordinance amendments. That action clears the way for wind farm development in the township. Also, on that same day, the Fairgrove Township Board approved ordinances for wind development in that township. And, the Akron Township is also working on regulations for wind farm development. Consumers Energy is looking at building wind turbines in Columbia and Akron townships. According to the unapproved Columbia meeting minutes, Consumers is looking at the possibility of 50-90 turbines in those two townships. However, the number of turbines will depend on the amount of generating power of each when the type of turbine is actually selected. NextEra Energy Resources LLC is the company that’s looking to develop a wind farm in Fairgrove Township. NextEra Energy is the first company to develop an operational wind farm in Tuscola County. NextEra Energy built 68 wind turbines in Gilford Township and seven in Blumfield Township to create the “Tuscola – Bay Wind Farm.” That system became operational in December 2012. Development of that wind farm was over $250 million. tuscolatodayDOTcom/index.php/2013/01/05/townships-readying-for-wind/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357407797855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:43:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357410592160-16</Id><Topic><Title>Townships readying for wind</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357407797855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 12:43:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For every KW of wind or sun The "Big O " said we must keep fuel fired generators on standby,so why invest in both. Wind and sun will go the way of the pet rock. Fuel cells for home use will be the thing of the future and will put KW's back around the clock. GE is building a large base overseas now.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1357410592160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 13:29:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357410693431-17</Id><Title>I have nothing better to do in life but post all day</Title><Msg>I love Obama he gives me government doe to type letter all day long. This will be good experience for my up coming job interview. I might as well put this experience on my resume. Add: Full time poster for yahoo. How we can benefit from society as a full time poster and government doe. And a great combo!</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1357410693431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 13:31:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357411479902-18</Id><Topic><Title>Remarks of President Barack Obama The Weekly Address</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357394228875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 08:57:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Emperor is so bi-partisan in his apprpoach :) May the Glorious One reign for 1,000 years!</Msg><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1357411479902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 13:44:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357424094488-19</Id><Topic><Title>The rumor going around that XOM purchased Hovensa!!</Title><Username>cytech00851</Username><Timestamp>1357337224322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 17:07:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is a load of #$%$. Esso has had enough of refining in the Caribs. Why do you think yhey sold that junk heap in Aruba to Oscar?</Msg><Username>ihategooks</Username><Timestamp>1357424094488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 17:14:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357434563979-20</Id><Title>SolarCity expects 60% capacity boost as US homes embrace PV</Title><Msg>SolarCity expects 60% capacity boost as US homes embrace PV Published: Friday, January 4 2013 SolarCity expects to install 60% more capacity in 2013 than it did last year, as it looks to take advantage of the growing stability of the US residential solar market. SolarCity, whose share price has defied sceptics since it launched its initial public offering (IPO) last month, says it installed 156MW across the residential and commercial rooftop segments in 2012, slightly more than it originally intended. The California-based company, which has yet to turn a profit, put up 72MW in 2011. The residential segment accounted for 54% of SolarCity’s installations in 2012 – but will account for more than three-quarters in 2013, or 190MW total, the company predicts. By comparison, it expects its commercial installations – a segment that includes government contracts, such as schools – to decline to 60MW this year, from 71MW in 2012. SolarCity’s share price closed up 5.6% at $13.02 on 3 January – significantly higher than its IPO price of $8, and not far off the $14-$15 range the company had initially suggested it would sell its shares for before backing down amid market uncertainty. Small-scale solar is seen as a paragon of stability in the otherwise volatile US renewables market, thanks to a federal tax credit that will remain in place through 2016. The residential sector has chalked up growth for six straight quarters, with California continuing to lead the country. More than 20 US states are expected to have installed more than 10MW of PV in 2012, up from four in 2008, according to the Solar Energy Industries Association. The utility-scale segment is also booming in the US – a point driven home by MidAmerican Energy’s recent purchase of two projects totaling 579MW in California’s Antelope Valley from SunPower. Shares in Total-owned SunPower soared nearly 48% on 3 January on news of that deal. Many analysts expect the utility-scale market to temporarily cool off around 2015 in the US as key states meet their mid-term renewable portfolio standards. The US likely installed more than 3GW of PV in 2012, up from 1.9GW in 2011, giving it a roughly 10% share of the global market. In 2010 the US accounted for just half that figure. Karl-Erik Stromsta, London rechargenewsDOTcom/energy/solar/article330367DOTece</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357434563979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:09:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357434861610-21</Id><Topic><Title>SolarCity expects 60% capacity boost as US homes embrace PV</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357434563979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:09:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Peak natural gas in America, December 2013 &amp; January 2014</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357434861610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 20:14:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>