<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367831601555-1</Id><Topic><Title>Nancy Grace is a DIS'GRACE !!!</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1367630630058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:23:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the commie clown rat.</Msg><Username>bluemax19</Username><Timestamp>1367831601555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 05:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367846218457-2</Id><Title>Cheniere: LNG facility ahead of schedule</Title><Msg>Cheniere: LNG facility ahead of schedule Posted on May 6, 2013 at 6:53 am by Associated Press Tugboats pull an LNG tanker to Cheniere Energy's Sabine Pass terminal in 2008. (Nick De La Torre / Houston Chronicle) BATON ROUGE, La. — Cheniere Energy Inc. says construction is ahead of schedule on the first two units of its Sabine Pass liquefied natural gas facility, with around 26 percent of the work complete as of March 31. The company told The Advocate the Cameron Parish facility’s first two production units are expected to begin producing LNG in late 2015. Meanwhile, two additional units have received all of the necessary Federal Energy Regulatory Commission and U.S. Department of Energy approvals. The company is in the process of securing the financing to build those units. The company borrowed $5.9 billion to build the first two units. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/06/cheniere-lng-facility-ahead-of-schedule/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367846218457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:16:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367846340130-3</Id><Title>Statoil says higher petroleum tax risks harming investments</Title><Msg>Statoil says higher petroleum tax risks harming investments Posted on May 6, 2013 at 6:58 am by Bloomberg Workers on Statoil's Maersk Developer platform in the Gulf of Mexico (Photo: Helge Hansen/Statoil) Statoil ASA (STL) said the government’s unexpected move to raise taxes on oil companies risks harming investments and casts doubt over the long-term predictability of the framework for offshore production. The government yesterday said it will limit the so-called upflift on cash flow to 22 percent from 30 percent and raise the special petroleum tax to 51 percent from 50 percent, keeping a top tax rate of 78 percent. The increase will raise total taxes by about 3 billion kroner ($520 million) a year, the government said yesterday. Statoil, which is 67 percent owned by the Norwegian state, said today that the changes will cut operating cash flow by below 500 million kroner this year and increase to full effect after four to five years. It will reduce tax deductions by 38 million kroner for 1 billion kroner invested, the Stavanger- based company said. “The proposed change in the Norwegian petroleum tax reduces the attractiveness of future projects, particularly marginal fields, and raises questions regarding the predictability and stability of the fiscal framework for long-term investments on the Norwegian continental shelf,” said Torgrim Reitan, chief financial officer of Statoil, in a statement. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/06/statoil-says-higher-petroleum-tax-risks-harming-investments/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367846340130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:19:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367846608230-4</Id><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Msg>Military budgets are being cut across Europe with France announcing new big cuts in recent days. So much for US hopes for more war spending in Europe. The recent visit to France by US Treasury Sec. Lew to insult the French for these sorts of “stupid” austerity measures seems to have been a singular failure. Only one country in Europe really has the ability to spend more on war and that is Germany. Germany has no intention of spending more however. There are many reasons for that: 1. It is a waste of money 2. Previous insults and efforts to “contain” German power and impose low force levels the past 70 years seem to have left a sour taste, and reduced enthusiasm for the irrelevant goals of foreigners 3. It is more profitable to be a neutral player and sell weapons to peaceful countries – the Chancellor decides who those are If there is to be another war the US will pay just about everything, or maybe everything. At some point the cost of these wars will require massive tax increases in the USA - bad for oil demand as the USA is the biggest waster of oil on the planet This grim outlook facing US militarists and the Middle Eastern clique who strive to influence them, hopefully will dissuade them from starting yet another war... In the meantime the war on fossil fuels continues apace – we have plenty of money for that…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367846720241-5</Id><Topic><Title>Carbon prices rocket on Merkel hopes</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367795875358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 19:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>excellent</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846720241</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367846755268-6</Id><Topic><Title>Carbon prices rocket on Merkel hopes</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367795875358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 19:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>excellent</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846755268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367846820671-7</Id><Title>Solar PV Module Prices Have Fallen 80% Since 2008, Wind Turbines 29%</Title><Msg>Solar PV Module Prices Have Fallen 80% Since 2008, Wind Turbines 29% May 6, 2013 Zachary Shahan I know most of you have seen such graphs many times, but I can’t resist sharing another one every once in awhile. And the truth is, a lot of people are completely oblivious to this. Those who follow cleantech news know the strong trend, but the common person certainly doesn’t. Do everyone a favor — share this graph with your friends! Wind Power Prices Also Dropping Wind turbine prices have followed a similar (if not quite as extreme) trend. Since 2008, wind turbine prices have fallen 29%. Wind power is more mature than solar. It is already the cheapest electricity option in many or even most places. You can see in the graph below that it had most of its massive price drops in the 1990s. The full BNEF presentation those graphs come from was a presentation at the Clean Energy Ministerial in Delhi, India on April 17, 2013. Stay tuned, because I’ve got a post coming in about one hour that goes very well with these, but takes things even a step further. cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/05/06/solar-pv-module-prices-have-fallen-80-since-2008-wind-turbines-29/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367846820671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367849871018-8</Id><Topic><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good article. In your closing statement you opine that the grim outlook facing our militarists and allies will be dissuaded from war. Wish you were right but the grimness and horror seem to attract these individuals.Looks like we are going in there soon.The right wing is already having huge wargasms.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1367849871018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367850331257-9</Id><Topic><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US has been the biggest defender of freedom in the world. America does not start wars. Afghanistan-started by World Trace Center attack. Iraq-Invasion of Kuwait. Obama, with his support of Muslim Brotherhood takeovers is not in that tradition since they do not respect freedom and peaceful coexistence with their neighbors.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367850331257</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367850845002-10</Id><Topic><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't confuse the Republican elites with the "right wing" . Many conservatives do not support the ideas of McCain and Graham in the US Senate and they are hawks.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367850845002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367850936399-11</Id><Title>★★★★KEEP ON BUYING Dummies...Bernanke pullback Friday ???</Title><Msg>very soon boys......</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1367850936399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367851490362-12</Id><Topic><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One other thing. I think the logic is flawed in this report. If you really believed that wars are started to fill the coffers of "militarists" then would it not seem that a downturn in profits from Europe would cause them to "create" another war, not dissuade them. By that logic Europe should keep buying to keep the peace.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367851490362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367852291057-13</Id><Topic><Title>German renewable energy helped cut European power prices in April</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367692680429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 14:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Solar power is good but needs to prove it can stand on it's own feet and not be propped up by government money transfers and can sustain it's own maintenance costs in the long run and consider that they only produce for about 12 out of 24 hours each day.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367852291057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:58:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367854519842-14</Id><Topic><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The right wing is already having huge wargasms. --- at least we tried...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367854519842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855055879-15</Id><Topic><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the biggest defender of freedom in the world. *-- *War of 1812 and Invasion of Canada started by the USA *Mexican American war started by USA *Invasion of Nicaragua by US paramilitary forces with Southern government state backing *Spanish American and Philippines war started by USA *Invasion of Mexico 1916-1917 --- US action *Selling arms during World War I...not very neutral *Left Russia to the Communists 1918-1919 at first hint of danger after placing itself as the party in charge: support of Bolshevik freedom to exist and slaughter tens of millions *escalated a meaningless conflict in Vietnam into an all out war that killed many millions. *invaded Iraq 2003 for no reason, or a made up reason ........ I'm unconvinced about the USA being a beacon of world peace and harmony. It's 200 or so history is very thoroughly soiled, and it is a matter of opinion whether its record is worse than others... You will not get support for the war you obviously want....</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367855055879</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367855155176-16</Id><Topic><Title>German renewable energy helped cut European power prices in April</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367692680429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 14:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know nothing about the economics involved, or the process of development of technology.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367855155176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 11:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367858007912-17</Id><Topic><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Say what you want about the wisdom of the Iraq war but that was a continuation of hostilities begun by Saddam Hussein when he invaded the peaceful country of Kuwait and refused to abide by the terms of a cease fire agreement he made. Mexico started the Mexican war in response to Statehood of Texas which was at that time an independent Republic agreed to by the treaty of Velasco made by the leader (dictator) of Mexico. I believe the actions in 1916-17 would probably be in response to Poncho Villa's raids on US properties. Also, not being neutral is not the same thing as starting a war. Vietnam was a war inherited from the French although the US did unwisely make it larger. No country gets perfect marks looking in hindsight but the US has done the best at expanding freedom and prosperity in the world. Only nuts want war but only cowards will submit to tyranny to avoid it.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367858007912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367863786666-18</Id><Title>Solar = Disruptive Technology (Graph)</Title><Msg>Solar = Disruptive Technology (Graph) I recently ran across this interesting graph on reddit: Click to embiggen. The title of the article in which the graph was housed (similar to mine above) was: “Solar Energy: This Is What A Disruptive Technology Looks Like.” I think the graph is pretty clear — while the price of retail electricity, residential natural gas, and crude oil have all remained fairly constant in the past few decades (in inflation-adjusted terms), the price of solar has rolled down a long, big hill. And, the good news is, it’s still rolling. For a bit more detail on the methodology, Brian McConnell, a software engineer and the creator of The Joule Standard, explains: “ Using data from the Energy Information Agency, I pulled together a history of retail prices for natural gas, crude oil, gasoline and residential electricity, all adjusted for inflation. For each energy source, I converted the prices to $/gigajoule, using conversion factors from engineering tables. (For example, a million cubic feet of natural gas contains 1.083 gigajoules of energy content). Next, using data from the National Renewable Energy Laboratory and other sources, I looked up the price history for solar power, in terms of dollar per Watt of system capacity (a standard unit of measure for solar). With this data, I built a cost model to translate the cost of a solar cell into $/gigajoule. The basic idea is to amortize the system cost over its useful life, and divide this by the average amount of power it generates per month. This allows the cost of solar to be compared directly to other sources. The comparison shows quite clearly that the cost effectiveness of solar power is increasing exponentially. In 1977, solar cells cost upwards of $70 per Watt of capacity. In 2013, that cost has dropped to $0.74 per Watt, a 100:1 improvement (source: The Economist). On average, solar power improves 14% per year in solarloveDOTorg/solar-disruptive-technology-graph/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367863786666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367864093972-19</Id><Title>Judge seeks fast action on challenge to SEC oil disclosure rule</Title><Msg>Judge seeks fast action on challenge to SEC oil disclosure rule By Ben Geman - 05/06/13 10:52 AM ET A federal judge hopes to move quickly on industry litigation challenging Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) rules that will force oil, gas and mining companies to disclose payments to foreign governments. The case is proceeding in the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia Circuit because appellate judges ruled in late April that the case should begin there. In a Friday order, District Judge John Bates said he’ll consider the industry challenge to the 2012 rule based on the same briefs that were previously filed before the appeals court. He ordered the industry groups and the SEC to file them with the lower court by May 10. The process laid out Friday is the latest development in a legal fight that pits the American Petroleum Institute and the U.S. Chamber of Commerce against the SEC. Click here and here for more on the case. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/297897-judge-seeks-fast-action-on-challenge-to-sec-oil-disclosure-rule</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367864093972</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367864266292-20</Id><Title>Major oil sands producer: We need Keystone pipeline</Title><Msg>Major oil sands producer: We need Keystone pipeline By Ben Geman - 05/06/13 12:31 PM ET A big player in Canada’s oil sands believes the Keystone XL pipeline will eventually be needed to keep expanding production of the resource. “Long-term, we do need Keystone to be able to grow the volumes in Canada,” Canadian Natural Resources Ltd. President Steve Laut tells The Globe and Mail. The comment could provide political ammunition to environmental groups battling TransCanada Corp.’s proposed pipeline. Keystone opponents argue it will be a catalyst for expanding oil sands production, thereby worsening greenhouse gas emissions. As The Globe and Mail piece notes, Laut’s view breaks with other industry officials and a U.S. State Department analysis, which found that building Keystone wouldn’t have much affect on overall production growth. The Obama administration is weighing whether to grant a permit for Keystone, which would bring oil from Alberta’s oil sands projects across the U.S. border en route to Gulf Coast refineries. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/297929-major-oil-sands-producer-we-need-keystone-pipeline</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367864266292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367864672897-21</Id><Topic><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please. Most Republicans echo the satanic` bad breath of Count Cheney who cannot get enough of war, torture and poverty. The Bush museum is a monument to pain and death.You Republicans will pay one day for what you did to so many innocent people including Americans..</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1367864672897</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367874074545-22</Id><Topic><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A lot of people got hurt in the US Revolutionary war too. I guess you would through Washington and Jefferson into the same pit. I am not a fan of Bush or the way Iraq was handled so it is hard to take a side that would seem so but I would say that most US responses in war are motivated in stopping a greater evil of continued persecution and tyranny. If you want to believe propaganda of the Hollywood airheads and so called newsmen with thrills going up their legs then too bad for you</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367874074545</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 17:01:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367876216568-23</Id><Topic><Title>Europe cuts military spending as USA wastes…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367846608230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 09:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ u</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1367876216568</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 17:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367891217948-24</Id><Title>NRA Cowards Ban Guns Inside Convention.</Title><Msg>All the NRA cowards and their small weeners won't have their little wee wee extender pee shooters inside the conference because the gun manufacturer executives are afraid of their "target market" of fools and lunatics and would never allow their wealthy lifestyles to be threatened by these freaks so NO GUNS ALLOWED AT THE NRA CONVENTION. Filthy cowards all you right wingers are. With all your guns one F-16 will wipe you all out and don't you forget it.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1367891217948</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:46:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367891677999-25</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Cowards Ban Guns Inside Convention.</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1367891217948</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:46:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The poster boy for brain death is out of the asylum on parole again. But back soon I'm sure.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1367891677999</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367895796402-26</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Cowards Ban Guns Inside Convention.</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1367891217948</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:46:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahlleeee is a comie coward #$%$ runt with a dumb mouth.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1367895796402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367896101153-27</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Cowards Ban Guns Inside Convention.</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1367891217948</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 21:46:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see your vapid posting is still your primary tact. You're a true right wing coward. Too bad you'll never be man enough step into the light and challenge the facts within the post that the NRA executives are afraid of their members and they are such hypocritical liars(like you) that they won't let their beloved guns(profits) into the facility where they are holding convention. They are fascists cloaked by fuax patriotism. And you infernal are a coward..You always have been and you always will be... And are you still cashing the social security checks you impotent old hypocrite.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1367896101153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367896379812-28</Id><Topic><Title>maxidopey</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1367310662866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 04:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better change your name u commie coward #$%$ runt. Bet u have no teath in your mouth now.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1367896379812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>