<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365485341118-1</Id><Title>White House engaging lawmakers on energy tax code issues</Title><Msg>White House engaging lawmakers on energy tax code issues By Zack Colman - 04/08/13 03:58 PM ET The White House is working behind the scenes with some lawmakers on energy issues in preparation for Congress tackling tax code reform, an aide to President Obama said Monday. Heather Zichal, Obama’s top climate aide, said the administration is meeting with both Republicans and Democrats to discuss energy tax policy issues important to the president. “I think there’s an important dialogue happening. We’re hopeful in trying to create space to be able to actually do that,” Zichal said Monday during a Washington, D.C.-area event hosted by Transportation Energy Partners. While Zichal characterized Congress’ chances of taking up tax reform as “up in the air,” she said the White House is “standing by ready to engage.” Zichal mentioned a few of the administration’s specific tax policy aims, but declined to elaborate beyond her public comments. “I’m not in a position to go into detail on that right now,” she told reporters. If Congress does dive into tax reform, many of the energy measures Obama prefers would likely run into opposition from fiscal conservatives. Conservatives have pushed back against energy subsidies — especially for renewable energy — they say would expand the federal deficit. They have been particularly critical of the production tax credit for renewable energy, which Obama wants to make permanent. The credit subsidizes renewable energy generation from wind, biomass, geothermal and other forms of renewable energy. The incentive currently faces expiration every couple of years. Renewable energy proponents say the uncertainty of congressional approval stunts investment. Zichal said baking the credit into the tax code is a significant administration priority. She explained it would help reach a second-term goal to double renewable.. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/292417-white-house-engaging-lawmakers-on-energy-tax-code-issues</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365485341118</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 01:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365485671320-2</Id><Title>Greenhouse gas rules will be enacted soon, says Obama aide</Title><Msg>Greenhouse gas rules will be enacted soon, says Obama aide By Zack Colman - 04/08/13 02:32 PM ET The White House will enact greenhouse gas emission rules for power plants in the “not-too-distant future,” Heather Zichal, President Obama’s top climate adviser, said Monday. The proposed Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) standards for coal-fired power plants are “pretty historic” and “very much in line with the president’s broader climate objectives,” Zichal said at a Washington, D.C.-area conference hosted by Transportation Energy Partners. Zichal made the comments after a recent Washington Post report suggested the administration might postpone and tweak the emissions rules, which were proposed about one year ago over strong opposition from industry groups and congressional Republicans. Environmental groups back the emissions limits, and want Obama to go even further by imposing greenhouse gas limits on plants that are already up and running. The rules awaiting approval would only apply to coal-powered plants that are built in the future. The White House has not said whether similar standards for existing plants are being considered, though Obama said in his State of the Union speech that he would use executive authority to address emissions if Congress fails to do so legislatively. Zichal didn't address the prospects of emissions rules for existing power plants on Monday, but said the EPA is a focal point of Obama's climate strategy. “You’ve heard directly from the president that energy and climate policy is going to be a top focus in his second term," she said. The rules for coal-fired plants are a major component of the White House's efforts to reduce carbon emissions. Democrats, environmental groups and public health advocates say the proposed rules would help stem climate change and reduce exposure to harmful pollutants, saving billions in.. thehillDOcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/292377-obama-aide-final-power-plant-emissions-rules-coming-soon</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365485671320</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 01:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365486599278-3</Id><Title>Energy Secretary Nominee: Need Carbon Price To Double Or Triple Cost Of Dirty Energy</Title><Msg>Energy Secretary Nominee: Need Carbon Price To Double Or Triple Cost Of Dirty Energy April 8, 2013 Guest Contributor Reposted from Climate Progress: Tuesday is the confirmation hearing date for Energy Secretary nominee Ernest Moniz. The MIT professor will face the Senate Energy and Natural Resources committee (webcast here starts at 10 am ET). I have known Moniz for 30 years. Turns out he was my professor for advanced electromagnetism in 1982. Then I worked with him again at the Clinton Energy Department in 1997 and 1998 (his full bio is here). I think he’s a fine choice for Secretary — and considerably better than many of thealternatives. Some have complained that Moniz, like Chu, is not an energy deployment guy. True enough, but somehow U.S. renewable electricity supply managed to double under Chu. Of course, that’s also mostly a coincidence because the energy secretary doesn’t actually have much power over energy in this country. For those worry about fracking, for instance, the EPA administrator nominee — Gina McCarthy — will play a much more salient role. And she’s the one who will be in charge of developing carbon regulations. She gets a confirmation hearing on Thursday. Moniz is exceedingly knowledgeable about carbon issues. Just last year told the Switch Energy Project he supports a carbon price that would substantially increase electricity costs: “If we start really squeezing down on carbon dioxide over the next few decades, well, that could double; it could eventually triple…. I think inevitably if we squeeze down on carbon, we squeeze up on the cost, it brings along with it a push toward efficiency; it brings along with it a push towards clean technologies in a conventional pollution sense; it brings along with it a push towards security. Because after all, the security issues revolve around carbon-bearing fuels.” video: cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/04/08/energy-secretary-nominee-need-carbon-price-to-double-or-triple-cost-of-dirty-energy/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365486599278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 01:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365486757467-4</Id><Title>Ethanol industry seeks toned-down renewable fuel goals</Title><Msg>Ethanol industry seeks toned-down renewable fuel goals By Ben Goad - 04/08/13 12:43 PM ET A key industry group is urging the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) to ratchet back this year’s volume requirements for biofuel production, arguing the proposed standards are unrealistic. Informal comments submitted Monday, the Renewable Fuels Association (RFA) advised EPA to revise its cellulosic and advanced biofuel standardsset out earlier this year. The proposed rule sets the 2013 standard for cellulosic fuel – made from non-edible feedstock – at 14 million gallons, up from 8.65 million gallons last year. The figure was based on expectations that two companies, KiOR and INEOS Bio, would be able to meet those production goals. RFA argues in its comments that current projections indicate the proposed standard is not realistic. RFA, a leading ethanol trade group, did not specify a better number. Rather, the organization is urging the agency to coordinate with the two companies. RFA is also asking EPA to bring its advanced biofuel proposed standard in line with expectations related to sugarcane imports, a crucial element of production. “We do not believe the levels of sugarcane ethanol imports assumed by EPA are reasonable given current market conditions,” Renewable Fuels Association President Bob Dinneen said. Additionally, RFA is asking EPA to expedite the release of 2014 standards, “so stakeholders can engage with the Agency to ensure the program is implemented as efficiently as possible next year,” Dinneen said. The comments areavailable here. thehillDOTcom/blogs/regwatch/energyenvironment/292355-ethanol-industry-seeks-toned-down-renewable-fuel-goals</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365486757467</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 01:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365509954305-5</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>sanromanwiliam</Username><Timestamp>1361547275275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:34:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>today $4</Msg><Username>kaim.brian</Username><Timestamp>1365509954305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365509979149-6</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve = ignorance personified</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1364674108192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>come on maxi its just entertainment. Hell I might even come down there and take u out for a beer and a steak. Probably the best u have had in a long time.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1365509979149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365517482398-7</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT !</Title><Username>barry.white95</Username><Timestamp>1362318160412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:42:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very nice report !</Msg><Username>mary.grooms</Username><Timestamp>1365517482398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365518604803-8</Id><Title>Green taxes offset retiree cost...</Title><Msg>Taxes on energy consumption and pollution reduce the burden of supporting the elderly. The reason is simple: The elderly collect very little income from wages &amp; salaries, effectively approaching 0 as a percent of national income as they age. Their main means of support is government spending and savings. So when government taxes energy consumption &amp; pollution and spends the money, money which is collected as income by younger people, it amounts to a transfer of income &amp; wealth from old to young. This is one way the German government manages to support the elderly with ease. The technology generated by taxing energy consumption and subsidizing science also generates useful industrial advantages, and associated reductions in pollution reduce healthcare expenses. The USA would do well to adopt this model.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365518604803</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365519097169-9</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve is a bonafide COWARD</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1360340542136</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 11:22:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have composed a song and sent it to your email address for you to read</Msg><Username>proclaimmusic</Username><Timestamp>1365519097169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365520866292-10</Id><Title>Immigration: how you slam the door nearly shut...</Title><Msg>First you need an effective Ministry of the Interior to monitor people. Second you need an effective immigration law. Third, you need to implement it. This was done in Germany from the end of World War II to the present and it was not done in the USA. Germany allowed nearly 16 million Germans in with almost no questions asked (Germans can tell a German easily), but anyone else seeking entry had to pass a battery of fitness tests, medical tests, and stringent regulations governing their length of stay and how they could be employed. The result was to funnel the immigrants to low skilled, high risk, debilitating jobs, jobs with effectively no chance of advancement in society, and very little chance of being acceptable as a marriage partner to any German. Acquiring German citizenship is still extremely difficult unless one is born to a Germany. Americans and the right cultural background would find the route very easy if they applied themselves, but for other they might as well not even try... This policy prevented the chaos that has converted American cities into dens of crime and cultural collapse.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365520866292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365521784522-11</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT !</Title><Username>barry.white95</Username><Timestamp>1362318160412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:42:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very helpful !</Msg><Username>lucille.coffey</Username><Timestamp>1365521784522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:36:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365521927393-12</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very helpful !</Msg><Username>lucille.coffey</Username><Timestamp>1365521927393</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365523847470-13</Id><Topic><Title>STOP THE KEYSTONE PIPELINE</Title><Username>kythumper</Username><Timestamp>1365374196796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 18:36:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pipelines have the best safety record in transporting petroleum products world wide. And they are more cost effective than marine vessels, trains, or trucks. So if you favor lower oil costs and safety of the environment you should favor pipelines. Now whether these cost savings will be passed onto the consumer, that is more a function of supply and demand issues.</Msg><Username>redsky_night</Username><Timestamp>1365523847470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:10:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365524992560-14</Id><Title>gun safety= "you don't have guns---we do"---Government.</Title><Msg>pay heed</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365524992560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365526104810-15</Id><Title>Oil going much higher this summer!! Very bullish for oil!</Title><Msg>Rocket shot up!</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1365526104810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365527968207-16</Id><Title>MTBE liability...</Title><Msg>It would be interesting to see how much Exxon will be sued now that they have lost their case in New Hampshire over groundwater pollution with MTBE. "In Europe, Achten (2002) during a study conducted in Germany, confirmed the presence of MTBE traces in numerous rivers, in water entering urban wastewater treatment plants but also after purification, substantiating the relative inability of the plants to cope with the MTBE pollution. Kolb and Puttman (2006) determined the MTBE concentrations in 83 finished drinking water samples from 50 cities in Germany.... In France, in 1999, the drinking water distribution had to be interrupted for several days in (Pas-de-Calais).... --Petroleum Microbiology, concepts, environmental implications, industrial applications (2005)</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365527968207</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365528548474-17</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT !</Title><Username>barry.white95</Username><Timestamp>1362318160412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:42:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for this report</Msg><Username>willian.madrigal</Username><Timestamp>1365528548474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365528747573-18</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for this report</Msg><Username>willian.madrigal</Username><Timestamp>1365528747573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365530772153-19</Id><Title>70% of Portugal's electricity consumption supplied by renewable sources in Q1 2013</Title><Msg>70% of Portugal's electricity consumption supplied by renewable sources in Q1 2013 twitterDOTcom/ekopolitan/status/321410942825033728</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365530772153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 14:06:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365531514434-20</Id><Title>Question</Title><Msg>As I have pointed out shareholders have suffered through 5 years of drastic underperformance. Not much us peon individual shareholders can do about this management that is aggressively anti shareholder. My question is how in the world do institutional shareholders put up with this terrible stock performance and management that screws over the shareholders so badly?</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1365531514434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 14:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365534451783-21</Id><Topic><Title>MTBE liability...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365527968207</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:19:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is just the first step. Exxon has a history of appealing these State judgements to federal courts for years, if not decades.</Msg><Username>ploddingalong98</Username><Timestamp>1365534451783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:07:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365538287208-22</Id><Title>Typical</Title><Msg>Typical day for XOM. End of day crump. Worst performing oil stock for fourth of fifth day in a row. Continuing its 4 years of uninterrupted drastic underperformance. Tillerson isn't competent to run a lemonade stand. Company should give the guy $100 million to take a hike.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1365538287208</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365538930146-23</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT !</Title><Username>barry.white95</Username><Timestamp>1362318160412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:42:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing.</Msg><Username>paulcoleman168</Username><Timestamp>1365538930146</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365539104143-24</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great job.</Msg><Username>paulcoleman168</Username><Timestamp>1365539104143</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365542206883-25</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT !</Title><Username>barry.white95</Username><Timestamp>1362318160412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:42:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very useful.</Msg><Username>andresmith537</Username><Timestamp>1365542206883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365542362361-26</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well done.</Msg><Username>andresmith537</Username><Timestamp>1365542362361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365546411081-27</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR XOM BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT !</Title><Username>barry.white95</Username><Timestamp>1362318160412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 08:42:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you very much!</Msg><Username>ingramayolanda</Username><Timestamp>1365546411081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365546585764-28</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very helpful.</Msg><Username>ingramayolanda</Username><Timestamp>1365546585764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:29:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365549976605-29</Id><Title>Outlook</Title><Msg>Its been a lousy 5 years for Exxon shareholders as I've outlined (and a quick review of a Yahoo chart will confirm.). Unfortunately the future does not look better. The basic problem is that the company is spending all their profits to try to replenish their depleting reserves but still have been unable to do so. Therefore as investor James Chanos says Exxon is in a stealth liquidation mode ( between the weak stock price and buy backs the market cap of XOM is down by a third in 5 years.) Because of this massive spending Exxon's cash is depleting and soon the company will not be able to spend $20 billion a year on buy backs knocking out a major prop of its stock price. This will also impact future dividend increases. This was a major reason for the downgrade recently by Oppenheimer. Exxon has also been forced to make deals with powerful state oil companies in Russia and the Middle East which have been quite unfavorable. There does not appear to be any prospect of improvement in production at any time in the foreseeable future. Add to this the very ill advised purchase of XTO at a huge premium and the company's dependence on the unfavorable economics of natural gas. By the way NG has risen a good bit recently benefitting such stocks as Anadarko and Devon and EOG but not Exxon. Finally there is the weak extremely shareholder unfriendly management of Rex Tillerson which will do nothing that may increase shareholder value (compare with the shareholder friendly management of Chevron and compare the stock perform- ance.). These factors go a long way in explaining the drastic near daily underperformance of this stock for the last half decade and don't portend a good future for shareholders in Exxon.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1365549976605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365552683349-30</Id><Topic><Title>MTBE liability...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365527968207</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:19:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XOM will go UP on this news. It is mere peanuts compared to XOM's total revenue.</Msg><Username>cadmium_nitrate</Username><Timestamp>1365552683349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365553102719-31</Id><Title>President Obama shows his cards</Title><Msg>President Obama shows his cards By Ben Geman and Zack Colman - 04/09/13 07:14 PM ET COMING WEDNESDAY: The delayed White House fiscal 2014 budget plan. The budget will likely revive President Obama's fight with Republicans and oil-patch Democrats over petroleum industry tax breaks. Past budget plans have consistently called for stripping billions of dollars in tax incentives from oil and gas, but Congress hasn’t gone along. The budget could also put meat on the bones of other White House energy-related plans that Obama has touted in recent months, including his call to steer $2 billion over a decade from offshore oil-and-gas royalties into the development of technologies that wean the transportation sector off oil. In the afternoon, top officials with the Energy Department, Environmental Protection Agency and the Interior Department will brief reporters. Watch E2-Wire tomorrow for coverage of the plan's energy and climate change provisions. THE REST OF WEDNESDAY'S AGENDA: Big companies to press Obama on climate More than 30 companies, including thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/292777-overnight-energy-obama-shows-his-cards</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365553102719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:18:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365554800094-32</Id><Title>XOM Suing Arkansas for Taking Oil from Its Leaky Pipelines and Mixing with Groundwater, Lakes</Title><Msg>Arkansas has taken millions of barrels of oil and mixed this oil with the groundwater and lakes in order to hide the oil.</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1365554800094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365555509720-33</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve = ignorance personified</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1364674108192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxipad strokes weiners!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>max_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1365555509720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365555571430-34</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve = ignorance personified</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1364674108192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxipad really loves MEAT. I have a nice hotdog for him....</Msg><Username>max_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1365555571430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365560102050-35</Id><Topic><Title>Outlook</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1365549976605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True. I expect the upcoming announcement on the 2013 dividend to be yet another Rishiki-like "stink face" to the shareholders from Rex and his crony board.</Msg><Username>tsobie</Username><Timestamp>1365560102050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 22:15:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365560438979-36</Id><Topic><Title>Question</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1365531514434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 14:18:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The institutional ownership may well be pension funds and other "basket" type holders. The individuals who ultimately care have no proxy vote while the fund managers may have no skin in the game.</Msg><Username>tsobie</Username><Timestamp>1365560438979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 22:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>