<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361250221008-1</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Love War Profits, Hate Soldiers</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1360899512097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 22:38:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another demonstration of your extreme brain death. Thank you for the entertainment.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1361250221008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 00:03:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361260160990-2</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Love War Profits, Hate Soldiers</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1360899512097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 22:38:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no one likes u commie POS so leave america before tea baggers through u out.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1361260160990</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 02:49:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361274723470-3</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361200842179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 10:20:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold 30 Year UK Gilts @3.443% yield to maturity, sold all £ for € @ 1.1610 €/£ ..... £ basis: 1.1589 €/£ (0.8629 £/€) gain on £, +0.18% loss on bonds -0.1% ..... net gain on bonds and £: +0.08% 5% £ 95% €</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361274723470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:52:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361275473265-4</Id><Topic><Title>Quantum Chemistry Application - Methanol to gasoline</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361216459694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 14:40:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Methanol to gasoline is very old technology." Vulcanizing rubber is a very old technology. Producing gasoline from crude oil is an very old technology. Computers and chemical simulations of are a very old technology. Wow - it sure is easy to make sweeping, brief, and worthless statements. What is relevant is the process, its efficiency, and cost. You have not competed against the most efficient process as it has not been possible to discover it without the aid of supercomputers. If you actually read the presentation you would be able to grasp why this is so. One could make the asinine statement that a 1985 or 1995 computer could perform some of the calculations involved, that is if you didn't mind waiting around about 10,000 years for it to complete the simulation. Trial and error at such a snail's pace is not very effective. You are stuck in the past and oblivious to the modern world... just sad</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361275473265</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:04:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361277468716-5</Id><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Msg>Chancellor Merkel has a Doctorate in Quantum Chemistry. While there is no chance anybody around here could possibly discover the current state of German technology, you can be certain that she and her government is aware of it. Policy goals for advanced energy technology and efficiency set by the German government are informed by rational thought on what is possible. It is safe to assume for a lawyer-President that is probably not so, and why platitudes and "balanced" approaches are the preferred route. But then someone so ignorant would not know enough to even follow a balanced approach, unless he happened to fall upon by chance. Quantum optics and chemistry, and in particular the computation tools which are driving it now, opens up a new world of materials, efficiency and what is possible... This new world is not friendly to the fossil fuel industry.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361278379032-6</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats for sure</Msg><Username>ed_tillery</Username><Timestamp>1361278379032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:52:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361279009879-7</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>traded well while it lasted though</Msg><Username>lucasjohn476</Username><Timestamp>1361279009879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:03:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361279854887-8</Id><Title>Government by the Imbecility Principle</Title><Msg>The US currency has lost more than 1/3 of its value against the euro since the election of W Bush, and this despite all the problems in southern Europe. Prospects for it lose another 1/3 are good considering the massive US trade deficit, budget deficit, asinine healthcare policy, and hopeless divided government. The process seems to be for both major US parties pick a trained politician to become President and preferably one with as little useful experience as possible. Actors turned politicians, or "businessmen" aided in their pursuits by political connections are good candidates to lead. It just pathetic.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361279854887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:17:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361280522273-9</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we shall see</Msg><Username>claud.strock</Username><Timestamp>1361280522273</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:28:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361280917433-10</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361200842179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 10:20:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold all € for £ @ 0.8632 £/€ € basis: 0.8613 £/€ (1.1610 €/£). Gain on €: +0.22% 100% £ @ LIBOR 0.50%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361280917433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:35:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361282251835-11</Id><Topic><Title>[EXCLUSIVE] XOM CEO on MAD MONEY! [EXCLUSIVE]</Title><Username>jeffreyevans708</Username><Timestamp>1360886411313</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 19:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not that sure, this stock is overweight</Msg><Username>shalemachine</Username><Timestamp>1361282251835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:57:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361282341793-12</Id><Topic><Title>Quantum Chemistry Application - Methanol to gasoline</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361216459694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 14:40:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the music today comes from shale gas, this thing you mention is not innovation</Msg><Username>gregtiberius</Username><Timestamp>1361282341793</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:59:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361282446686-13</Id><Topic><Title>Government by the Imbecility Principle</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361279854887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:17:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>keep on thinking with developed western countries mind and continue to underperform for years. China is investing in Africa and LatAm with other logic...and doing great in resources</Msg><Username>gregtiberius</Username><Timestamp>1361282446686</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 09:00:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361282901602-14</Id><Title>Mega Alert: ILNS on Tuesday opening! EARLY ALERT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>MONSTER GAPPING!</Msg><Username>southpeir</Username><Timestamp>1361282901602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 09:08:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361282908650-15</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>listen to the masters</Msg><Username>steven.laverriere</Username><Timestamp>1361282908650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 09:08:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361283053263-16</Id><Topic><Title>Government by the Imbecility Principle</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361279854887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 08:17:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The same China that has abandoned egalitarian education and copied the German way of subsidizing an elite straight to the top. Yes they are doing much better since they started doing that after 1985. China will become like Germany one day if they keep that up. German technology also substantially aids China's advance, and Germany makes hundreds of billions yearly in trade with countries with inferior technology. Technology, not resources, is the source of wealth. Latin America, Africa, and other resource based economies have always been poor and will always be poor. They lack human capital and the "western" perspective on how to acquire it.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361283053263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 09:10:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361284466578-17</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow great stuff cant wait</Msg><Username>rickybradford979</Username><Timestamp>1361284466578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 09:34:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361285098282-18</Id><Title>Next-Generation Lithium-Ion Battery Designed, Should Hit Market Within 2-3 Years</Title><Msg>Next-Generation Lithium-Ion Battery Designed, Should Hit Market Within 2-3 Years February 19, 2013 Nathan Next-generation lithium-ion batteries that hold more than 3 times the charge that current batteries do and can recharge in around 10 minutes are now within reach. The new design, created by researchers at USC, may be commercially available within only 2-3 years according to those involved. The design is based on replacing the currently used graphite anodes with porous silicon nanoparticles. This follows work done by the same researchers last year using silicon nanowires. The nanowire version actually lasts much longer (2000 recharge cycles) than the current nanoparticle version (200 recharge cycles) and conventional graphite-based designs (500 recharge cycles). But the researchers are confident that the lifespan of the nanoparticle design can be greatly improved in the near future. The problem with nanowires is just that they are relatively hard to mass manufacture, while silicon nanoparticles are readily available. The impressive charge capacity and recharge rate could be very useful for many slow-charging batteries currently in use, such as those used in electric and hybrid cars, laptops, cell phones, etc. “It’s exciting research. It opens the door for the design of the next generation lithium-ion batteries,” said Chongwu Zhou, professor at the USC Viterbi School of Engineering, and lead researcher. “Researchers have long attempted to use silicon, which is cheap and has a high potential capacity, in battery anodes. (Anodes are where current flows into a battery, while cathodes are where current flows out.) The problem has been that previous silicon anode designs, which were basically tiny plates of the material, broke down from repeated swelling and shrinking during charging/discharging cycles and quickly became useless,” the University of Southern California press release states. So, last year, the researchers began experimenting with silicon nanowires, with their small size and their porous nature offering some resistance to the damage caused by swelling. “The tiny pores on the nanowires allowed the silicon to expand and contract without breaking while simultaneously increasing the surface area — which in turn allows lithium ions to diffuse in and out of the battery more quickly, improving performance.” The researchers are also working on the development of a new cathode material to pair with the silicon nanowires and nanoparticles, potentially creating an entirely new battery design. The new research was published in Nano Research. sDOTtt/1zWPs</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361285098282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 09:44:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361285321332-19</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I appreciate this I was really lookin' for something like this newsletter.</Msg><Username>romerotimothy528</Username><Timestamp>1361285321332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 09:48:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361286071056-20</Id><Title>Oil Sands Mining Uses Up Almost as Much Energy as It Produces, Study Finds</Title><Msg>Oil Sands Mining Uses Up Almost as Much Energy as It Produces, Study Finds Thanks to high global oil prices, industry can afford the large amount of energy needed to extract the oil and turn it into a usable fuel. By Rachel Nuwer Feb 19, 2013 Suncor Millenium oil sands mine on the east side of the Athabasca River in Alberta, Canada. Credit: David Dodge, Pembina Institute The average "energy returned on investment," or EROI, for conventional oil is roughly 25:1. In other words, 25 units of oil-based energy are obtained for every one unit of other energy that is invested to extract it. But tar sands oil is in a category all its own. Tar sands retrieved by surface mining has an EROI of only about 5:1, according to research scheduled to be released Tuesday. Tar sands retrieved from deeper beneath the earth, through steam injection, fares even worse, with a maximum average ratio of just 2.9 to 1. That means one unit of natural gas is needed to create less than three units of oil-based energy. "They have to use a lot of natural gas to upgrade this heavy, sticky, gooky almost tar-like stuff to make it fluid enough to use," said Charles Hall, a professor at the State University of New York's College of Environmental Science and Forestry. Hydrogen from gas heats the tar sands so the viscous form of petroleum it contains, known as bitumen, can be liquefied and pumped out of the ground. In this way, Hall said, gas helps turn tar sands "into something a bit closer to what we call oil." With most of the world's highest quality resources already exhausted, companies are turning to formerly undesirable alternatives such as tar sands oil, which come with higher energetic price tags yet lower returns. "We built our nation, economy and civilization on cheap energy—that's where this incredible growth of the U.S. economy has come from," said Hall, who coined the term EROI in 1979. "But that characteristic high energy return on investment fuel from much of the last century is no longer here." The latest EROI values for tar sands were calculated by David Hughes, a fellow at the Post Carbon Institute, a non-profit devoted to issues such as climate change and energy scarcity, based in Santa Rosa, Calif. The institute plans to release Hughes' findings on Tuesday. Hughes' figures include the energy it takes to mine bitumen as well as to upgrade it to synthetic oil that can be put into a refinery. It also includes the liquefied natural gas used to turn it into dilbit (diluted bitumen) so it can flow through pipelines. Hall, who wasn't involved in Hughes' study, thinks the EROI for oil sands would fall closer to 1:1 if the tar sands' full life cycle—including transportation, refinement into higher quality products, end use efficiency and environmental costs—was taken into account. Travis Davies, manager of media and issues at the Canadian Association of Petroleum Producers, disputes Hughes' calculations. He said oil sands create 6 to 10 energy units for each energy unit used, but he did not cite a source for those figures. Both Hughes and Hall think the new data should be factored into the debate over Canada's tar sands reserves, which cover an area about the size of Florida. Environmentalists argue that the oil sands should be left in the ground, because they produce much more carbon than other fossil fuels. The industry, supported by the Canadian government, says the oil sands are crucial to Canada's economy and can provide the United States with a reliable source of fuel from a friendly neighbor. What isn't often mentioned, Hughes said, is the energy required to extract the oil, or the rate at which it can feasibly be recovered. "Unless we talk about all three metrics—size of the resource, net energy and rate of supply—we're not getting the full story," he said. Canada's Oil Sands Boom The world currently burns through an estimated 88.25 million barrels of oil per day. As the supply of sweet, light crude diminishes, it is being replaced by unconventional alternatives, including tar sands. Most unconventional energy sources have much lower efficiencies than conventional gas and oil, which operate at a combined energy-returned-on-investment ratio of about 18:1. Shale gas, for example, performs at about 6.5:1 to 7.6:1—a bit better than the 2.9:1 to 5.1 for tar sands oil. Corn ethanol, with an EROI of about 1.3:1, sits at the bottom of the barrel for investment pay off. "If you accept the fact that fossil fuels are finite—and I think most people would—then using a lot more fossil fuels for recovering energy as opposed to doing actual work basically uses them up quicker with no net payback in terms of useful work," Hughes said. "It's an issue of diminishing returns." Canada is touted as having the third largest oil reserves in the world. But its supply of conventional oil is shrinking, and oil sands extraction has been growing fast in the past decade, from about 700,000 barrels per day in 2000 to 1.7 million today. Hughes based his calculations on the 25.6 billion barrels of Canadian tar sands oil that are currently under active development. What concerns him more is the EROI of the estimated 143 billion additional barrels of oil sands that are sitting under Alberta's boreal forests, especially since only 8 percent of that oil is accessible via surface mining. "Those EROI numbers are going to go down as we move away from the highest quality to the lesser quality parts of the resource," Hughes said. "I'd expect that downward shift to probably start about now." When the entire life cycle of the fuels is considered—including production, transportation and burning the final product— the greenhouse gas differential between conventional oil and tar sands oil is about 20 percent, according to a 2011 study from Stanford University. While no rigorous studies have been conducted on the association between diminishing EROI values and increased greenhouse gas emissions, Hughes thinks "it's a pretty safe assumption to make" that they are linked. Those emissions are only going to increase as Canada ramps up to the 5 million barrels per day already approved for extraction, said Simon Dyer, policy director for the Pembina Institute, a Canadian non-profit focused on developing sustainable energy solutions. "The impacts today are actually irrelevant compared to the tripling of emissions that hasn’t yet expressed itself on the landscape," Dyer said. "At a time when we need to be de-carbonizing our economy and making moves to lower our sources of carbon energy, clearly oil sands are a step in the wrong direction." More Than Just Dollars Whether mining tar sands oil makes sense financially, depends on the world market price of oil—and on whether a company has already paid off its infrastructure costs or is building a new mine. With the current price of synthetic crude oil sometimes dipping as low as $30 per barrel, a company that has paid off its infrastructure can still make a profit. For a company that's still building, however, the market price would have to be about $100 per barrel in order to justify construction, Hughes said. "Cost-wise, this is the most expensive oil being produced today," Dyer said. "It's a pretty clear indicator that our solution to energy needs is not chasing lower and lower quality fossil fuel resources that come with higher impacts." If oil sands oil eventually finds an easy outlet to the Gulf Coast—perhaps through the proposed Keystone XL pipeline project—the price for upgraded synthetic oil will likely rise to reflect the world market value, currently $110 per barrel. Profitability aside, the development of Canada's oil sands reserves will never offset declines in crude oil. At the world's current rate of oil consumption—32.2 billion barrels per year—Canada's tar sands oil reserves remain at a finite 168.6 billion barrels, enough to keep the world fueled for less than six years. insideclimatenewsDOTorg/news/20130219/oil-sands-mining-tar-sands-alberta-canada-energy-return-on-investment-eroi-natural-gas-in-situ-dilbit-bitumen</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361286071056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:01:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361286758746-21</Id><Title>Puget Sound Energy Wind Farms Post New One-Day Generating Record</Title><Msg>Puget Sound Energy Wind Farms Post New One-Day Generating Record Tuesday’s output meets one-fourth of PSE customers’ power needs February 14, 2013 06:07 PM Eastern Time BELLEVUE, Wash.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Nearly a quarter of the electricity Puget Sound Energy customers consumed on Tuesday came from the utility’s three wind farms, marking a new one-day production record for the PSE energy facilities. “Wind is now a key resource for providing our customers with reliable, affordable electricity. And when combined with our hydro, natural gas and coal power plants, wind gives us flexible, cost-effective options for serving local homes and businesses.” . Between midnight Monday and midnight Tuesday, the 1.1 million homes and businesses powered by PSE received 23.5 percent of their electricity from the utility’s three Eastern Washington wind farms. “This milestone underscores the role wind power can play in meeting our energy needs,” said David Mills, PSE vice president of Energy Supply Operations. “Wind is now a key resource for providing our customers with reliable, affordable electricity. And when combined with our hydro, natural gas and coal power plants, wind gives us flexible, cost-effective options for serving local homes and businesses.” Winds east of the Cascades allow PSE’s three wind farms to generate power approximately two-thirds of the time. On average, the facilities are supplying about 10 percent of all the power used by PSE’s electric customers. PSE is the Pacific Northwest’s largest utility producer of wind energy. The company’s first wind farm, Hopkins Ridge, came online in late 2005 in Columbia County. The Wild Horse Wind and Solar Facility, in Kittitas County, entered service a year later. PSE completed Washington’s largest wind farm to date – the Lower Snake River Wind Facility, in Garfield County – nearly one year ago. On Tuesday, the utility’s wind farms produced 16,593 megawatt-hours of electricity; that is almost 90 percent of the facilities’ one-day generating capacity. The new 24-hour record is enough electricity to fully power 503,000 homes for a full day. Since January 2006, PSE’s wind farms have produced more than 7.5 million megawatt-hours of electricity – enough to power 625,000 homes for an entire year. businesswireDOTcom/portal/site/home/permalink/?ndmViewId=news_view&amp;newsLang=en&amp;newsId=20130214006635&amp;div=447208641</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361286758746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:12:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361286908279-22</Id><Topic><Title>Puget Sound Energy Wind Farms Post New One-Day Generating Record</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361286758746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:12:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Change is occuring</Msg><Username>moooooooooooooooooooooooo4u</Username><Timestamp>1361286908279</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:15:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361287406137-23</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great strategy imo</Msg><Username>delagarza.cecil</Username><Timestamp>1361287406137</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:23:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361287888237-24</Id><Title>USA: MassCEC Receives 3 Bids for New Bedford Marine Commerce Terminal Development</Title><Msg>USA: MassCEC Receives 3 Bids for New Bedford Marine Commerce Terminal Development Posted on Feb 19th, 2013 Massachusetts Clean Energy Center (MassCEC) CEO Alicia Barton received three construction bids for the development of the New Bedford Marine Commerce Terminal, which once constructed, will be the first facility in the nation designed to support the construction, assembly, and deployment of offshore wind projects. MassCEC received bids from three contractors: Cashman Equipment Corp. of Braintree, Cashman-Weeks NB of Quincy and Great Lakes Dredge &amp; Dock Company, LLC of Oak Brook, Illinois. “The development of this port facility will further establish Massachusetts as the hub for the emerging offshore wind energy industry along the East Coast,” said Energy and Environmental Affairs Secretary Rick Sullivan, who chairs the MassCEC Board of Directors. This multi-purpose facility will also be able to handle high-volume bulk and container shipping, as well as large specialty marine cargo. As part of construction, the project includes the dredging and removal of approximately 250,000 cubic yards of contaminated sediment, a significant environmental benefit to the City of New Bedford. The first-of-its kind in North America, the terminal will be engineered to sustain mobile crane and storage loads that rival the highest capacity ports in the world. “This is another significant step toward the construction of this one-of-a-kind facility, which will create local jobs and help to establish Massachusetts as a global destination for the offshore wind energy sector,” said MassCEC CEO Alicia Barton. MassCEC will review the bids submitted with the goal of signing with a general contractor as soon as possible, but not later than 90 days. A committee of MassCEC staff and professional engineers will review the bids for compliance with the bid requirements and determine the lowest qualified bidders. The terminal, which will be located inside New Bedford Harbor and protected by the hurricane barrier, will be in close proximity to offshore wind planning areas along the East Coast that are under consideration for development. The federal government is leading an offshore wind permitting and leasing process in nine states, including Massachusetts, along the Atlantic Coast. That process is expected to lead to the construction of multiple projects, many of which could make use of this first-in-the-nation facility. Offshore wind is the largest potential source of clean energy for Massachusetts, and its development can create a significant new industry here in the Commonwealth. The U.S. Department of Energy projects 43,000 clean energy jobs will be created in the offshore wind industry nationally by 2020. The Patrick-Murray Administration set the ambitious goal of reaching 2,000 megawatts of wind energy in Massachusetts by 2020. This goal is part of Governor Patrick’s nation-leading support for clean energy policies aimed at reducing reliance on foreign sources of energy, cutting energy costs and use, while cutting harmful greenhouse gas emissions. The bid review committee is comprised of: Bill White, Director of Offshore Wind Sector Development, MassCEC, Roberto Ramirez Chief Financial Officer, MassCEC Sarah Colao Associate General Counsel, MassCEC, Rahul Yarala, Director of Wind Technology Testing Center, MassCEC Dr. Eric Hines, Professional Engineer, LeMessurier Consultants Chet Myers, Professional Engineer, Apex Companies, LLC Susan Nilson, Professional Engineer, CLE Engineering, Inc. Allen Waller, Professional Engineer, Aspera Associates Ronald Labelle, Professional Engineer, Commissioner of the New Bedford Department of Public Infrastructure offshorewindDOTbiz/2013/02/19/usa-masscec-receives-3-bids-for-new-bedford-marine-commerce-terminal-development/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361287888237</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:31:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361288342993-25</Id><Title>Texas Achieves New Wind Energy Record</Title><Msg>Texas Achieves New Wind Energy Record by NAW Staff on Thursday 14 February 2013 Share on email Wind energy generation provided a record-breaking 9.481 GW of power on the Electric Reliability Council of Texas (ERCOT) grid at 7:08 p.m. on Feb. 9, ERCOT reports. Wind power generation provided nearly 28% of ERCOT's system load at the time, surpassing the previous record of 8.667 GW, set on Jan. 29. Of the total, 7.205 GW came from West Texas, 1.62 GW came from the Texas Gulf Coast, 431 MW came from northern Texas and 225 MW came from southern Texas. "As wind generation capacity continues to be added in ERCOT and additional transmission lines are being completed to accommodate that generation, we continue to set new records," says Kent Saathoff, ERCOT’s vice president of grid operations and system planning. "While wind generation over the course of a day can change very quickly, improved tools help us predict those patterns and enable us to reliably use this resource to its fullest potential." ERCOT has more than 10.4 GW of commercial wind power capacity. Wind power constituted 9.2% of the total energy used in the ERCOT region in 2012, compared to 8.5% in 2011. The completion of the remainder of the high-voltage transmission projects in the Competitive Renewable Energy Zones by the end of this year will continue to improve ERCOT’s ability to move wind power from West Texas to the metropolitan areas where demand on the grid is highest, ERCOT notes. nawindpowerDOTcom/e107_plugins/content/content.php?contentDOT11122#.USObhRG9KK0</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361288342993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:39:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361288413021-26</Id><Topic><Title>Oil Sands Mining Uses Up Almost as Much Energy as It Produces, Study Finds</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361286071056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:01:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is certain, too, than governments will force the oil industry to clean up the massive pollution they have caused around the world even after the price of oil is pushed below their production cost by new technologies. OPEC will no doubt panic when the new technologies start destroying their market and attempt to extract their reserves as fast as possible before they become worthless, compounding the problem for "Big Oil." The oil industry also has underfunded pensions too. They are forced create liabilities on their balance sheet to cover at least part of the pollution cost, but those liabilities are not matched by assets to meet them except oil &amp; gas related assets which will have little to no value when oil prices drop.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361288413021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:40:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361291584409-27</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes they do</Msg><Username>martin_backus</Username><Timestamp>1361291584409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 11:33:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361292047665-28</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Achieves New Wind Energy Record</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361288342993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:39:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and rick uh I forgot perry hates EVERY watt of wind energy--he believes wind solar to be an attack on oil and gas--so sad the leaders of the gop--so sad</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1361292047665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 11:40:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361292322565-29</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Achieves New Wind Energy Record</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361288342993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 10:39:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1,000 GE Wind Units will be built near Rawlins,WY. Construction will start June 1st.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1361292322565</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 11:45:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361292755006-30</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yea i guess</Msg><Username>jamiemcgee52</Username><Timestamp>1361292755006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 11:52:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361293765980-31</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yea i guess</Msg><Username>dennisortiz82</Username><Timestamp>1361293765980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 12:09:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361296258316-32</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>changed my opinion on it for sure</Msg><Username>rosendo_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1361296258316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 12:50:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361297493259-33</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking over the website currently.</Msg><Username>wellsmario510</Username><Timestamp>1361297493259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 13:11:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361298185975-34</Id><Title>Electricity emissions fall as coal sidelined by renewables</Title><Msg>Electricity emissions fall as coal sidelined by renewables By Giles Parkinson on 13 February 2013 Emissions from Australia’s National Electricity Market (NEM) have fallen to 10 year lows, as demand continues to ease and the amount of coal reduction falls because of the growth of renewable energy, which has reached its highest levels since the 1980s. In its latest assessment of Australian electricity production and emissions, consulting group Pitt&amp;Sherry said even production from highly polluting brown coal generators has fallen in the past 12 months. Part of this was due to floods at the Yallourn mine in June, The report notes that a 500MW unit at the Wallerawang C power station near Lithgow in NSW has also been mothballed, for at least 12 months, as a result of the changing dynamics of the NEM. This adds to the near 3,000MW of coal-fired capacity put on hold in the past year. The latest data (illustrated in the graph below) shows that gas, hydro and wind generators have all increased output, with the Tasmanian hydro system reaching its highest level since joining the NEM in 2005, taking total hydro electricity production to it highest levels since 2000-01. Wind energy generation fell slightly in January from December, but Pitt&amp;Sherry said the commissioning of the 420MW Macarthur wind farm in Victoria would push wind output to its highest levels in the next month or so. Gas generation also reached its highest ever annualized levels in January. “These are precisely the changes in the electricity supply mix which the carbon price would be expected to induce,” the report said. Total renewables (hydro plus wind) reached 12.1 per cent of NEM generation in the year to January 2013. This is the highest share of renewable supply in what is now the NEM since the 1980s, when total demand for electricity was less than 60 per cent of its current level. “This fact highlights that the growing share of electricity supplied by low emission generators in the NEM, and the corresponding fall in average emissions intensity of total NEM generation to its lowest ever level, is due as much to the fall in demand for electricity from the NEM as to the increased output from low emission generators themselves,” the report said. “Had demand kept growing at the rates seen up to the end of 2006, the shares of gas, hydro and wind generation would have been significantly lower, for the same total output, and the emissions intensity of NEM generation higher. “ The report notes that the biggest falls in demand have occurred in NSW and Victoria, with demand in SA and Tasmania virtually unchanged for more than four years. “It is hard to identify all possible reasons for these changes in demand. In NSW, the closure of the Kurri Kurri aluminium smelter is obviously important,” it said. “However, the impact of increased rooftop photovoltaics, another factor thought to be important, is not obvious, since the two States with the highest PV take-up rates – Queensland and SA – also show the smallest reduction in demand on the NEM.” (One factor to explain that might be that those two states also recorded the highest growth in air conditioning in recent years). reneweconomyDOTcomDOTau/2013/electricity-emissions-fall-as-coal-sidelined-by-renewables-57857</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361298185975</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 13:23:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361298983105-35</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well be finished. Uncover out why.</Title><Username>beanpeter201</Username><Timestamp>1361274817647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 06:53:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your gross</Msg><Username>tabb_harry</Username><Timestamp>1361298983105</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 13:36:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361301264391-36</Id><Title>Petition seeks new EPA pathway to require greenhouse gas curbs</Title><Msg>Petition seeks new EPA pathway to require greenhouse gas curbs By Ben Geman - 02/19/13 06:42 AM ET An environmental group affiliated with New York University’s law school is petitioning the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) to wield a seldom-used section of the Clean Air Act to require greenhouse gas emissions curbs. The petition urges EPA to act under Section 115 of the air law, which enables EPA to demand action to curb pollution that’s endangering public health or welfare in foreign countries. “Section 115 provides a mandatory, efficient, and comprehensive approach to regulating greenhouse gas emissions. It is therefore the preferred mechanism under the Clean Air Act for responding to the dangers of climate change,” states the Institute for Policy Integrity’s petition, to be filed Tuesday. The attorneys, in the petition and an accompanying statement, argue that Section 115 should be employed to have EPA require states to control emissions, while providing the ability to use “flexible regulatory tools like market incentives” such as cap-and-trade. “EPA must now review Policy Integrity’s petition and respond within a ‘reasonable time frame.’ If accepted, EPA would likely issue orders to the governors of all fifty states, instructing them to develop plans to roll back greenhouse gas emissions – potentially by using cap‐and‐trade or other market mechanisms,” the group said. The attorneys also threatened to file a lawsuit if EPA denies the petition or does not respond, noting they can “pursue appropriate legal action to force the agency to respond.” The Institute for Policy Integrity’s petition is part of environmentalists’ stepped-up effort to win executive action on climate change at a time when global warming legislation is frozen in Congress. The idea of using Section 115 to address greenhouse gases has been batted around policy circles for years. Some experts are very critical of the concept. A 2010 paper by several experts with Resources For the Future (RFF), an environmental think tank, said use of the brief Section 115 would be highly vulnerable to challenge. “Courts usually take a dim view of attempts by agencies to use short, vague statutory language to justify sweeping regulatory changes,” the RFF scholars state. “Section 115 may appear to provide a perfect foundation for [greenhouse gas] regulation, but the EPA would risk putting great effort into developing a regulatory program only to discover that its foundation is built on sand,” they argue. But the Institute for Policy Integrity petition says that EPA would be on solid legal footing using Section 115. The section requires that EPA receive reports from a “duly constituted international agency” showing that U.S. emissions are harming a foreign nation; and that the nation has “reciprocity” with the U.S., which means the country has “has given the United States essentially the same rights with respect to the prevention or control of air pollution occurring in that country.” The petition argues that “all the prerequisites for action have been satisfied for greenhouse gases.” “EPA has already acknowledged – based in part on reports from the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change – that greenhouse gases from the United States endanger foreign countries; and other countries, such as Canada, have given the United States essentially reciprocal rights. EPA therefore must direct states to control their greenhouse gas emissions under Section 115,” the petition argues. China overtook the U.S. as the world’s top greenhouse-gas-emitting nation more than a half-dozen years ago, but aggregate historical emissions from the U.S. remain far higher. The Institute says U.S. emissions will “likely impact extreme weather events, food production, infectious disease, water scarcity, coastal erosion, and economic development across every continent.” EPA has begun moving ahead with greenhouse gas regulations under other portions of the sweeping air pollution law. It has proposed carbon emissions standards for new power plants under Section 111, which enables regulators to set standards for specific categories of industrial pollution sources. The agency is also under pressure to ensure rules for existing power plants under the portion of Section 111 that enables the regulators to require states to act. The new petition argues that Section 111 isn’t as well suited to controlling emissions as Section 115, or another provision of the sweeping law (Section 615) that was crafted to give EPA more tools to protect the ozone layer. Nonetheless, it urges EPA – under this “third-best option” – to broaden its use of Section 111 by imposing standards on a wider range of pollution sources. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/283689-petition-seeks-new-epa-pathway-to-require-greenhouse-gas-curbs</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361301264391</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 14:14:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361301816145-37</Id><Title>Here we go!</Title><Msg>Low volume but this is a nice start to the week. Go oil!</Msg><Username>christophmil</Username><Timestamp>1361301816145</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 14:23:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361301930453-38</Id><Topic><Title>Quantum Chemistry Application - Methanol to gasoline</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361216459694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 14:40:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are very naive and it is fun watching you make a fool of yourself with your incessant bragging. Please keep it up.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1361301930453</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 14:25:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361302014070-39</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Merkel's degree is in physical chemistry, not 'quantum chemistry.' Do you know the difference?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1361302014070</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 14:26:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361302703217-40</Id><Title>99.9% Electricity from Wind &amp; Solar by 2030</Title><Msg>99.9% Electricity from Wind &amp; Solar by 2030 Comment on this post Posted by Joanna Schroeder – February 19th, 2013 According to recent research from the University of Delaware, 99.9 percent of electrical needs in a large power grid can be provided by wind, solar and new storage technologies by 2030 at costs comparable to today. Author Dr. Cory Budischak will present the findings in more detail during the general session on Tuesday, March 26, 2013 as part of the 6th Annual Iowa Wind Power Conference. Other conference speakers include Governor Terry Branstad and Lt. Governor Kim Reynolds. In addition, the Director of Wind and Water from the US Department of Energy has been invited to speak. The conference will focus on four general themes that reflect the national and world leadership position that Iowa has achieved. Those themes include technology development, small &amp; community wind, operation &amp; maintenance and education training &amp; research. In addition, a Research Poster Display featuring dozens of new university research projects will be a key element of the event. Click here for more information about the conference. domesticfuelDOTcom/2013/02/19/99-9-electricity-from-wind-solar-by-2030/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361302703217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 14:38:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361303250807-41</Id><Title>European Parliament Approves Plan to Bolster Carbon Trading</Title><Msg>European Parliament Approves Plan to Bolster Carbon Trading By STANLEY REED Published: February 19, 2013 LONDON — Lawmakers in Brussels moved Tuesday to shore up the sagging market for carbon emissions permits, a key component of the European Union’s efforts to reduce air pollution. Prices of carbon allowances, which permit companies to emit greenhouse gases, fell last month to as low as €2.80 per ton, or $3.75, compared with €9 per ton a year ago and €30 per ton in 2008. To reduce the supply of permits and drive up the price, the environmental committee of the European Parliament voted to allow the European Commission to reduce the number of allowances to be auctioned over the next three years. After the committee’s vote, prices fell to around €4.60 per ton, from a close of €5.13 on Monday. But the panel’s vote had been expected, and the plan still needs approval from the full European Parliament and the governments of the Union’s 27 member states. “It is really the first step in a long, long process,” said Kash Burchett, an analyst at the energy research firm IHS. The committee’s vote — 38 to 25, with 2 abstentions — is “a lifeline for the carbon market and for emissions trading as a policy tool for curbing emissions,” said Stig Schjoelset, head of carbon analysis at Thomson Reuters Point Carbon, a market research firm in Oslo. If the vote had gone the other way, Mr. Schjoelset said, the Emissions Trading System would have been “more or less dead.” The European Union introduced the system in 2005 in a bid to force polluters like utilities and manufacturers to reduce their carbon emissions. Under the system, companies are allocated a certain number of permits, each allowing them to emit one metric ton of carbon dioxide per year. If emissions exceed the level allowed by the permits, the companies must buy additional permits. Companies that do not comply face heavy fines. The total number of permits is scheduled to be reduced over time, forcing a corresponding reduction in emissions. The Union is on track to meet its goal of reducing emissions in 2020 to 80 percent of 1990 levels, but that is mainly because the recession has reduced industrial activity and energy use. As a result, companies have a surplus of permits on hand, which depresses their price. It is widely believed that the European Commission has handed out too many credits. In 2012, for example, ArcelorMittal, the Luxembourg-based steel maker, sold 21.8 million tons of credits — about one quarter of the number it received from the commission — for $220 million. The company said it spent the proceeds on energy-saving investments. Advocates say that carbon pricing, if properly managed, is the most efficient way to lower emissions. By putting a hefty price on carbon, the system lets investment decisions drive emissions reductions, rather than having governments dictate investment in particular clean energy sources like solar or wind. But industrialists and analysts say that single-digit prices for carbon permits do not provide sufficient incentive for companies to switch to cleaner fuels and energy-efficient technology. “Driving energy investment in Europe through a higher carbon price will lower costs,” said David Hone, the chief climate adviser to Royal Dutch Shell and the chairman of the International Emissions Trading Association in Geneva. “That price signal isn’t there today.” Mr. Schjoelset said a price of €30 to €40 per ton was needed to encourage electricity producers to switch from coal to natural gas, a cleaner fuel. He said it would take a price of €60 to €150 per ton to push utilities to invest in expensive carbon-reducing technologies like carbon capture and storage. Politicians and analysts said the Parliament committee’s vote might be the first step in restoring the credibility of the Emissions Trading System, which is still considered the world’s flagship carbon program. “It is important that we get this right, and the sooner we get it right the better,” the European climate action commissioner, Connie Hedegaard, said during an interview Monday. The plan approved Tuesday would take 900 million carbon credits that are now scheduled to be auctioned from 2013 to 2015 and “backload” them so they are auctioned in 2019 and 2020. That will put a dent in the surplus of carbon credits, which is estimated at two billion tons. This article has been revised to reflect the following correction: Correction: February 19, 2013 An earlier version of this article misidentified an analyst at IHT, an energy research firm. He is Kash Burchett, not Kass Burchett. nytimesDOTcom/2013/02/20/business/global/european-parliament-approves-plan-to-bolster-carbon-trading.html?_r=0</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361303250807</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 14:47:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361303830477-42</Id><Topic><Title>Quantum Chemistry Application - Methanol to gasoline</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361216459694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 14:40:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do not have to do anything to keep up the pressure on your worthless industry and company, except pay my taxes to the Germany government. I do hope you have all your money and retirement or whatever you live on in XOM stock. It will be enjoyable to watch you become very poor and insane - your attitude and arrogance warrants that, along with the other despoilers and parasites... Filth.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361303830477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 14:57:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361304214207-43</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wrong. Her doctoral thesis is on Quantum Chemistry. "Untersuchung des Mechanismus von Zerfallsreaktionen mit einfachem Bindungsbruch und Berechnung ihrer Geschwindigkeitskonstanten auf der Grundlage quantenchemischer und statistischer Methoden" "Investigation of the mechanism of decay reactions with single bond breaking and calculation of their velocity constants on the basis of QUANTUM CHEMISTRY and statistical methods"</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361304214207</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 15:03:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361305245030-44</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Do you know the difference?" You have already demonstrated a complete inability to comprehend complex issues so any discussion with you is pointless except to prove your inability further which is redundant. I do not have a degree in Quantum Chemistry if that is what you are trying to ascertain, rather a Doctorate in Economics. Reading and comprehending basic English, German and mathematics is not that difficult though. My wife is well educated in chemistry however which is stimulating. You however, lack any value that I can discern. Irrelevant and dismissed...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361305245030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 15:20:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361308217796-45</Id><Topic><Title>How democrats govern</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1360983376137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 21:56:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More lies as always. Four of the last IL govs went to prison. THREE were Democrats: Blago, Walker, Kerner. Discouraging to you when the big lie doesn't work? Live with it.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1361308217796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:10:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361308385417-46</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I DO have a degree in chemistry, among others. You are a laugh but please keep posting as yours are much more humorous than those of wahleee boy and his aliases.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1361308385417</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:13:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361308971737-47</Id><Topic><Title>Quantum Chemistry Application - Methanol to gasoline</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361216459694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 14:40:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess being derogatory and obscene is the best you can do when you have nothing of substance to say, which is most of the time. The oil industry is not 'my industry' nor is XOM 'my company.' XOM is among my many investments which are certainly not limited to equities. I could live very comfortably for the rest of my days if I never made another dime in interest or earnings or even if all of my investments declined by 90% - neither of which I expect to happen. I hope you enjoy living in your super race fantasies. It's been proven wrong multiple times before. So I guess we know who is truly irrelevant. Enjoy</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1361308971737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 16:22:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361314859251-48</Id><Title>Exxon Breakup</Title><Msg>I would like to see Exxon split up and enhance shareholder value.I get tired of holding a bond stock</Msg><Username>jtgol</Username><Timestamp>1361314859251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 18:00:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361315996563-49</Id><Title>☛☛☛MOST "RIDICULOUS" MARKET in U.S. History..P/Es pathetic &amp; rising !!</Title><Msg>really!!</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1361315996563</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 18:19:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361320578623-50</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First i would say Germany is in good hands. Second i would say there does not appear to be any reasonable alternative to crude oil as a concentrated liquid fuel and starting material for chemicals. Perhaps we see more alternate fuels and more nat gas, cng gas, and lng, but dont expect any miracles or energy revolution.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1361320578623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 19:36:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361321886255-51</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I say dont count on any quantum computers taking over either. Thinking quantum computers are going to stay just an intellecutal curiosity for a long time yet. jmho</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1361321886255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 19:58:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361324670858-52</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve &amp; donald trump</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1361323379512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:22:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why cause we worked for our $. Keep ur hands out of our pockets commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1361324670858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:44:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361324815432-53</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve is a typical teabagger</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1360340514110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 11:21:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey stupid the poor r getting poorer and my $ is out of here and away from ur lazy poor commie fingers.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1361324815432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:46:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361324902950-54</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve is the ultimate jerk !</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1360340612898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 11:23:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>try getting a couple of thumbs up dumb stupid poor boy.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1361324902950</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:48:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361324985898-55</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve is a sniveling weasel</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1360340708573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 11:25:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no one likes the commie coward #$%$.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1361324985898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:49:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361325090585-56</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve is an obscene jerk</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1360340399751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 11:19:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u hungry and cold tonight, try dumpsters for scraps and shelter.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1361325090585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:51:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361325202198-57</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve is mentally unbalanced</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1360340478325</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 11:21:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More like a commie coward #$%$. CCC the maxi dopey.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1361325202198</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:53:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361325282718-58</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve is a bonafide COWARD</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1360340542136</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 11:22:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cant wait to through u into the ocean.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1361325282718</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:54:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361332693255-59</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Breakup</Title><Username>jtgol</Username><Timestamp>1361314859251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 18:00:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then sell. All I can say is I'm happy to have held for past 30 years.</Msg><Username>dmc092</Username><Timestamp>1361332693255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:58:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361334927902-60</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Breakup</Title><Username>jtgol</Username><Timestamp>1361314859251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 18:00:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u musta got in around same time I did. interest rates were thru roof but Exxon was paying 3$ divvy on a 30$ stock. coulda got more in a cd but 10% from the tiger in the tank was better than putting it in the bank</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1361334927902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 23:35:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>