<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371645654970-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obamanomics vs. German economics…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371475723208</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 09:28:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>….Goethe and Fouqué Fouqué for his tales of the fair damsel, such as Hollywood puts in front of little girls. Little girls grow to be women, and the sublime touches a note in them. Goethe’s tales of sorcery appeal to me too.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371645654970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371646394725-2</Id><Topic><Title>British Bio-refining Proceedings; Deutschland Biofuels…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371094959610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 23:42:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump. Agricultural land around Berlin is going heavily into bio-fuels production. Land values are being pushed up everywhere, even with current technology. According to professionals at Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin only about 3% of the world's arable land is going to bio-fuels. Bayer AG is working steadily to improve crop yields as are other companies so crop yield will increase from biological science even as other scientists increase the yield at biorefining end. In between is buggy whip Energy &amp; Co... - Big Oil -</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371646394725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371646453928-3</Id><Title>Graph of the Day: Why the fossil fuel industry hates renewables</Title><Msg>Graph of the Day: Why the fossil fuel industry hates renewables By Giles Parkinson on 18 June 2013 This article follows on from our story yesterday on Alinta, and the complaint by CEO Jeff Dimery that wind energy is “undermining the running regime of exiting thermal generation assets”. There is no doubt that it is. But while some could argue whether this is a good thing (early retirement of ageing polluting assets in a clean energy transition) or a bad thing (stranded assets, loss of value), it seems that it is inevitable as the world transitions to an energy system based around renewables. This series of graphs – taken from an expansive presentation of energy data collected by Germany’s Franhofer Institute for Sustainable Energy – gives some insight into why the owners of fossil fuel plants hate this scenario. The growing impact of wind farms and solar panels in Europe, and in Germany in particular, are having a massive impact on energy markets – and the impact is very much more an economic one than a technical one. The same is true in Australia, as we discussed yesterday. The first two sets of graphs represent the electricity output in Germany in weeks 3 and 4 of 2013, from January 14 to January 27. This is the way the fossil fuel generators would like the market to be. Demand is constant, the nuclear and brown coal generators operate with minimal variability, and even black coal generators enjoy relatively stable demand (and revenue) for most of the working week. Gas is switched on and off as demand fluctuates (mostly between day and night), and the contribution of hydro, wind and solar is minimal. This mixture of baseload, peak load and some variable renewables is the way that most energy markets have worked for the past few decades. Now let’s fast forward to just a few weeks ago. These next two graphs (below) tell us what happened in weeks 22 and 23, from May 27 to June 9. Germany’s 33GW of solar PV is now powering up, and larger fluctuations of wind pow</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371646453928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:54:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371646532871-4</Id><Topic><Title>Graph of the Day: Why the fossil fuel industry hates renewables</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371646453928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:54:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and larger fluctuations of wind power are also having an impact on the market. The output from the nuclear and brown coal generators is dramatically lowered – their total weekly outputs in January were at least 50 per cent higher than in May, and their peak requirement was 25 per cent higher. The output of black coal generators has been slashed by nearly half in the latest period and has become highly variable (most have to shut down completely over the weekend and sometime overnight), and the demand for gas has fallen by more than half – even though it is used to fill gaps between wind and solar, it is rarely required to switch on for the daytime peaks. Screen Shot 2013-06-16 at 10.11.45 AM Screen Shot 2013-06-16 at 10.11.57 AM These highlight some of the big problems with the growing penetration of renewables in Germany. Remember, at this level, the market is around 20 per cent, but the government wants this to rise to 40 per cent by 2030. Gas plants, however, are struggling to stay open. Coal generators in Germany – like Alinta and others in Australia – are screaming blue murder because they are being levered out of the market. Most of the new coal plants currently being built in Germany – even the brown coal ones – are designed to be flexible so they can fit in around renewables – which is now the dominant influence on prices in the market. This was an issue which is being deliberated in German policy circles at the moment and was highlighted by the International Energy Agency in two recent reports – the old style energy markets that focused uniquely on a price for kWh produced are being made redundant, and will need to be replaced by soemthing more sophisticated, along the lines of a “capabilities” market promoted by the likes of the Regulatory Project. Effectively, it is a way of finding a market design that reflects the new market dynamics, the plunging cost of solar PV and wind, and the need to provide an economic incentive (subsidy) to retai</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371646532871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371657065405-5</Id><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending June 14, 2013</Title><Msg>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending June 14, 2013 U.S. crude oil refinery inputs averaged over 15.5 million barrels per day during the week ending June 14, 2013, 294 thousand barrels per day above the previous week’s average. Refineries operated at 89.3 percent of their operable capacity last week. Gasoline production decreased last week, averaging 9.1 million barrels per day. Distillate fuel production decreased slightly last week, averaging about 4.7 million barrels per day. U.S. crude oil imports averaged over 8.4 million barrels per day last week, up by 586 thousand barrels per day from the previous week. Over the last four weeks, crude oil imports have averaged over 7.8 million barrels per day, 1.3 million barrels per day below the same four-week period last year. Total motor gasoline imports (including both finished gasoline and gasoline blending components) last week averaged 556 thousand barrels per day. Distillate fuel imports averaged 87 thousand barrels per day last week. U.S. commercial crude oil inventories (excluding those in the Strategic Petroleum Reserve) increased by 0.3 million barrels from the previous week. At 394.1 million barrels, U.S. crude oil inventories are above the upper limit of the average range for this time of year. Total motor gasoline inventories increased by 0.2 million barrels last week and are also above the upper limit of the average range. Finished gasoline inventories decreased while blending components inventories increased last week. Distillate fuel inventories decreased by 0.5 million barrels last week and remained in the lower half of the average range for this time of year. Propane/propylene inventories increased by 3.5 million barrels from last week’s revised total of 49.7 million barrels, and are in the upper half of the average range. Total commercial petroleum inventories increased by 6.8 million barrels last week. Total products supplied over the last four-week URL at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371657065405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 11:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371661527022-6</Id><Title>JUST WONDERING</Title><Msg>Will Exxon purchase POLR?</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1371661527022</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371667279764-7</Id><Title>Top White House climate adviser vows Obama will act soon</Title><Msg>Top White House climate adviser vows Obama will act soon By Zack Colman - 06/19/13 10:32 AM ET President Obama's top climate adviser on Wednesday vowed that “meaningful” action on global warming was coming soon. Heather Zichal, the deputy assistant to the president on energy and climate change, said she didn’t want to get “in front of the big man” and unveil specific plans during an event in Washington, D.C., hosted by The New Republic. She spoke broadly, however, of bolstering energy efficiency, expanding clean energy on public lands and using various “tools” -- including the Clean Air Act -- to address climate. Zichal’s comments come as speculation grows that the administration is preparing sweeping climate change proposals. Bloomberg reported that Obama has told donors he will take action next month. Capitol Hill has been left guessing what the White House is cooking up on climate, though Zichal's comments shed some light on the plan. Rep. Henry Waxman (D-Calif.), the top Democrat on the House Energy and Commerce Committee, told The Hill on Tuesday that he understands Obama will reveal his actions “soon.” “What they’re going to announce, I don’t know,” said Waxman, who recently joined Sen. Sheldon Whitehouse (D-R.I.) to discuss climate issues with White House chief of staff Denis McDonough. But any climate measures from the president will likely face opposition from Republican lawmakers who are wary of further regulations they say hamper businesses. Many Republicans also dispute or deny the scientific consensus that human activity is contributing to global warming. Some disagree altogether that growing greenhouse gas concentrations are baking the planet, or that the world is getting warmer. Obama in his State of the Union address though vowed to act on climate change if Congress does not, saying it would be a second-term priority. Zichal said the president is focused on “depoliticizing” climate policy as he prepares to roll out</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371667279764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 14:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371668517515-8</Id><Title>Taper is here: moderate pace of purchase for 2nd half of 2013</Title><Msg>They need to stop anyway. The fed balance sheet is ready to explode.</Msg><Username>tfmvance</Username><Timestamp>1371668517515</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 15:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371679231564-9</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go away you two imbeciles !~</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371679231564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 18:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371686598397-10</Id><Title>U.S. needs oil sands as surge from shale bonanza seen overdone</Title><Msg>U.S. needs oil sands as surge from shale bonanza seen overdone</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371686598397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371686632530-11</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. needs oil sands as surge from shale bonanza seen overdone</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371686598397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:03:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The U.S. will continue to need crude from Canada’s oil sands because rising production from its shale formations is too expensive to maintain.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371686632530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371689065405-12</Id><Topic><Title>U.S. needs oil sands as surge from shale bonanza seen overdone</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371686598397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:03:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you enjoy talking to yourself, stooge ?</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371689065405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371689112910-13</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese is a walking encyclopedia.....</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370133089920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This guy has to go on ignore !</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371689112910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371689205374-14</Id><Topic><Title>USDA considers banning bluecheese !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371242397997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 16:39:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey bluecheese, you're spoiled rotten garbage !!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371689205374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>