<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366435314624-1</Id><Title>Ethanol plant exec: Change to fuel mandate would hurt Iowa cellulosic plant</Title><Msg>Apr 19, 2013 A meaningful change to the country’s renewable fuel mandate would drastically curtail the market opportunity for a cellulosic ethanol plant being built in Emmetsburg by ethanol producer Poet and Dutch-based DSM Advanced Biofuels, a DSM North America company official said on Friday. Hugh Welsh, president of DSM North America, said without the Renewable Fuel Standard -- an 8-year-old law that requires biofuels to be blended into the country’s gasoline and diesel supply – there would be no incentive for refiners to use ethanol. The damage would be especially severe for cellulosic ethanol, made from crop residue, grasses, wood chips and other materials, that has been slow to grow. Currently, most of the ethanol produced in the United States comes from corn. “The reason we invested that $150 million in Emmetsburg, Iowa, was because of the RFS,” Welsh said in an interview. Without the Renewable Fuel Standard “there would be a market for cellulosic ethanol but that market would be much smaller. It would be the end of investment in cellulosic ethanol in the United States because the market won’t be there.” Sioux Falls-based Poet and DSM Advanced Biofuels are constructing a cellulosic facility adjacent to Poet's corn-fed ethanol plant in Emmetsburg. The initial capacity is expected to be 20 million gallons in the first year, growing to approximately 25 million gallons per year. There are cellulosic plants in the late stages of development or under construction in more than 20 states and other countries, a promising sign for the next generation of biofuels. Locally, DuPont Industrial Biosciences also is building a 30-million-gallon-capacity refinery in Nevada that is expected to open in 2014. The EPA has proposed 14 million gallons of cellulosic fuel to be included in motor fuel this year, up from 2012, when it set the mandate at 8.7 million gallons. The... desmoinesregisterDOTcom/article/20130419/BUSINESS/130419025/0/NEWS/?odyssey=nav%7Chead</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366435314624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 01:21:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366436556602-2</Id><Title>Blew Cheeser............wake up &amp; smell the ethanol.....</Title><Msg>The volcanic eruption in Iceland, since its first spewing of volcanic ash has, in just FOUR DAYS, NEGATED EVERY SINGLE EFFORT you have made in the past five years to control CO2 emissions on our planet – all of you. Of course you know about this evil carbon dioxide that we are trying to suppress – it’s that vital chemical compound that every plant requires to live and grow and to synthesize into oxygen for us humans and all animal life. I know, it’s very disheartening to realize that all of the carbon emission savings you have accomplished while suffering the inconvenience and expense of: driving Prius hybrids, buying fabric grocery bags, sitting up till midnight to finish your kid’s “The Green Revolution” science project, throwing out all of your non-green cleaning supplies, using only two squares of toilet paper, putting a brick in your toilet tank reservoir, selling your SUV and speedboat, vacationing at home instead of abroad, nearly getting hit every day on your bicycle, replacing all of your 50 cents light bulbs with $10.00 light bulbs …well, all of those things you have done have all gone down the tubes in just four days. The volcanic ash emitted into the Earth’s atmosphere in just four days – yes – FOUR DAYS ONLY by that volcano in Iceland, has totally erased every single effort you have made to reduce the evil beast, carbon. And there are around 200 active volcanoes on the planet spewing out this crud at any one time – EVERY DAY. I don’t really want to rain on your parade too much, but I should mention that when the volcano Mt Pinatubo erupted in the Philippines in 1991, it spewed out more greenhouse gases into the atmosphere than the entire human race had emitted in all its years on earth. Yes folks, Mt Pinatubo was active for over one year – think about it. Of course I shouldn’t spoil this touchy-feely tree-hugging moment and mention the effect of solar and cosmic activity and the well-recognized 800-year global heating and cooling cycle, which keep happening, despite our completely insignificant efforts to effect climate change. And I do wish I had a silver lining to this volcanic ash cloud but the fact of the matter is that the bush fire season across the western USA and Australia this year alone will negate your efforts to reduce carbon in our world for the next two to three years. And it happens every year. Just remember that your government just tried to impose a whopping carbon tax on you on the basis of the bogus “human-caused” climate change scenario. Hey, isn’t it interesting how they don’t mention “Global Warming” any more, but just “Climate Change” - you know why? It’s because the planet has COOLED by 0.7 degrees in the past century and these global warming bull artists got caught with their pants down. And just keep in mind that you might yet have an Emissions Trading Scheme – that whopping new tax –imposed on you, that will achieve absolutely nothing except make you poorer. It won’t stop any volcanoes from erupting, that’s for sure. But hey, relax, give the world a hug and have a nice day! Just a note: Mt. Pinatubo (as mentioned above) in the P.I. produced more chloro-fluoro carbons in a month than mankind had ever manufactured to that date. In my opinion, the crusade against freon and the banning of the older freon products that really worked well in all our refrigeration and air conditioning equipment was done for two main reasons. 1. DuPont’s patents expired so they would lose their exclusive right to produce them meaning COMPETITION and we don’t want that!; and 2. Successful experiments had already been done to show that electric power could be generated using these refrigerants in a turbine/generator system instead of using water (steam) to spin the turbine but at MUCH LOWER TEMPERATURES (the old freon 12 boils at much lower temps than water and so does iso-pentane but you can’t get them), thereby allowing use of solar energy and geothermal energy to heat (boil) the freon and spin the turbines. But then, we wouldn’t have to burn all that oil and gas to make electricity! The joke is on us for believing the psuedo-science we’re being fed.</Msg><Username>travel_linman</Username><Timestamp>1366436556602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 01:42:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366459155425-3</Id><Topic><Title>MASSIVE LAYOFFS by Boeing..1800 Engineers...2300 Machinists *DREAMLINER flop !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366412634107</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:03:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobumba a flop</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366459155425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:59:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366463997962-4</Id><Title>Extent of the Attack...</Title><Msg>Science &amp; technology being funded by the German government aims to destroy every aspect of the fossil fuel based energy system including its associated materials applications. *liquid fuels *gaseous fuels *solid fuels *petrochemical products The motivation is two fold: 1) To put an end to net C02 and other greenhouse gas emissions 2) To put an end to the imports of energy products from third world countries 3) To utterly dominate the industrial system of the future to drive out of business the industrial system of competitors who have based their economies around fossil fuels Sadly for the competition the institutions that are being used to conduct this scientific and industrial offense are not newly created or untried. They have been systematically built up since the end of World War II. The entire Germany educational system is designed mesh with them. This simply builds off the institutions that were constructed during the 19th century, and systematically extended.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366463997962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:19:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366469042396-5</Id><Topic><Title>Boston is NIGHTMARE scenario for Obummer and his minions....</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1366377030072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 09:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'll say it again</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1366469042396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366472073440-6</Id><Title>A Purified Elite USA is ideal for Europe</Title><Msg>The way it works is thus: America's elites use their power to collect as much income &amp; wealth as they can and then they spend it. They spend it on very high valued cars, watches, clothes, cosmetics and other items. Other useful items purchased by American elites, or used by others to photograph them, include lens that cost tens of thousand of euros or more. There are other items far too numerous to list. The important thing is the production these items is uniquely suited to the kind of high technology industry you find in places like Germany. Other European countries introduce value with their mix of artistic and technological power and fill in niches the power of rationalism can't quite match. So even American porn stars are useful. They collect large income and spend it on such items. Hollywood actors and actresses of the non-porn variety are useful too. The parasitic bankers who run their casino on Wall Street are especially good spenders, and now that they have the Federal Reserve backing them and the US Treasury they are really becoming bold. The millionaires feeding off defense contracts and sitting as the executives of major defense contractors are useful - the more war the better. The executives working for American corporations which specialize in the more basic things the American lower classes purchase are of course very good customers. ........... I don't see this orgy of consumerism ending anytime soon, indeed China has joined the game and their contribution is really quite impressive. Obama's inability to lead, and spend wildly instead just reinforces these trends. In the meantime we are building a new industrial world to replace the fossil fuel based one. Fossil fuels were quite important at powering the technologies of the last industrial revolution, the one that propelled European civilization above everyone else on the planet. Now it is time for the next one. This next one will transform military technology as well...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366472073440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366493914485-7</Id><Title>EXXON Info</Title><Msg>Seems funny to see a question about EXXON, on it's web board, but, here it goes, when are we to find out about an increase in our stock. I'm thinking about .05 cents, maybe .06 if lucky. No .10 cents like last year.</Msg><Username>dennie_cunningham</Username><Timestamp>1366493914485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:38:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366496394186-8</Id><Topic><Title>EXXON Info</Title><Username>dennie_cunningham</Username><Timestamp>1366493914485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:38:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why not 10cents like last year? I think XOM will take a hit if it's anything less.</Msg><Username>thorbo52</Username><Timestamp>1366496394186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366503694662-9</Id><Topic><Title>Boston is NIGHTMARE scenario for Obummer and his minions....</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1366377030072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 09:10:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone at Langly does not like him.....Got to think Obama enjoyed the morons in Boston cheering USA after they were subjected to martial law</Msg><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1366503694662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366504779464-10</Id><Title>Carbon bubble: $6 trillion of new investments at risk</Title><Msg>Giles Parkinson on 19 April 2013 Call it an act of the greatest folly, or simply one of greed. But it seems that the world’s energy companies are hell-bent on spending up to $6 trillion of shareholder funds and bank debt in the next decade on fossil fuel investments – assets that could well become stranded and worthless if the world acts to limit climate change. This is the conclusion of a new report on the so-called “Carbon Bubble”, which highlights the fact that the bubble is getting bigger. It now estimates that between 60 and 80 per cent of the coal, oil and gas reserves of publicly listed companies could be classified as unburnable if the world is to achieve emissions reductions that offer the greatest chance of limiting average global warming to 2°C. Research by Carbon Tracker and the Grantham Research Institute on Climate Change and the Environment at London School of Economics and Political Science shows that 200 major listed companies own 762 billion tonnes of carbon dioxide (CO2) through their reserves of coal, oil and gas. These reserves currently supports share value of $4 trillion and service $1.5 trillion in outstanding corporate debt. But to achieve emissions reductions consistent with an 80 per cent chance of achieving the 2°C target, the fossil fuel reserves of these listed companies would likely have to comply with a budget of just 125 billion tonnes to 275 billion tonnes of CO2. That means cutting them by three quarters or more, even more than that estimated last year by the International Energy Agency. To make matters worse, a further $674 billion was invested in new fossil fuel investments in 2012, and at the current rate more than $6 trillion will be invested over the coming decade – much, or even all of which could become stranded assets. The research is delivered as a warning to asset managers, shareholders and bankers, but it comes in the reneweconomyDOTcomDOTau/2013/carbon-bubble-6-trillion-of-new-investments-at-risk-30099</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366504779464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366513340334-11</Id><Topic><Title>Carbon bubble: $6 trillion of new investments at risk</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366504779464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Garbage propaganda</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1366513340334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366513778561-12</Id><Topic><Title>Russia/Chechnya</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366384489503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:14:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we learn all the time. It seems you never do.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1366513778561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366514146850-13</Id><Topic><Title>Artificial Photosynthesis, major new threat for oil &amp; gas</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366257529466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As always, it is you who are irrelevant and worthless - but most amusing.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1366514146850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:15:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366516137296-14</Id><Topic><Title>EU policy: nearly eliminate fossil fuels by 2050</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365778020508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:47:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump....</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366516137296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>