<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369660431328-1</Id><Title>US Senate energy panel chairman reintroduces electricity storage bill</Title><Msg>Washington (Platts)--24May2013/102 pm EDT/1702 GMT The chairman of the US Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee has reintroduced a bill aimed at boosting the development of variable renewable power sources, including solar and wind, through new tax incentives for storage technologies. Senator Ron Wyden, an Oregon Democrat, reintroduced Thursday the Storage Technology for Renewable and Green Energy Act (S. 1030) along with Susan Collins, a Maine Republican, Jeff Merkley, an Oregon Democrat, and Angus King, a Maine Independent. "Building out more energy storage will increase the amount of renewable power on the grid, reduce our country's need for new power plants and make the US energy system more reliable," Wyden said in a statement. The bill would provide a 20% investment tax credit for a storage system connected to the electric grid and distribution system. Up to $40 million would be available per project. The bill also provides a 30% investment tax credit, up to $1 million per project, to businesses for technologies that can store energy during non-peak hours and distribute it to meet demand during peak electricity hours. Wyden said Friday the bill was "substantially similar" to a bill he introduced in 2011 with Collins and former New Mexico Democrat Jeff Bingaman, the then-chairman of the committee, but the prior bill was never voted out of committee. The new bill contains one significant change: reducing the eligibility standard for the credit to 5 kWh storage systems from 20 kWh. Wyden said dropping the threshold will make more small businesses eligible. The bill is technology neutral, Wyden said, allowing technologies that store electricity from wind, coal or nuclear sources to be eligible for the credit. Eligible technologies include pumped hydro, compressed air, batteries, flywheels, thermal storage and smart-grid enabled plug-in electric vehicles, he said plattsDOTcom/RSSFeedDetailedNews/RSSFeed/ElectricPower/21071684</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369660431328</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369661897209-2</Id><Title>Kolbert: Keystone XL is ‘Just Another Step On The March To Disaster’</Title><Msg>Joe Romm on May 26, 2013 at 12:30 pm Elizabeth Kolbert is one of the most thoughtful climate journalists. Her terrific 2006 book, Field Notes from a Catastrophe, famously ends, “It may seem impossible to imagine that a technologically advanced society could choose, in essence, to destroy itself, but that is what we are now in the process of doing.” Seven years later, we’re still doing it (see “Into The Valley Of 400 PPM Rode The 7 Billion“). Kolbert has a great New Yorker piece this week, “Lines in The Sand,” on crossing the 400 parts per million threshold of CO2, as measured at Hawaii’s Mauna Loa observatory. She quotes one marine geologist who said that hitting 400 ppm, “feels like the inevitable march toward disaster.” Of course, it isn’t inevitable, which was the point of Kolbert’s quote above — it is a choice. That said, most people do feel powerless to change direction, since the choice to avert disaster isn’t directly in our hands. It is in the hands of the most powerful opinion makers and political leaders, like President Obama. Kolbert concludes her piece: Were we to burn through all known fossil-fuel reserves, the results would be unimaginably bleak: major cities would be flooded out, a large portion of the world’s arable land would be transformed into deserts, and the oceans would be turned into liquid dead zones. If we take the future at all seriously, which is to say as a time period that someone is going to have to live in, then we need to leave a big percentage of the planet’s coal and oil and natural gas in the ground. These basic facts have been established for decades, and every President since George Bush senior has vowed to do something to avert catastrophe. The numbers from Mauna Loa show that they have failed. In rejecting Keystone, President Obama would not solve the underlying problem, which, as pipeline proponents thinkprogressDOTorg/climate/2013/05/26/2046481/kolbert-keystone-xl-is-just-another-step-on-the-march-to-disaster/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369661897209</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 09:38:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369677224587-3</Id><Title>Reagan's 1986 Amnesty emboldened Bush to incarcerate border guards returning fire at smugglers</Title><Msg>McCain and Rubio are eager to flood the US with latino gang bangers. The GOP dominated Senate and House doubled welfare spending over the Clinton's in Bush's first term to pay for their open border drug and terror war fodder. Liebermen, Cantor and Schumer were so proud of the bi-partisanship</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1369677224587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369685718779-4</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan's 1986 Amnesty emboldened Bush to incarcerate border guards returning fire at smugglers</Title><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1369677224587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 13:53:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who paid u to say this?</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1369685718779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 16:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>