<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370145686660-1</Id><Topic><Title>Is bluechesse just talking to himself ?</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1369874941332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 20:49:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>max 411 dosnt have two nickels to rub together and eats out of dumpster.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1370145686660</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 00:01:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370150575885-2</Id><Title>Northern Gateway Pipeline: Alberta Hopeful Despite BC Rejection</Title><Msg>Northern Gateway Pipeline: Alberta Hopeful Despite BC Rejection CP | By The Canadian Press Posted: 05/31/2013 4:40 pm EDT | Updated: 05/31/2013 5:25 pm EDT EDMONTON - Alberta hasn't given up hope for the proposed Northern Gateway oilsands pipeline despite the B.C. government's rejection of the project. The government says Calgary-based Enbridge (TSX:ENB) has not adequately explained how it would deal with a major oilspill on land or in coastal waters. Alberta Environment Minister Diana McQueen says she respects that B.C. has concerns about the proposed $6-billion project that need to be addressed. In a written statement, McQueen says Alberta trusts that the panel reviewing the project will make its decisions based on science and all the evidence that has been presented. McQueen says she expects that B.C. government's concerns will be discussed and addressed through the federally regulated panel. She says B.C. and Alberta both have strong environmental standards and a shared commitment to economic growth and job creation. huffingtonpostDOTca/2013/05/31/northern-gateway-pipeline-alberta-responds_n_3368464.html?ir=Canada+Alberta</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370150575885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 01:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370196460519-3</Id><Title>How rich is too rich?</Title><Msg>Germany’s national wealth computed as total private and government assets minus government debt is now more than twice the US level on a per capita basis. That works out to over $35 trillion in assets in dollar terms. If the Nordic lands, the Low Countries, Austria, and Switzerland are added in to compute the sum for the purest Germanic European lands, the total exceeds the entire national wealth of the USA. When we speak of a war on fossil fuels, it is useful to keep in mind how big the war chest is and how paltry the sums being considered truly are. For a poorer country like the USA, and one saddled with wars, teeming slums, and a dysfunctional political system these challenges doubtless appear very daunting. Of course the answer to the lead question is simple: you can’t be rich enough. Try to enjoy yourself now in your faltering fortunes. Try not to lose too much money too if the US market should happen to crash yet again. It’s in a precarious place. We will be returning to Germany tomorrow, by the way. I've done my duty in visiting the tiresome Connecticut, spiced by amusements courtesy of a made up ghost lol. Deutschland über alles!!!</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1370196460519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:07:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370196582565-4</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese is a walking encyclopedia.....</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370133089920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Cheese! Cut and paste, cut and paste... any of your ideas or thought process? Same on the CVX message Board, always someone else's writings. Not 1 thought of your own.</Msg><Username>kea_lani_maui</Username><Timestamp>1370196582565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370197143885-5</Id><Title>British Columbia export group finds partners in bid to sell LNG to Asia</Title><Msg>British Columbia export group finds partners in bid to sell LNG to Asia</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370197143885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:19:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370198316150-6</Id><Title>What TransCanada’s CEO Is Not Saying About The Keystone Tar Sands Pipeline</Title><Msg>Ryan Koronowski on Jun 1, 2013 at 11:41 am TransCanada has lobbied the U.S. government to approve the Keystone XL pipeline, hoping to transport the heavy, bitumen-laden tar sands crude oil to coastal refineries in Texas. The corporation’s Chief Executive Officer Russ Girling said in an interview scheduled to air this weekend on Bloomberg Television that rejecting the pipeline would increase greenhouse gas emissions. Girling said that currently, the U.S. imports more crude in tankers that run on oil — so approving the pipeline would allow the U.S. to use more oil from Canada, transported by pipeline and not by tanker. Girling said: “If you deny the pipeline it’s a lose-lose. We lose jobs. We lose economic development and we lose energy security. And it likely leads to greater emissions in GHG.” The problem is, this is not really what would happen if the pipeline is constructed. The State Department’s draft environmental assessment report said: There is existing demand for crude oil, particularly heavy crude oil at refiners in the Gulf Coast area, but the ultimate disposition of crude oil transported by the proposed Project, and any refined products produced from that crude oil, would be determined by future market forces. Which of course means that there is no assurance that the oil transported by the pipeline would not be refined and exported on tankers of their own, destined for other countries. The global oil market does not operate in nearly so zero-sum of a game. Morover, gas prices for U.S. consumers would increase, not decrease, according to recent reports. Additionally, as the EPA made clear in its public comment submitted to the State Department’s draft report, the pipeline itself will emit greenhouse gases as tar sands crude is not going to pump itself down the length of the pipeline: power is required. EPA recommended thinkprogressDOTorg/climate/2013/06/01/2088651/what-transcanadas-ceo-is-not-saying-about-the-keystone-tar-sands-pipeline/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370198316150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>