<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368680381730-1</Id><Topic><Title>Wind farms get pass on eagle deaths</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368636348856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Enjoy your Coonmander-In-Chief! Ya'll elected him anyways.</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1368680381730</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 00:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368683834727-2</Id><Title>Premier Wall pitches made-in-Saskatchewan carbon capture technology to U.S.</Title><Msg>The Canadian Press Posted: 05/14/2013 3:18 PM | Comments: 0 | Last Modified: 05/14/2013 5:11 PM REGINA - Saskatchewan Premier Brad Wall says the province has game-changing carbon capture technology and he's trying to sell the idea to the world. Wall spoke Tuesday at an annual carbon capture conference in Pittsburgh. The premier says there was "very keen interest" from companies and other governments in a carbon capture project at the Boundary Dam power station near Estevan. The Saskatchewan government wants to commercialize the technology being tested at the plant. Wall says the project will be tried out this fall and will "go live" as a generating facility next year. "But we're getting close enough now where SaskPower officials are starting to welcome earnest consideration to join this consortium and invest, you know, bring some of those capital dollars to our province," said Wall. Carbon capture involves gathering carbon dioxide from power plants and injecting it deep into porous rock formations so it doesn't add to greenhouse gas emissions. The plan at Boundary Dam is to capture up to 90 per cent of CO2 emissions. Most of the CO2 will be sold to oil and gas companies that use it to push more oil out of the ground in what's called enhanced oil recovery. Saskatchewan has put about $1.1 billion to the carbon capture project and the federal government has ponied up $240 million. The province, which relies heavily on coal-fire power plants, needs carbon capture to work. Coal currently provides more than 50 per cent of Saskatchewan's electricity and the province has an estimated 300-year supply, according to SaskPower's website. "In the years ahead, when the federal regulations require that certain coal plants simply can't operate anymore, what are we going to do? Are we going to shut them all down and winnipegfreepressDOTcom/arts-and-life/life/sci_tech/premier-wall-pitches-made-in-saskatchewan-carbon-capture-technology-to-us--207427411.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368683834727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 01:57:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368700529393-3</Id><Topic><Title>Wind farms get pass on eagle deaths</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368636348856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As opposed to polluting power sources that kills everything? What's your point?</Msg><Username>investor_james</Username><Timestamp>1368700529393</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 06:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368708570318-4</Id><Title>Scotland’s Rockstar Clean Energy Leadership — 39% Renewable Electricity Today, 100% By 2020, &amp; More</Title><Msg>Scotland’s Rockstar Clean Energy Leadership — 39% Renewable Electricity Today, 100% By 2020, &amp; More May 15, 2013 Zachary Shahan Scotland may not be as large as Germany or Australia or the US, but it certainly deserves a bit more attention when it comes to its clean energy leadership. Scotland already gets over 30% renewable electricity — about 33% today according to the interviewee in the first video below; 39% of total electricity demand in 2012, according to the Scottish government. It has a 2020 target of 100% renewable electricity. And it also has an ambitious overall renewable energy target. Notably, Scotland has some wonderful renewable energy resources — especially wind and tidal resources. But come on, who doesn’t have wonderful renewable energy resources? From sunshine to wind to geothermal to less popular types of renewable energy, countries around the world have clean, renewable resources they can tap to generate their own energy. Check out these two videos below from Fully Charged for more on Scotland’s rockstar clean energy leadership (h/t NewEnergyNews): cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/05/15/scotlands-rockstar-clean-energy-leadership-33-renewable-electricity-today-100-by-2020-more/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368708570318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 08:49:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368715990693-5</Id><Topic><Title>Wind farms get pass on eagle deaths</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368636348856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So does this mean sell XOM?</Msg><Username>jamotide</Username><Timestamp>1368715990693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 10:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368718538568-6</Id><Topic><Title>buybacks</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1368566441861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:20:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so does the company approach a stockholder to buy back shares, or does the stock holder approach the company?</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1368718538568</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368720416893-7</Id><Topic><Title>buybacks</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1368566441861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:20:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither. Xom buys the shares on the open market and puts them into its treasury. It's basically supply and demand and it therefore affects the price of the shares. It increases the earnings per share and is considered a way to increase value to existing shareholders. This is all nice in theory. Xom has spent over $200 billion buying shares back, but the stock has not appreciated much. Maybe a way to look at it is if they didn't buy them back, the stock could be sitting in the 40s. If you google Xom share buybacks, you will find several articles debating and explaining the share buybacks.</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1368720416893</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 12:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368720443541-8</Id><Title>Oil Bulls, Russian Pacific Fleet Warships Enter Mediterranean, oil price spike coming</Title><Msg>Looks like oil is going to launch.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1368720443541</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 12:07:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368728515652-9</Id><Title>Nearly 100% Of New California Electricity To Be Solar In 2H 2013</Title><Msg>May 16, 2013 Zachary Shahan Herman Trabish of Greentech Media has happened across a pretty interesting find — 97% of new electricity generation capacity in line to be added to the California grid in the second half (2H) of 2012 is from solar power projects. This is according to the California Independent System Operator (the ISO), as published in the 2012 Annual Report on Market Issues and Performance. In total, 1,633 megawatts of generation capacity are in line to be added to the grid in 2H 2013. A whopping 1,581 megawatts (MW) are from solar projects. 52 MW are from biomass projects. That’s a big shift from the first half of the year (and, well, all of previous history). Herman writes: “By the end of the first half of the year, the ISO will have added 3,391 megawatts of nameplate capacity, of which 2,296 megawatts will be natural gas, 565 megawatts will be wind and 530 megawatts will be solar.” Here’s a chart for a visual display of these points and the situation in 2012: Image Credit: California ISO Herman spent a lot of time discussing various factors related to natural gas in his post (I’d recommend checking it out). A few key points I’d pull out of it are as follows (images added): 1.Natural gas prices seem to have gotten too low to warrant investment in new natural gas projects. From the report: “The 2012 net revenue estimates for hypothetical combined-cycle and combustion-turbine units continued to fall substantially below the estimates of the annualized fixed costs for these technologies. For a new combined-cycle unit, net operating revenues earned from the markets in 2012 are estimated to be about $38 per kilowatt-year in Southern California, compared to potential annualized fixed costs of $176 per kilowatt-year.” (See 3 charts above.) 2.More periods like 2H 2013 to come — this is the future. cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/05/16/nearly-100-of-new-california-electricity-to-be-solar-in-2h-2013/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368728515652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 14:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368749042438-10</Id><Title>Feds make concessions to oil industry in new hydraulic fracturing rule</Title><Msg>May 16, 2013 at 1:53 pm by Jennifer A. Dlouhy The Obama administration on Thursday unveiled a new plan to tighten standards for drilling on public lands and force companies to reveal the chemicals they use in the process, after making significant concessions to the oil industry. Although it is poised to be the first major federal rule governing the hydraulic fracturing process that is unlocking vast domestic oil and gas reserves, the measure would apply only on the small sliver of U.S. land under the Interior Department’s control. Rewritten in response to a flood of criticism from both environmentalists and the oil industry, the new proposal left both groups unsatisfied. Conservationists said it doesn’t go far enough to protect drinking water near drilling sites, and industry officials said the mandates could hike costs and cause delays in drilling. In Canada: Quebec proposes law to ban fracking Interior Secretary Sally Jewell cast the proposed rule as a pragmatic approach to protecting environment and public health while allowing oil and gas development on federal lands. “We are proposing some common-sense updates that increase safety while also providing flexibility and facilitating coordination with states and tribes,” Jewell said. “As we continue to offer millions of acres of America’s public lands for oil and gas development, it is important that the public has full confidence that the right safety and environmental protections are in place.” To a striking degree, Interior Department officials emphasized their desire for a final set of mandates that protects public health and the environment while providing flexibility and avoiding duplicate regulation. Jewell acknowledged that the measure was sure to be criticized on all sides. “You’re going to hear from folks that we caved to industry or we’re bowing to pressure from environmentalists,” J... fuelfixDOcom/blog/2013/05/16/feds-make-concessions-to-oil-industry-in-new-hydraulic-fracturing-rule/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368749042438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 20:04:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368749465076-11</Id><Title>Calling Big Oil’s bluff</Title><Msg>Monte Shaw - 05/16/13 04:00 PM ET I grew up in Iowa and witnessed E10, or fuel made with 10 percent ethanol, enter the marketplace. I watched ethanol displace methyl tert-butyl ether (MTBE) in California, the Northeast and then nationwide. And as crude oil prices continued their inexorable march from $20 per barrel to more than $100, I’ve seen E10 become the ubiquitous fuel in our nation. What does each of these things have in common? The oil industry said they couldn’t be done, and they were wrong. Not surprisingly, Big Oil is back to its old tricks, this time trying to convince Congress and the Environmental Protection Agency that the Renewable Fuels Standard (RFS) cannot work and should be eliminated. To combat Big Oil’s monopoly on transportation fuels, the RFS requires refiners to gradually increase the amount of renewable fuels available to consumers over time. However, refiners now say it cannot be done. Once again, they are wrong. We call this the Big Oil Bluff. The Big Oil Bluff claims that blends above 10 percent ethanol cannot be sold — the so-called E10 blend wall. So, as the RFS increases, oil refiners can’t use more ethanol, and instead have no choice but to artificially reduce U.S. fuel supplies to meet the RFS percentage. The Bluff’s logic maintains that less gasoline would spike prices and the threat of high gas prices would serve as the justification necessary for Congress or the EPA to eliminate the RFS. There’s just one problem. The central argument of the Big Oil Bluff is the existence of a real E10 blend wall. However, the E10 blend wall does not exist. Increasing consumer access to lower-cost E15 and E85, 15 percent and 85 percent ethanol respectively, solves the problem. Yet, Big Oil has not worked to expand consumer access to these fuels. In fact, the oil industry has engaged in a relentless effort to obstruct the introduction of E15 and thehillDOTcom/blogs/congress-blog/energy-a-environment/300189-calling-big-oils-bluff</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368749465076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 20:11:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368750683056-12</Id><Title>Keystone XL pipeline 'needs to go ahead,' Harper tells U.S. VIDEO</Title><Msg>Prime minister attends NYC session with Council on Foreign Relations By Meagan Fitzpatrick, CBC News Posted: May 16, 2013 12:50 PM ET Last Updated: May 16, 2013 7:07 PM ET Read 589 comments589 Prime Minister Stephen Harper told an American audience today that the Keystone XL pipeline "absolutely needs to go ahead." Harper made the pipeline pitch while taking questions at the Council on Foreign Relations in New York City. He laid out the case for why U.S. President Barack Obama's administration should approve the proposed pipeline that would connect Alberta's oilsands to the Gulf Coast, touting job creation prospects. Harper said the project will create 40,000 jobs south of the Canadian border and that can't be ignored. "This is an enormous benefit to the U.S. in terms of long-term energy security," Harper added. He acknowledged environmental challenges, but said that the intensity of greenhouse gas emissions attributed to the Alberta oilsands have dropped by 25 per cent over the last decade and that the government is continuing to invest in technology to further reduce emissions. The prime minister also said that the amount of emissions from the oilsands plays a small part in total global emissions. "It's almost nothing globally," he said, adding later that Canada is a small contributor compared to other big oil producers such as Venezuela. "I don't have to tell you there are probably reasons beyond just emissions why you would want to have your oil from Canada rather than Venezuela," he said. Harper said when all the economic and other factors are weighed, it's clear why there is such broad support for the Keystone XL project in the U.S. Technology key to cutting emissions "I think this absolutely needs to go ahead but you can rest assured that making our emissions targets including in the oilsands sector is an important objective for the government of Canada," he said. cbcDOTca/news/politics/story/2013/05/16/pol-harper-new-york.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368750683056</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 20:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368755105002-13</Id><Topic><Title>Wind farms get pass on eagle deaths</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368636348856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not the first time Keith has raised concerns over wind power. A 2008 paper published in the Journal of Atmospheric Sciences, co-written by Keith with atmospheric scientist Daniel Kirk-Davidoff of the University of Maryland, said huge wind farms could change air patterns enough that it would also affect worldwide climate. A more alarming conclusion came from a 2011 paper published by the Max Planck Institute for Biogeochemistry, a German research organization, that said that trying to get the maximum power from the Earth's winds could have the same impact on climate change as a doubling in atmospheric carbon dioxide. (The Planck paper, published in Earth System Dynamics, is another that argues that wind is a limited resource, concluding it is "considerably less than recent estimates that claim abundant wind power availability.") National Geographic</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368755105002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 21:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368757095100-14</Id><Title>Second appeals court strikes down Obama NLRB appointments</Title><Msg>A second federal appeals court has struck down President Obama’s 2012 recess appointments to the National Labor Relations Board as unconstitutional. The Third Circuit Court of Appeals, which covers parts of Delaware, New Jersey, and Pennsylvania, ruled 2-1 that President Obama violated the constitution’s separation of powers when he recess-appointed Democrat Craig Becker to the NLRB in March 2010. “We hold that the ‘the Recess of the Senate,’ in the Recess Appointments Clause refers to only intersession breaks,” the ruling states. “As a consequence, we conclude that the National Labor Relations Board panel below lacked the requisite number of members [three] to exercise the Board’s authority.” The ruling stems from a disputed union election that occurred at a New Jersey nursing home. The NLRB denied the nursing home’s motion that the board illegitimately forced the company to recognize unionized managers. The Appeals Court ruled that the board did not have the authority to dismiss the motion because of the recess appointments. The Third Circuit is not the first federal court to declare Obama’s recess appointments to the NLRB unconstitutional. The D.C. Circuit Court of Appeals overturned an NLRB ruling in January because Obama unconstitutionally recess appointed Democrats Sharon Block and Richard Griffin while the Senate was still in session. The D.C. Circuit is now considering a number of appeals to other NLRB rulings putting 910 rulings the board has issued since the recess appointments at risk of being overturned. The board has continued to operate in the face of the legal challenge, issuing more than 200 additional rulings since the D.C. Circuit declared it unconstitutional.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368757095100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 22:18:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368757211107-15</Id><Title>Congressmen criticize Obama administration’s management of drilling permits</Title><Msg>The Department of the Interior admitted to Congress on Thursday morning that it could process oil and natural gas drilling applications more efficiently than it does right now during a hearing on the administration’s management of federal property. “There are opportunities for greater efficiencies,” Tommy Beaudreau, the acting assistant secretary of Land and Minerals Management for the Interior Department, told a subcommittee of the House Oversight and Government Reform Committee. The hearing focused on the Obama administration’s efforts to allow drilling for natural resources on federally owned land. The federal government approved 7,124 permits for drilling on federal lands in 2007, with an average approval time of 196 days. However, the Obama administration approved only 4,256 in 2012, at an average time of 228 days, Rep. Jason Chaffetz (R., Utah) said. States can take under a month, and sometimes under two weeks, to issue a permit, multiple congressmen said.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368757211107</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 22:20:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368757374518-16</Id><Title>Ed Markey Claims to Have Brought the World the Internet</Title><Msg>If it weren’t for Rep. Ed Markey (D., Mass.) the world would still be without smart phones, Facebook, Skype, and even Google. So says a recent ad released by his Senate campaign. Markey explains that before him, the Internet was nothing. “It’s hard to believe but twenty years ago almost no one had broadband,” says Markey. “Facebook, Skype, Google … the stuff of science fiction.” But then Ed Markey came around and opened the door for the Internet to flourish by fighting the telecom monopolies. Markey follows in the footsteps of Al Gore, who falsely claimed to have invented the Internet. Gore was at least inducted to the Internet Hall of Fame. Markey has yet to be nominated. The ad also features a glowing testimonial from a former staffer of Markey’s, who also contributed to his current campaign. Markey is running against Republican Gabriel Gomez in the special election next month for the Massachusetts Senate seat vacated by Secretary of State John Kerry.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368757374518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 22:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368757519545-17</Id><Title>Shaheen Scrutinized for IRS Letters</Title><Msg>Amid the unfolding Internal Revenue Service scandal, Sen. Jeanne Shaheen (D., N.H.) is facing renewed criticism for a letter she sent to the IRS in 2012, Fosters reports. The IRS revealed last week that it had targeted conservative groups, singling out their applications for tax-exempt status for further review and, in some cases, asking inappropriate and unnecessary questions of those applicants. Shaheen and other senators sent a letter to the IRS in February 2012 asking it to closely monitory 501(c)(4)s, especially organizations which were “abusing the tax code” and engaging in political campaigning: In their letter, Shaheen and the other senators questioned whether some groups with overtly political aims were masquerading as social welfare organizations in order to skirt federal tax laws. The senators urged the IRS to prevent organizations “focused on federal election activities” from “abusing the tax code.” The same group sent a second letter to former IRS commissioner Douglas H. Shulman in March 2012. They called for the IRS to implement a strict cap on the amount of political spending permissible for tax-exempt groups. The senators also called for the IRS to require organizations to document the exact percentage of their undertakings dedicated to “social welfare.” Shaheen criticized the IRS this week and called for a full audit by an inspector general. New Hampshire Republicans are criticizing what they see as a hypocritical stance, according to Fosters: “There are very serious questions about whether Shaheen’s partisan effort to pressure the IRS to increase investigations of 501(c)(4) organizations contributed to the outrageous practices that took place at the agency,” said [New Hampshire GOP] executive director Matthew Slater.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368757519545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 22:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368759738003-18</Id><Title>Industry Groups Urge Supreme Court To Ban EPA From Regulating CO2</Title><Msg>Ryan Koronowski on May 16, 2013 at 4:48 pm Conservative states, business groups, fossil fuel companies, and politicians who deny the science of climate change are petitioning the Supreme Court to reverse Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) regulations on greenhouse gases and to weaken the Clean Air Act. This would involve the Court either limiting or reversing its own 2007 decision, Massachusetts v. EPA, which found that the EPA is required to regulate carbon pollution as pollution. Reuters reported that the Court’s decision of whether or not to take up the petitioners’ case will have a significant impact on future efforts to reduce carbon emissions. The appeals to the Supreme Court follow the DC Circuit Court of Appeals’ refusal to reconsider the matter. The Court is expected to decide whether to hear the petitions in October. The nine petitions, filed over the last few months, seek review of EPA regulations. Petitioners include: states with fossil fuel-friendly governors like Texas, Alaska, and Virginia; industry groups such as the Chamber of Commerce, the American Petroleum Institute, and the National Association of Manufacturers; as well as fossil fuel companies like Peabody Energy (the world’s largest private-sector coal company). The petition led by Texas includes as fellow petitioners Gov.Rick Perry (R), Virginia Attorney General Ken Cuccinelli (R), and Reps. Marsha Blackburn (R-TN), and Michelle Bachmann (R-MN), who deny the reality of climate science. Since the Court ruled that CO2 is a pollutant, the EPA found that it was a threat to public health through an endangerment finding: “Pursuant to CAA section 202(a), the Administrator finds that greenhouse gases in the atmosphere may reasonably be anticipated both to endanger public health and to endanger public welfare.” In August of 2012, EPA implemented new mileage standards thinkprogressDOTorg/climate/2013/05/16/2016631/epa-is-required-to-regulate-carbon-pollution-from-existing-power-plants/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368759738003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 23:02:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>