<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366608274788-1</Id><Title>Aerial photos of the Exxon Mobil campus PHOTOS</Title><Msg>Aerial photos of the Exxon Mobil campus PHOTOS Posted on April 21, 2013 at 2:00 am by Nancy Sarnoff The Exxon Mobil campus north of Houston is taking shape, and a good place get a look at what’s being developed is from above. Aerial photos show multiple buildings and parking garages being framed on the 386-acre site west of Interstate 45 near the Hardy Toll Road. It’s like a small downtown being built from scratch. There are about 20 structures under construction by a workforce of 3,000, said company spokesman Patrick McGinn. When it’s completed in mid-2015, the development will house 10,000 people. Employees are expected to start moving in early next year, McGinn said. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/04/21/aerial-photos-of-the-exxon-mobil-campus/#11356-1</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366608274788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:24:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366608799486-2</Id><Title>Renewables Investment Seen Tripling Amid Supply Glut</Title><Msg>By Louise Downing &amp; Alex Morales - Apr 21, 2013 5:01 PM MT. 17 Comments The plunge in the cost of wind and solar power that bankrupted more than two dozen manufacturers is forecast to spur a tripling of investment in renewables by 2030 and to reduce the grip fossil fuels have on world energy supply. Annual spending on clean-energy projects that don’t add to greenhouse-gas pollution may rise to $630 billion at the end of the next decade from $190 billion last year, Bloomberg New Energy Finance said in a report today. That’s 37 percent more than estimated in November 2011 [b][color=#00CC00]and means renewables would account for half of all generation capacity by 2030.[/color][/b] The findings contrast with production gluts that made most solar and wind manufacturers unprofitable last year, tipping a unit of Suntech Power Holdings Co. (STP) into bankruptcy and Vestas Wind Systems A/S (VWS) into record losses. While suppliers are suffering, lower equipment prices are making more projects profitable to develop and advancing the day when renewables can rival coal and oil on cost. “The apocalyptic views about what it will cost to shift the world to renewable energy simply aren’t true,” Michael Liebreich, chief executive officer of New Energy Finance, said in an interview. “Three years ago, we thought wind and solar would be cheap as chips, and they’ve even gone below that.” Energy Conference Executives including NRG Energy Inc. CEO David Crane and Suma Chakrabarti, head of the European Bank for Reconstruction &amp; Development, will discuss the trends at a conference hosted by New Energy Finance today in New York. The London-based research group owned by Bloomberg LP estimates the cost of installing a gigawatt of renewable energy capacity is now about 10 percent lower during the period through 2030 than it projected in 2011. A gigawatt is enough to supply about 800,000 homes bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-04-21/renewables-investment-seen-tripling-amid-supply-glut.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366608799486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366608860222-3</Id><Topic><Title>EU policy: nearly eliminate fossil fuels by 2050</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365778020508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:47:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you Hans. However much your 'wife' mate hates fossil fuels, perhaps nuclear fuels....did she ever consider driving to point A to point B? Fossil fuels. Might get her from A to B. And when she switches on her electric lights, or electric powered gas or oil funance.....does she know what she's talking about?</Msg><Username>lookingood_gal</Username><Timestamp>1366608860222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366608913884-4</Id><Title>♫♫♫♫ I DON'T HEAR ANY MUSIC...Futures "RED" by open....real RED !!</Title><Msg>no buyers boys !!</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366608913884</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:35:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366609519221-5</Id><Title>****WHAT DUMMIE would be buying now ?? Bwhahahahahaha! DOWN DOWN DOWN boys !</Title><Msg>wayyyyyyyyy down we go......</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366609519221</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366611091546-6</Id><Title>林志玲林志 EACH American owe me $80,000 now and growing daily...Bwhahahahahaha!</Title><Msg>plus all interest..newborns too !!</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366611091546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366624679194-7</Id><Topic><Title>林志玲林志 EACH American owe me $80,000 now and growing daily...Bwhahahahahaha!</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366611091546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:11:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>americans are a dumb race of people.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366624679194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 05:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366624724723-8</Id><Topic><Title>BREAK POINT....The FAILURE of the "Bernanke Disasterous Experiment" has begun.....</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366585252615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 19:00:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>surprise morons.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366624724723</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 05:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366633055246-9</Id><Title>Caterpillar's CEO trying to blow sunshine UP MY ACE..They MISSED period..MKT tanks</Title><Msg>They missed BAD !! MARKET SHPOULD TANK !!</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366633055246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 08:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366635971555-10</Id><Topic><Title>EU policy: nearly eliminate fossil fuels by 2050</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365778020508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:47:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another ID... Your desperation is obvious and it doesn't impress me. I think you should keep buying....</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366635971555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:06:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366637183786-11</Id><Topic><Title>"""""Everyone with SENSE selling tomorrow boys ! PARTYS OVER.....</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366593623029</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 21:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US has been selling off its wealth to fund consumption and now Japan is going to do the same. Japan's net savings rate will fall sharply negative as their real interest rates become negative from their monetary policy. The wealth will end up being transferred mostly to Europe... It will be a slow process of impoverishment for the average American and Japanese citizen. At some point the USA will be unable to maintain its military, or especially the technologies of the future, and the responsibility will pass to Europe. --------------- Anybody with any sense out of the US long ago... German real estate is the place to be.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366637183786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366637246265-12</Id><Title>Zinc-Iron Redox Flow Batteries — The Next Big Thing In Energy Storage?</Title><Msg>April 22, 2013 Zachary Shahan I recently had the opportunity to chat with the CFO and President of Zinc Air Inc., Craig Wilkins, as well as one of the company’s advisors, Greg Hayes. It was a very interesting discussion and it looks like Zinc Air Inc. has what could be a very promising grid storage technology, and the technology is just about ready for market. As always, we will have to see how the market responds. However, for now, below is a bit of info for you to chew over. First of all, despite the name (I’ll come back to that), the company isn’t developing zinc-air battery technology, but rather zinc-iron redox flow battery technology. Its key benefits, according to Wilkins, are: “reliability, durability, safety, and low cost.” (I’ll delve in a little more near the bottom of this post.) Despite its wide array of claimed benefits, you probably haven’t heard about this company before. The reason, according to Hayes, is that they haven’t had to go the megaphone-advertising, attract-investors route — the startup has been funded by a handful of wealthy individuals. ”We’ve been able to raise a lot of capital through private, high-net-worth individuals,” Hayes added. And I could hear the gratefulness in Hayes and Wilkins’ voices. They are well aware of the fatigue investors, experts in the field, and the broader public have from overhyped technologies that never make it to market. As noted at the top, Zinc Air Inc. (ZAI) is just about 6 months out from its technology being used in its first commercial project. As such, the company is coming out from under the radar more. The company has been around for about four years in total, mostly working on nitty gritty of its zinc-iron redox flow battery technology. This is following about eight years of DOE-funded research. “We have been spending a great deal of that time developing the technology,” Hayes said, but cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/04/22/zinc-iron-redox-flow-batteries-zinc-air-energy-storage/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366637246265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366637822987-13</Id><Topic><Title>Artificial Photosynthesis, major new threat for oil &amp; gas</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366257529466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listen to the little "chemist" boy speak his usual foul mouth trash. You are nothing but a degenerate bum. You represent your "culture" well. You are irrelevant and have been dismissed.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366637822987</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366637956845-14</Id><Title>Kewaunee nuclear power plant shutdown cost is nearly $1 billion</Title><Msg>Thomas Content of the Journal Sentinel April 20, 2013 When the Kewaunee Power Station stops generating electricity next month, a new chapter in its life will open - one that could last until the 2070s and cost nearly $1 billion. The plant operators will begin the process of decommissioning the nuclear power plant, an endeavor that aims to restore the site along Lake Michigan to what it looked like in the 1960s, before the facility was built. Kewaunee owner Dominion Resources Inc. has announced it will shut the plant on May 7, a move that is expected to result in the loss of hundreds of jobs. The reactor is closing because the Wisconsin utilities that had purchased its electricity declined to continue buying it, citing the low price of natural gas. Dominion put the power plant up for sale in 2011, but no buyer emerged. So in a few short weeks, the mission of those who work at Kewaunee will change from generating power to cleaning up the power plant site. "We've got 60 years to turn it back to a 'greenfield' site," said Mark Kanz, spokesman for Dominion. "At some point it basically has to look like the farm fields in the 1960s, before any construction started here." As part of the decommissioning, all buildings on the 900-acre site east of Green Bay will be torn down and low-level radioactive waste will be shipped out of state. What could remain on site for generations, however, are the concrete casks of spent nuclear fuel - the high-level radioactive waste that is changed out every 18 months when a reactor refuels. The federal government is responsible for the cleanup of the spent fuel, meaning taxpayers will be on the hook for the cost of placing spent fuel in storage and a possible move to a long-term disposal site. For years, federal agencies had been considering a plan to open a nuclear fuel waste repository at the jsonlineDOTcom/business/kewaunee-nuclear-power-plant-shutdown-cost-is-nearly-1-billion-lr9j5fg-203912611.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366637956845</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:39:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366638100840-15</Id><Topic><Title>Artificial Photosynthesis, major new threat for oil &amp; gas</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366257529466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you. Your posts are most amusing. I'll delight in watching the little Hitler go down in flames.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1366638100840</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366638415174-16</Id><Title>Public Comment Period Ending on Controversial Keystone Report</Title><Msg>When the State Department will make the written comments public, as required under the National Environmental Protection Act, remains unclear. By John H. Cushman Jr., InsideClimate News Apr 22, 2013 WASHINGTON—Advocates and opponents of the Keystone XL pipeline are due to file detailed comments on its environmental impacts on Monday, after the State Department refused to extend the comment period, which environmental groups had complained was too short. As many as a million members of the public are expected to meet the comment deadline, which by happenstance fell on Earth Day, April 22. Comments are also expected from industry, labor and environmental groups on both sides of the debate over the proposed pipeline, which would carry oil from Canada’s tar sands region to refineries on the U.S. Gulf Coast. The government of Alberta, the American Petroleum Institute, the Natural Resources Defense Council, the Sierra Club and other groups said they will release copies of their comments soon. But it is not clear when the State Department will make all the written comments public, as required under the National Environmental Protection Act. The commenters are all seeking to influence the draft supplemental environmental impact statement, or SEIS, that the State Department released in March, which appeared to open the door to a decision later this year to grant the pipeline a permit. Once the final SEIS is issued, the State Department must begin a separate deliberation to determine if the project is in the national interest—a question that goes beyond environmental considerations. Environmental groups have complained they didn't have enough time to critique the environmental assessment, which ran to thousands of pages. They said they weren't given access to some of the underlying studies used for the project. But on Friday, Assistant Secretary of insideclimatenewsDOTorg/news/20130422/public-comment-period-ending-controversial-keystone-report</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366638415174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366640014024-17</Id><Topic><Title>Is really exxon worth buying?</Title><Username>ruiz.paul</Username><Timestamp>1366638315364</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:45:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>got it, try :)</Msg><Username>kimbrovski</Username><Timestamp>1366640014024</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366642684044-18</Id><Title>Got upgrade</Title><Msg>XOM is upgraded to a strong buy at stoxline website. Looks like it is the time to get in.</Msg><Username>zcymizlter</Username><Timestamp>1366642684044</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366643066146-19</Id><Topic><Title>Artificial Photosynthesis, major new threat for oil &amp; gas</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366257529466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is the Americans who copied Hitler's and Goebbels' propaganda. *Interstates so American housewives, father and children could tour the countryside in their cars. *the #$%$s hated urban and loved rural culture. So the US government did everything it could to build up suburbs and small towns with home loans. *the #$%$s loved war above all else. The US is the biggest warmonger on the planet now and real #$%$s, many with SS ranks, helped design your military industrial complex. We know the names too. Anyone with internet can find them easily. ............. Prussian is not #$%$, but I doubt you would like either one. Everywhere you look in Berlin you will see the style in new buildings. Palaces and public works commissioned by government, Soviet style factories and "workers" habitations gutted and replaced by Prussian styles. Soviet style schools replaced by Prussian elitism.... In the meantime you follow the Hitler model in all its obscene populism waste, and disorder. Eichmann, one his disciples, was a failure in the Prussian schools. He learned his "administrative" skills at Vacuum Oil Company - the last real job he had. You must be proud to have such an alumnus... You must be a masochist. And obscene as always.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366643066146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366646390641-20</Id><Topic><Title>Artificial Photosynthesis, major new threat for oil &amp; gas</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366257529466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love your delirium and fantasy. Please keep it up - it brightens the day.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1366646390641</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647234249-21</Id><Topic><Title>Artificial Photosynthesis, major new threat for oil &amp; gas</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366257529466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we could arrange to have your day darkened quite considerably. Come to Germany and spread your libel against the country in any public place of your choosing. It would not take very much for me to personally make an example out of someone like you in the German courts if given the chance… I doubt you could even afford the plane ticket.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366647234249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:13:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366651819767-22</Id><Topic><Title>EXXON Info</Title><Username>dennie_cunningham</Username><Timestamp>1366493914485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:38:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The game is for XOM to dedicate their $ to buy-backs so they can artificially achieve their EPS goals so they can bonus and "stock award" themselves to oblivion while the common shareholder gets cut out. Inducsty analysts have turned sour on this stockholder averse company. Expect a 2 cent increase....nothing more.</Msg><Username>tsobie</Username><Timestamp>1366651819767</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:30:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366662457736-23</Id><Topic><Title>EXXON Info</Title><Username>dennie_cunningham</Username><Timestamp>1366493914485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:38:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>usually the day before they announce earnings, which is Thursday I believe. So I think we will here on Wednesday.. Not 100% sure.</Msg><Username>lincoln1136</Username><Timestamp>1366662457736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366662710106-24</Id><Topic><Title>Artificial Photosynthesis, major new threat for oil &amp; gas</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366257529466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your idiocy and inability to comprehend never ceases to amaze, I relish my daily diet of your posts.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1366662710106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366664819048-25</Id><Topic><Title>stock splits &amp; dividends</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1364316386810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 12:46:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the info.</Msg><Username>helpme_hanna</Username><Timestamp>1366664819048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366665120285-26</Id><Topic><Title>Artificial Photosynthesis, major new threat for oil &amp; gas</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366257529466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a true self-loathing masochist could enjoy a daily diet such as that. At least you are honest about it. It’s a shame you can’t work up the courage to come to Germany. You could be chastised more fully. I can’t say I would bother with you, as you have already admitted your submissiveness just now. The German government very well could prosecute you if you insulted its institutions on German soil… Since there are no juries agents of the state would decide whether you were guilty, rather like I choose your intent when I read what you write. You are just a pathetic submissive trying to get attention...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366665120285</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366677145351-27</Id><Title>Ignoring Carbon Cost ‘Bad Investment Decision,’ David Blood Says</Title><Msg>Ignoring Carbon Cost ‘Bad Investment Decision,’ David Blood Says 22 April 2013 April 22 (Bloomberg) — David Blood, who co-founded Generation Investment Management LLP with Al Gore, said investors should stop giving money to companies that don’t account for the cost of pumping carbon into the atmosphere. “We’re still seeing businesses assume that there’s no price on carbon,” Blood, a former Goldman Sachs Group Inc. executive, said today at the Bloomberg New Energy Finance conference in New York. “Allocating capital to companies that don’t know the price of carbon is a bad investment decision.” Deploying a carbon tax, opposed to implementing cap-and- trade initiatives, would be simpler, even accounting for economic differences between richer and poorer nations, Blood said. Politicians in favor of such measures should be more courageous in pressing for them, he said. About a decade ago, many thought the capital markets alone could solve energy issues related to climate change, “but I think the lesson from the last 10 years is that that’s not accurate,” Blood said. “We have to move away from the idea that this is a short-term economic question.” aboutDOTbnefDOTcom/bnef-news/ignoring-carbon-cost-bad-investment-decision-david-blood-says-2/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366677145351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366678640267-28</Id><Topic><Title>EXXON Info</Title><Username>dennie_cunningham</Username><Timestamp>1366493914485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:38:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Link, thanks for the reply.</Msg><Username>dennie_cunningham</Username><Timestamp>1366678640267</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366683563220-29</Id><Title>Dividend dates for stock?</Title><Msg>Anyone know the dates?</Msg><Username>mier43</Username><Timestamp>1366683563220</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 22:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366686614084-30</Id><Topic><Title>Artificial Photosynthesis, major new threat for oil &amp; gas</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366257529466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Says the nut case who spends all his time posting to get attention.... A real laugher. BTW: I as usual doubt much of what you ay about Germany which you seem to defend irrationally - BUT please point out any of my posts where I have insulted its institutions. I might in the future if I so choose, enjoying the freedom of speech in this country that you seem to believe is so terrible while using it in continually criticizing the US and other countries. Truly fascinating.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1366686614084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>