<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368942181663-1</Id><Title>Refinery woes pushing Midwestern gas prices to all-time highs</Title><Msg>Refinery woes pushing Midwestern gas prices to all-time highs</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368942181663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 01:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368966612670-2</Id><Title>Maine Gov. signs bill to ban ethanol gas</Title><Msg>Maine Gov. signs bill to ban ethanol gas May 17, 2013 Legislation (LD 453) that prohibits a person from selling or offering for sale gasoline that contains corn-based ethanol as an additive at a level greater than 10% by volume has been signed into law by Maine Gov. Paul LePage. According to the Specialty Equipment Market Association (SEMA) Action Network (SAN), the law would not take effect until at least two other New England states (Connecticut, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, Rhode Island and Vermont) have enacted laws that prohibit the sale of gasoline that contains corn-based ethanol at a level greater than 10% by volume. Separate legislation (LD 115) to prohibit the sale and distribution of corn-based ethanol if at least two other New England states pass a similar prohibition failed in the Maine Senate by a 21-14 vote. However, the bill remains alive as senators reconsider the initial vote. LD 115 recognizes that ethanol increases water formation which can then corrode metals, plastics and rubber, especially over a period of time when the vehicle is not used. Current high-performance specialty parts along with pre-model year 2001 cars and parts may be most susceptible to corrosion. LD 115 recognizes that the life span of vehicles and equipment can be dramatically reduced with the wrong fuel and that owners could be confronted with breakdowns. Anti-corrosion additives are available for each purchase of gasoline but can become expensive, burdensome and require consumer education. For more information visit the SAN website. For more on ethanol bans, see Florida bill to end ethanol gas sent to governor. moderntiredealerDOTcom/news/story/2013/05/will-new-england-ban-ethanol-gas.aspx?prestitial=1</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368966612670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368966712703-3</Id><Topic><Title>Maine Gov. signs bill to ban ethanol gas</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368966612670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:30:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>May 15 By Michael Shepherd mainetoday Staff Writer AUGUSTA — The Maine Senate rejected a bill that could eventually ban the use of ethanol in motor fuel in the state in an initial vote Wednesday. The bill, L.D. 115, would ban the use of ethanol in motor fuel in Maine, but only if two other New England states also prohibit the additive. The 21-14 Senate vote against the bill is in conflict with a 109-32 vote in support of the bill in the House of Representatives last week. More votes are pending in order to reconcile the difference between the legislative chambers. Rep. Jeffrey Timberlake, R-Turner, the bill’s sponsor, has made reducing the use of ethanol, a corn-based additive that many say is harmful to small engines and older car engines, a main priority of his this legislative session. Another of his bills, L.D. 105, also was passed initially by the House last week. It would allow the sale of gasoline containing only 5 percent ethanol instead of the current 10 percent. On the House floor last week, supporters of the bill also argued that using corn-based ethanol is essentially putting food in fuel tanks. Opponents said barring the sale of fuel with 10 percent ethanol fuel would put the state at odds with the federal Clean Air Act. Arguments in the Senate on Wednesday followed that track. “I don’t know how many stories I’ve heard about people having engines that were ruined” because of ethanol, said Assistant Senate Majority Leader Troy Jackson, D-Allagash. “Personally, I would pay a couple cents more (to buy fuel without it), but I don’t believe that’s going to be the case.” Most gas available in the United States contains 10 percent ethanol, but the federal Environmental Protection Agency has declared a 15-percent blend safe for engines and allowed its sale. Last week, both chambers of the Maine Legislature unanimously passed a resolution imploring the pressheraldDOTcom/news/Maine-Senate-votes-against-possible-ethanol-ban.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368966712703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368969499711-4</Id><Title>China gives environmental approval to country's biggest hydro dam</Title><Msg>BEIJING Wed May 15, 2013 5:47am EDT (Reuters) - China's environment ministry has given the go-ahead for the construction of what will become the country's tallest hydroelectric dam despite acknowledging it will have an impact on plants and rare fish. The dam, with a height of 314 meters (1,030 feet), will serve the Shuangjiangkou hydropower project on the Dadu River in southwestern Sichuan province. To be built over 10 years by a subsidiary of state power firm Guodian Group, it is expected to cost 24.68 billion yuan ($4.02 billion) in investment. The ministry, in a statement issued late on Tuesday, said an environmental impact assessment had acknowledged that the project would have a negative impact on rare fish and flora and affect protected local nature reserves. Developers, it said, had pledged to take "counter-measures" to mitigate the effects. The project still requires the formal go-ahead from the State Council, China's cabinet. China aims to raise the share of non-fossil fuels in its energy mix to 15 percent by 2020, up from 9.4 percent in 2011. Hydropower is expected to make the biggest contribution. It has vowed to speed up construction of dams in the 2011-2015 period after slowing it down following the completion of the controversial Three Gorges project in 2005. The Three Gorges Dam, which serves the world's biggest hydropower station on the Yangtze river, measures 185 meters. The 300-m Nurek dam in Tajikistan in Central Asia is the world's highest, though other taller dams are now under construction. China's tallest dam now, at 292 meters, is the Xiaowan Dam on the Lancang River, also known as the Mekong. On completion, the Sichuan project will have a total installed capacity of 20 gigawatts (GW), with annual power generation to exceed 7 billion kilowatt-hours (kWh). The government said this year that hydropower capacity was expected to reach 290 GW by 2015 reutersDOTcom/article/2013/05/15/us-china-hydropower-idUSBRE94E0EW20130515</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368969499711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368970525367-5</Id><Title>Florida Governor Urged to Veto Anti-Ethanol Bill</Title><Msg>Florida Governor Urged to Veto Anti-Ethanol Bill Posted on 13 May 2013 by Andy Eubank In the wake of a bill passed by the Florida Legislation to repeal a law calling for the use of 10% ethanol blends in the state, automotive technician and talk show host Bobby Likis had an op-ed in the Pensacola News Journal over the weekend calling on the governor to veto the bill.“What could be more devastating than ditching 35 years of progress? If the Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS) is repealed, we will haplessly relinquish the fast track to the future while fellow states and countries worldwide embrace strategic biofuels production and use,” wrote Likis. Who among us foolishly says, “We don’t care about what ‘they’ are doing. We care about Florida?” Well, we’d better care. Because of “them,” more efficient, better-mpg engines, cleaner air, national security and lots of dollars — in Florida — are at stake. So whose agenda is behind repealing the RFS anyway? Can’t be those who have the economics of the state at heart or interest in lower emissions, lower gas prices and optimized engine performance. All these are attributes of the renewable fuel, ethanol. And yet, the Florida Legislature would put all of this in our rear view mirror. Governor Scott, now is the time for one good man to come to the aid of his state—by vetoing HB4001/SB320. Florida’s Renewable Fuel Standard Act, which requires that all gasoline sold in Florida contain 9-10 percent ethanol, or other alternative fuel, by volume has been in effect for five years. The legislature passed a bill to repeal the act last month but it has not yet been signed by the governor. hoosieragtodayDOTcom/indexDOTphp/2013/05/13/florida-governor-urged-to-veto-anti-ethanol-bill/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368970525367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 09:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368987615639-6</Id><Topic><Title>With Record Sales, Tesla Turns A Profit As Consumer Reports Says It ‘Comes Close’ To Being ‘The Best Car Ever’!</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368469187102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 14:19:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How Adding An Electric Car Cut Solar Payback Time In Half May 18 2013 Nicholas Brown Do you think that buying an electric vehicle could reduce the payback time of a solar power system by 50%? Let us explore that. This is the story of a family in Pennsylvania who installed a 9.43 kW solar panel array to offset their electricity usage. They found themselves saving considerably more money than they originally would have. The solar power system was installed in October 2011. It consists of 41 panels. Each of the panels can generate 230 watts DC. The quoted cost of the solar system was $5.50 per watt of its generation capacity, which translates to $51,865. Yes, it is a very large system! Their electric bill was $2,500 per year, and the financial payback time of the solar system after state and federal government incentives was estimated to be 11.7 years. A year later, they replaced their 2007 Acura RDX with a 2013 Chevy Volt. They used the surplus electricity they generated to power the Chevy Volt, so they were able to eliminate their Acura RDX gasoline bill without incurring any new electricity costs, and now they have a solar-powered car! They said this cut the payback time of the solar system in half, down to 5.96 years, but the purchase price of the Chevy Volt does not appear to have been factored in. The Volt’s gas bill is up to $50 per month, while the RDX gas bill was $250 per month. The 2007 Acura RDX crossover achieves 19 MPG combined. I should note that the gas bills for both vehicles are a bit high. The writer of the story said they added 7,228 miles to the Chevrolet Volt in “only” six months (they drive an average of 1,250 miles per month), and that they “racked up a lot of miles.” 5,255 of the 7,228 miles accumulated on the Volt were on electricity alone (72% of pure electric driving). The writer of the story said that they fill the Volt’s 9 gal cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/05/18/how-adding-an-electric-car-cut-solar-payback-time-in-half/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368987615639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 14:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369009408295-7</Id><Topic><Title>Premier Wall pitches made-in-Saskatchewan carbon capture technology to U.S.</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368683834727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 01:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Inexpensive carbon capture will become available for installation by the late summer of 2014. It'll steal market share from natural gas. The LNG market will quickly all but vanish. My opinion only! MOO! MOOOOOOOOOOOOO00000000000ooooooooo!!!!!!!!!!!!1</Msg><Username>moooooooooooooooooooooooo4u</Username><Timestamp>1369009408295</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 20:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369015040433-8</Id><Topic><Title>Renewable power generation grew 7 percent in Texas last year</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368882919176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 09:15:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My girlfriend, Jennifer Lawrence loves diamonds! View her reaction at 1:45 of this video... youtubeDOTcom/watch?v=WJmhsJ5T5L0</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369015040433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>