<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-18"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374121984041-1</Id><Title>German Space Proceedings: MAPHEUS-4: X-rays in microgravity</Title><Msg>DLR 15.07.13 another example of Germany's efforts to promote industrial technology via energy &amp; material efficiency... **higher efficiency manufacturing, especially of turbine blades **superior packing of granular materials for greater material and energy efficiency DLR launches sounding rocket with materials physics experiments Close to four minutes of microgravity prevailed in the sounding rocket MAPHEUS-4, which was launched on 15 July 2013 at 07:53 local time, from the Esrange Space Center in northern Sweden... For the first time, the diffusion of aluminium and nickel was recorded under space conditions using X-ray analysis. The scientists at the DLR Institute of Materials Physics in Space examined the behaviour of granular gases in microgravity... Before the launch, a small furnace containing the six samples containing various proportions of aluminium and nickel was preheated to 900 degrees Celsius. The furnace had already had its premiere in November 2012, when the scientists tested it on board the sounding rocket MAPHEUS-3... The data acquired during microgravity is compared with model calculations and data from the terrestrial laboratory. The results can then contribute, among other things, to optimising industrial casting processes such as those used to produce turbine blades. To better understand the behaviour of granular gases, researchers from the Institute subjected small metal balls to microgravity conditions. During the flight, four magnets placed the balls in motion and two high-speed cameras, which acquired up to 500 high-resolution images per second, recorded the particles as they pushed against each other and determined the velocity distribution. With the results, the researchers can analyse how granular gases – for example bulk goods like pills – can be packed more densely and in a more stable way</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1374121984041</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 00:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374155071181-2</Id><Title>Is XOM going to partner with IOC?</Title><Msg>Does anyone here on this XOM board really think that they are getting a deal done with Inter Oil in the next few weeks? or will it be years?</Msg><Username>iocrules</Username><Timestamp>1374155071181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 09:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374155259539-3</Id><Title>State regulators approve need for pipeline upgrade</Title><Msg>State regulators approve need for pipeline upgrade Article by: DAVID SHAFFER , Star Tribune Updated: July 17, 2013 - 9:11 PM Despite opposition from anti-pipeline activists, Minnesota regulators approve a proposed expansion of a crude oil pipeline through the state. The Minnesota Public Utilities Commission unanimously approved plans Wednesday by Enbridge Energy to boost the capacity of its Alberta Clipper oil pipeline in Minnesota as environmental and Native American protesters chanted in opposition. The Enbridge project, like TransCanada’s proposed Keystone XL pipeline in western states, has drawn protesters who oppose transporting more crude oil from the tar sands region of Alberta to the United States. But the Minnesota Commerce Department, which reviews energy projects, supported the upgrade, saying it would ensure “a continued, reliable cost-effective supply of crude oil to Minnesota and the region from a consistent and stable supply region.” The department projected that a likely alternative if the pipeline isn’t built — shipping crude by railroad — would require 7,000 tank cars traveling through the state. “There is no need for this pipeline,” John Munter, who lives with his family in Warba, Minn., about 4 miles from the Enbridge line, said as he stood outside the PUC’s offices with a sign that said, “No Tar Sands Genocide.” Munter was the first anti-pipeline protester to show up for the St. Paul meeting, but was later joined by about 50 others, many of whom wanted to speak to the PUC, which didn’t allow testimony. The protesters included activists from MN350.org, a climate-change advocacy group, and Honor the Earth, led by Winona LaDuke of the White Earth Reservation in Minnesota. (In 1996 and 2000, LaDuke was the Green Party’s vice presidential candidate on the ticket headed by Ralph Nader.) Commissioners, after a brief discussion that was repeatedly interrupted by protesters, voted that the project is needed, citing its favorable economics. Regu</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374155259539</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 09:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374155839635-4</Id><Topic><Title>City of Detroit about to declare bankruptcy</Title><Username>think5pm</Username><Timestamp>1373996373656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:39:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“There’s probably no city that’s more financially challenged in the entire United States,” Michigan Governor Rick Snyder said in March, referring to the Michigan city of Detroit. The multiple problems of mismanagement of the city’s services, loads of liabilities and an ever growing deficit are compounded by widespread blight and ever falling economic activity. Although Detroit covers a larger area than Boston, Manhattan and San Francisco combined it has 60,000 vacant plots of land and 78,000 vacant buildings of which 38,000 are thought to be in a potentially dangerous condition. Since Detroit’s heyday as the center of US car production in the 1950’s its population has shrunk by 60%.</Msg><Username>iocrules</Username><Timestamp>1374155839635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 09:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374156611160-5</Id><Title>A global technological arms race is underway to deflate the massively inflated global energy price.</Title><Msg>*Pacific area seaborne coal prices are now down 60% in the past 5 years, matching declines in spot power prices in Germany. *Japan will start burning coal in lieu of imported LNG to lower its industrial input costs. They are expanding solar power too, using feed-in-tariffs to nullify the fixed cost. Eventually the fixed cost will fall below the cost of coal from government driven industrial-technological policy and then neither Japan, nor Germany, nor anyone else will need the feed-in-tariffs. The free market and what it and American companies would do, or can do, to develop technology is totally irrelevant. Perth (Platts)—11 Jul 2013 “August-loading cargoes of 6,000 kcal/kg NAR Newcastle thermal coal were bid at $77.25/mt to an offer at $78/mt in Asian trade Thursday, after a 25,000 mt parcel for August-loading traded at $76.50/mt onscreen Wednesday. September-loading shipments had a bid-offer spread of $76-77.40/mt FOB Newcastle Thursday. Japanese thermal coal buyers were heard to have purchased some cargoes of Newcastle 6,000 kcal/kg NAR thermal coal this week, including an October-loading cargo at $77.50/mt FOB, market sources said. Hokkaido Electric Power Co. last week bought five spot Panamaxes of Newcastle 6,300 kcal/kg GAR coal for Q3 delivery at close to $80/mt FOB and the utility is expected to return to the market soon for Q4 cargoes. "Hokkadio tenders regularly, issuing one tender per quarter," said one market participant. "Customers in Japan are getting good prices." Japanese power companies are waiting for the government to allow the restart of some idle nuclear power reactors, but power companies have to go through a complex new regulatory process, said one market source. "There are new regulations on nuclear power plant operators requiring Japanese power companies to register with the government, and this can take up to six months," he said. Some Japanese power plants were understood to have experimented with thermal coal with an ash</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1374156611160</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 10:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374161083254-6</Id><Title>Oil shortfalls, watch oil prices rocket again.</Title><Msg>Retest of highs coming.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1374161083254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 11:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374161813754-7</Id><Title>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report for week ending July 12, 2013</Title><Msg>Weekly Natural Gas Storage Report for week ending July 12, 2013 Released: July 18, 2013 at 10:30 a.m. | Next Release: July 25, 2013 Summary Working gas in storage was 2,745 Bcf as of Friday, July 12, 2013, according to EIA estimates. This represents a net increase of 58 Bcf from the previous week. Stocks were 414 Bcf less than last year at this time and 34 Bcf below the 5-year average of 2,779 Bcf. In the East Region, stocks were 101 Bcf below the 5-year average following net injections of 37 Bcf. Stocks in the Producing Region were 36 Bcf above the 5-year average of 977 Bcf after a net injection of 15 Bcf. Stocks in the West Region were 31 Bcf above the 5-year average after a net addition of 6 Bcf. At 2,745 Bcf, total working gas is within the 5-year historical range. ir eia gov/ngs/ngs html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374161813754</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 11:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374163780783-8</Id><Topic><Title>Let's just rename this the BLUEcheesie board</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374106090778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:08:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a life you have bluecheese. Ever think of applying for a job with a local paper......so you could plagarize other's work ?</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374163780783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 12:09:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374164914609-9</Id><Title>SUNSHINE OILSANDS READY TO PRODUCE</Title><Msg>Its time for SUNSHINE OILSANDS to produce folks start accumulating</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1374164914609</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 12:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374170762257-10</Id><Title>Biodiesel can solve the ethanol debate, supporters say</Title><Msg>Biodiesel can solve the ethanol debate, supporters say July 18, 2013 at 12:43 pm by Zain Shauk Iman Noshadi, a doctoral student of Richard Parnas at the University of Connecticut, holds a vial of biodiesel and its byproduct, glycerol, in a lab on campus in Storrs, Conn. (AP Photo/Republican-American, Alec Johnson) Amid the oil industry’s all-out blitz to kill a government mandate for corn-based ethanol, biodiesel producers say they have a solution that could help everyone involved. It goes like this: Buy more biodiesel. That proposal may not be so far-fetched. Federal mandates require fuel producers to buy and blend specific amounts of ethanol and other biofuels. But those mandates have increased to levels that the oil industry says are nearly impossible for it to meet and have driven up prices. Refiners say that they can’t blend more than 10 percent ethanol into their gasoline for safe operation in many vehicles, but government mandates currently require them to surpass that total. Biofuels: Ethanol brawl heats up between oil and corn industries Biodiesel makers, however, say that if refiners buy more biodiesel they can satisfy their requirements for more corn-based ethanol under current rules from the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. Biodiesel, made from used cooking oils, discarded animal fats and other items, qualifies as an advanced biofuel under EPA rules, as opposed to corn-based ethanol, which is considered a conventional biofuel. “Advanced biofuels can qualify to meet the conventional obligation, but not vice versa,” said Joe Jobe, CEO of the National Biodiesel Board. While oil companies say a frenzy to buy ethanol credits has driven up prices, they could instead be purchasing credits that represent gallons of biodiesel, Jobe said. The American Petroleum Institute, the oil industry’s main lobbying group, did not immediately respond to a request for comment. Neither did the EPA. Bill Day, a spokesman for Valero, the nation’s largest refin</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374170762257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 14:06:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374170988575-11</Id><Title>So let’s see if you Americans know anything about your country…</Title><Msg>What is the most European county in the Southern United States with a population over 250,000 ? ....with high population growth rate nearly 30%/decade. A diamond in the rough. I am going to invest there. There is a way for me to legally acquire guns in America too, so that problem is solved. Sold € to buy $ @ 1.3112 $/€. Gain on €, £, and €, £ bonds in $ +2.6%... Allocation $: 12.5%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1374170988575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 14:09:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374172342501-12</Id><Title>TransCanada Says Keystone XL Start in 2015 ‘Difficult’</Title><Msg>TransCanada Says Keystone XL Start in 2015 ‘Difficult’ Rebecca Penty - Jul 18, 2013 11:42 AM MT 8 Comments TransCanada Corp. (TRP) Chief Executive Officer Russ Girling said the timeline for U.S. approval of the $5.3 billion Keystone XL pipeline project will make the start of operations in the second half of 2015 “difficult.” The CEO said a final environmental impact statement from the State Department may come in “weeks, not months,” after which there will be a 90-day review of whether the project is in the U.S. national interest. “I hope a decision can be made this year,” Girling said today in an interview at Bloomberg headquarters in New York. If approved, Calgary-based TransCanada needs 24 months to build the pipeline, which would connect oil production from Alberta to refineries on the U.S. Gulf Coast. President Barack Obama initially rejected the project in January 2012, citing concerns with its path through ecologically sensitive lands in Nebraska. The company reapplied with a new Nebraska route last year and split the project in two, building the southern portion that doesn’t require a permit first. Environmentalists oppose the project because of the potential for oil spills along its more than 2,000-mile (3,200 kilometer) route. Some opponents are also blocking it because it will transport crude from Alberta’s oil-sands projects, which generate more greenhouse gases than most conventional production. “Keystone is not the driver of whether Canadian oil sands will be produced,” Girling said. “They will be produced anyway.” Sixth Anniversary In September, the project will reach its sixth anniversary from the initial application date, Girling said. The company in April bumped back its target to complete the line to the second half of 2015, forecasting costs will rise amid delays receiving the needed approvals for construction. TransCanada continues to incur costs to store the equipment it has already purchased and to maintain the pipe, in some ca</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374172342501</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 14:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374172584413-13</Id><Topic><Title>Oil shortfalls, watch oil prices rocket again.</Title><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1374161083254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 11:24:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Considering how well XOM is doing, the market is in agreement.</Msg><Username>game_theory</Username><Timestamp>1374172584413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 14:36:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374172674726-14</Id><Title>100% Electric Cars Outselling Plug-in Hybrid Electric Cars In US (2013)</Title><Msg>100% Electric Cars Outselling Plug-in Hybrid Electric Cars In US (2013) July 18, 2013 Zachary Shahan This article was first published on EV Obsession: Green Car Reports recently stumbled across an interesting fact — 100% electric vehicles (led by the Nissan Leaf and Tesla Model S) have actually outsold plug-in hybrid electric vehicles (PHEVs) in the first half of 2013 in the US. electric cars outselling plug in electric cars PHEVs have generally been portrayed as a bridge technology between gasmobiles and 100% electric vehicles. But if 100% electric vehicles are already outselling PHEVs, one might wonder how long that bridge technology will be useful, and how intelligent it was for some companies to invest in and develop high-quality PHEVs like the Chevy Volt and Fisker Karma. Green Car Reports writes: From January through June of this year, the combination of 9,839 Nissan Leafs, 882 Mitsubishi i-MiEVs, and approximately 9,400 Tesla Model S cars (plus 1,700-odd compliance cars and others) exceeds the total of 18,335 plug-in hybrids and Chevrolet Volt range-extended electric cars. Slightly different six-month sales totals from the Electric Drive Transportation Association tell the same story. EDTA reports 22,712 battery-electric cars (we presume they use different estimates for the monthly sales that Tesla doesn’t report) against the same 18,335 plug-in hybrids and range-extended electrics that we tallied. Tesla has been responsible for a good portion of those 100% EV sales. Surely, the great range of the Model S has been a part of that, as well as the car winning just about every car award imaginable and being regarded by Consumer Reports as the best car its team has ever tested. However, I think the fact that over 12,000 fully electric vehicles (including almost 10,000 Nissan Leafs) were also sold shows that so-called “range anxiety” is not a concern for many people. I’ve written many times that range anxiety is overhyped. The avera</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374172674726</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 14:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374173367650-15</Id><Topic><Title>Have You Looked At Sweat Crude Futures Prices?</Title><Username>stevie_b_in_hawaii</Username><Timestamp>1374091305592</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:01:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take Profit while others are being greedy.</Msg><Username>stevie_b_in_hawaii</Username><Timestamp>1374173367650</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 14:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374173681099-16</Id><Topic><Title>Oil shortfalls, watch oil prices rocket again.</Title><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1374161083254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 11:24:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahahaha I think you should remove the $10bbl fear bubble in Oil Prices produced by Egypt before setting off those rockets. We have seen this before &amp; it reads like a book. Transports get killed and shet runs down hill to the already weak &amp; fragile world economies. Wall St. will is shorting Oil at these levels has they always have in the past.</Msg><Username>stevie_b_in_hawaii</Username><Timestamp>1374173681099</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 14:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374175704652-17</Id><Topic><Title>Is XOM going to partner with IOC?</Title><Username>iocrules</Username><Timestamp>1374155071181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 09:44:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Covered my IOC short and went long today. GS guy on the floor says deal announced next week and very good for both partners. No buyout but lots of upfront cash for IOC. Lots of wet gas for XOM. I hear as soon as Monday. Friday trading should provide confirmation.</Msg><Username>janinesor</Username><Timestamp>1374175704652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 15:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374175923084-18</Id><Title>Exxon vs Bluecheese</Title><Msg>I can't quite figure out who has the most info....Bluecheese makes some 30-50 posts per day on XOM, CVX, WMT, and others....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1374175923084</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 15:32:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374187426190-19</Id><Title>XOM will be 100$/shr</Title><Msg>within 6mnts.</Msg><Username>dibm</Username><Timestamp>1374187426190</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 18:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374187562248-20</Id><Title>McCarthy Confirmation to Lead EPA Clears Way for Rules</Title><Msg>McCarthy Confirmation to Lead EPA Clears Way for Rules By Mark Drajem - Jul 18, 2013 1:54 PM MT Gina McCarthy won U.S. Senate confirmation as head of the Environmental Protection Agency and carry out President Barack Obama’s agenda to adopt measures aimed at reducing air pollution and fighting climate change. McCarthy, the agency’s assistant administrator, directed EPA rulemaking in Obama’s first term, forcing coal-fired power plants to curb mercury emissions, imposing new standards on boilers in hospitals and paper mills and setting limits on pollution from cement plants. She’ll be charged with implementing those measures now, as well as writing the first rules limiting carbon emissions from power plants. McCarthy, 59, is a 25-year veteran of state and local government in New England, where she worked for Republicans including former Massachusetts Governor Mitt Romney. McCarthy was confirmed 59-40 today. “She’s worked for four Republican governors and the last Republican candidate for president,” Republican Senator Lamar Alexander of Tennessee told reporters. “We’re not likely to get a Democratic head of the Environmental Protection Agency who’s got a record any better than that.” With a strong Boston accent, short shock of white hair and disarming sense of humor, McCarthy won the praise of both environmental groups, which largely support the administration’s efforts, and industry groups, which have fought them. ‘Directness, Openness’ “What many in industry appreciate about her style is her directness and openness to engagement with the regulated community,” Scott Segal, a lawyer representing power producers and oil refiners at Bracewell &amp; Giuliani LLP, said when she was nominated in March. While utilities or coal producers may object to the overall regulation, “McCarthy listens and allows for the possibility of midcourse corrections,” he said. McCarthy takes over an agency that Republicans have criticized over pollution limits that they say will c</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374187562248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 18:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374189964502-21</Id><Title>Global Warming will kill all human life on Earth !!!</Title><Msg>Thank you Standard Oil. Petroleum refuse and pollution cannot be cured. Enjoy what life you have left.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1374189964502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374190256709-22</Id><Title>Exxon 3 For 1 Split Announcement.</Title><Msg>We need a 3 for 1 Splitz !!!</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1374190256709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374190740932-23</Id><Topic><Title>XOM will be 100$/shr</Title><Username>dibm</Username><Timestamp>1374187426190</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 18:43:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I say within 3 months.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374190740932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374190782137-24</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon vs Bluecheese</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1374175923084</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 15:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bluecheese has NO life..............idiot poster</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374190782137</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:39:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374190886236-25</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese sure does enjoy talking to himself</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373991530250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump !!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374190886236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374190918479-26</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese sure does enjoy talking to himself</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373991530250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>double bump !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374190918479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:41:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374190943039-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Bluecheese Boards</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1374012244923</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 18:04:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump !!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374190943039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374191007069-28</Id><Topic><Title>Has "molded bluecheese" ever gotten a thumbs up ????</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373579593170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 17:53:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One ? Just one ?????????? NADA !</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374191007069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374191250935-29</Id><Title>White House steps up biofuel support amid escalating attacks</Title><Msg>White House steps up biofuel support amid escalating attacks Zack Colman - 07/18/13 01:18 PM ET The White House on Thursday doubled down on its support of a biofuel-blending rule that’s drawing intense attacks from the oil industry and lawmakers on Capitol Hill. Heather Zichal, President Obama’s top energy and climate adviser, said the renewable fuel standard is the “backbone of our policy” for reducing oil imports, and added it would help reduce greenhouse gas emissions. “Calls to repeal the renewable fuel standard are nothing but short-sighted,” Zichal said at a Thursday event hosted by The Hill and the Advanced Biofuels Association. Zichal said the Obama administration would remain committed to the standard in the face of the “RFS battles that we know are ahead of us.” That fight is already underway. Both the House and the Senate have held hearings this week and last that touched on the mandate, which requires refiners to combine 36 billion gallons of renewable fuel into conventional petroleum by 2022. The House Energy and Commerce Committee will also hold a hearing on the blending rule next week. The panel’s top two members, Chairman Fred Upton (R-Mich.) and ranking member Rep. Henry Waxman (D-Calif.), have produced a series of white papers on the rule. Measures to repeal the standard have been filed in both chambers. The American Petroleum Institute, the oil industry’s main trade association, supports those bills. The oil industry says refiners are being forced to buy credits for next generation biofuels that haven’t yet reach commercial scale to meet the mandate’s targets. It also says refiners are approaching a “blend wall” in which they’ll need to blend higher concentrations of ethanol fuel to meet the rule’s accelerating marks. Some environmental groups also have challenged the standard, though they're looking for changes rather than eliminating the rule. They have questioned the environmental benefits of the standard, as the</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374191250935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:47:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374191510070-30</Id><Title>EPA comment period closed on corn fiber as ag residue, biobutanol</Title><Msg>EPA comment period closed on corn fiber as ag residue, biobutanol By Holly Jessen | July 18, 2013 In all, the U.S. EPA received 117 comments on a proposed rule on renewable fuel standard (RFS) pathways, including corn kernel fiber-to-cellulosic ethanol and issues relating to biobutanol. The comment period ended July 15. The Renewable Fuels Association submitted 28 pages of comments on the proposed rule. In it, the group supported EPA’s efforts to add corn kernel fiber to the list of qualifying cellulosic biofuel feedstocks as well as what it called a simplified approach to cellulosic RIN generation. “We applaud EPA for confirming that corn kernel fiber is ‘crop residue,’ and believe the agency has proposed a sensible and straightforward approach to RIN generation for renewable fuels derived from cellulosic biomass feedstocks,” wrote RFA President and CEO Bob Dinneen. “Several technologies to convert corn kernel fiber into cellulosic ethanol have been developed in recent years, and a number of existing ethanol plants have already adopted these technologies or are poised to integrate them in the near future. The volumes of cellulosic ethanol produced from corn kernel fiber can meaningfully contribute to RFS2 cellulosic biofuel requirements in the near term.” Growth Energy’s comments advocated for additional pathways to meet the goals of the RFS, including the pathway of corn fiber-to-cellulosic ethanol and other crop residues. “We believe that any renewable biomass meeting the 60 percent greenhouse gas threshold should be able to generate cellulosic RINs,” the comments said. The National Corn Growers Association also submitted comments. The group said it felt all biomass feedstocks should be categorized as renewable and that corn fiber should be defined as crop residue as well as qualify as a feedstock for cellulosic ethanol, generating D3 RINs. “100 percent of the volume of renewable fuel from specific cellulosic feedstock sources should be allowed to generate</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374191510070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374192575059-31</Id><Title>★★★★★TOP is in !! BAD DAY tomorrow...DETROIT+GOOG+MSFT=minus -400pts !</Title><Msg>KABOOM time....get short ...SHORTIE !</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1374192575059</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 20:09:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374199136625-32</Id><Title>The Bernack won't stop until oil is $150/bbl</Title><Msg>Ben is XOM's Best. Friend. Ever!!!</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1374199136625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 21:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374203601293-33</Id><Topic><Title>White House steps up biofuel support amid escalating attacks</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374191250935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:47:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Consumers may not be as organized,but this guy in the WH is a moron.</Msg><Username>bioditz</Username><Timestamp>1374203601293</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 23:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374203766119-34</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming will kill all human life on Earth !!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1374189964502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 19:26:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be so dramatic...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1374203766119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 23:16:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>