<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367644145444-1</Id><Title>Environmental groups sue EPA over refinery emissions</Title><Msg>May 3, 2013 at 7:17 am by Matthew Tresaugue Environmentalists have filed a lawsuit to force federal regulators to review the way they calculate emissions from petrochemical plants, oil refineries and other large industrial facilities. In the suit filed on Thursday, Air Alliance Houston and three other groups accuse the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency of using outdated and inaccurate formulas to estimate levels of air pollution. The groups say studies show that actual smog-forming emissions can be 132 times greater than EPA estimates, which are based on data provided by the industry. The agency, as a result, does not possess reliable data to protect public health, according to the suit filed in U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia. “The EPA has a history of dragging its feet on this issue,” said Jennifer Duggan, an attorney for the Environmental Integrity Project, a legal group representing Air Alliance Houston and the other organizations in the case. “It has been aware of these inaccuracies for some time.” An EPA spokeswoman said the agency is reviewing the suit but would not provide additional comment. The lawsuit comes five years after the city of Houston raised similar issues with the federal agency, which uses the emissions data to develop pollution controls, establish limits and guide enforcement. In response, the agency acknowledged flaws in its formulas and promised to make changes. No formula review But the EPA has not conducted a review of the formulas used to estimate emissions from flares, wastewater treatment systems and storage tanks at chemical plants and oil refineries, the suit contends. Flares, which burn off pressurized gases during startups, shutdowns and equipment malfunctions, are of particular concern because the EPA relies on a 30-year-old study to calculate their emissions. The lawsuit says the fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/03/environmental-groups-sue-epa-over-refinery-emissions/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367644145444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 01:09:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367672862134-2</Id><Title>Fireworks and toys for boys…</Title><Msg>“The Pentagon has redesigned its biggest "bunker buster" bomb with more advanced features intended to enable it to destroy Iran's most heavily fortified and defended nuclear site.” “so far, the Defense Department has now spent more than $400 million on the bombs, which are build by Boeing” --- Wall Street Journal 3 May 2013 It’s good to see the US government spending in the “general welfare.” I’m just waiting for the outbreak of the of the Sino-American arms race. That one promises to be very impressive. Between the Chinese militarists and American militarists both spending, demand for scientific intellect (for quantum tech toys), and industrial equipment to fuel the supply side of the China’s economy, promises to be greater than ever. It’s going to cost a lot of money too: a tax on oil will be the easiest way to pay for it. American income tax rates are now higher then German rates in many US states, so higher income taxes are not going to be a good approach – unless the US government wants to encourage more people to renounce their citizenship to escape taxes…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367672862134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 09:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367673599915-3</Id><Title>capture “wasted” wind power and store it in the battery, meaning operators can capture revenue previously left on t</Title><Msg>... the brilliant turbine to capture “wasted” wind power and store it in the battery, meaning operators can capture revenue previously left on the table ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367673599915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 09:19:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367674041586-4</Id><Title>Eos Energy Storage Launches 1st Pilot Project With Con Edison</Title><Msg>May 4, 2013 Zachary Shahan Eos Energy Storage Aurora Battery. Click to see larger image. Eos Energy Storage this week launched its first pilot project with Con Edison. The pilot project will see Eos’s potentially disruptive energy storage technology used at Con Edison’s New York City facilities. Interestingly, this announcement came out at about the time (maybe the exact time) I was writing a long article about Eos and its innovative energy storage technology (click that link for a lot more information). I saw the announcement after that article was written and scheduled, so I decided to just write another one to piggy-back on that. This New York pilot project has received funding from the New York State Energy Research and Development Authority (NYSERDA). Naturally, the goal is to demonstrate the Eos Aurora’s usefulness in helping the utility to manage the grid at a low cost for customers. “Our belief is that affordable energy storage will improve the efficiency and resilience of the electricity grid while reducing costs for utilities and customers alike, and it is a great opportunity to prove this together with a pre-eminent utility like Con Edison,” Eos CEO Michael Oster said. Here are a few more details from the press release, most of which were mentioned in my much lengthier post on the technology: “Eos stated that the pilot, targeted to begin in early 2014, is a milestone in the scale-up and commercialization of Eos’s core product, a 1MW/6MWh grid-scale battery called the Eos Aurora. The Aurora is backed by Eos’s novel, low-cost and proprietary zinc hybrid cathode technology, which has a 75% round-trip efficiency rate and a 10,000-cycle/30-year lifetime.” Naturally, a Con Edison representative had some positive words about Eos and its technology. “Con Edison looks forward to installing and measuring Eos’s new battery. As pioneers in the cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/05/04/eos-energy-storage-launches-1st-pilot-project-with-con-edison/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367674041586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 09:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367675228356-5</Id><Topic><Title>Nancy Grace is a DIS'GRACE !!!</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1367630630058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:23:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She's pitiful.......along with all the clowns on HLN.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1367675228356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 09:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367678166619-6</Id><Topic><Title>Nancy Grace is a DIS'GRACE !!!</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1367630630058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:23:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But you're watching it.... BTW - how does this relate to XOM??</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1367678166619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 10:36:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367691999295-7</Id><Title>CONNECTICUT SENATE VOTES FOR RENEWABLE ENERGY REFORM BILL WILL PROVIDE FOR CHEAPER, CLEANER, MORE RELIABLE ELECTRICITY</Title><Msg>05/02/2013 By States News Service The following information was released by the Connecticut General Assembly, Senate Democrats: Renewable energy reform legislation passed the Connecticut State Senate on Wednesday afternoon that will help the state continue to meet its world-leading renewable energy goals while also taking innovative steps to reduce the cost of electricity across the board. State Senator Bob Duff (D-Norwalk), Senate Chair of the Energy and Technology Committee, led passage of the legislation, saying that it addresses the states urgent economic need to lower overall electric rates, while also deriving more power from renewable sources. Connecticut has made one of the most substantial commitments to renewable energy in the country, even the world. With this bill, we are reaffirming that commitment, but carrying it out in a more affordable way, said Senator Duff. Connecticut has some of the highest electricity costs in the country. Bringing those costs down is important for our economy, our households and businesses. At the same time, we must make real progress on renewable energy. I believe this bill strikes the appropriate balance to achieve both. For years, weve known that Connecticut has been forced to buy some less desirable, out of state energy resources in order to meet our States bold and admirable renewable energy goals, said Rep. Lonnie Reed (D-Branford), House Chair of the Energy and Technology Committee. We had two choices to correct the situation. Either diminish our goals or replace dirtier renewable generation like Maine biomass with clean options. This bill does that and protects the integrity of our whole renewables program. Hopefully, it will help lead to more affordable energy as well. Effective immediately, the bill permits the Commissioner of the Department of Energy and power-engDOTcom/news/2013/05/02/connecticut-senate-votes-for-renewable-energy-reform-bill-will-provide-for-cheaper-cleaner-more-reli.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367691999295</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 14:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367692680429-8</Id><Title>German renewable energy helped cut European power prices in April</Title><Msg>03 May 2013 Record output from German wind and solar plants helped to reduce European power prices in April, according to Platts the energy data provider. European continental day-ahead power prices averaged €45.20 per megawatt-hour in April, compared to €55.02 in March and €49.37 in April 2012. Year on year, this represents an 8.5% reduction in price. Platts credits this to a number of days when there was record output from renewable sources in Germany, especially on April 24 when solar photovoltaic output exceeded 23GW. That is the equivalent of 20 nuclear power plants, or one third of the country's working-day afternoon demand. This is in contrast to UK and continental day-ahead gas prices, which rose in the last 12 months by 17% and 14%, respectively. “Prices of power for immediate delivery turned bearish across Europe last month, with healthy wind, solar and hydro power output more than offsetting Germany’s production slowdown from the nuclear plant maintenance period,” said Andreas Franke, Platts power editor. “German day-ahead, peak-load power output for a week day fell to a record low April 18 at €27.15/MWh, as wind and solar power output reached an hourly record of 36GW.” Germany is installing new solar photovoltaic capacity at a staggering rate: around 270MW per month. In February, for example, this new capacity was spread out amongst more than 8,300 different systems, many of them community owned, and the largest of which was a new solar park in Brandenburg with a total capacity of 8.2MW. There are complaints in Germany that subsidies for solar power are disproportionately high, taking up half of the country’s funding for renewables but providing only 20% of its renewable energy. As a result, the feed-in tariff rate is being cut by 1.8% at the end of this month. Nevertheless, solar is very attractive and not just in Germany. 97% (1,581MW) of eaemDOTcoDOTuk/news/german-renewable-energy-helped-cut-european-power-prices-april</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367692680429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 14:38:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367692727117-9</Id><Topic><Title>German renewable energy helped cut European power prices in April</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367692680429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 14:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>97% (1,581MW) of the new generation capacity in the California transmission system operator’s schedule for installation in the second half of 2013 is solar. The rest is biomass (52MW). It is seen as a trend, as a renewables are displacing natural gas in the state. “This is the shape of things to come,” observed V. John White, executive director of the Center for Energy Efficiency and Renewable Technologies (CEERT). In many places, such as Italy, Spain, Germany, Portugal and the US Southwest, solar is at grid parity. In other words, it is the same price to build a solar plant as a gas or coal one. Solar is therefore getting cheaper, while gas and coal (everywhere except Germany) are getting more expensive. Moreover, the end could be in sight for the cut-price natural gas boom caused by the North American shale gas revolution, which also brought cheap coal to the UK. In the first four months of this year, coal-based electricity generation in the United States increased by 12.7%, while that from natural gas fell 10.7%, according to Gencsape. Unless the US does install more renewable energy, its recent trend of reducing greenhouse gas emissions will be reversed. Germany still does rely heavily on coal particularly in the east of the country, despite the solar boom. It remains the world's biggest producer of coal, and the country needs nuclear, coal or gas for base power to ensure a continuous supply, as does the UK. This is giving rise to talk of a tax on lignite being introduced. The UK's answer is a carbon price floor.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367692727117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 14:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367714590757-10</Id><Title>Obama says U.S. natural gas exports could help Central America</Title><Msg>Sat May 4 2013 8:39pmBST * Closes out three-day Latin America tour * Obama administration mulling natural gas exports * Opposed by some U.S. interests By Steve Holland and Isabella Cota SAN JOSE, May 4 (Reuters) - President Barack Obama said in Central America on Saturday that the United States might be able to help relieve that region's growing energy demands by exporting liquefied natural gas, a move opposed by some U.S. businesses and environmentalists. At a development forum that ended his three-day trip to Mexico and Costa Rica, Obama held out the prospect that surging supplies of natural gas in the United States could be sold in the area to help reduce its energy costs. Obama's Energy Department is to decide in the coming months, possibly this summer, whether to approve more than two dozen applications for natural gas exports to companies in countries that do not currently have a free-trade agreement with the United States. It is one of the first big energy decisions he faces early in his second term. Obama made a case for taking the step. The United States, riding a surge of natural gas production, is likely to be a net natural gas exporter as soon as 2020, he said. He said he discussed with Central American presidents at a dinner on Friday night how U.S. natural gas can be used by the region as a bridging mechanism to relieve its energy demands until alternative energy sources can be increased. "I've got to make an executive decision broadly about whether or not we export liquefied natural gas at all," Obama said. Helping Central America would be a factor in the decision-making, he added. U.S. companies that produce the gas feel the supply is more than adequate, but some U.S. businesses oppose large-scale liquefied natural gas exports out of concerns it will dramatically increase the price of the energy in the United States. Environmentalists have raised concerns as ukDOTreutersDOTcom/article/2013/05/04/usa-obama-centam-idUKL2N0DL0G320130504</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367714590757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 20:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367715611783-11</Id><Title>Renewable Energy Standards Face Challenge From Fossil Fuel Interests</Title><Msg>05/04/2013 6:13 pm EDT A funny thing is happening on the way to conservative attacks on solar energy—some conservatives are championing renewable energy over fossil fuel interests. The reason is simple: It’s called employment. It turns out that renewable energy, as popular as mom’s apple pie with American consumers, is also good for American business. And now jobs-conscious legislators from both parties are listening. Renewable energy standards, or RESs—sometimes called Renewable Portfolio Standards (RPS), just to add to the alphabet-soup mix—require electric utilities to buy a percentage of their power from renewable sources, such as solar, and wind by a certain date. These standards range from modest (Indiana wants its power to be 10 percent renewable by 2025) to ambitious (California requires 33 perecent by 2020). An electric utility can meet an RES law any number of ways, which vary by state. Buying electricity from a wind farm in a remote location or from a homeowner’s solar rooftop are two common examples. Alone, the RES laws won’t make a huge dent in the United States’ carbon pollution. But they’re creating critical mass. Businesses are employing people and making money on a slow shift to renewable power. In the windy Great Plains states, farmers pocket money from wind turbine leases. In sunny California, there are more solar installers than actors. On the other hand, the fossil fuel industry sees even a small RES as a threat to its business model. So it has partnered with the American Legislative Exchange Council to draft model laws delaying or repealing 22 states’ RES laws. After all, those laws are a government mandate that any freedom-loving state legislature would hate, right? But it hasn’t worked out that way. In North Carolina last week, Republicans helped defeat a bill that would have phased out a state RES. In doing so, huffingtonpostDOTcom/2013/05/04/renewable-energy-standards_n_3211017.html?utm_hp_ref=green</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367715611783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 21:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>