<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367330027850-1</Id><Topic><Title>Executive Order on C02...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367239006530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 08:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US Congress is to blame for writing legislation so crudely. The courts and executive making up law to make up for Congress’ failure to do its job is not dictatorship. Obama may well be a leftist too, but environmental policy and leftism are not synonymous, and if he wrote an Executive Order such as I mentioned it would be very right-wing, not left. The US Congress would be very motivated to write a piece of legislation similar to Germany’s energy policies if they realized that he was just going use the EPA to fine their big polluters until they did.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367330027850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 09:53:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367330227774-2</Id><Topic><Title>The left wants a bigger war – on fossil fuels.</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367237784284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 08:16:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gore’s ideas about women and breeding are peculiar. I think that a woman with exquisite genes should be pregnant many times. 100 euro silk panties, and 900 euro camisoles, etc and standing around looking at women's clothing for hours upon hours needs some purpose besides feminine vanity and a willingness to indulge it... I don’t know if that fits with his ideas about saving the planet – probably not. I don’t know any radical Greens, so I can’t comment about their treatment – except to just steal their agenda and implement it professionally…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367330227774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 09:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367332112656-3</Id><Topic><Title>The left wants a bigger war – on fossil fuels.</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367237784284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 08:16:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Al Gore believes that the sterilization should be voluntary – at first – “women who are evolved will volunteer to be sterilized for the greater good for planet.” BUT, if women do not choose to sterilize themselves, Al Gore believes that the government should force women (under 25) to be sterilized. "We have to take drastic steps to save the planet. There are too many people – we must take aggressive action or we will all be dead,” Gore said in a speech Monday in New York. He has played on his own fears so long that he has lost his mind. Hitler had thoughts like this and we know where he went.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367332112656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367334505114-4</Id><Title>OT Market</Title><Msg>Seems like a lot of the stock "Gurus" are saying to sell in May and go away. Given their track records, If the experts are saying to sell, should we start buying?</Msg><Username>ploddingalong98</Username><Timestamp>1367334505114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367335631158-5</Id><Topic><Title>Executive Order on C02...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367239006530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 08:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meanwhile, while the paranoid left wing enviro-nuts are destroying our industry they do little to nothing letting the China and third world nations move forward without the shackles of these types of regulations giving them a pricing advantage and all it does is just shift emissions to another location on the globe but making no difference in total global emissions and possibly even making it worse. If they do address this it usually is to shackle the US and the west with the bill for improving third world equipment once again causing higher taxes or fees there and once again making our products more costly and less competitive while less responsible countries laugh all the way to the bank. This kind of thinking is like someone who cuts themselves on purpose.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367335631158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367338012491-6</Id><Topic><Title>Executive Order on C02...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367239006530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 08:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is not an issue if you make residential pay high power rates to finance the fixed costs of the alternative energy, and then sell the power to industry at the much lower marginal costs. In Germany, industrial power rates are at 1978 levels because of this policy. The short term burden of high residential power rates can be alleviated with payroll tax cuts. The government reaps high saving from lower pollution and lower healthcare costs from lower pollution, internalizing the gains for society across its various budgets. The fossil fuel industry is the only loser. It will go extinct eventually… Since industry and the economy is not the loser, and the only loser is the fossil fuel lobby, the GOP must be beholden to this lobby more than the others, assuming it rationally understands the issues. This is a big assumption. Their poor policies in this area, and many others are why China competes easily with the US. They fail against Germany...Of course the USA has consistently failed against Germany for decades too... Bad policies are to blame.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367338012491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 12:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367338059939-7</Id><Title>Universal Bioenergy Inc. (UBRG)... Somebody is buying HUGE blocks</Title><Msg>Maybe something big</Msg><Username>penybull68</Username><Timestamp>1367338059939</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 12:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367340613553-8</Id><Title>nat gas</Title><Msg>Can anyone tell me how XOM is situated as to Nat gas? will xom be strong when the world switches to natgas? and when might that be?</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1367340613553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 12:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367343968089-9</Id><Title>Bought $KOG &amp; $NORX.</Title><Msg>Long-term growth prospects look good. Also, possible takeout targets.</Msg><Username>jdr52683</Username><Timestamp>1367343968089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367344983601-10</Id><Title>Saudi oil minister predicts more active US in energy markets</Title><Msg>Zack Colman - 04/30/13 11:41 AM ET Saudi Arabia’s oil chief said Tuesday that he expects newfound fossil fuel reserves in the United States will further integrate — rather than isolate — the nation into the international market. “I believe these reserves will lead the United States into a much deeper engagement in world energy markets,” Saudi Petroleum and Natural Resources Minister Ali al-Naimi said at a Washington, D.C., event hosted by the Center for Strategic and International Studies. The recent discovery of a wealth of U.S. fossil fuels has many lawmakers heralding a not-too-distant future free of oil imports from the Middle East, Venezuela and other nations. Al-Naimi said talks of North American energy independence is “naïve and simplistic,” explaining such discourse “fails to recognize the interconnected nature of global energy markets.” Since the United States consumes more oil than it produces, it still makes sense for the United States to import some of it because prices are set globally, al-Naimi said. He said that helps explain why U.S. imports of Middle East oil still rose last year despite frequent boasts of North American energy independence on Capitol Hill. On the possibility of the United States hoarding its fossil fuel supplies for domestic consumption, al-Naimi therefore said, “I don’t believe that is in anybody’s best interest, and I don’t think that will happen.” Many lawmakers feel the same way. Some have touted increasing exports — especially for liquefied natural gas — as a way to generate more federal revenues and jobs. Even further, some see exports as a tool to free allies from relying on less friendly suppliers. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/296929-saudi-oil-minister-predicts-more-active-us-in-energy-markets</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367344983601</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 14:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367345114590-11</Id><Title>☛☛☛HEY BERNANKE..we don't have 85 billion for your crazy "experiment" !!!</Title><Msg>ridiculos and insane</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1367345114590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 14:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367346014353-12</Id><Title>Canergy selects Chemtex and Beta Renewables for its Cellulosic Ethanol Project in California</Title><Msg>April 30, 2013, 12:05 p.m. EDT Canergy selects Chemtex for the development of their 25 million gallon a year cellulosic biofuels facility to be located in the Imperial Valley of California. BRAWLEY, CA &amp; Wilmington, Apr 30, 2013 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE via COMTEX) -- via PRWEB - Canergy, LLC, an advanced biofuels company based in California that is focused on the production of ultra-low carbon intensity ethanol from sustainable non-food energy crops, is pleased to announce that it has selected Chemtex, a leader in chemical engineering and renewable processes, and Beta Renewables, a global leader in cellulosic bio-fuels, for the development of their 25 million gallon a year cellulosic biofuels facility to be located in the Imperial Valley of California. Construction of the new facility is targeted to begin in Q1, 2014 pending successful completion of permitting and financial activities. The facility is expected to be operational in 2016. Tim Brummels, Canergy's CEO, said, "We are excited to be moving this project forward. California is the country's largest retail gasoline market and this first project's biofuel will facilitate obligated parties compliance with California policy directives to reduce their carbon footprint through 2020. We have completed extensive research and have concluded that PROESA(R) Technology is both ready now and is the most advanced and competitive cellulosic platform in the marketplace today. We are also excited to have CHS Inc., a leading global energy, grains and foods company, working with us as a development partner in the project." John Litterio, Director of Renewable Fuels Marketing for CHS, said, "CHS is a leading ethanol marketer with global trading offices in the United States, Brazil and Europe. Our financial strength, logistical expertise, risk management services and 30+ years of biofuels experience wl marketwatchDOTcom/story/canergy-selects-chemtex-and-beta-renewables-for-its-cellulosic-ethanol-project-in-california-2013-04-30</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367346014353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 14:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367346208010-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bought $KOG &amp; $NORX.</Title><Username>jdr52683</Username><Timestamp>1367343968089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try DEJ</Msg><Username>johnandjoy1</Username><Timestamp>1367346208010</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 14:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367348615595-14</Id><Topic><Title>Executive Order on C02...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367239006530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 08:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In essence I think you are saying we should basically tax individuals (residential) and transfer the money by way of power companies to industrial corporations to lower their cost and in theory they would lower the price of goods made. Wealth transfers from all incomes to corporations would not fly in the US and payroll tax cuts further deplete SS and Medicare funding which causes another problem down the road. It is a shell game that only makes life more costly and the savings on healthcare costs is theoretical and dubious IMO. Lastly, the industries issue with CO2 is not just energy costs but also the cost of direct emissions compliance which can be significant and may even force them to friendlier countries.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367348615595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 15:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367348823098-15</Id><Title>☛☛☛HEY BERNANKE..you only created a FALSE MARKET !!.</Title><Msg>really.......</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1367348823098</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 15:07:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367351803852-16</Id><Topic><Title>Executive Order on C02...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367239006530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 08:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a reason why American industry consistently fails. I’m well aware of your attitude, and the GOP, and I will personally never invest any money in the USA because of it. I consider it a failed state. The industrial power rate is the only relevant rate for industry. The gains from low marginal cost power (low because they use no fuel) do not just flow to industry but to workers and the government in taxes. The payroll taxes paid are higher when industry prospers, and it is possible to cut payroll taxes just as the German government did this year. In a poor, mismanaged economy like you have in the USA a payroll tax increase is required. Residential power expenditure is not used for investment and production, but for consumption, and it is irrelevant whether voters choose to spend their money on clean energy sources or fossil fuels + waste on other items. The reduction in pollution is relevant however. The reduction is scientifically verifiable. Your belief that this reduction does not reduce the incidence of disease, and healthcare costs in general, is simply wrong and refuted by medical science. Also, the creation of an industry to produce alternative energy results in a much larger employment of scientists. The discoveries flowing from the employment of the scientists represent a dividend, one which increases the productivity of capital in both the alternative energy field and other industries, lowering future power costs, and increasing profits and incomes across the economy. Fossil fuels produce no such dividend. Eventually you will deplete your resources too, and then your economy will certainly collapse, unless you can find someone else’s resources to purchase – at higher and higher prices... Alternatively you will be able to buy very modern versions of current German energy technology, at very high markups, that is assuming you still have any more money left to buy them…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367351803852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 15:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367356518176-17</Id><Topic><Title>Executive Order on C02...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367239006530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 08:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would not disagree that the US economy is mismanaged but with Germany bankrolling the grossly mismanaged economies of socialist EU countries I would not be too eager to crow about economic health. On the health issue you are talking about CO2 emissions and I do not believe that raising CO2 a couple hundred ppm's over 400 can be shown to cause a significant increase in health issues since the US OSHA has determined that permissible exposures up to 5000 ppm are ok and that is a long way from 600. Now particulants and certain chemicals yes and they should be regulated in a reasonable way. Don't get me wrong. I am not in support of a total hands off approach but one that is reasonable and that really works without government subsidies and wealth transfers. If German scientists can find a way then all power to them. I don't see much reasonableness in current environmental activism but more like followers of a very dogmatic semi-religious cult. Even Gore calls skeptics "deniers" like some modern version of the Spanish Inquisition.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367356518176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 17:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367359903942-18</Id><Topic><Title>Canergy selects Chemtex and Beta Renewables for its Cellulosic Ethanol Project in California</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367346014353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 14:20:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting article. What are sustainable non-food energy crops? What are cellulosic biofuels. I assume no corn will be used to make this Ethanol? Thanks.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1367359903942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367360400204-19</Id><Topic><Title>nat gas</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1367340613553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 12:50:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cummings is in final stage of developing a new engine for 18 Wheelers. 30% more efficient and with no pollution. Many companies are installing Nat Gas fueling stations across the US. CMI has the lead on this with Westport.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1367360400204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:20:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367360515943-20</Id><Topic><Title>Canergy selects Chemtex and Beta Renewables for its Cellulosic Ethanol Project in California</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367346014353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 14:20:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is no wonder why California is bankrupt. How much of the profit (if any) from this will come from government subsidies? What is the raw material used?</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367360515943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367360707185-21</Id><Topic><Title>nat gas</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1367340613553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 12:50:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Natural gas is overrated.</Msg><Username>josharnold346</Username><Timestamp>1367360707185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367364514256-22</Id><Title>Instead of Biofuel Boondogles using killed trees</Title><Msg>Plant more trees and let them grow. It is estimated by the U.S. Forest Service that all the forests in the United States, combined, sequestered approximately 309 million tons of carbon each year from 1952 - 1992, offsetting approximately 25 percent of human-caused emissions of carbon during that period. Over a 50-year lifespan, a tree generates almost $32,000 worth of oxygen, providing $62,000 worth of air pollution control. This tree would also be responsible for recycling $37,500 worth of water and controlling $31,000 worth of soil erosion. When they die then sequester the carbon in the wood. Use Natural gas already converted because it is much cheaper. God's designs are always better than mans.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1367364514256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 19:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367366285203-23</Id><Topic><Title>"""""Everyone with SENSE selling tomorrow boys ! PARTYS OVER.....</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366593623029</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 21:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another brilliant call...............dummy !</Msg><Username>young4ever399</Username><Timestamp>1367366285203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 19:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367367732755-24</Id><Title>Fracking rules coming 'in weeks,' says Interior chief Jewell</Title><Msg>Fracking rules coming 'in weeks,' says Interior chief Jewell By Zack Colman - 04/30/13 01:47 PM ET Draft federal rules on hydraulic fracturing, or fracking, will be released in a matter of “weeks, not months,” Interior Secretary Sally Jewell said Tuesday. The draft rules have undergone “sufficient change,” Jewell said during a media call. They’ll go through a public comment period once revealed. Interior decided in January to rewrite the rules that would govern fracking on federal lands. The controversial drilling method involves injecting a high-pressure mixture of water, sand and chemicals into tight-rock formations to tap oil and gas reserves buried deep underground. Environmentalists are concerned that fracking pollutes groundwater and have called for strong regulations to protect drinking reservoirs. The draft rules are expected to establish new requirements for maintaining well integrity and managing so-called flowback water. They will also force drillers to disclose chemicals they use during the fracking process. The oil and gas industry contends fracking is safe, noting that states have regulated the practice for decades. The industry is pushing back against the rules, which it says would be duplicative and would fail to account for geological differences between states. Jewell, for her part, has said a “one-size-fits-all” approach to regulating fracking won’t work. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/296973-fracking-rules-coming-in-weeks-says-interior-chief-jewell</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367367732755</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 20:22:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367369986779-25</Id><Title>☛☛☛HEY BERNANKE we don't have 85 billion per month for your crazy "experiment"</Title><Msg>BOOKWORM has NEVER even had a real job...he's ruining the old folks, YOU, and your kids future.....just keep on buying into disaster.....</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1367369986779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 20:59:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367370307074-26</Id><Topic><Title>nat gas</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1367340613553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 12:50:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No its not. Just wait and see what is going to happen when they start liquifying all this</Msg><Username>apshz</Username><Timestamp>1367370307074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 21:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367371461806-27</Id><Title>^^^CHINESE PMI falls to 50.6...barely hanging on before contraction!^^^.</Title><Msg>manufacturing drops.....</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1367371461806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 21:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367373143835-28</Id><Title>Is this True: Rush Near Death Due to...</Title><Msg>Is this rumor true: Rush is near death due to liver failure caused by his massive illegal intake of narcotic pain pills? Does anyone know?</Msg><Username>dubyuhandfansareevil</Username><Timestamp>1367373143835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 21:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367373630489-29</Id><Title>玲林志玲HONG KONG HARRY say BERNANKE know NOT what he do......</Title><Msg>Each American now owes us $85000.00...even new borns</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1367373630489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 22:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367375014394-30</Id><Title>Good time oil bulls for much higher prices. Bullish on oil. 5.00/gal gas no big deal.</Title><Msg>It's a time the oil bulls will roar.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1367375014394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 22:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367379077809-31</Id><Topic><Title>Good time oil bulls for much higher prices. Bullish on oil. 5.00/gal gas no big deal.</Title><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1367375014394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 22:23:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Economy starts slipping when gasoline gets above $3.75 per gallon. Possible we'll stay in the $3.50 +/- $0.25 for some time. All bets off if Saudi Arabia past peak oil.</Msg><Username>freemywilly99</Username><Timestamp>1367379077809</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 23:31:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>