<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364877997262-1</Id><Topic><Title>Best way to invest in Advanced Energy...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361540776959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 08:46:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Purchases complete. Allocations, residential real estate – 75%: Berlin – 20%, high &amp; middle class Stuttgart – 25%, middle class München – 20%, high &amp; middle class Ruhrgebiet: Duisburg &amp; Essen – 5%, middle class Ludwigshafen am Rhine – 5%, middle class Bonds &amp; deposits – 25%: 30 Year German government bonds @2.22% –15,0% 10 Year German government bonds @1.29% – 7,5% 3 month German government treasury bills @0% – 2,0% euro deposit – 0,5%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1364877997262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 00:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364891655612-2</Id><Topic><Title>I'm DONE with ref_steve..........</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1364776708785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 20:38:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u got that right.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1364891655612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 04:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364904621492-3</Id><Title>The USA's hidden deficits...</Title><Msg>The USA's fiscal deficits are obvious to all. The sad thing is they understate the true state of the USA's problem. The USA's infrastructure is very poorly maintained. This saves money while the infrastructure is run down but at the expense of much higher future costs and reduced future economic activity. This is a major problem for a country that saves nothing in the present and is already borrowing massively to keep up war spending and welfare, and is counting on higher future economic activity to pay it off. If the USA was actually maintaining its infrastructure it would be incurring much higher budget deficits... European countries with Germanic nobility do not share these difficulties. The infrastructure is in excellent condition and being improved. GDP across these countries is nearly identical to the USA, which contrasts with the much lower levels of other countries. Nobles have always been caretakers of the society and make certain their countries' (their being quite literal because they own very large amounts of them) are in good order. Other countries have a much poorer record. The US did well without a nobility for many years just by copying Germanic (noble) Europe, which worked well as long as its population still had the discipline and a memory of an ordered society.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1364904621492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 08:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364908879332-4</Id><Title>YTRV--OPENING IN CANADA--OIL PLAY WITH HUGE UPSIDE</Title><Msg>F-FOLD</Msg><Username>fkiesereda</Username><Timestamp>1364908879332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 09:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364909361367-5</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>sanromanwiliam</Username><Timestamp>1361547275275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:34:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rehwr</Msg><Username>amadeus_miller</Username><Timestamp>1364909361367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 09:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364913787151-6</Id><Title>The Way to Fix the USA</Title><Msg>Abolish the U.S. Senate and replace with an upper chamber composed of nobles. Sell hereditary noble titles to families with over $50 million in net worth, and have the nobles elect whomever they want, among themselves, for the high chamber... Restrict voting for the U.S. Congress to those with net worth over $500,000 and have the President elected by Congress and the upper Chamber of Nobles... Trial by jury should be abolished and replaced with trial by judges picked by the noble upper chamber - Noblesse de robe... The USA's problems would vanish very quickly...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1364913787151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:43:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364913974410-7</Id><Topic><Title>The USA's hidden deficits...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1364904621492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 08:10:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I look at our countries (USA) 3 or 4 trillion dollar war tab for Iraq and Afghanistan and the certainly coming wars in Iran, Syria and North Korea I am afraid to say that we have too much German nobility here in Unser Amerika. This is our problem and not welfare. At least those on welfare immediately spend or consume what we give them, ergo creating employment.Iam happy to see that Northern Europe is doing well but I would attribute it to their willingness to assess their economies scientifically and not give in to the naive belief that the free market is the ultimate answer.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1364913974410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364915368102-8</Id><Title>what consequence came from the end of BUBBLE$?</Title><Msg>TELL ME NOW</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1364915368102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 11:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364920550270-9</Id><Title>: )</Title><Msg>I’ve had picks texted to me daily and these guys rock. Picks are the closest thing you can get to a sure thing in the trading game. Sign up now!Text “stocks” now to 555888</Msg><Username>colegallagher854</Username><Timestamp>1364920550270</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 12:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364920899098-10</Id><Topic><Title>The USA's hidden deficits...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1364904621492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 08:10:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only way I know to get America’s wealthy to stop fighting a scientific approach to government is to make them the government, or at least a major part of it. Noble titles and their own chamber would do that. Indeed, the concept of driving science forward with research was created in Universities set up by Germanic nobles around Europe, especially in Germany itself. It was motivated by greed and elitism and worked marvelously for all concerned. Masters have to come from someplace, and one must be creative, and do research, and be smarter than others to be a Master. America’s first attempt at Universities was a failure as they thought the German approach much too elitist and preferred instead to “spread the knowledge” of America’s Professors by having them lecture and teach instead of do mostly research. The American attitude quickly ended because it was obvious Germany would just go right past them in science and industrial power if they kept it up. Germany’s Masters were kind enough to show them the right way forward. It was costly for Germany to fight a bigger, scientifically-industrial powered version of itself decades later. You will never succeed competing against a Germanic Europe who are masters of their own craft, and one that is teaching China in the same craft...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1364920899098</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 12:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364933494583-11</Id><Topic><Title>...and up we go?!!!!!</Title><Username>beneped01</Username><Timestamp>1364852511475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 17:41:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey there! Still making every effort........best to you too.</Msg><Username>beneped01</Username><Timestamp>1364933494583</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 16:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364953309941-12</Id><Title>Is That a Leaky Exxon Pipeline Under Your House or Are You Drilling for Oil?</Title><Msg>It's sure is a gusher!!!</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1364953309941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 21:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364953685976-13</Id><Title>Everybody in Arkansas Is Out Digging in Their Backyards to Strike Oil from Exxon Pipelines</Title><Msg>And when they strike a gusher, they will become rich oil tycoons like Jed Clampett.</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1364953685976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 21:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>