<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-25"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369460136093-1</Id><Title>Crude landlocked as Canadians join U.S. to halt pipelines</Title><Msg>Crude landlocked as Canadians join U.S. to halt pipelines Posted on May 24, 2013 at 6:55 am by Bloomberg British Columbia, the Canadian province whose official slogan to its own beauty is “Super, Natural,” is invoking another saying: “No more supertankers.” That’s potentially big trouble in a nation where oil exports amount to $73 billion annually and the industry employs more than 550,000 workers. It’s also a bad omen for nations, notably China, that have invested billions in Canadian oil projects with expectations that they will one day be able to buy vast quantities of heavy Canadian crude. To do that means not just pumping it from the vast tar sands — thought to hold as many as 170 billion barrels — lying mainly to the east in the neighboring province of Alberta. It also means building pipelines to carry that heavy oil, known as bitumen, west to the coast. From there, fleets of supertankers will be needed to ship it across the Pacific to Asian markets that desperately want cheap oil. Two such projects, representing about C$11.4 billion ($11.1 billion) in investments, are on the drawing boards. British Columbia, with its mountainous forests, national parks and salmon streams standing between the crude and the sea, wants no part of those pipelines — nor does it want its scenic bays to be turned into supertanker terminals. In Vancouver, with a metro-area population of 2.5 million, the evergreen-rimmed, blue sprawl of English Bay laps up to the city center and is already a port for supertankers taking crude from an existing pipeline known as the Trans Mountain conduit. Sean Austin offered an opinion sounded often there — that enough is enough. “English Bay shouldn’t become a parking lot for supertankers,” Austin, a 41-year-old construction worker, said in an interview as the sun set over a seawall behind him. Chinese Caught Out? An end to the fuelfixODTcom/blog/2013/05/24/crude-landlocked-as-canadians-join-u-s-to-halt-pipelines/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369460136093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 01:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369460667472-2</Id><Title>Group: State Department inspector general is probing Keystone pipeline review</Title><Msg>Ben Geman - 05/24/13 04:23 PM ET A liberal watchdog group says the State Department’s inspector general (IG) is probing possible conflicts of interest in the federal environmental review of the proposed Keystone XL oil sands pipeline. The Checks and Balances Project said it will unveil evidence next Wednesday of an IG inquiry into State’s use of Environmental Resources Management (ERM), the consultants behind State's March draft analysis that gave Keystone a largely clean bill of health. In April, Checks and Balances and other green groups called for an IG probe. Their request followed revelations in Mother Jones magazine that a senior ERM analyst had worked as a consultant for Keystone developer TransCanada Corp. on previous projects. The Mother Jones story, based on unredacted ERM filings with State, showed that the ERM official had also worked with big oil companies, and also showed previous work with oil industry interests by two other ERM contributors to the Keystone analysis. Doug Welty, a spokesman for State’s IG office, said Friday that it’s the IG’s policy not to comment on “any possible, pending, ongoing or future investigations.” The April letter to the IG from the green groups urged a probe into allegedly “incomplete statements on the Organizational Conflict of Interest ... questionnaire” by ERM, and the State Department contracting officer’s determination that ERM did not have any conflicts of interest. The letter from groups including Greenpeace, Public Citizen, Friends of the Earth and others alleged ERM has “direct business relationships” in recent years with oil companies that have a financial interest in Keystone. The Checks and Balances Project said that next Wednesday it will disclose a voicemail from an agent heading the IG probe and email correspondence. Environmental groups oppose Keystone, which would bring oil sands thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/301915-group-state-dept-ig-is-probing-keystone-pipeline-review</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369460667472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 01:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369461957303-3</Id><Title>California’s Third Cap And Trade Auction Sells Out, At Record Price</Title><Msg>May 24, 2013 Silvio Marcacci Seems like someone forgot to tell California that cap and trade was dying an untimely death. The state’s third carbon allowance auction was held last week, and businesses snapped up all available 2013 permits, setting a record price level in the process. In addition to the 2013 permits, over three-quarters of advance allowances for 2016 were sold to businesses. With just over six months left until California links up to Quebec’s cap and trade market through the Western Climate Initiative, the system’s growing strength is apparent and stands as yet another example of how the EU Emissions Trading System’s collapse isn’t the end of cap and trade. Permits Selling Out, For Record Prices The May 16 auction was California’s third, and sold more than 14.5 million allowances for $14 per ton. Permit prices have continued their brisk rise, increasing from $10.09 in the first auction held November 2012 to $13.62 in the second auction held in February 2013. Every auction held to date has sold out of all current allowances offered. While the price for advance allocations covering emissions in 2016 held steady at the market floor price of $10.71 per ton compared to those sold in February, the volume dramatically increased compared to previous auctions. The system has never sold more than half of its advance allocations. Following the auction, California allowances were trading up at $14.50 on the IntercontinentalExchange secondary market. Roughly 50 million allowances have now been sold through the auctions, raising $256 million for clean energy investments in California, and $556 million for the state’s largest utilities to protect ratepayers from energy bill price hikes. Keep Directing Revenue Toward Clean Energy However, California’s market revenue has become controversial in recent weeks, perhaps a victim of its own success. Governor Jerry cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/05/24/californias-cap-and-trade-system-keeps-getting-stronger/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369461957303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 02:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369464165653-4</Id><Title>Bobby Likis: Use ethanol to meet clean air standards</Title><Msg>By Bobby Likis May 24, 2013 On May 13 your editorial called for Gov. Rick Scott to sign HB4001, removing ethanol from the Renewable Fuel Standards. Many of the points on which you based your opinion are wrong. The governor should veto this jobs and investment-killing bill. For 42 years, I've operated Car Clinic Service. Mine was the first Bosch Authorized Service Center in Florida. We take engine care very seriously. The governor has said that Florida must be "Open for business." The stability of public policy is essential for investors. And, locally produced ethanol, in Florida, has nothing to do with corn, as your editorial suggested. Your editorial suggested that ethanol damages engines, but here are the facts: of the 175,000 cars and small trucks that we have serviced in 42 years, not one engine has been damaged by ethanol. When it comes to the fuel line and primer, ethanol is no worse than gasoline when proper storage guidelines are followed. Your editorial said that ethanol harms boat engines, but industry leader Mercury Marine says that ethanol may help maintain drier fuel tanks. The fact is that heat and oil contamination do more damage to injector seals. For the last 35 years, carmakers have designed their fuel systems to use E10. It makes no sense that after all this time ethanol is now a problem. Dr. Andrew Randall, engine technical director with Earnhardt Childress Racing, leads a team of 130 engine builders, who make 650 NASCAR engines annually. He says E30 can be used in today's engines. We know the oil companies are not about to give up their monopoly. Today people can buy pure gas in nearly every community. They pay more. Removing ethanol from the RFS does nothing. Except that ethanol, unlike gasoline, provides high octane in a clean-air form. The issues linked to ethanol-laced fuel are that ethanol is used to replace the MTBE octane additive that was found to sun-sentinelDOTcom/news/opinion/fl-readers-view-ethanol-20130524,0,6754922.story</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369464165653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 02:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369486551716-5</Id><Title>Moniz: ‘This is the crucial decade’ to develop renewable energy VIDEO</Title><Msg>Moniz: ‘This is the crucial decade’ to develop renewable energy VIDEO Posted on May 24, 2013 at 12:06 pm by Simone Sebastian Newly appointed Energy Secretary Ernest Moniz credits natural gas for helping the United States lower carbon dioxide emissions in recent years, characterizing the energy revolution as a gift to the country. “This natural gas boom,” he said, ” is a boon. “ Moniz delivered his thoughts during a town hall meeting with Energy Department employees this week. He was sworn in as energy secretary on Tuesday. Calling the nation’s natural gas revolution “remarkable,” Moniz warned that it shouldn’t’ be taken for granted. Though it produces lower carbon emissions than other fossil fuels, it should be viewed as a bridge to a more renewable energy-driven economy, Moniz said. “ Buying time is not very useful if you don’t use the time,” he said, noting that the nation should focus on developing and lowering the cost renewable energy technologies. “What does using the time mean? It means pushing hard on the renewable technologies,” Moniz added. “This is the time to get those ready for the market place on a big scale. This is the decade, the crucial decade, for us to accomplish that.” Despite its recent struggles, solar energy has a bright future, Moniz said. It emerged as the fastest-growing renewable energy in Texas last year. “I’m very bullish,” he siad. “It’s going to be a lot bigger than most people think, sooner than they think.” He also expressed optimism about about the potential of offshore wind, geothermal and hydropower. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/24/moniz-this-is-the-crucial-decade-to-develop-renewable-energy/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369486551716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 08:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369486808404-6</Id><Title>Railroad Commission approves well integrity rules</Title><Msg>May 24, 2013 at 3:41 pm by Jeannie Kever The Texas Railroad Commission adopted long-awaited changes to its rules for the construction of oil and gas wells Friday, saying its actions showed the value of allowing the state to regulate the industry. The changes clarify standards for drilling, casing and cementing of wells and require that the commission be notified of any failed pressure test. The new rules take effect Jan. 1. The unanimous vote came as legislators consider whether the agency, which regulates oil and gas drilling and production in Texas, should be disbanded after efforts to institute recommendations made by the Sunset Advisory Commission failed to win approval in the House of Representatives. The proposals approved Friday, amendments to a section of the state’s regulations known as Rule 13, had been under discussion for months. Commission Chairman Barry Smitherman suggested the effort “illustrates the importance of allowing state regulators, not the federal government, to regulate our booming oil and gas industry.” The new rules were praised by the Texas Oil &amp; Gas Association, which represents the industry. “As technology used in oil and natural gas production evolves and improves, the Texas Railroad Commission is wise to examine rules related to well integrity,” Deb Hastings, executive vice president of the association said in a statement. “Through the Railroad Commission’s leadership, Texas is once again setting the national standard in crafting energy policy for the 21st century.” Unlikely alliance: Political foes plea for more time on federal fracturing rule Environmentalists have been watching, too. “I think generally, we’re pleased,” Cyrus Reed, conservation director for the Lone Star chapter of the Sierra Club, said after the approval. He said he was disappointed that some technical specifications had been changed from the commission’s original fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/24/railroad-commission-approves-well-integrity-rules/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369486808404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 09:00:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369487926835-7</Id><Title>Carbon Tax Good For Climate And Economy, Says US Congressional Budget Office</Title><Msg>May 25 2013 Guest Contributor The US Congressional Budget Office has completed its study of impact of carbon tax on the US economy. The CBO was given the tax to assess the impact of carbon tax on fossil fuels on the US economy and the country’s greenhouse gas emissions. In its second report on the subject, the CBO has given elaborate description of what a possible carbon tax regime could look like. The report seems extremely balanced as it elaborates the findings one step at a time without jumping to conclusions. One of the significant findings of the report is that while the share of US’ greenhouse gas emissions in the world would reduce to 15% from the current levels of 18%, it is important that efforts are made to reduce them. It says that it is important to do so to prevent “potentially catastrophic damage.” As mentioned in an earlier report, the CBO estimates that a $20 per tonne tax on carbon dioxide emissions would yield revenue of $1.3 trillion over a period of 10 years. The emissions would also reduce by 8% during this period. The report states that levying a carbon tax would certainly have an impact on the consumer prices which may have a cascading effect on the overall national economic growth. However, this damage can be countered by using the carbon tax revenue to a) reduce the fiscal deficit and b) reduce income tax and other taxes to support businesses and consumers. Thus, a revenue-neutral carbon tax may prove beneficial to the environment as well as the economy. Next, the CBO has stated the possible points of implementation of carbon tax on fossil fuels – coal, oil and natural gas. It has been suggested the miners and well operators or the electricity generators can be placed under the carbon tax regime. This procedure would be convenient as reporting and monitoring process is well established at these points. The report itself is cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/05/25/carbon-tax-good-for-climate-and-economy-says-us-congressional-budget-office/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369487926835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 09:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369490258898-8</Id><Title>SaskPower set to start testing world’s first carbon-capture facility</Title><Msg>SaskPower set to start testing world’s first carbon-capture facility</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369490258898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 09:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369492464233-9</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOULD BE IMPEACHED !!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>candoit_y</Username><Timestamp>1369315895927</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what #$%$ hole would give this thumbs down and yet be on the Mobile Site? That in itself is an oxymoron.</Msg><Username>presidentobama2013</Username><Timestamp>1369492464233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 10:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369514975171-10</Id><Title>McCain is an open border socialist</Title><Msg>McCain's vision of a world without borders offering an endless supply of slave labor for Wall Street while bleeding American taxpayers is happening fast.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1369514975171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 16:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369515690160-11</Id><Title>USAA insurance running a scam. If your house burns they don't pay you on the spot (full payment option). They force you to rebuild and use their low bid and then nickel and dime you to death. Switch to a full payment up front company! not the same co. 20 years ago switch to Chubb, etc. USAA and Robles== RICO at its finest what a scam</Title><Msg>what a scam</Msg><Username>thebottomlime</Username><Timestamp>1369515690160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 17:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369524613139-12</Id><Topic><Title>McCain is an open border socialist</Title><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1369514975171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 16:49:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and Obama, Reid, Pelosi et. all are any different on this issue? Are you a Democrat trying to divert attention away from the Democrats who are enacting open border legislation and executive orders?</Msg><Username>mp15shoot</Username><Timestamp>1369524613139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 19:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369534006842-13</Id><Topic><Title>USAA insurance running a scam. If your house burns they don't pay you on the spot (full payment option). They force you to rebuild and use their low bid and then nickel and dime you to death. Switch to a full payment up front company! not the same co. 20 years ago switch to Chubb, etc. USAA and Robles== RICO at its finest what a scam</Title><Username>thebottomlime</Username><Timestamp>1369515690160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 17:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What Insurance Firm do you work for? Or said differently, what's your problem with USAA? This is the XOM Board, not a Chubb promotion clinic. USAA is undoubtedly the BEST Insurance Company in USA. For your Home, Auto, etc.</Msg><Username>calif_orniakid</Username><Timestamp>1369534006842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 22:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>