<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373028908576-1</Id><Topic><Title>War on Fossil Fuels Bond Purchase...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372171614589</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:46:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PURCHASE: German 30 Year Bonds at 2.51% ytm, allocation 8.25% Allocations: 89.75% German Residential Real Estate {Berlin, Munich, Stuttgart, Frankfurt, Ruhr, Ludwigshafen} 8.25% German 30 Year Bonds 2.00% euro cash and German t-bills</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373028908576</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 08:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373032278309-2</Id><Topic><Title>War on Fossil Fuels Bond Purchase...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372171614589</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:46:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold 30 years at 2.495% ytm... change in price +0.30%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373032278309</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373032747382-3</Id><Title>Sumitomo Electric to Supply Hokkaido Battery System, Nikkei Says</Title><Msg>Sumitomo Electric to Supply Hokkaido Battery System, Nikkei Says 4 July 2013 July 5 (Bloomberg) — Sumitomo Electric Industries Ltd. will supply a storage battery system for Hokkaido Electric Power Co., the Nikkei newspaper reported today without saying where it got the information. The company’s system, which will have 60 megawatt hours of storage capacity, will be set up at a substation to expand the utility’s grid capacity, according to the paper. Mitsuyo Tsuruta, a Sumitomo Electric spokeswoman, declined to comment, saying that the Osaka-based company isn’t the source of the information. The Ministry of Economy, Trade and Industry said in April that it will set up a storage system after the utility received applications for large-scale solar projects that would exceed the grid’s capacity. bnef</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373032747382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:59:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373037587270-4</Id><Topic><Title>Keep an eye on XOM</Title><Username>hpwamrs</Username><Timestamp>1372966738962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:38:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xom is going to do what xom wants to do.I have had this stock for 20 years</Msg><Username>billybob4480</Username><Timestamp>1373037587270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373048708841-5</Id><Title>Europe should head to the woods for biofuels, report says</Title><Msg>Europe should head to the woods for biofuels, report says July 5, 2013 at 10:16 am by Emily Pickrell In the European Union’s quest to reach 20 percent renewables by 2020, it should avoid the temptation to latch on to ethanol and other biofuels that drain scarce land and water resources, according to a government report issued Wednesday by the European Environment Agency. “Biomass from waste and residues from agriculture and forestry offer high resource efficiency whereas the environmental benefits from cultivating crops for bioenergy (‘energy cropping’) are often limited,” the report wrote. IEA: Renewables will surpass natural gas for power generation by 2016 Europe’s renewable targets were established in its 2009 Renewable Energy Directive, which also included a 10 percent target for transportation fuel. And while solar and wind energy have scaled up throughout Europe, reaching that 10 percent biofuel goal will be challenging, especially if ethanol is largely excluded from the mix. European consumption of ethanol grew from 2,000 barrels per day in 2001 to nearly 90,000 barrels per day in 2012, according to IndexMundi, a commodities website. But using corn-based ethanol to meet the biofuel target is being questioned, with critics saying the environment could be worse for the move. “While some bioenergy sources and technologies offer significant advantages over fossil fuel-based systems, others lead to environmental concerns,” the report said. “This is particularly the case where bioenergy involves using agricultural land to cultivate energy crops, since it often results in changes to land use, including expanding or intensifying agriculture at other locations.” Biomass: In 1776, energy was rooted in wood The issue echoes domestic debates over ethanol, with critics arguing that the benefits of ethanol are outweighed by the demands made on scare natural resources, especially water. The Energy Independence and Security Act of 2007 required re</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373048708841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:25:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373051118222-6</Id><Topic><Title>Bluecheese: All his posts are "absolutely worthless" !</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371752941651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Name one that's not basically worthless. All he does is copy &amp; paste info available to anyone.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373051118222</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:05:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373062785202-7</Id><Title>Calls Grow for EPA to Implement Tailpipe Emissions Rules</Title><Msg>Calls Grow for EPA to Implement Tailpipe Emissions Rules By Pat Bradley Enlarge image Credit Jensbn/Wikimedia Commons Public Domain The call is becoming stronger for the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency to adopt a proposed rule to tighten emissions from motor vehicles. The proposed Tier 3 Standards would set new emissions standards for passenger cars, light duty trucks and some medium and heavy duty vehicles beginning in 2017. Tailpipe standards limiting nitrogen oxides, volatile organic compounds, known as VOCs, and soot would be phased in through 2025. Sulfur limits would be effective in 2017. A coalition of fifteen states and cities, including Vermont, is calling on the Environmental Protection Agency to adopt the rule swiftly. Vermont Assistant Attorney General Thea Schwartz notes that it’s estimated that under the new guidelines smog emissions will be reduced by 80-percent and soot by 70-percent. The American Lung Association is also advocating for implementation of the rule. During a recent conference call, association Senior Vice President Paul Billings noted that nine health and medical groups submitted comments in support of the new rule, along with major environmental and consumer advocates, and state and local pollution control officials. Billings calculates that over 275-thousand comments in support were filed, from a diversity of interests including organized labor and major auto makers. Mayor Michael Bissonette of Chicopee, Massachusetts joined the Lung Association in it’s call for action on the Tier 3 rule, saying the standards will make existing cars cleaner and will push automakers to develop cleaner vehicles and will help communities achieve national air quality standards. Mayor Bissonette is Vice Chairman of the U.S. Conference of Mayors Standing Committee on the Environment and explained that a resolution was adopted by the entire body of the conference in support of implementing the new standards. American Academy</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373062785202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 18:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>