<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-01"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367389298117-1</Id><Title>buy bac standing ovation goog sucks bk in 10 years</Title><Msg>sad for goog back to 100 forxom</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1367389298117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 02:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367400733468-2</Id><Topic><Title>maxidopey</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1367310662866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 04:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is hiding in a ge cardboard box in a swamp some where.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1367400733468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 05:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367412660257-3</Id><Topic><Title>Executive Order on C02...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367239006530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 08:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very sloppy work… The objection to C02 is not as a health risk, but as a greenhouse gas. You make up an assumption to advance irrelevant points. One source on oil pollution is PETROLEUM MICROBIOLOGY: Concepts, Environmental Implications, Industrial Applications, 2008 There’s air pollution and water pollution for all the other fossil fuels too which impact on healthcare costs in many ways. The solution is to eliminate them as Germany is doing. Electric is development now, too in the same manner as the Tupolev design bureau or Lockheed might have been given an order for some new aircraft or missile… We’re better than them, though. ..... I don't consider the Southern European problem very vexing now. Their unemployment rate is quite high, and their welfare systems are being thoroughly gutted. That's survival of the fittest at its best... We're more than rich enough to toss them crumbs to keep them from totally self-destructing, while they are purified. When that is complete Europe will be like a compressed spring being released.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367412660257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367412695675-4</Id><Topic><Title>Executive Order on C02...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367239006530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 08:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**Electric car is development now</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1367412695675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367412723930-5</Id><Topic><Title>Good time oil bulls for much higher prices. Bullish on oil. 5.00/gal gas no big deal.</Title><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1367375014394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 22:23:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely bullish on oil too. Even though everyone is looking at alternative fuels these days, oil will still be around for quite some time longer.</Msg><Username>timothy_iacono</Username><Timestamp>1367412723930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367414388579-6</Id><Title>Renville Co., Minn., could host first major project to use wind power to produce hydrogen</Title><Msg>Monday, April 29, 2013 - 11:11pm Tom ChervenyWest Central Tribune BIRD ISLAND — Renville County could become host to the first large-scale commercial project to produce hydrogen from wind in the U.S. Norfolk Wind Energy of Bird Island and Emerald H2 of Minneapolis entered into an agreement to develop the project, the companies announced Monday. Norfolk Wind Energy is a community wind project of farmers and landowners in the area south of Bird Island. They are seeking to erect wind turbines with a capacity to produce 40 megawatts of electricity, with the opportunity to eventually expand to 100 megawatts, according to Dave Scheibel of Bird Island, its founder and president. Emerald H2 of Minneapolis holds rights to a technology that is believed to be more efficient at using electricity to produce hydrogen from water than systems now in use, according to Scheibel. Norfolk Wind would use electricity generated by the wind during periods of time where there is low electrical demand to produce hydrogen, said Scheibel. Electricity produced during other periods would be transmitted to the grid and sold to a utility customer. The proposed project would be the first to demonstrate whether hydrogen can be produced from wind-produced electricity on a large scale. The proposed project would include a capacity for using 10 megawatts of wind-generated electricity to produce 500,000 kilograms of hydrogen. Emerald H2 and Norfolk Wind are currently in discussions with a distributor to sell the hydrogen to industrial customers within a 100- to 150-mile radius of Bird Island. Hydrogen is used in a wide range of industrial applications, from oil refining and altering stainless steel to producing polymers, solvents and even the fats for margarine. If this proves viable, Scheibel said the hope here is to eventually use the hydrogen to make anhydrous ammonia. In effect, wctribDOTcom/content/renville-co-minn-could-host-first-major-project-use-wind-power-produce-hydrogen</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367414388579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367422491397-7</Id><Title>★★★★CUT all STOCKS in half..that's what they're worth boys ! Just like housing.........</Title><Msg>STRONG SELL to all.....</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1367422491397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367422587434-8</Id><Title>★★★★LOW BARS+ BERNANKE's "experiment" powering MKTs..Pisanti is a freaking BROKER !</Title><Msg>really !</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1367422587434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:36:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367423554051-9</Id><Title>★★★★LOOK !!!....it's 1929 all over AGAIN !!</Title><Msg>identical set-up</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1367423554051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367424845080-10</Id><Title>Need investment advice.</Title><Msg>I turned 65 yesterday. I also retired yesterday from panhandling after doing that for 43 years. I have lived very modestly over the last 43 years and have about $50,000,000 saved in the bank from panhandling. I was thinking about buying some shares of XOM. (about 10,000 shares). I think it may be around $100 by the end of the year. What do you think?</Msg><Username>panhandler_jim</Username><Timestamp>1367424845080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:14:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367430146429-11</Id><Title>Mommy....</Title><Msg>Why did big oil kill America?</Msg><Username>bdatri49</Username><Timestamp>1367430146429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367431290437-12</Id><Title>Moody's: Modest amount of controversial natural gas exports will get approval</Title><Msg>Zack Colman - 05/01/13 12:05 PM ET The Obama administration will likely approve a limited number of politically controversial natural gas export projects despite some fears on Capitol Hill about a massive expansion, according to a Moody's report released Wednesday. It said the Energy Department (DOE) would likely approve three out of the 20 applications under review for exporting natural gas to nations that lack a free-trade agreement with the United States. One such application already has received the go-ahead from the DOE. Those projects have alarmed some lawmakers, who are tussling over whether to allow a major expansion of natural gas exports. The DOE must determine deals to non-free trade countries are in the national interest under federal law, meaning they must clear a more stringent standard than contracts with free-trade nations. Given the process at the DOE and the time it takes to build export facilities, Moody's said the United States won't be a major player in the international market until 2020. Republicans and some Democrats want to send more natural gas to non-free trade nations, arguing doing so would add jobs and generate revenues. But several Democrats worry that too rapid an increase would drive domestic energy prices upward. The report comes as House lawmakers are preparing to dive into the geopolitical implications of exporting natural gas. The Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee will also hold a series of natural gas “roundtables” this month, one of which will focus on exports. A bulk of the liquefied natural gas shipped from the United States will likely head to Asia and will help other nations secure lower-cost contracts, Moody's said. While the United States doesn’t figure to become a player in the global natural gas trade until the next decade, its expected emergence already is having an impact, the thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/297205-moodys-us-natural-gas-exports-would-benefit-asia-europe</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367431290437</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367434015953-13</Id><Title>how is XOM situated to profit on nat gas?</Title><Msg>xx</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1367434015953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367435395384-14</Id><Topic><Title>Need investment advice.</Title><Username>panhandler_jim</Username><Timestamp>1367424845080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:14:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forget about stock. Write a book on your approach to panhandlng. I'll buy the first copy.</Msg><Username>ploddingalong98</Username><Timestamp>1367435395384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367436638069-15</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>Stock continues its awful performance in rising and falling markets. Five solid years of underperformance since Rex Tillerson took over. Between consistent production shortfalls, the idiotic XTO acquisition, and earnings misses there is no doubt that he is the most incompetent CEO of a major oil company ever.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1367436638069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367439997435-16</Id><Topic><Title>how is XOM situated to profit on nat gas?</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1367434015953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:46:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XOM isn't.</Msg><Username>andrew_w_smith</Username><Timestamp>1367439997435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367442795275-17</Id><Topic><Title>Need investment advice.</Title><Username>panhandler_jim</Username><Timestamp>1367424845080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 12:14:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your advice is get your money out of the bank buy a defensible farm, guns, ammo and advertise for a harem.</Msg><Username>alsharpton2</Username><Timestamp>1367442795275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367447691069-18</Id><Title>Questions</Title><Msg>I would like to address some serious questions to anyone on this board who is not a spammer, politico, or (lame) comedian. 1. Given that Exxon stock has not gone up over the last 4 to 5 years while the Dow is up thousands of points (look at a 6 month, 1, 2, or 5 year chart vs the Dow or S&amp;P you may be surprised) do you think that if you performed as poorly for your employer as Rex Tillerson has for Exxon shareholders that you would still have a job? 2. What is the role of the "independent" board of directors? Is it just to collect their pay and ignore the awful stock performance, the XTO disaster, the production shortfalls, the earnings misses etc ? 3. Are all the large mutual fund holders just passive index funds with no input? One final comment, I don't object to Rex Tillerson's pay because running Exxon is a massive job. I just object to the fact that he has done such an abysmal job and seems so woefully incompetent, He may have been a great petroleum engineer but he has been a pathetic CEO at least according to stock investors. SERIOUS replies appreciated!</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1367447691069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367450472400-19</Id><Topic><Title>Questions</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1367447691069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:34:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the massive amount of cap ex is holding the stock back.</Msg><Username>m1975johnson1975</Username><Timestamp>1367450472400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 19:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367450529719-20</Id><Topic><Title>Is this True: Rush Near Death Due to...</Title><Username>dubyuhandfansareevil</Username><Timestamp>1367373143835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 21:52:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Few people are as qualified as you for the moron designation.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1367450529719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 19:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367451698591-21</Id><Topic><Title>Questions</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1367447691069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:34:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your mention of XTO as a mistake is mis-guided, to say the least. I will give you this: There are many who would disagree with me but, they are all on this stupid chatboard with the other "low information" posters who only skim the reality of current events and then shoot off their mouth without a modicum of knowledge.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1367451698591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 19:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367452850593-22</Id><Topic><Title>how is XOM situated to profit on nat gas?</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1367434015953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:46:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wrong dip sh-t! They own more than anybody else on the planet.</Msg><Username>rallen_46038</Username><Timestamp>1367452850593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 20:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367454262793-23</Id><Topic><Title>★★★★LOOK !!!....it's 1929 all over AGAIN !!</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1367423554051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:52:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it's Jimmy Carter all over again but still not as bad until interest rates hit 20%.</Msg><Username>onions2089</Username><Timestamp>1367454262793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 20:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367455346167-24</Id><Topic><Title>Questions</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1367447691069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:34:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The XTO acquisition is not a mistake because of my opinion or the opinions of others on the message boards. It has been judged a huge mistake by the market as the stock has very badly underperformed since the acquisitions. Analysts may frequently be wrong but in this case the market has agreed with the near universal criticism of this acquisition.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1367455346167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 20:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367455619483-25</Id><Topic><Title>Questions</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1367447691069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:34:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree that XOM has large capex. The problem is not the amount of capex, its the results- consistently falling production despite the huge capex. Finding oil is a dirty, difficult, expensive job that I know nothing about. However, Mr. Tillerson is paid tens of millions of dollars to run Exxon that includes increasing production. It's his job. The failure is his.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1367455619483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 20:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367456572950-26</Id><Topic><Title>Questions</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1367447691069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:34:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A lot of the production shortfall is from dry nat gas North America. They are choosing to not produce as much as they could because of low prices. In the long run it should be the right decision. IMO, as long as they can keep up the big share buybacks, XOM stock should break out to all time highs. Gonna depend on capex and how the restructuring goes.</Msg><Username>m1975johnson1975</Username><Timestamp>1367456572950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 21:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367463100820-27</Id><Title>The Commodity Boom Is Over</Title><Msg>In China the investment share of GDP stands at 48%, 12% higher than any other industrializing country in the past. While many point to such high numbers as proof that the commodity boom will last forever, the truth of the matter is that such growth is unsustainable. Below is a chart from Credit Suisse that shows us Japan and Korea when they went through a similar investment expansion boom. If history is any guide, what is clear from the above chart is that sooner or later (I think sooner), China's investment boom has only one way to go and that is down -- for many years to come. And while many might say China is a unique situation and things are different this time, my take is that there are limits to how long you can defy gravity. A China slowdown will affect the commodities space across the board. Both commodities and commodity producing stocks will be affected. Another interesting chart is Australia's capex to GDP. What this chart basically means is that many companies have purchased and or invested very large sums of money on capital expenditures. So what might this mean for many mining companies, if commodity prices were to correct substantially over the next several years? The answer is that the money they spent on capital expenditures will not have the desired effect and most likely their stocks will lose in value or underperform. Remember markets are forward looking. Even if demand for many commodities is still strong today, stocks look forward and try to discount what demand and corporate profits will be in the future. Two very big mining companies that come to mind are BHP Billiton (BHP) and Rio Tinto (RIO). And if one looks at their charts below, it is evident that they have been underperforming for two years now. Another company that comes to mind is Caterpillar (CAT). As fellow S.A. Contributor Sneha Shah recently pointed out, the company reported another bad quarter. While Caterpillar management initially gave guidance of $7-9 in earnings for 2013 during its Q412 earnings call, now management has revised down its guidance saying that it will only make $7 in earnings for 2013. That's a very big downward revision if you ask me. She also points to the fact that the biggest hit to earnings so far is the mining sector, where orders have declined by almost 50% year on year. Given the over-spending in the mining sector over the last several years (as per the capex/GDP chart of Australia), I think mining orders for Caterpillar equipment will continue to fall for longer than most people imagine.</Msg><Username>jpmhedgefund</Username><Timestamp>1367463100820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367463189364-28</Id><Topic><Title>^^^CHINESE PMI falls to 50.6...barely hanging on before contraction!^^^.</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1367371461806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 21:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oups!!!</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1367463189364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>