<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370787938403-1</Id><Title>War on Fossil Fuels: campaign to integrate of Eastern Europe into the Germanic/EU market</Title><Msg>The theft of land by the former communist regimes of Eastern Europe is being undone. The process has taken quite some time because of the complex legal issues involved. The countries concerned have found close cooperation with Germany quite favorable to their interests too. Cooperation brings with it effectively unlimited capital, excellent administrative and legal resources, and the world’s best technology. Land is an important factor of renewable energy production of course, and matching of very cheap land with technology and capital will bring forth much new supply. Enormous tracts of land are available for wind &amp; solar power and bio-fuels production now that the communists are gone. With the accession of the countries to the EU the land will be put to work as the technology improves, driven forward by the German government-industrial alliance. The development of Eastern Europe's renewable energy production potential will not be favorable to the interests of the fossil fuel industry. The supply, and especial bio-fuels supplies, will simply displace demand that formerly went to Big Oil.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1370787938403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:25:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370792271864-2</Id><Title>Exxon positives</Title><Msg>Here are just a few positives: •Profit margin of 10.86% •ROE of 28.26% •Enormous operating cash flow of $50.48 billion •Dividend yield of 2.80% •Superb historical stock performance •Quality debt management •Unfathomable profits •Excellent capital allocation •Analysts love the stock: 7 Buy, 16 Hold, 1 Sell •Trading at only 9 times earnings •Resiliency in bear markets •Superior technology and planning compared to peers •Increasing international demand thanks to emerging markets •Developed largest natural gas field in the world •89% of employees approve of CEO Rex W. Tillerson Nice!!!</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1370792271864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370798162113-3</Id><Title>Obummer presidency unraveling daily......I LOVE IT !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>FYI...</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370798162113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370803760206-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer presidency unraveling daily......I LOVE IT !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370798162113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:16:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It couldn't have happened to a more evil man.</Msg><Username>iitriumvirate</Username><Timestamp>1370803760206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 14:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370820535898-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer presidency unraveling daily......I LOVE IT !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370798162113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:16:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought Romney won?? Fox news and rove said landslide?? #$%$ Morris said Romney Fox news lied--NO WAY--you LIE --the next thing you will tell me is saddam had nothing to do with 9/11</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1370820535898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:28:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370820908317-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer presidency unraveling daily......I LOVE IT !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370798162113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:16:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>grasping for straws little man ???</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370820908317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370821613927-7</Id><Title>The King's of useless info:</Title><Msg>bluecheese and hansesteelyard.............what's the devil is your point ? Any fool can copy and paste. Please go away until you have something useful to say.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370821613927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370822089979-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer presidency unraveling daily......I LOVE IT !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370798162113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:16:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try this: freedomoutpostDOTcom/2013/06/bombshell-document-examiner-tied-to-obama-defense-attorney-says-birth-certificate-is-100-fraud/</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1370822089979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370822380211-9</Id><Title>Two Senate Panels Compete for Control Over Ethanol Mandate</Title><Msg>Amy Harder National Journal – 8 hrs ago Two Senate committees are wrestling over a critical energy policy that influences prices of both fuel and food: the renewable-fuels standard that mandates an increasing amount of biofuels—mostly corn-based ethanol—to be blended with gasoline each year. The two panels that set energy and environment policy both want jurisdiction over the mandate, which has come under intense scrutiny from both parties in the past year. The standard is administered by the Environmental Protection Agency, which is squarely in the wheelhouse of the Environment and Public Works Committee. That puts the burden on the backs of Energy and Natural Resources Committee leaders to argue why they should have top billing on the issue. “We obviously feel we do,” said Energy and Natural Resources Chairman Ron Wyden, D-Ore., regarding which committee has primary jurisdiction over the renewable-fuels standard, or RFS. The mandate was created by a 2005 energy bill and expanded under another measure in 2007. The Energy and Natural Resources Committee has primary jurisdiction over issues involved with both those laws. Wyden also noted that the RFS involves fuel, a primary focus of his committee. “That’s the operative word,” Wyden said, adding that he wants to talk to his colleagues, including Energy and Natural Resources ranking member Lisa Murkowski, R-Alaska, and Environment and Public Works Chairwoman Barbara Boxer, D-Calif., before commenting more on the issue. Murkowski and Wyden seem to be on the same page. “When you think about the initiatives that we have identified as priorities, one of them is how we can consume less, and the RFS allows us to be consuming less when it comes to our oil,” Murkowski said. When asked which committee has primary jurisdiction over the mandate, Murkowski smiled. “Of course, that’s the great debate,” she said. “There newsDOTyahooDOTcom/two-senate-panels-compete-control-over-ethanol-mandate-144600286.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370822380211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370822949515-10</Id><Title>NSA whistleblower is a hero ------ kudos to him !!!</Title><Msg>YESSSSSS</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370822949515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370825299156-11</Id><Topic><Title>NSA whistleblower is a hero ------ kudos to him !!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370822949515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow--he told --AGAIN--something that was passed into law by W and GOP congress--they called the "patriot act"--thanks for the heads up W lied about WMDs and used our military to OCCUPY other nations--another whistle blown there are no "death panels" in healthcare--another whistle blown "Mission Accomplished"--not even close--another whistle blown No Child Left Behind--a national disaster--another whistle blown Lance Armstrong used taxpayer dollars to purchase HGH--another whistle blown KUDOS to me</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1370825299156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:48:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370825703658-12</Id><Topic><Title>NSA whistleblower is a hero ------ kudos to him !!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370822949515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush did it to PROTECT American Citizens ----OBUMMER extented and EXPANDED it hunt down and SPY on American Citizens---namely his political enemies-----HUGE HUGE HUGE DIFFERENCE----which, i know is lost on sheeple like you.</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370825703658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>