<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-21"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361423205820-1</Id><Title>O'Malley's offshore wind bill advances in House</Title><Msg>O'Malley's offshore wind bill advances in House Comments By Michael Dresser, The Baltimore Sun 12:34 p.m. EST, February 20, 2013 Moving Gov. Martin O’Malley one step closer to a long-sought victory, the House of Delegates gave preliminary approval Wednesday to legislation intended to foster development of an offshore wind industry off Ocean City. The legislation advanced after delegates decisively rejected a flurry of amendments by Republican opponents of the measure, who objected to subsidizing the emerging industry. O’Malley contend the measure would help diversify Maryland’s electricity supply, promote the use of renewable energy and create jobs. The bill, which is expected to pass this year after two years in which it failed, could receive final approval in the House by the end of the week. A companion bill is still making its way through the Senate. baltimoresunDOTcom/news/maryland/politics/blog/bal-omalleys-offshore-wind-bill-advances-in-house-20130220,0,1822386DOTstory</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361423205820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 00:06:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361450704539-2</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report, thanks!</Msg><Username>reeves.cliff</Username><Timestamp>1361450704539</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:45:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361453738504-3</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful report, thanks</Msg><Username>winfreymark364</Username><Timestamp>1361453738504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:35:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361453768373-4</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful report, thanks</Msg><Username>winfreymark364</Username><Timestamp>1361453768373</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:36:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361455789052-5</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>adorable post, thanks!</Msg><Username>jonesherman118</Username><Timestamp>1361455789052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:09:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361455809090-6</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>adorable post, thanks!</Msg><Username>jonesherman118</Username><Timestamp>1361455809090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:10:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361456854421-7</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361365719176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:08:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold all £ for € @1.1572 €/£ £ basis 1.1585 €/£ (0.8632 £/€). Loss on £: -0.11% gain on bond 0.222%*0.50 = +0.111% ..... net chance in £/gilt trade: 0%... 100% € (German deposit)</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361456854421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:27:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361457376553-8</Id><Title>Federal Reserve: worried about losses on bond buying...</Title><Msg>I mentioned in previous posts they were losing money buying bonds now that the bond market has moved against them, and what is worse they have been using borrowed money from their member banks to do it. They have not been "printing" money to pay for the bonds, hence the concern about the losses. If they did print money it would cause the bonds to fall in price even more and that would not help their problem. In other words their strategy is a failure. The length of time they will be able to keep up their buying and losses is limited too. The stock market will not be pleased when the party ends.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361457376553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:36:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361457795980-9</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report</Msg><Username>davidscott440</Username><Timestamp>1361457795980</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:43:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361457814109-10</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report</Msg><Username>davidscott440</Username><Timestamp>1361457814109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:43:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361458135448-11</Id><Title>PG&amp;E swings to loss, hurt by blast-related costs</Title><Msg>PG&amp;E swings to loss, hurt by blast-related costs Feb. 21, 2013, 8:44 a.m. EST 0 Comments By Ben Fox PG&amp;E Corp. PCG -2.24% swung to a fourth-quarter loss, with the results being dragged down by a series of natural gas and environmental costs. For the new year, the gas-and-electricity utility predicted adjusted earnings of $2.55 to $2.75 a share, compared with estimates of $2.78 from analysts polled by Thomson Reuters. PG&amp;E, which serves central and northern California, has had its profits hampered by charges related to a fatal 2010 natural gas pipeline explosion in San Bruno, Calif. After a yearlong probe, federal investigators blamed PG&amp;E for the blast and concluded that pipeline defects that went unnoticed for decades caused the rupture. The investigators also found that the utility's poor record-keeping and inadequate attention to pipeline safety were contributing factors. The violations could result in billions of dollars in fines. In addition, more than 100 victims of the disaster have filed lawsuits against the company. Company executives said late last year they want to settle allegations over the pipeline explosion, although they declined to estimate the size of potential fines. PG&amp;E reported a loss of $13 million, or three cents a share, compared with a year-earlier profit of $83 million, or 20 cents. The latest period includes a handful of one-time items related to pipeline-related costs, penalties, third-party claims, and insurance recoveries, as well as environmental costs associated with historic operations at the natural gas compressor station in Hinkley, California. Excluding these items, earnings from operations fell to 59 cents from 89 cents. Analysts most recently forecast earnings of 59 cents. Shares closed Wednesday at $43.12 and were inactive premarket. The stock is up 7.6% over the past three months. marketwatchDOTcom/story/pge-swings-to-loss-hurt-by-blast-related-costs-2013-02-21</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361458135448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:48:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361458994882-12</Id><Title>Energy &amp; Gold price crash ahead...epic...</Title><Msg>There is simply no justification for the prices at all... Advanced energy technologies will bring down the price of oil, gas, coal, and power. The inability or lack of willpower on the part of American industry and energy companies to move forward is irrelevant. Europe has more than sufficient industrial and scientific muscle to develop and deploy the technologies. The market has been removed from the equation by the use of government to tax and control end market prices, and the inputs to produce the products most of which are human capital funded by government. Even within the old energy field like oil and gas costs are plummeting as supercomputers and other technologies lower costs. The thesis that central bank efforts to lower interest rates is inflationary is simply a wrong. They have not created money. They have borrowed money and bought long term bonds with it. There is a difference. While their campaign runs up the stock market and oil price as long as they can keep it up, it will go in the opposite direction as it unravels...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361458994882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:03:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361459568833-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361365719176</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:08:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold all € for £ @0.8664 £/€ € basis 0.8642 £/€ (1.1572 €/£) gain on €: +0.26% 100% £</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361459568833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:12:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361460638081-14</Id><Title>China On Track to Exceed Targets, Install 140 GW of Wind Capacity by 2015</Title><Msg>China On Track to Exceed Targets, Install 140 GW of Wind Capacity by 2015 GTM Research and Azure International release the Q4 update of the China Wind Market Quarterly report series. STAFF: FEBRUARY 15, 2013 The news cycle for China’s wind sector may finally have turned, according to the new China Wind Market Quarterly report by GTM Research and Azure International. The final month of 2012 and first weeks of 2013 brought a flurry of government announcements with major near-term implications. In December, the government took steps to resolve financing issues in the sector by redistributing surcharge revenues and pre-appropriating funds for 2013. And in January two separate announcements raised targets for wind and solar installations in 2013, setting an overall target of 49 gigawatts of renewable capacity additions in 2013, of which 18 gigawatts will be wind. The government appears to be back in the game of promoting the domestic renewable energy market, with government policy in China beginning to act as a counterweight to foreign forces that have hurt the wind and solar sectors. According to the new report, this implies that more announcements may be on the way for wind. One near-term possibility is improved financing. How will all the new solar be financed, given the problems distributing renewable surcharges? Most likely, the state banking sector will play a major role, and this could bring new cash to the balance sheets of Chinese wind firms -- which would in turn filter down to OEMs and component suppliers. FIGURE: China Installed Wind Capacity, 2004-2012, Forecast to 2020 Source: China Wind Market Quarterly: 4th Quarter 2012 “China’s wind industry retains its leadership position worldwide, whether looking at policy targets, overall installation numbers or innovation,” said Anders Hove, one of the report’s authors. “Fully understanding the world’s largest wind energy market requires an in-depth understanding of complex issues, and that’s why this report is timely. We need to understand the reasons for interconnection delays, develop an expectation for future curtailment, and look province by province at the cash flow issues created by slow disbursement of renewable energy surcharge funds.” Today, GTM Research and Azure International publish the second installment of their China Wind Market Quarterly report. This 90-page report provides the latest information on developments in China’s wind market as well as analysis of: Wind capacity by manufacturer Wind capacity by developer Wind capacity by geography Curtailed wind power in China by geography China’s wind policies Major wind company financial trends The report also contains comprehensive analyses of over ten major wind developers currently operating in China, including: Longyuan, Huaneng, Datang, Guodian, Shenhua and Huadian, among others. The China Wind Market Quarterly is the wind industry’s most in-depth and frequently updated resource, providing energy professionals with tactical and useful data and analysis of China’s wind market. To learn more about this greentechmediaDOTcom/articles/read/china-on-track-to-exceed-targets-install-140-gw-of-wind-capacity-by-2015</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361460638081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:30:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361463343426-15</Id><Title>on the subject of commodities oil,gold, fertilizer,food crops, metals etc.</Title><Msg>Sorry to insult your intelligence but to make a point, currently world governents none more so than USA are fighting to recover from recession and stop the economy descent. So how do they do this, one way is to pressure down commodity prices to stimulate industry oil being a prime example. For gold the government does not want it held too much in people vaults but their money invested to grow production and jobs. Now world governments (consumer;/producer/industrial), can "cartel" commodity prices for a whle until market forces make thier rebound/revert irresitable. Bottom line is momentum traders flee the short term but long term oil is going to rebound like a depressed spring. The pressure down of commodity prices is going to cause lack of new production and slower exploration and even shut in of non-conventional oil. all this means buying opportunity coming. on gold its being abandoned by the momentum/short term traders but comes back once the inflation the governments want return. jmho</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1361463343426</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:15:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361463659068-16</Id><Topic><Title>on the subject of commodities oil,gold, fertilizer,food crops, metals etc.</Title><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1361463343426</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:15:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Depression of price of oil by governments will ultimately lead to lack of effort/capital spending on new production especially new higher cost production. thinking buy opportunity coming/started. looking for massive rebound iin price of oil once economy rebounds. longer time horizon and oil stocks go much higher.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1361463659068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:20:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361465288019-17</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome!</Msg><Username>burnett_darren</Username><Timestamp>1361465288019</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:48:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361465307606-18</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome!</Msg><Username>burnett_darren</Username><Timestamp>1361465307606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:48:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361465377804-19</Id><Title>Currency Purchase</Title><Msg>sold all £ for € @1.1555 €/£ £ basis 1.1542 €/£ (0.8664 £/€). gain on £: +0.12% 100% €</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361465377804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:49:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361468765927-20</Id><Title>Top oil lobbyist: New climate bill will never reach Senate floor</Title><Msg>Top oil lobbyist: New climate bill will never reach Senate floor By Ben Geman - 02/21/13 11:05 AM ET The head of a powerful oil industry trade group predicts the Senate will shy away from debate on new Democratic legislation that imposes fees on carbon emissions from coal and petroleum. American Petroleum Institute CEO Jack Gerard said he did not expect the Senate to vote on the bill sponsored by Sens. Barbara Boxer (D-Calif.) and Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.). “I think no, it will not get to the floor, and I think the reason it won't get to the floor is the dynamics surrounding carbon has changed,” Gerard told E&amp;E TV. Boxer said she wants the bill to get a vote, but a spokesman for Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid (D-Nev.) was noncommittal last week. Gerard noted that the expansion of natural gas production, which is allowing gas to increasingly displace more carbon-heavy coal, has helped drive the recent reduction of U.S. carbon emissions without legislation. “The United States has done more than anybody else around the world to reduce their carbon emissions, and that is due largely to the increased use of clean burning natural gas,” Gerard said in the interview broadcast Wednesday. Climate legislation faces grim prospects in Congress. Green groups are pressing President Obama to take more aggressive steps using his executive powers, such as imposing carbon standards on existing power plants. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/284203-top-oil-lobbyist-new-climate-bill-will-never-reach-senate-floor</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361468765927</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:46:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361469757119-21</Id><Topic><Title>Top oil lobbyist: New climate bill will never reach Senate floor</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361468765927</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:46:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gas has worse climate footprint than coal Wednesday, February 13, 2013 By Renfrey Clarke As the fossil fuel lobby tells it, natural gas — in chemical terms, almost all methane — is clean and green. Burn it in a modern power plant, and per unit of electricity produced, only about half as much carbon dioxide is sent up the exhaust stack compared to good-quality coal. That’s like saying you’re making progress if you get off heroin onto amphetamines. Natural gas is still a fossil fuel. Even if the sums worked the way the gas corporations suggest, a wholesale switch to gas would put off climate disaster only by a few decades. In any case, the real sums are quite different. When you extract and burn natural gas, you never get to burn all of it. Some escapes, meaning that the gas-fired electricity you produce will almost always have a worse “climate footprint”, over the most relevant period, than if you were using coal. That statement would have seemed highly speculative just a few years ago. But methane has long been known to be a powerful greenhouse gas. Now, new studies are showing that in practical gasfield operations, far more methane reaches the atmosphere than the guesses of the energy corporations would suggest. The worst leakage, it used to be thought, occurred with so-called unconventional sources — coal seam gas and shale gas. But “fugitive emissions” from conventional gasfields, evidence now shows, can also be alarmingly high. And whatever the source of the methane leaks, recent research has substantially raised the estimate for their warming impact — to an astonishing 105 times the figure for carbon dioxide, measured over 20 years. Three field studies, reported over the past year, have exposed the claims of the gas industry that its product has a role to play in limiting climate change. All three of these studies use “top-down” methods to calculate methane leakage rates. Top-down methods sample methane concentrations in the air above gasfields, and use mathematical models to calculate the amount of methane that would need to have leaked to produce this effect. “Bottom-up” calculations, by contrast, examine the wells, valves and pipes, and try to total up the quantity of gas that is lost from them. Top-down methods are complex, but yield a fairly robust figure for the emitted methane. With bottom-up calculations, leaks are inevitably missed. Of course, not all the methane detected above gasfields results from extraction operations; some has come from sources such as wetlands or cattle and sheep. But by observing the ratio of different carbon isotopes found in the methane molecules, scientists can tell “new” methane from fossil methane that has been underground for millions of years. Colorado conventional In 2008, geochemist Gabrielle Pétron of the US National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) observed that methane readings in data from an observation tower north of Denver, Colorado, were markedly higher when the wind blew from the north-east — that is, from the direction of the Denver-Julesburg (conventional) oil and gas basin, with its more than 14,000 active gas and condensate wells. Years of complex work followed, culminating in February last year with the publication by Pétron and colleagues of a paper concluding that leakage from the field was probably around 4% of the gas produced, and perhaps significantly higher. That suggests leakage at least twice the rate earlier assumed. An October blog for the journal Nature explains: “Most estimates suggest that around 1-2% of the methane is lost… These [estimates] come from ‘bottom-up’ calculations by industry and government regulators, but there is very little hard data.” The Pétron team’s findings were disputed in a peer-reviewed commentary published by the Journal of Geophysical Research in November. But preliminary results from a subsequent study, using isotopic analysis of methane emissions from the Denver-Julesburg field, now reportedly line up with the findings by Pétron and her collaborators. Queensland coal seam For the next blow against the fossil gas merchants, we need look no further than Southern Cross University in northern New South Wales. Importing a specialised spectrometer, biochemists Isaac Santos and Damien Maher drove to the Tara coal seam gas field on the western Darling Downs. Over their 500 kilometre trip to Tara, the researchers recorded atmospheric methane figures of 1.78 to 1.94 parts per million. Those are typical present-day world background levels. Once on the gasfield, the team drove back and forth on public roads, taking measurements every second and pinpointing them with GPS. “In Tara the concentrations are consistently higher than two parts per million and approach seven parts per million in a few locations,” Southern Cross University reported Maher as saying. “This is about three and a half times higher than expected if there was no change in the atmosphere.” “The concentrations are higher here than any measured in gasfields anywhere else that I can think of, including in Russia,” Maher told the Sydney Morning Herald. The response from gas industry spokespeople was vitriolic. “The Australian Petroleum Production and Exploration Association … attacked the research, saying it was ‘premature and questionable’,” the SMH reported on November 14. Federal Energy and Resources Minister Martin Ferguson thundered to an energy conference in Sydney that the study was “a cynical attempt to grab headlines” that “abandoned usual scientific practice.” Isotopic analysis nevertheless showed that the elevated methane levels at Tara were due to geologic methane. A problem for the researchers is the lack of baseline data from the Tara field; the gas developers there did not record background methane levels before starting to drill. But it is unlikely that natural seepage is an important factor in the high readings at Tara. Observations near Lismore and Casino in the Richmond River basin, a prospective but still-undeveloped coal seam gas region, did not approach those at Tara — even near intensive cattle operations. Utah: the Uinta Basin The most recent findings to be released are from another intensive top-down study conducted in the US by scientists from the NOAA and the University of Colorado. This time, the target was the rich oil and gas fields of the Uinta Basin in eastern Utah. During the winter of 2011-12 the scientists conducted an air and ground survey of the basin, taking readings of at least seven pollutant gases. Preliminary results were reported to a meeting of the American Geophysical Union in December 2012. “Overall methane levels are very high (often 2.5 ppm) in the gasfield,” the NOAA said. Modelling of methane leakage in the Uinta Basin pointed to an “eye-popping” figure of 9% of total production. “That figure is nearly double the cumulative loss rates estimated from industry data,” a commentary in the journal Nature observed. Home mostly to conventional oil and gas wells, the Uinta Basin is noted for a high rate of “fracking” — that is, hydraulic fracturing, in which drillers inject a high-pressure mix of water, sand and chemicals to open fissures in underground rocks to speed oil and gas flow. Often used in conventional oil and gas extraction, fracking is also frequently used in production of coal seam gas, and is fundamental to the rapidly-expanding shale gas industry. The technique is particularly associated with high gas releases during drilling, since an estimated 30-70% of the injected water resurfaces, bringing gas with it. Fracking can also open alternative routes for gas to reach the surface via rock faults, bypassing the well and its collection mechanisms. This may partly explain the striking divergence between top-down and bottom-up figures for gas leakage. Significantly, the figures for gas leakage in the Denver-Julesburg and Uinta Basins are within or above the range indicated in 2011 by the first serious attempt to quantify emissions from shale gas extraction. Conducted by a team under Cornell University scientist Robert Howarth, this study put leakage from the shale gas industry in the US at 3.6-7.9%. Howarth’s findings were derided by energy industry spokespeople who pointed to the study’s limited data sample. But the new work suggests that Howarth’s figures were, if anything, conservative. Warming Effects Meanwhile, what exactly are the warming effects of methane once it reaches the atmosphere? Methane in the air oxidises relatively quickly to carbon dioxide and water. Almost all of it is gone within twenty years of its release. Usually, the gas is described as having a warming impact per molecule 20-25 times that of carbon dioxide, measured over 100 years. But this 100-year measure is only a convention, and an inept one at that. Climate change is moving much faster than expected. Over as little as a decade, a big pulse of methane from unconventional gas development could help push the climate past “tipping points” such as the collapse of Arctic sea ice or Amazonian forests. On a 20-year time-frame, methane is cited as having a warming footprint 72-79 times that of carbon dioxide. And that’s not the whole story. In the atmosphere methane interacts with aerosols, ultrafine airborne particles. NASA scientist Drew Shindell, who studies these reactions, calculates that when they’re taken into account methane has a 20-year climate impact 105 times that of carbon dioxide. If methane leakage is just 1%, that means, gas-fired electricity has a 20-year warming effect roughly equal to black coal. And leakage in the Uinta Basin has now been put at 9%. What’s worse than heroin addiction, quicker and far more drastic in the damage it wreaks? Drinking methylated spirits? That’s the sort of grim metaphor we have to invoke if we’re to describe the potential impacts of the fossil gas industry. Relate article: White paper reveals gas industry scared of global protests greenleftDOTorgDOTau/node/53313</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361469757119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:02:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361471540267-22</Id><Title>Bill to seek 10% solar energy standard</Title><Msg>Bill to seek 10% solar energy standard By Leslie Brooks Suzukamo pioneerpress Posted: 02/20/2013 12:01:00 AM CST Updated: 02/20/2013 09:34:16 PM CST Minnesota should have a mandate for using solar energy similar to the one it has for using renewable wind energy, say backers of a pair of bills to be filed Thursday in the State Legislature. The bills would require the state's utilities to produce 10 percent of electricity from solar energy by 2030. A solar standard would raise present utility rates by 1 percent per year, starting with the first year, and be borne by ratepayers, its backers said in a news conference at the State Capitol Wednesday, Feb. 20. But legislators sponsoring the Solar Energy Jobs Act emphasized it as a jobs bill, saying it will create 2,000 jobs in its first year alone, based on analysis using software from the National Renewable Energy Laboratory. State Rep. Will Morgan, DFL-Burnsville, and the author of the House version, said a solar energy standard also could attract more than $230 million in investments in its first year and create new businesses or lure existing ones from out of state. "This bill will provide jobs -- thousands of them across the life of the bill," he said. The International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, which trains members as solar installers, supports the bill, said Andy Snope, the union's business representative. The Senate version of the bill is sponsored by Sen. Chris Eaton, DFL-Brooklyn Center. Minneapolis-based Xcel Energy, the state's largest utility and likely the biggest consumer of any new solar generation, opposes the 10 percent standard. Solar energy is not the most cost-effective way to expand the state's use of renewable energy, its officials say. "Rather than a 10 percent mandate, we should ask, 'What is the goal we're trying to achieve?' " Xcel regional vice president Laura McCarten said. "If the goal is improved environmental performance, shouldn't we try to get there in the most cost-effective manner?" The cheapest form of new energy generation involves a program that conserves energy and reduces the need for additional generation, which cost between 1.3 cents and 2.2 cents per kilowatt-hour, she said. Next comes wind energy, with its production tax credits, and natural gas, which each cost roughly in the range of 4 cents to 5 cents per kilowatt-hour, McCarten said. Large utility-scale solar projects -- like a newly opened 2,000 kilowatt project in Slayton, Minn., from which Xcel is buying power -- create electricity at a cost of between 10 cents and 15 cents per kilowatt-hour, including investment tax credits, McCarten said. But small rooftop projects on homes and businesses can cost between 20 cents to 50 cents per kilowatt-hour even with the tax credits, she said. Xcel supports creating jobs and stimulating the economy but said "reasonable energy costs" are critical for both, McCarten said. The state's solar industry agreed with Xcel's cost estimates for large solar projects, but it says Xcel is overstating the cost of rooftop installations. The cost of producing solar energy has dropped dramatically in just the past few years, and it is expected to decline further as the technology improves said Lynn Hinkle, director of policy development for the Minnesota Solar Energy Industries Association, the industry's trade association. "It's a moving target," he said. Still, a 10 percent solar standard would require Minnesota to boost its solar energy capacity from 13 megawatts today -- or less than 1 percent of Minnesota's present electricity generation capacity -- to 5,300 megawatts by 2030, assuming power demand remains flat, Hinkle said. That's a daunting goal, but the backers said the solar goal is comparable to one for wind energy when the state's renewable energy goals were enacted in 2007. Utilities then had little wind energy online, but now most are on track to meet the state mandate of deriving at least 20 percent of their electricity production from wind energy by 2025 -- or, in the case of Xcel, a mandated 25 percent by 2020, said Ken Bradley, program director of Environment Minnesota and chairman of the Solar Works for Minnesota coalition of groups pushing for more solar energy development. Minnesota, he said, has as much sunshine as Jacksonville, Fla., and cold sunny winter days actually help because the panels work better if they don't overheat, he said. The backers of the bill said an early January poll by Minnesota Environmental Partnership showed 74 percent of voters support a 10 percent solar standard. The poll also showed 73 percent of voters would pay $1 more per month on their electricity bills for more solar power, the group said. The margin of error for the poll was 4.4 percentage points, the group said. The 10 percent mandate under the Solar Energy Jobs Act would be in addition to the state's current renewable energy requirements and should not conflict with wind energy production, Hinkle said. twincitiesDOTcom/business/ci_22629279/lawmakers-propose-10-solar-mandate-minnesota-utilities</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361471540267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:32:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361473148595-23</Id><Title>U.S. electric utilities flock to lower-priced wind power</Title><Msg>U.S. electric utilities flock to lower-priced wind power Xcel, MidAmerican among leaders as more utilities sign up for consumer savings WASHINGTON, D.C., February 20, 2013 – U.S. electric utilities are locking in fixed-price contracts for wind power, now more cost-competitive than ever, illustrating the success of a key federal tax policy in holding down rates for consumers. A total of 66 U.S. utilities bought or owned wind power by the start of this year – nearly half for large amounts over 100 megawatts (MW) – up from 42 a year before. Utilities have continued to sign up for more since Congress and President Obama extended the Production Tax Credit for wind energy in the "fiscal cliff" bill signed at the beginning of January. "AWEA applauds these utilities for maximizing the PTC opportunity to continue bringing low-cost, fixed price wind power to their customers," said Rob Gramlich, Interim CEO of the American Wind Energy Association (AWEA). "From Xcel Energy in Minnesota to OG&amp;E in Arkansas, electric consumers are racking up the savings as a result. The wind energy industry looks forward to our continued partnerships with utilities across the country to lock in the economic development, rate stabilizing and environmental benefits of more wind power." Among the utilities making major wind power purchases and reporting consumer savings are: -Xcel Energy, the number one wind energy provider in the nation, is considering adding more wind generation in Minnesota and Colorado because of the PTC extension.Earlier this month, Judy Poferl, president and CEO, of Xcel Energy's Northern States Power Company-Minnesota said, "Although Xcel Energy is well ahead of meeting our state's renewable energy requirements, we are open to adding cost-effective wind projects that could provide long-term value to our customers. The extension of the federal renewable electricity Production Tax Credit may make cost-effective projects available to serve our customers." In Colorado, Xcel Energy has repeatedly set national records for generating more than half its electricity from wind power and is now seeking regulatory approval to accelerate its resource acquisition process to allow for the addition of value priced wind energy. "We have a great opportunity to see if additional wind resources in Colorado would be of economic benefit to our customers with the extension of the federal tax credit, but we must act quickly," said Ben Fowke, chairman, president, and CEO of Xcel Energy. "Our request is not being driven by state renewable energy standards, but by the opportunity to reduce costs." -MidAmerican Energy, the No. 1 utility in the U.S. in terms of ownership of wind capacity, announced Dec. 31, 2012 that it had completed three more wind projects totaling 407 MW in Iowa. MidAmerican is a subsidiary of Berkshire Hathaway, the holding company controlled by investor Warren Buffett. "Wind now comprises 30 percent of MidAmerican Energy's generation portfolio," announced Bill Fehrman, president and CEO. -Tri-State Generation and Transmission Association, citing the recently extended PTC and ongoing Renewable Portfolio Standard requirements in moving forward withan RFPto be executed by June 30 for approximately 100 MW of renewable energy to take advantage of competitive market prices. -Oklahoma Gas &amp; Electric, which in a filing in Arkansas, reported cost savings to its customers from the "clean, renewable energy" of its Crossroads wind farm: "From September 2011 through June 2012, fuel costs to Arkansas customers were approximately $1.2 million lower because of the incorporation of Crossroads into OG&amp;E's generation fleet. OG&amp;E estimates that fuel savings to Arkansas customers from September 2011 through December of 2012 will be in the range of $2.2 million. Total Company production cost savings for the first five years of operation are estimated to be $268 million. Over the expected twenty-five-year life of the asset production cost, the savings are estimated to be $2.3 billion." -Minnesota Power, part of ALLETE Inc., which completed phases two and three of its 210-MW Bison Wind Energy Center in North Dakota. With the purchase of a direct-current transmission line to Duluth, the company can phase out a long-term contract for coal generation and replace it with wind energy, increasing renewables to 20 percent of its generation mix en route to meeting Minnesota's goal of 25 percent by 2025. "By meeting an aggressive timetable we are able to capitalize on the wind production tax credits to the benefit of our customers in providing a clean, cost-effective energy resource," Minnesota Power COO Brad Oachs said in a news release. - Alliant Energy Corp., a subsidiary of Interstate Power &amp; Light Co., which on Dec. 21, 2012 issued an RFP for approximately 100 MW of wind power in the Midwest. - Nebraska electric utilities: AlthoughNebraska utilities had not been planning to add more wind power until 2017, Nebraska Public Power District recently signed a purchase agreement for 75 MW; Omaha Public Power District is in the process of signing for an additional 200 MW; and Lincoln Electric is seeking 50 MW, all as a result of the PTC's extension for projects started in 2013. - Puget Sound Energy, which announced last week it had set a new record by generating 23.5 percent of its energy from the utility's three Eastern Washington wind farms: "This milestone underscores the role wind power can play in meeting our energy needs," said David Mills, PSE vice president of Energy Supply Operations. "Wind is now a key resource for providing our customers with reliable, affordable electricity. And when combined with our hydro, natural gas and coal power plants, wind gives us flexible, cost-effective options for serving local homes and businesses." - DTE Energy: The company's ECHO Wind project, slated for 2013, will have a combined levelized cost of approximately $52.50 per megawatt-hour (MWh), down substantially from power purchase prices several years earlier, according to the Michigan Public Service Commission. DTE says its investment in that and two other recent wind parks will contribute $150 million in economic benefits to Michigan. - Consumers Electric Power estimates that Macon County and the state of Michigan received an economic boost of nearly $10 million from the development of the company's first wind farm, the Lake Winds Energy Park. The Michigan Public Service Commission said Feb. 15, 2013, in releasing its "Report on the Implementation of the P.A. 295 Renewable Energy Standard and the Cost-Effectiveness of the Energy Standards," that: "Compared to building a new, conventional coal facility, renewable energy contracts are significantly lower in price…less than any newly built generation including new natural gas combined cycle plants. Based on contract pricing trends and the January 2013 announcement that federal legislation extended the eligibility of the Production Tax Credit for projects that begin construction by December 31, 2013, Commission Staff anticipates that the cost of renewable energy will continue to decline, while the benefits from energy optimization savings and emission reductions from offset generation will continue to increase." As the Michigan PSC noted, utilities are cutting pollution by purchasing more wind energy. Currently installed wind turbines will avoid nearly 100 million metric tons this year of carbon dioxide emissions, for instance, equal to 1.8% of the entire country's carbon emissions. Other new wind power purchasers last year included at least 18 industrial buyers, 11 school districts, and eight towns or cities, showing a significant trend toward nontraditional power purchasers from the industrial sector. Manufacturers of everything from plastics to light bulbs, semiconductors, and badges, farms, and medical centers are now directly purchasing wind power. Spurred by the federal incentive, American wind power grew by 28 percent in 2012 alone, for the first time becoming the number one source of new electric generating capacity, and pouring $25 billion of private investment into the economy. The top states for new installations last year were: 1. Texas, 2. California, 3. Kansas, 4. Oklahoma, 5. Illinois, 6. Iowa, 7. Oregon, 8. Michigan, 9. Pennsylvania, and 10. Colorado. Illinois saw the installation of over 800 MW, for example, with half that output sold into the Tennessee Valley Authority market. As one of America's wind power hubs, Illinois is home to wind power innovation. This year saw the installation of the first concrete wind tower there, which the manufacturer says can support taller turbines to access better winds and open up new areas for development. The global wind energy industry will gather in Chicago this May 5-8, 2013 for the world's largest annual wind energy event, WINDPOWER 2013. Utility members in AWEA are eligible for a 50 percent discount on a main conference registration this year – to register, click here and use registration code WP13UT today before registration prices increase after March 11th. Thousands of workers and leaders from all sectors will be in Chicago to show their wares, attend conference sessions, and seek further solutions for success. aweaDOTorg/newsroom/pressreleases/utilitiesflocktowindDOTcfm</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361473148595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:59:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361473343709-24</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report</Msg><Username>william.curter</Username><Timestamp>1361473343709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:02:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361473364214-25</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report</Msg><Username>william.curter</Username><Timestamp>1361473364214</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:02:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361473659477-26</Id><Title>China pushes forward with carbon tax plans</Title><Msg>China pushes forward with carbon tax plans Ministry of Finance confirms plans for a range of new environmental taxes designed to tackle carbon emissions and environmental damage By BusinessGreen staff 21 Feb 2013 The Chinese government has provided further details of its plans to introduce a carbon tax as part of a package of tax reforms that will also see new levies introduced on scarce resources and environmentally damaging activities. State news agency Xinhua reported this week that a senior official at the Ministry of Finance (MOF) has confirmed the plans are progressing and will see a new carbon tax and environmental protection replace existing pollution discharge fees. Writing on the MOF website Jia Chen, head of the ministry's tax policy division, revealed local taxation authorities, rather than national environmental protection bodies, will collect the new levies. He also confirmed the government will push forward with plans for resource taxes, including new levies on coal and water. Crucially, the new coal tax will be calculated on the price of coal rather than the amount sold, effectively leading to increased taxes on China's booming coal industry. In addition, Jia said that the government was considering taxing a wide range of environmentally damaging or energy intensive goods and services. Xinhua cited batteries, as well as luxury goods such as private jets, as examples of goods that could face new taxes. The MOF provided no information on when the new taxes will be introduced, but the statement will fuel speculation that major tax reforms designed to tackle China's environmental problems are imminent. The government is currently under mounting pressure to address the smog crisis afflicting many of China's cities, while it has also pledged internationally to try and cut the carbon intensity of its economy by 40 to 45 per cent against 2005 levels by 2020. It has signalled in the past that it is planning to introduce a carbon tax, with reports suggesting last year that a 10 yuan (£1) a tonne carbon tax on large polluters will be introduced by 2015, before then climbing steadily through to 2020. Work is also underway to introduce a number of regional emission trading schemes, which would provide another carbon pricing mechanism for Chinese firms while also providing the foundations for a national carbon market. China's adoption of a carbon tax or carbon market mechanism would inevitably have considerable international repercussions. Most notably it would provide a major boost to international carbon markets, potentially offering a major new regional market the emissions trading schemes in Europe and Australia could integrate with. It would also inevitably inform on-going trade spats between China and the US and Europe centred on both the EU's plans to introduce an emissions levy on flights and allegations that China is unfairly subsidising its clean tech manufacturers. And it could help neutralise some of the criticism aimed at proposed carbon taxes in the US and more ambitious climate action in the EU, which has argued against such measures on the grounds China is not taking similar steps. In other developments, the Chinese Ministry of Environment posted a statement on its website announcing that six of the countries most polluting industries must adhere to tight new air quality standards from next month. The statement says that from March 1 power and industrtial plants in 47 major cities must adhere to "strict" new standards designed to tackle the country's escalating smog crisis. The new rules raise the prospect of enforced shutdowns for some factories and power plants if they fail to take urgent steps to tackle their emissions. businessgreenDOTcom/bg/news/2249513/china-pushes-forward-with-carbon-tax-plans</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361473659477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:07:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361474056974-27</Id><Title>XOM will be</Title><Msg>Buying a lot of product from ZTHO from now on. ZTHO will be a 10 bagger for sure now that XOM will be doing business with them.</Msg><Username>nickels_to_dollars</Username><Timestamp>1361474056974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:14:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361474291070-28</Id><Title>Biodiesel proponents lobby for high-blend exemption</Title><Msg>Biodiesel proponents lobby for high-blend exemption Posted: Thursday, February 21, 2013 5:00 am By Gene Lucht Iowa Farmer Today | 0 comments DES MOINES — Biodiesel proponents are watching the possibility of a gas-tax increase in Iowa with great interest. “It (the fuel tax increase) is a possibility,” says Mark Cobb, a fuel marketer and chairman of the Iowa Biodiesel Board. “We are just asking legislators that if that is talked about . . . that maybe they consider some type of exemption for fuels that are blended at a higher rate.” The biodiesel industry recently kicked off an effort to increase the amount of biodiesel in fuel. Presently, many companies use a 5-percent mix of biodiesel to regular diesel fuel. The industry is pushing a “B10 by 22” campaign. Cobb says Illinois has a sales tax on gasoline that includes an exemption for anything over a B10 level. “We realize that there has to be money for roads, and we support that,” Cobb quickly adds. “We’re not proposing anything of that magnitude (like the Illinois law).” He notes a recent economic study indicating biodiesel supported nearly 5,000 jobs in the state in 2012 and contributed nearly $400 million to the state’s gross domestic product. Cobb and others in the industry got a chance to talk to state lawmakers this past week when they held a Biodiesel on the Hill event in the Capitol. “We’re really thanking the Legislature for their support over the past five or six years,” says Randy Olson, executive director of the Iowa Biodiesel Board. “Our state’s citizens and lawmakers have supported biofuels, and that has allowed us in Iowa to become a leader in biofuel production.” Olson says he also was encouraged President Barack Obama alluded to sustainable forms of energy during his recent State of the Union address in Washington, D.C. Also, he says the industry continues to work to ensure the integrity of the renewable identification numbers in the industry. “We think the industry is policing itself now,” Olson adds. “The integrity today is solid.” iowafarmertodayDOTcom/news/crop/biodiesel-proponents-lobby-for-high-blend-exemption/article_33b42edc-7b85-11e2-8aba-001a4bcf887a.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361474291070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:18:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361475334783-29</Id><Title>Subject</Title><Msg>Cape Wind Developer Among Companies Vying For Virginia Offshore Wind Energy Area by NAW Staff on Wednesday 20 February 2013 Energy Management Inc. (EMI), the developer of the Cape Wind offshore wind project, is among the developers that have expressed interest in building a wind farm off the Virginia coast. EMI's application was one of two qualification packages recently submitted to the U.S. Department of the Interior's Bureau of Ocean Energy Management (BOEM); the other was from Sea Breeze Energy LLC, BOEM spokesperson Tracey Moriarty confirmed to NAW. However, BOEM is not yet seeking specific project proposals at this time, so the details about each developer’s intentions for the area remain unclear. The expressions of interest come in response to Virginia's proposed sale notice, which was published last December. In addition to EMI and Sea Breeze Energy, eight other companies already submitted nominations in response to BOEM’s February 2012 call for information and nominations for commercial wind leasing offshore Virginia: Apex Virginia Offshore Wind LLC, Arcadia Offshore Virginia LLC, Cirrus Wind Energy LLC, Dominion Virginia Power, enXco Development Corp. (EDF Renewable Energy), Fisherman's Energy LLC, Iberdrola Renewables Inc. and Orisol Energy US Inc. The proposed lease area offshore Virginia will be auctioned as a single lease and totals about 112,800 acres located about 23.5 nautical miles off the southern part of the Virginia coast. It is expected to support more than 2 GW of wind energy generation. BOEM will hold competitive lease sales for the area sometime this year. The qualification process is ongoing, and the companies that are qualified to bid on the upcoming lease sale will be announced as part of the final sale notice, which is expected to be published later this year, Moriarty says. nawindpowerDOTcom/e107_plugins/content/contentDOTphp?content.11143#DOTUSZ2NxG9KK0</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361475334783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:35:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361477036595-30</Id><Title>In eastern Ontario, a battery five times the size of Niagara Falls</Title><Msg>In eastern Ontario, a battery five times the size of Niagara Falls SHAWN MCCARTHY - GLOBAL ENERGY REPORTER MARMORA, Ont. — The Globe and Mail Published Tuesday, Feb. 19 2013, 3:32 PM EST Last updated Wednesday, Feb. 20 2013, 7:17 AM EST On the wind-swept ridge of a mountainous slag heap, Northland Power Inc. plans to construct a miniature Niagara Falls to store power and provide it to Ontario’s grid when the province’s proliferating wind turbines are asleep. For 24 years, U.S.-based Bethlehem Steel Corp. pulled iron ore from an open-pit mine a dozen kilometres south of this town of 6,400, situated halfway between Ottawa and Toronto. When the mine was closed in 1979, the company left a gaping hole that is now filled with water. Above the pit, vast piles of boulders and crushed rocks lie where they were discarded after the ore had been extracted. Toronto-based Northland is proposing a $700-million, “pumped storage” hydroelectric project that would create a waterfall five times the height of Niagara Falls – though with a fraction of the volume – descending from the slag mountain to the mine pit below. To operate the plant, Northland plans to purchase electricity from Ontario’s grid at night when prices are low and use it to pump water from the mine pit up to a newly constructed reservoir. During the day, the company would release the water for a 258-metre plunge to a powerhouse and generate 400-megawatts of power to take advantage of peak-time power prices when demand is high and wind turbines typically are less active. Efficient technology to store electricity has become the holy grail for the power system as it copes with increasing production from intermittent sources such as wind and solar, and dramatic swings in demand. Some experts have dubbed storage the “missing link” that would allow renewable operators to generate their electricity under the most favourable conditions and dispatch it when it is needed most. Indeed, the province forecasts that wind capacity will climb to 7,800 megawatts by 2018, up from 1,700 megawatts currently. But grid managers will face enormous challenges in dealing with the variable nature of that wind energy supply, which ranges from operating at full capacity to a mere 10 per cent of potential output. “Storage is the answer to their dreams in terms of dealing with intermittency and the need to firm up renewable power,” said John Wright, Northland’s director of business development. The company also operates wind and thermal generating stations in Ontario, Quebec and the United States. Companies across the world are racing to commercialize a wide range of storage technologies: from modern flywheels to compressed air storage to dozens of advanced battery types. Those innovations will not only improve the economics of intermittent sources such as wind and solar, they could provide competition to natural gas-fired and diesel generation, help transmission companies regulate their increasingly volatile systems, and hasten the day when electric vehicles are not only economic but serve as batteries for household energy use. “As the business develops, it is going to represent a game changer for the power sector,” said Jim Burpee, chief executive officer at the Canadian Electricity Association, which represents utilities across Canada. “If you have access to storage, you would need less peak generation or generation from other sources.” Players range from Toronto startup Temporal Power, which has re-engineered the flywheel; to Boston-area General Compression Inc., which stores energy in compressed air facilities in underground caverns; to multinational General Electric Co., which is rolling out new sodium metal chloride batteries that can operate on industrial or grid-scale applications. Temporal recently won a contract with Ontario’s Independent Electricity System Operator – a government agency that manages the grid – to provide storage capacity that would allow IESO to manage its system more efficiently. “In the absence of storage, we would reach a point where it is difficult to incorporate more renewable resources because of their variability,” said IESO chief executive Paul Murphy. “Whereas if you had storage that was economic and controllable, then that would no longer be a limitation.” The IESO wants the flexibility to refuse to accept wind-generated electricity onto the system during hours when it is not needed. Hydro One – the provincially owned corporation that owns transmission and distribution lines in Ontario – is participating in pilot projects with Temporal and Toronto-based Electrovaya Inc., which is developing a lithium ion battery. With economically efficient storage options, Hydro One could expand the level of variable power it can hook up on local feeder lines, and make better use of its assets, the company says. One advocate of storage and its powerful promise is Annette Verschuren, former chief executive at Home Depot Canada and a well-connected business leader. Ms. Verschuren is chief executive at NRStor Inc., which works with startup firms to speed commercialization of emerging storage technology. Backed by venture capitalist Northwater Capital Management Inc., NRStor is working with both Temporal and General Compression to commercialize their technology, and helped negotiate their contracts with IESO. Ms. Verschuren said Canada should be a leader in the fledgling field. “Why can’t we be leaders in the world in terms of innovation, in terms of all aspects of the business?” she said. “If you could capture that clean energy from intermittent [sources] and then hold it until it is needed and match it to demand, the significance of that is enormous … We can make ‘when the wind blows’ a hell of a lot more efficient by having storage and the capability to hold that energy for the time that it is needed on the grid.” A few power technologies that are being commercialized in Canada and across the world: theglobeandmailDOTcom/report-on-business/industry-news/energy-and-resources/in-eastern-ontario-a-battery-five-times-the-size-of-niagara-falls/article8820070/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361477036595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:03:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361477735696-31</Id><Title>BASF/Solvay - 1400 home fuel cell</Title><Msg>BRUSSELS — Chemicals giant Solvay hailed the successful entry into service in Flanders of what it said was the largest fuel cell of its type in the world on Feb. 6 A super-battery that produces enough electricity to power nearly 1,400 homes, the Proton Exchange Membrane (PEM) fuel cell has been producing clean electricity at a "steady rate" for weeks at a SolVin plant part-owned by Germany's BASF in Antwerp, northern Dutch-speaking Belgium. SolVin is a market leader in vinyl, or PVC production. The fuel cell converts the chemical energy from hydrogen into clean electricity through an electrochemical reaction with oxygen, and "has generated over 500 MWh in about 800 hours of operation," Solvay said in a news release. The company said this equates to the electricity consumption of 1,370 families over the same period. Fuel-cell technology is tipped by developers as a future power solution for everything from cars to ships. Flanders has benefited from a 14-million-euro investment ($18.5 million) in this applied technology, with the EU, the Dutch and the Belgian Flemish governments backers of Solvay's 5.0-million euros investment.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361477735696</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:15:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361480050569-32</Id><Title>Splitz Announcement.</Title><Msg>We need a substantial Hikez to Divy and a 100 dollar share price by 4/15.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1361480050569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:54:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361480243930-33</Id><Title>API, others appeal E15 standing ruling to US Supreme Court</Title><Msg>API, others appeal E15 standing ruling to US Supreme Court WASHINGTON, DC, Feb. 21 02/21/2013 By Nick Snow OGJ Washington Editor The American Petroleum Institute and eight other trade associations asked the US Supreme Court to overturn a federal appeals court’s ruling that they lack standing to legally challenge the US Environmental Protection Agency’s introduction of gasoline with a 15% ethanol blend into the US market. The groups filed their petition because the US Circuit of Appeals Court for the District of Columbia concluded that none of the 17 petitioners—including engine manufacturers and food producers as well as the petroleum industry—had legal standing to challenge E15 partial waivers EPA issued in 2012, API Downstream Group Director Bob Greco said on Feb. 21. “Had EPA stayed within its statutory authority and followed proper procedures, it would have waited until ongoing E15 testing on engines and fuel systems was completed before allowing the use of E15,” he told reporter during a teleconference. “Then it would have discovered that E15 is not safe for millions of vehicles now on the road.” “The DC Circuit’s decision could not have come at a worse time—in the dead heat of August, as the most devastating drought we’ve experienced in the last 50 years drove corn prices up nearly 40% in a matter of weeks,” added Louis Finkel, executive vice-president for government affairs, Grocery Manufacturers Association, who also participated. “The decision effectively increased demand for a crop that was already in extremely short supply, thanks to Mother Nature and an unworkable [federal Renewable Fuels Standard] policy,” he maintained. “Although we hope the court will resolve the E15 problem, we also believe our experience here represents only one of many underlying problems with the RFS, so we are calling on Congress to repeal the program,” Greco said. RFS impacts Finkel said the RFS contributed to an increase in acreage planted with corn from nearly 82 million acres in 2005 to more than 96 million acres in 2012. By comparison, the acreage planted with the next two biggest crops, soybeans and wheat, stayed flat, he noted. “From 2005 through 2011, the price of corn rose by $4.05; soybeans by $6.85; and wheat by $4.08,” the GMA official said. “By comparison, in the previous 6-year period, commodities rose only modestly. “These increased acres planted should provide some price relief by adding additional supply,” he said. “However, any gains in supply are largely offset by the fact that 40% of production acreage planted is devoted to ethanol production. And again, flooding the market with E15 will make it worse for consumers.” In addition to API and GMA, the petitioners included the American Meat Institute, National Chicken Council, the National Retail Federation’s National Council of Chain Restaurants, North American Meat Association, National Pork Producers Council, National Turkey Federation, and the Snack Food Council. The American Fuel &amp; Petrochemical Manufacturers, the other large US oil and gas association which would have to deal with widespread use of gasoline with a higher ethanol content, plans to file its own petition before the Apr. 15 deadline, a spokeswoman told OGJ. ogjDOTcom/articles/2013/02/api--others-appeal-e15-standing-ruling-to-us-supreme-court.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361480243930</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:57:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361482307271-34</Id><Topic><Title>BASF/Solvay - 1400 home fuel cell</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361477735696</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:15:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agence France-Presse...2013...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361482307271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:31:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361483971320-35</Id><Topic><Title>Are the DJIA and Obama Peaking at Same Time?</Title><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1361474272248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:17:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...and yet his approval numbers remain at 3 TIMES those of the drunk, Orange Bonerz!</Msg><Username>hello2bushdepression</Username><Timestamp>1361483971320</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:59:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361484215890-36</Id><Topic><Title>Are the DJIA and Obama Peaking at Same Time?</Title><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1361474272248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:17:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of bright ideas, whose bright idea was this? "I know how hard it is for you to put food on your family."—Greater Nashua, N.H., Chamber of Commerce, Jan. 27, 2000</Msg><Username>hello2bushdepression</Username><Timestamp>1361484215890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:03:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361485517543-37</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful info, thanks</Msg><Username>starkweatherjames977</Username><Timestamp>1361485517543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:25:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361485531072-38</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful info, thanks</Msg><Username>starkweatherjames977</Username><Timestamp>1361485531072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:25:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361502796310-39</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a wife and two generations of "infernos" so far. You should try it. It might bring you a little maturity and needed humility.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1361502796310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 22:13:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361502881778-40</Id><Topic><Title>O'Malley's offshore wind bill advances in House</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361423205820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 00:06:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't need a MD offshore wind bill. O'Malley produces enough useless wind to power the whole state.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1361502881778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 22:14:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361504583135-41</Id><Title>Currency Purchase</Title><Msg>Sold all euros for Swiss Francs: 1.228 Sfr./€</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361504583135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 22:43:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361507238218-42</Id><Topic><Title>Germany and Quantum Chemistry</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361277468716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 07:37:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you are saying if you met a friendly, vivacious college age woman who could use a couple million $ and a lover to raise some children with you would pass up the opportunity to lend your services? You are very boring inferno... The French elites would think you #$%$, or at least quite common.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361507238218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 23:27:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>