<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368007316184-1</Id><Topic><Title>Mark Sanford Proves How Hypocritical And Dumb South Carolinians Are..</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1367975175783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 21:06:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahlee u #$%$ face try another lobotomy.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1368007316184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 06:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368007424936-2</Id><Topic><Title>★★★★HEY BERNANKE..Your "experiment" should have stopped 8 months ago !</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1367972188930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 20:16:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats what we votrd for. Forget gold and bullets now u better start hording food.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1368007424936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 06:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368007471208-3</Id><Topic><Title>☛☛☛HEY NUTJOBs....just like 1929...ZERO technical buying ! bwhahahahaha!</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1367945595434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ maxi411 u commie freak.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1368007471208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 06:04:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368019691098-4</Id><Title>Julia biggest find ever in GOM?</Title><Msg>the deep water Julia field was sanctioned for joint development by Xom and Sto. news reports suggest this is the biggest find in GOM by xom at 6 b bbl........the 1998 lease contains royalty relief provision that exempts fed gov payments until development costs recouped.</Msg><Username>jwsull</Username><Timestamp>1368019691098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368022792061-5</Id><Title>Gore: 'There's no such thing as ethical oil'</Title><Msg>Gore: 'There's no such thing as ethical oil' Zack Colman - 05/08/13 09:14 AM ET There’s only dirty oil and dirtier oil,” Gore told Canada’s The Globe and Mail. Former Vice President Al Gore on Tuesday said "there's no such thing as ethical oil," slamming the notion that importing oil from U.S. ally Canada was better than doing so from unfriendly nations. “There’s no such thing as ethical oil. There’s only dirty oil and dirtier oil,” Gore told Canada’s The Globe and Mail during a Tuesday event in Toronto. Gore was responding to Globe and Mail Editor-in-Chief John Stackhouse on whether it made a difference that oil sands from the proposed Keystone XL pipeline would come from a democratic nation. U.S. backers of the Canada-to-Texas pipeline have pointed out that the crude it carries would displace imports from less friendly nations, such as Venezuela. The pipeline, which is at the center of an intense lobbying and political fight, is under federal review. Gore said he understood the economic factors behind the upcoming White House ruling, but said he didn’t know what President Obama would decide. Industry groups, Canadian officials, some unions and Republicans and centrist Democrats want to build the pipeline. They say it promises jobs and oil from an ally. But green and left-wing groups — and their Democratic friends in Congress — oppose Keystone. They say it would deepen U.S. dependence on fossil fuels and pump more greenhouse gases into the air. On that note, Gore said thought the U.S. needed to change its ways to reduce the demand for Canada’s oil sands, according to The Globe and Mail. Still, Gore put some of the blame on Canada. “I had hoped that Canada would point the way toward a better path, but as yet it has not,” he said. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/298443-gore-oil-from-a-friend-is-still-oil</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368022792061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368023527206-6</Id><Topic><Title>A Purified Elite USA is ideal for Europe</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366472073440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump... ***On the debt to fund the orgy of spending: The debt is owned by the top few percent of the US population. They are saving as the rest of the USA, led by the US government, squanders the money. As interest rates increase in the future this will necessitate major tax increases to service the debt. The taxes will end up being paid by lower income people and reduce demand for basic consumption items. The interest income accruing to the top few percent of the American population will find a home in demand for European products - Porsches, BMWs, Mercedes, Rolex watches, articles de Paris, Zeiss lens, perfumes, fine wines, cheeses, European vacations...etc... Keep spending... It's good to see the US stock market rallying so smartly too -- based mostly on profits earned outside the USA. American corporate executives really have outdone themselves.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368023527206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:32:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368030749749-7</Id><Topic><Title>Gore: 'There's no such thing as ethical oil'</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368022792061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gore again demonstrates he is the same mental category as our wahleee boy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368030749749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368038418979-8</Id><Title>Interior’s fracking rules in cross hairs ahead of upcoming release</Title><Msg>Julian Hattem - 05/08/13 01:17 PM ET Lawmakers from both parties are pouncing on the federal government's attempt to regulate hydraulic fracturing, the natural gas extraction method also known as fracking, even before the draft rules have been released. At a hearing before the House Natural Resources Committee on Wednesday, Republicans accused the Interior Department of executive overreach and heard from a number of state officials and gas industry executives who asked for relief from federal rules. Democrats countered by warning of industry pressure and ineffective safety standards. With Interior expected to release draft rules governing fracking on public lands in the coming weeks, a core disagreement dividing legislators comes down to who should regulate fracking: the federal government or the states. "States are able to carefully craft regulations to meet the unique geologic and hydrologic needs of their states," said Rep. Doc Hastings (R-Wash.), the chairman of the House committee, who claimed that federal rules would be redundant, costly and would needlessly delay gas production. "The regulatory needs of North Dakota versus Ohio and New Mexico are vastly different," he added. "Imposing a one-size-fits-all regulatory structure, as the Obama administration is attempting to do, will not work." "States have successfully regulated more then 1.2 million hydraulic fracturing operations spanning 60 years," argued Montana state Sen. Alan Olson (R). "New federal mandates are not necessary given their exemplary safety record." Democrats, though, called on the federal government to step in and insure uniform safety standards across the country. "State regulations vary widely in their requirements and in the stringency of those requirements — and the efficacy varies as well," countered Rep. Rush Holt (D-N.J.). "That's why it's important that the thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/298521-interiors-fracking-rules-in-crosshairs-ahead-of-upcoming-release</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368038418979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:40:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368038517080-9</Id><Topic><Title>Gore: 'There's no such thing as ethical oil'</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368022792061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:19:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deepen our dependence on oil? The demand is already there. What Keystone changes is just the price tag.</Msg><Username>jamie_williams67</Username><Timestamp>1368038517080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368038723955-10</Id><Title>Sen. Baucus pushed to back carbon tax</Title><Msg>Sen. Baucus pushed to back carbon tax Ben Geman - 05/08/13 11:20 AM ET The Washington Post’s editorial board is urging retiring Sen. Max Baucus (D-Mont.) to back carbon taxes in the wider tax code overhaul that the powerful Finance Committee chairman wants to achieve. The Post’s new editorial calls a carbon tax “an elegant policy Congress could immediately take off the shelf.” It’s not the first time the paper has backed the idea. But ThePost’s latest push could buoy a loose collection of policy wonks and climate activists seeking any traction in their steep uphill climb in favor of carbon taxes. E2-Wire looked at the against-the-odds push in detail here. The Post, for its part, both makes the case for a tax and notes the long odds, calling it “one of the best ideas in Washington almost no one in Congress will talk about.” From The Post: It would make polluters pay for their own pollution, which is the best way to encourage greener thinking. It would cut emissions without overspending national wealth on grandiose central planning or command-and-control regulation. And it would raise revenue, which lawmakers could use for debt reduction, lowering other taxes, improving the social safety net or some combination. The paper urges lawmakers to read the recent, wide-ranging energy tax policy paper that the Finance Committee staff recently released. The Finance Committee discussion paper describes carbon tax proposals among a slew of other policy ideas, but doesn’t endorse anything. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/298479-baucus-pushed-to-back-carbon-tax</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368038723955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:45:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368039568276-11</Id><Title>Offshore Wind Industry Will Become €130 Billion Annual Market By 2020</Title><Msg>May 8, 2013 Silvio Marcacci Offshore wind power may yet not match the overall strength of onshore wind, but the industry is on course grow rapidly to become an €130 billion global market by 2020. Global offshore wind market image via Roland Berger A new report from industry consultants Roland Berger, “Offshore Wind Toward 2020,” concludes a combination of industry trends will soon make offshore wind cost competitive with other generation sources in many markets. Europe is expected to continue dominating the global offshore wind industry, but the Asia Pacific and North American regions will soon represent significant market shares as technological innovation reduce many bottlenecks that have stymied project development to date. Europe Continues To Dominate Global Markets New turbines are expected to sprout from seas across the globe, but Europe will lead the charge, buoyed by ambitious national policy goals in multiple countries. The European Union has set 2020 targets of 35% electricity from renewables, with a 12% carve out for wind and 40 gigawatts (GW) installed offshore capacity. So far, those targets have helped build 5GW offshore wind capacity, with new installations exceeding more than one offshore turbine per business day in 2012, equivalent to 10% of Europe’s annual wind energy installations. In many cases, actual generation from wind farms has exceeded expectations. But current offshore output will be swamped by future additions – by 2020 reaching 4.5GW of new annual offshore wind capacity additions, worth more than €14 billion per year. Those estimates would more than triple annual capacity additions and double total investments for 2013, currently at 1.8GW and €7 billion respectively. Growing Asia-Pacific, North American Markets Just like a rising tide, the offshore wind market’s growth will raise boats outside of European waters... cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/05/08/offshore-wind-industry-will-become-e130-billion-annual-market-by-2020/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368039568276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368044056778-12</Id><Title>conservative ethics</Title><Msg>Famiily values, you all?</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1368044056778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368058383117-13</Id><Title>Energy - what a waste!</Title><Msg>Evan R. Gaddis - 05/08/13 05:11 PM ET As much energy as the United States consumes, it’s nothing compared to how much energy we allow to go to waste. Amazingly, almost two-thirds of energy produced is going to waste, according to data released by the U.S. Energy Information Administration/Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory. In 2011, EIA estimated that the equivalent of 39 quadrillion British Thermal Units (“quads”) of electricity was generated from a variety of sources: natural gas, coal, nuclear, hydro, and renewables. Of the 39 quads, only about one-third was actually used for residential, commercial and industrial uses; the other two-thirds of electricity was wasted -- lost due to inefficiencies and waste in transmission lines, the electrical distribution grid, and end-use of electricity in homes and businesses. Until now, most of our national energy conversation has focused on energy generation issues, but it is clearer than ever that energy efficiency must be a cornerstone in the foundation of our national energy policy. Greater energy efficiency will boost economic productivity and competitiveness and enhance U.S. energy security while reducing emissions. We have the technologies to vastly improve energy efficiency today. Buildings consume 70 percent of the electricity in the U.S. annually. Recent advances in building equipment, lighting, sensors, controls, and integrated systems now make it possible to achieve a significant reduction in a building’s energy use, transforming older inefficient buildings into high performance building (HPBs). The industrial sector consumes about 23 percent of the nation’s electrical energy. When high-efficiency drives and NEMA Premium motors are combined with sensors, intelligent process controls and monitoring systems, it is estimated that 15-30 percent energy savings are achievable. These savings go directly to a thehillDOTcom/blogs/congress-blog/energy-a-environment/298583-energy-what-a-waste-</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368058383117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 20:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>