<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374232142163-1</Id><Title>How long can FED print US Dollars?</Title><Msg>At one time, the US dollar was craved by everyone. When the US dollar starts showing up everywhere that will be the day the economy collapse. Until then the US dollar will do like most African countries did for years and PRINT!!! PRINT!!!PRINT!!! Rarity is a prize, over-production is a bust!!! Until then, order that triple cheese burger and watch the market continue higher.</Msg><Username>ggray1956</Username><Timestamp>1374232142163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 07:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374237262277-2</Id><Title>TransCanada rebuffs EPA’s call for Keystone clean energy</Title><Msg>TransCanada rebuffs EPA’s call for Keystone clean energy July 19, 2013 at 6:55 am by Bloomberg In a July 17 letter to the U.S. State Department, the Calgary-based company said the EPA suggested it buy renewable energy to run pumping stations from Alberta to Steele City, Nebraska. The EPA, in an April filing with the State Department, also said the U.S. should work with Canada to promote technology to capture and store underground the carbon-dioxide emissions generated in the production of Canadian oil. The State Department is reviewing the $5.3 billion project because it crosses an international border. TransCanada first applied for a permit for the project in 2008. “Keystone does not control the source of the power it purchases,” according to the letter, released yesterday by the company. “TransCanada has invested over $5 billion in emission-less energy sources including the largest wind farm in Maine and 13 hydro power stations in the U.S. Northeast.” The EPA said the pipeline will increase global warming emissions because developing crude from western Canada’s oil sands produces more carbon dioxide than the typical oil used in the U.S. In addition to the impact on climate change, environmental groups oppose the project because of the potential for oil spills along its more than 875-mile (1,408-kilometer) route. Revised Path President Barack Obama in 2012 rejected the original route proposed by TransCanada after officials in Nebraska said it endangered a sensitive wetland. The company has since proposed a new pathway that extends further east in the state to avoid the area. A draft environmental analysis prepared for the State Department said Keystone wouldn’t raise the risks of climate change because Alberta’s oil would probably be developed with or without the pipeline. If both Keystone and the other proposed pipelines from the oil sands aren’t built, the reduction in annual emissions would be at most 5.3 million metric tons a year of carbon dioxide, les</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374237262277</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 08:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374238008787-3</Id><Topic><Title>Is XOM going to partner with IOC?</Title><Username>iocrules</Username><Timestamp>1374155071181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 09:44:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW, thanks janinesor, I really did not want to hear that one... I despise IOC and think they are full of do do. They have lied for years, but this one may be true? With the action in the last few days you just may be right. Guess I should go long now? YIKES</Msg><Username>iocrules</Username><Timestamp>1374238008787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 08:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374238165037-4</Id><Topic><Title>How long can FED print US Dollars?</Title><Username>ggray1956</Username><Timestamp>1374232142163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 07:09:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is still the greatest in the world. where else are you going to put your money? Greece? Italy ? Germany? China? they all stink and now the only place is the USA and Ben knows that. It will come crashing down some day soon. It is going to be BAD too We have 70-75 TRILLION in unfunded liabilities and this will catch up to us. Look at Detroit, that is the way of the USA in DC. going to hell in a hand basket.</Msg><Username>iocrules</Username><Timestamp>1374238165037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 08:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374242286637-5</Id><Topic><Title>How long can FED print US Dollars?</Title><Username>ggray1956</Username><Timestamp>1374232142163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 07:09:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The U.S. trade deficits pull dollars out of the USA into offshore banking systems and cause deflation. The trade deficits are caused by too high price levels in the USA. The areas with the biggest deficits are the major American financial centers where and values, rents, and spending rates are highest, and public sector salaries &amp; benefits are highest, and the number of welfare collectors is highest. The US government, Federal Reserve, and Democrat dominated urban governments are responsible for that situation. It will be resolved by a crash in those economies to bring the price levels down. The Federal Reserve and US government tried its best to prop it back up but it will come crashing back down. Places like Detroit will be followed by Cleveland, Chicago, New York, San Francisco, Los Angeles, Boston, Washington DC... They could do QE for decades and it would make no difference to the inflation rate.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1374242286637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 09:58:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374244116052-6</Id><Title>moVed 2 5</Title><Msg>thE prEsident mandaTed OIL b dEsignEd oUt of Transportation over 10 yEars. hE juST moVed it 2 5</Msg><Username>ezekiel_trinity</Username><Timestamp>1374244116052</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 10:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374244378610-7</Id><Title>nRa</Title><Msg>nRA, rEd pLaGuE, Oil spEcuLatoRs – abomiNasHun thE US Obamas Nation</Msg><Username>ezekiel_trinity</Username><Timestamp>1374244378610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 10:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374244809142-8</Id><Title>dO NOT b aFraid</Title><Msg>aMeriCA 2 dIe mOst WILL C cHrist. upON thE tyMe u b here, wAlk thE pATh TOWARD HIM &amp; NOT sAtAn</Msg><Username>reverendjaa</Username><Timestamp>1374244809142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 10:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374245658711-9</Id><Title>thE liOns JungLe</Title><Msg>aNd When Christ cReated hIs MajestiC lIons aNd gAve Them thE titLe, “thE kING of The jUngle (thE lIOnS JUNGLE not maNkinds) &amp; mAnkInd hAs whAt hE hAs” hE wanTed cOexIstEnCe betwEEn mankInd anD thE lIon. thAt’s wHy dAviD wAlked Out. dAviD tRusTed The kEy ThaT chRisT gAve Him And Used it.</Msg><Username>reverendjaa</Username><Timestamp>1374245658711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 10:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374245747837-10</Id><Topic><Title>So let’s see if you Americans know anything about your country…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1374170988575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 14:09:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sold more € to buy $. @ $/€ 1.314 Allocation $: 20% Atlanta is added to the list…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1374245747837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 10:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374246220745-11</Id><Title>krAkaTowa</Title><Msg>sAtAN aND The Red pLAgUE PIGGGGGGGGGG puShes Back wITh their BOUGHT OFF sPeculators 2 PHUCK U 99% America and Teach U a LeSS sUn fRUm sAtAns US PIGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGS. mUD inSTeAD of ChriST 4 the aTheist NOT C rED plAgUE PIGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGG. iT iZ YOUR acKshUNs &amp; mIsGIvINgs rED plAguE aNd nRA thAt aLLoWS sAtAN 2 sTALK ALL uv AmERicAcA in 2011, 201x, 201. It iS thE bLUe PartEE thAt kEEpS cHRiST hErE in 2011, 201x, 201. dO u NjOY bEInG lIKenEd 2 PIGGGGGGGGGGGGGS 1 % ers rED plAguE aNd nRA? iS iT trUE thAT U r all a CroSS wIth a GoaT anD shEEP 2? dUE U EVER wANnabee kUMpetiTiVe aGaiN? wHY nOT 1% cEnTErs jOIn 99% Ers aND We DO NOT WANT yoUr mOniEs, bUT U R bEIng TOLD thaT 99% DO NOT lIkE thE wAY iT iS bEINg sPenT sO uNwIZe Lee iN 2011, 201x, 201. theRE IZ kNOw FuTuRe 4 YouR tEAChINgS nRa &amp; rED plAguE thAT gIVEs kUMfERT 2 EVIL mAn in 2011, 201x, 201. 99% ers DUZ NOT lIKe How thE monIeS R bEinG spEnt wHen iT iZ uSEd 2 • bLOw sOnaR UndeR thE oCeaNs AnD C’S Of ChrISt. • HunT &amp; mUrdER cHrisT wolVeS &amp; eARthEn AnIMaLS With sAtaNs PENIS pIstOLe. • dRill wITH sAtaNs PENIS 4 HIZ blAcK bLooD eVeN wHerE aMeriCA is Trying 2 gROW the PopulATION of CONDORS 2 OVER 20. • dESeCrATe thE eARtH &amp; aNimAls wITh a KeySTonE aND A brisTOL bAy.  uSE yoUR moNiEs nRa 2 aDvERtISE thE STOPPAGE oF EVIL Man hUNtinG mAn anD PROMOTE hoW imnPOrtANT ALL aNimAls R 2 OUR eXIsTeNcE.  uSE yoUr mONiES rED plAgUe 2 TAKE SATANS PENIS AWAY fROm aMEricA And GO GREEN aND DO NOT dEsECraTE thE eARtH anD iTs EarThen AnimAl hAbItAts aND bEauTee. mAkE tHe cHOicE wiZe Lee in 2011, 201x, 201. dUE U follOw IAM oRe AMI and WAKE UP AMERICA 2 39,000,000 LESS mONtaNA = kRAkaTowa nYC = missiNG glAss PalAcE EcOlipornia = 16.8 RicKEEEE thE mayAns SaW iT and EdgAr KC 2 – 1000% cOrrEcTo</Msg><Username>reverendjaa</Username><Timestamp>1374246220745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 11:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374247300925-12</Id><Title>wE R</Title><Msg>333 whY R their 6. bEcaUse there R 3 sides 2 a Try angle and 3 corners. WE GUARD ALL.</Msg><Username>reverendjaa</Username><Timestamp>1374247300925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 11:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374248030962-13</Id><Title>aNd lEts C</Title><Msg>oN this Page wHat hAppEnS wHen The pRmOnishun 2 B bEkUMs IZ ? iT’s AmericAca tYme tEstER mONtanA = kRakAtoWa EcolIpornIa = 16.8 rIckee</Msg><Username>reverendjaa</Username><Timestamp>1374248030962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 11:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374248911103-14</Id><Title>WARNING..... TRIPLE DIGIT LOSS IN THE DOW BY 3PM TODAY</Title><Msg>Market overbought and due for a correction?</Msg><Username>snakesoupagain</Username><Timestamp>1374248911103</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 11:48:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374250318947-15</Id><Title>SP500 has a RSI of 77="OVERBOUGHT"...next 15% correction!!!</Title><Msg>CNBC just said.....!!!</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1374250318947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374255257020-16</Id><Topic><Title>SP500 has a RSI of 77="OVERBOUGHT"...next 15% correction!!!</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1374250318947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH! Well, if CNBC says so, it MUST BE true... Lemming.</Msg><Username>fsmzl_ui</Username><Timestamp>1374255257020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374256156233-17</Id><Title>☛☛☛☛DETROIT a disaster..earnings AWFUL..MASSIVE SELLOFF 2:30pm</Title><Msg>BAD day boys.</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1374256156233</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374257016325-18</Id><Title>Where's the IGNORE button ???</Title><Msg>When it's really needed ? Good job Yahoo (ever wonder why they chose that name ?)</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374257016325</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374257210405-19</Id><Title>Oil companies break with trade group on renewable fuel mandate</Title><Msg>Oil companies break with trade group on renewable fuel mandate July 19, 2013 at 9:02 am by Jennifer A. Dlouhy The oil and gas industry’s top trade groups doggedly insist that Congress must completely scrap a federal mandate that forces gasoline makers to blend in ethanol and other renewable fuels. But not all oil companies are on board. At least two major integrated oil companies — Shell and BP — are pushing more modest changes to the eight-year-old renewable fuel standard, while others have biofuels investments that would be undermined if the mandate was dismantled. “Shell generally supports the RFS, but we do feel that it has to be revised,” said John Reese, the company’s downstream policy and advocacy manager, during an event Thursday that was organized by The Hill newspaper. As the world’s largest distributor of biofuels, Shell recently partnered with Virent Inc., to produce advanced alternatives made with plant materials at a pilot facility in Houston. “It’s because of those interests we have a little bit of a different interest than some others in the oil industry,” Reese said. BP, meanwhile, is one half of Butamax Advanced Biofuels, a joint venture with DuPont that aims to convert corn, wheat and other biomass into an alcohol that has a higher energy density than traditional ethanol and can be blended into gasoline at refineries. Butamax’s chief executive praised the renewable fuel standard in a June interview with Bloomberg. For its part, BP says changes are needed to the RFS, but the company hasn’t visibly been part of an effort to repeal the standard. “BP supports the goals of the RFS program to stimulate the development and deployment of biofuels technologies,” said spokesman Matt Hartwig. “There are challenges with the standard that must be addressed, and we continue to work with regulatory authorities to address these issues.” The renewable fuel standard obligates refiners to add steadily increasing amounts of ethanol and oth</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374257210405</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374258472701-20</Id><Topic><Title>SP500 has a RSI of 77="OVERBOUGHT"...next 15% correction!!!</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1374250318947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 12:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>look at s&amp;p 500 graph on stockcharts....RSI is a 77....it's mean overbought.....not CNBC folks!!!</Msg><Username>ticagrelor</Username><Timestamp>1374258472701</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374260046270-21</Id><Topic><Title>Have You Looked At Sweat Crude Futures Prices?</Title><Username>stevie_b_in_hawaii</Username><Timestamp>1374091305592</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:01:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>stevie_b_in_hawaii</Username><Timestamp>1374260046270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 14:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374260406981-22</Id><Title>Oil Manipulation: Biggest Drawdown In 30 Years In a Sluggish Economy</Title><Msg>While no build on the product supply side. Can you say BS? Everyone can see that oil is being moved around or stored where its not being reported. The math doesn't add up and the world is watching. No way did we use more oil during this time then any other time over the last 30 years. If you don't agree then that makes you a lair or a fool. Take you pick. I posted a link up on Twitter about this. @Honolulu_Trader Long SCO</Msg><Username>stevie_b_in_hawaii</Username><Timestamp>1374260406981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 15:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374261310593-23</Id><Title>Huge *POMO* today. Up we go on today's newly Printed Money.</Title><Msg>It just doesn't get any better than this. Ben is XOM's Best. Friend. Ever!</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1374261310593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 15:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374262259938-24</Id><Topic><Title>The Bluecheese Boards</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1374012244923</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 18:04:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's off and running again! Is he even smarter than the President!....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1374262259938</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 15:30:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374264447719-25</Id><Title>ALL TIME HIGH</Title><Msg>The stock closed at an all time high today!!!</Msg><Username>jeb1996</Username><Timestamp>1374264447719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374265869201-26</Id><Title>Split</Title><Msg>When will we get a split?</Msg><Username>inuvik2</Username><Timestamp>1374265869201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 16:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374277030869-27</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese sure does enjoy talking to himself</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373991530250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where the heck is University of Fa. (you twitt)</Msg><Username>echo.2l65</Username><Timestamp>1374277030869</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 19:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374277245358-28</Id><Title>Report: Federal study finds ‘fracking’ chemicals don't pollute aquifers</Title><Msg>Report: Federal study finds ‘fracking’ chemicals don't pollute aquifers Ben Geman - 07/19/13 05:29 PM ET Will a major Energy Department study of natural gas development in Western Pennsylvania give “fracking” there a clean bill of health? The Associated Press, in an in-depth story Friday, reported on research into the fate of chemicals used in the hydraulic fracturing process. From AP: A landmark federal study on hydraulic fracturing, or fracking, shows no evidence that chemicals from the natural gas drilling process moved up to contaminate drinking water aquifers at a western Pennsylvania drilling site, the Department of Energy told The Associated Press. The heavily reported story describes the results of an ongoing study by the Energy Department’s National Energy Technology Laboratory (NETL). “The study . . . marked the first time that a drilling company let government scientists inject special tracers into the fracking fluid and then continue regular monitoring to see whether it spread toward drinking water sources,” AP reports. AP’s story noted the results are preliminary and the study is ongoing. But that wasn’t enough for NETL, which sought to really drive the “preliminary” point home Friday afternoon by issuing a statement in response to the AP story. Here's the NETL statement: NETL has been conducting a study to monitor for any signs of groundwater contamination as a result of hydraulic fracturing operations at a site on the Marcellus Shale formation in Pennsylvania. We are still in the early stages of collecting, analyzing, and validating data from this site. While nothing of concern has been found thus far, the results are far too preliminary to make any firm claims. We expect a final report on the results by the end of the calendar year. thehill</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374277245358</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 19:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374277899659-29</Id><Title>oil rising big!!!</Title><Msg>profits</Msg><Username>jk43uuu</Username><Timestamp>1374277899659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 19:51:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374278688482-30</Id><Title>DuPont Seeks Cellulosic Ethanol Joint Ventures</Title><Msg>DuPont Seeks Cellulosic Ethanol Joint Ventures By Dow Jones Business News, July 19, 2013, 04:55:00 PM EDT --DuPont seeks partners for joint ventures in production of cellulosic ethanol --Company is talking with potential partners in U.S., China, Brazil, Europe, Southeast Asia --DuPont is investing more than $200 million in cellulosic ethanol plant in Iowa By Owen Fletcher Chemical giant DuPont Co. ( DD ) is seeking partners for joint ventures in the production of cellulosic ethanol, a next- generation biofuel, a DuPont official said. "DuPont would take a minority stake and...we would basically take an active role in setting production up" in the joint ventures, which the company is discussing with parties in the U.S., Southeast Asia, China, Brazil and Europe, Jan Koninckx, DuPont's business director for biorefineries, said in an interview this week. He declined to name potential partners but said interested parties include fuel companies and agribusinesses. Ethanol made from corn kernels drove the expansion of the U.S. ethanol industry starting in the mid-2000s, as a federal mandate required increasing amounts of the biofuel to be blended into motor fuel. Ethanol producers at the time hoped future growth could be driven by cellulosic ethanol, made from other biomass such as the stalks of corn plants, since the next-generation fuel satisfies another part of the federal renewable fuels mandate. But development of cellulosic ethanol has lagged the pace once expected, and little of it is now being produced. Wilmington, Del.-based DuPont is investing more than $200 million to build a cellulosic ethanol plant in Nevada, Iowa, that will produce ethanol from corn-plant residue left in fields after farmers harvest their grain. DuPont expects the facility to open next year. The plant will be profitable based on its production of 30 million gallons of ethanol a year, but it is also meant to demonstrate the use at full scale of DuPont's cellul</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374278688482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374278861598-31</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese sure does enjoy talking to himself</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373991530250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you ever get a thumbs UP yet ? Nope !</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374278861598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374278894939-32</Id><Topic><Title>The Bluecheese Boards</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1374012244923</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 18:04:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a pitiful life this fool must have !</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374278894939</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374278925627-33</Id><Topic><Title>The Bluecheese Boards</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1374012244923</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 18:04:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>asdfasdfasdfsdf</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1374278925627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374279227659-34</Id><Topic><Title>DuPont Seeks Cellulosic Ethanol Joint Ventures</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374278688482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:04:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chemtex inks long term supply agreement for US ethanol facility EBR Staff Writer Published 19 July 2013 Chemtex International, a US-based biofuel company, has inked today a long term supply agreement with Murphy Brown for its Cellulosic Ethanol facility, Project Alpha, in Clinton, North Carolina. As per the terms of the agreement, Murphy will provide energy crops and residues grown on the company's six thousand acres of land for the plant estimated to produce twenty million gallons of cellulosic ethanol. The proposed crops will be grown on acreage that is not typically used for grain production and would represent the support of the supply chain for the planned Chemtex biorefinery, the company stated in a statement. The supply agreement is expected to commence following the financial closure for the planned facility. Murphy Brown government relations and public affairs VP Don Butler said that the company is delighted to partner with Chemtex to bring Cellulosic Ethanol to Eastern North Carolina. "The production of these feedstocks will be a natural complement to livestock production in the state and will bring new opportunities for farmers large and small," added Butler. "This project will demonstrate to policymakers that their focus should be on encouraging these American-made next-generation biofuels that are produced without consuming foodstuffs." Chemtex is further planning to increase the supply through contracting additional acreage over the next few months. Chemtex supply chain development director Matt Harrod noted: "It's a privilege to be working with Murphy Brown and is representative of the support we have received in North Carolina. It's a great first step in filling out our supply needs and we are looking forward to contracting with additional farmers in the area." biofuelsandbiomass</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1374279227659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 20:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374284836361-35</Id><Title>~~~NOBAMA, Holder, Clinton, BIDEN, the IRS......better DUMP em' fast boys !!</Title><Msg>REALLY...you and yours are being undermined daily.......</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1374284836361</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 21:47:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374290759979-36</Id><Title>Did U Hear About the Rightwingnut Who Answered the Ad "Would U Like to Be Corn Holed: Call...."</Title><Msg>He thought the ad said "Would U Like to Be Corn Rowed" (and he liked the look of corn rows); so, he answered the ad and his wife was angry because he left her for another man. Can u believe it? Did anyone else read about this?</Msg><Username>dufusrightwingnutshorts</Username><Timestamp>1374290759979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 23:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>