<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360226220532-1</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ Morris--Fox news--R I P</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1360188731863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:12:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1360226220532</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 03:37:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360241132666-2</Id><Title>Where is maxi pad</Title><Msg>Looks like he is keeping his big commie mouth shut or maybe his jaw is wired.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1360241132666</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:45:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360241308844-3</Id><Topic><Title>Marxist US School System</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360180652438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:57:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the big joke on them comes when only those educated in private schools will have good jobs. Public school kids will pump gas, stock shelves and clean toilets for a living. Maybe change my diaper when I get old to.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1360241308844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:48:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360246498218-4</Id><Topic><Title>Currency Purchase...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360037947538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 23:19:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold £ for € @ 1.1671 €/£ £ basis 0.8605 £/€ (1.1621 €/£)... gain on £ +0.43%... 80% €, 20% £...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360246498218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:14:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360247001481-5</Id><Topic><Title>Marxist US School System</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360180652438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 14:57:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is correct. Still, if the streams are separated the schools can help those who cannot match the elite do better. There is such a thing as master mechanics, master watch makers, etc... From a US school system such thing is unlikely though. My children (working on that presently) will have private schools, if for some reason I cannot get them onto the Gymnasium route... I will "stack the deck" every way I can, "pull every string..." Of course is to be expected...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360247001481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:23:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360247960725-6</Id><Topic><Title>Hans and Franz</Title><Username>invest83838</Username><Timestamp>1360194936690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 18:55:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Women do look very sexy in hunting attire. My lady is not into military though, so breasts under tight military uniforms is not for me. Perhaps you did not know it, but upper class European women hunted with the men, and many still do on private estates. They dressed like pretty dolls at parties (in corsets and the rest to make their breasts more prominent) during one time of the day, and put on different outfits for outdoor entertainments...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360247960725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:39:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360248516972-7</Id><Title>Exelon Cuts Dividend as Quarterly Profit Falls</Title><Msg>Exelon Cuts Dividend as Quarterly Profit Falls By Julie Johnsson - Feb 7, 2013 6:27 AM MT. Exelon Corp., owner of the largest group of U.S. nuclear plants, will cut its quarterly dividend for the first time as falling electricity prices and expiring long-term contracts reduce profit. Cutting the payment to shareholders will “position us to maintain our investment-grade rating, return a stable dividend and provide capacity to invest in growth,” Christopher Crane, chief executive officer of Chicago-based Exelon, said in a statement today. Exelon will reduce its dividend to 31 cents a share in the second quarter from 52.5 cents. The company hasn’t cut its dividend in the 12 years since it was formed by the merger of Unicom Corp. and Peco Energy Inc. Exelon is rated BBB by Standard &amp; Poor’s, two levels above junk status. The change in dividend was announced as Exelon reported fourth-quarter profit declined 38 percent on lower power prices and higher nuclear fuel costs. Net income fell to $378 million, or 44 cents a share, from $606 million, or 91 cents, a year earlier. Excluding one-time costs, per-share profit was a penny less than the 65-cent average of 16 analysts’ estimates compiled by Bloomberg. The 6.78 percent dividend yield offered by Exelon was the highest among its U.S. peer group as of today, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. Exelon will make a first-quarter dividend payment on March 8 to shareholders of record on Feb. 19. “The big issue is definitely power prices,” Paul Patterson, a New York-based utilities analyst with Glenrock Associates LLC, said in a phone interview before earnings were released. Wholesale Power Exelon faces greater exposure to falling wholesale power prices as long-term contracts that locked in higher rates expire, Patterson said. Average electricity prices have dropped 45 percent since 2008, the market’s most recent peak, in the portion of PJM Interconnection LLC where most of Exelon’s fleet is based, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. Exelon is the largest U.S. nuclear operator, with 35,000 megawatts of capacity. That’s enough electricity to light 28 million homes, according to U.S. Energy Department estimates. Exelon’s utilities deliver electricity and natural gas to about 6.6 million customers. The announcement was made before regular trading began on U.S. markets. Exelon, which has five buy, 18 holds and one sale recommendation from analysts, rose 0.4 percent to $30.98 yesterday in New York. bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-02-07/exelon-quarterly-profit-drops-on-falling-power-prices.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360248516972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:48:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360249734849-8</Id><Topic><Title>Currency Purchase...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360037947538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 23:19:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold remaining 20% £ position for € @ 1.1703 €/£, gain on £ +0.70%... 100% €, German deposit...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360249734849</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:08:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360249880213-9</Id><Title>Renewable Energy Cheaper Than Coal &amp; Gas In Australia, Bloomberg New Energy Finance Finds</Title><Msg>Renewable Energy Cheaper Than Coal &amp; Gas In Australia, Bloomberg New Energy Finance Finds February 7, 2013 Giles Parkinson This article was originally published on RenewEconomy (image added): Australia solar rooftops via Shutterstock A new analysis from research firm Bloomberg New Energy Finance has concluded that electricity from unsubsidised renewable energy is already cheaper than electricity from new-build coal and gas-fired power stations in Australia. The modeling from the BNEF team in Sydney found that new wind farms could supply electricity at a cost of $80/MWh –compared with $143/MWh for new build coal, and $116/MWh for new build gas-fired generation. These figures include the cost of carbon emissions, but BNEF said even without a carbon price, wind energy remained 14 per cent cheaper than new coal and 18 per cent cheaper than new gas. “The perception that fossil fuels are cheap and renewables are expensive is now out of date”, said Michael Liebreich, chief executive of Bloomberg New Energy Finance. “The fact that wind power is now cheaper than coal and gas in a country with some of the world’s best fossil fuel resources shows that clean energy is a game changer which promises to turn the economics of power systems on its head,” he said. But before people, such as the conservative parties, reach for the smelling salts and wonder why renewables need support mechanisms such as the renewable energy target, BNEF said this was because new build renewables had to compete with existing plant, and the large scale RET was essential to enable the construction of new wind and solar farms. The study also found that Australia’s largest banks and found that lenders are unlikely to finance new coal without a substantial risk premium due to the reputational damage of emissions-intensive investments – if they are to finance coal at all. It said new gas-fired generation is expensive as the massive expansion of Australia’s liquefied natural gas (LNG) export market forces local prices upwards. The carbon price adds further costs to new coal- and gas-fired plant and is forecast to increase substantially over the lifetime of a new facility. BNEF’s analysts also conclude that by 2020, large-scale solar PV will also be cheaper than coal and gas, when carbon prices are factored in. In fact, it could be sooner than that, as we reported yesterday, companies such as Racth Australia, which owns coal, gas and wind projects, said the cost of new build solar PV was already around $120-$150/MWh and falling. The solar thermal industry predicts their technologies to fall to $120/MWh by 2020 at the latest. The Bloomberg analysis said the Australian economy is likely to be powered extensively by renewable energy in future and that investment in new fossil-fuel power generation may be limited. “It is very unlikely that new coal-fired power stations will be built in Australia. They are just too expensive now, compared to renewables”, said Kobad Bhavnagri, head of clean energy research for Bloomberg New Energy Finance in Australia. “Even baseload gas may struggle to compete with renewables. Australia is unlikely to require new baseload capacity until after 2020, and by this time wind and large-scale PV should be significantly cheaper than burning expensive, export-priced gas. “By 2020-30 we will be finding new and innovative ways to deal with the intermittency of wind and solar, so it is quite conceivable that we could leapfrog straight from coal to renewables to reduce emissions as carbon prices rise.” he added. sDOTtt/1zukg</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360249880213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:11:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250061388-10</Id><Topic><Title>Renewable Energy Cheaper Than Coal &amp; Gas In Australia, Bloomberg New Energy Finance Finds</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360249880213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:11:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market for expensive LNG is shrinking and will soon vanish forever! Inexpensive renewable energy is here forever!</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360250061388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:14:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360251060467-11</Id><Title>US halts offshore drilling on wells with faulty bolts</Title><Msg>US halts offshore drilling on wells with faulty bolts Posted on February 6, 2013 at 12:42 pm by Bloomberg in Offshore, Safety Comments(0) An offshore facility drilling for deep gas. (Photo: Lee Tilton, provided by the Bureau of Safety and Environmental Enforcement) Drilling regulators directed offshore operators to halt work on oil and gas wells in the U.S. Gulf of Mexico after discovering faulty bolts on equipment used to prevent blowouts. Drillers were told to replace bolts made by General Electric Co. used on equipment including blowout preventers, according to a Jan. 29 safety alert issued by the U.S. Bureau of Safety and Environmental Enforcement. The flaw was discovered after a leak of drilling mud from a Gulf well was blamed on the failure of bolts. Operators using blowout preventers with connectors fastened by the faulty bolts were told to suspend work until the bolts are replaced, according to the safety alert. A spokesman for the bureau, which is part of the Interior Department, wasn’t immediately available for comment on the alert or the industry’s reaction. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/02/06/us-halts-offshore-drilling-halted-on-wells-with-flawed-bolts/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360251060467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:31:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360252886836-12</Id><Topic><Title>Trek back to $80 begins soon</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359065370898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:09:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You were all advised.</Msg><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1360252886836</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:01:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360253599635-13</Id><Topic><Title>A Purified Elite America</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356825754436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 19:02:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump... Keep in mind, too, what the Federal Reserve and Central banks are doing too. The campaign they have in place to control the global economy is unprecedented. They are deliberately attempting to force more and more money into the hands of elites by forcing down interest rates, and asset prices up. At some point interest rates will rise but that will happen after the debt loads are higher, which will entail more money being transferred from low income people, in taxes, to elites who own the debt... The coordination of the entire global economy from Europe, to China, to the USA has never really be tried like this. They attempted it in the 1920s but were limited by the gold standard. It forced incredible concentrations of wealth into the hands of European nobles, American industrialists, etc... Today the program is far bigger and better organized. An important difference, too, is that Germany and the rest of Europe is very highly ordered and not suffering the aftermath of a World War. It is much easier to control society and the economy under such conditions. ..... The USA's government is the weak spot, but prospects for a benign conclusion to the outburst of leftist enthusiasm there and incompetent government are looking more promising now. I still won't invest there but with so many mechanisms in operation to enrich the elite they should be able to right the ship... It will require more taxes of course at some point...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360253599635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:13:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360254085396-14</Id><Topic><Title>A Purified Elite America</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356825754436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 19:02:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump... The debt that the Obama administration is running up (owned by the American upper class mostly) will be helpful in purifying American society too. The interest will certainly be paid by the lower classes. Even if the upper class is taxed and cannot deflect the tax away from itself, the tax to pay the debt they own will just be like money going from one pocket into the other. Elitism is the root to societal success...There is a logic to the policy. I think it would be wiser to balance the US budget immediately and capture the current gains rather than pushing harder, but others have different ideas about what is best. Real estate is very good way to capture gains from this... Upper middle class is the "sweet spot" I think, or if you want to get your hands dirty slumlording could work.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360254085396</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:21:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360254543464-15</Id><Title>OIL PRICES UP, OIL SHARES DOWN</Title><Msg>I guess that makes sense to somebody, not to me. The stock market is manipulated and controlled by banker gangsters. Word up.</Msg><Username>bokuden</Username><Timestamp>1360254543464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:29:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360257346409-16</Id><Topic><Title>Colossal Advancement for Exxon Mobil Corporation. **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>kennethmcintyre60</Username><Timestamp>1360243721253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:28:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already signed up since last week.</Msg><Username>rickyanthony438</Username><Timestamp>1360257346409</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:15:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360257427895-17</Id><Topic><Title>BYE BYE OIL</Title><Username>altrade65</Username><Timestamp>1360121481267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:31:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People have no idea of the many things made from crude oil. Things we like from peanut butter to chocolate to things we use from soap to baby oil are made with crude oil. Your phone and car would be a thing of the past without products from crude oil .</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1360257427895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:17:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360260259061-18</Id><Topic><Title>Colossal Advancement for Exxon Mobil Corporation. **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>kennethmcintyre60</Username><Timestamp>1360243721253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:28:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very honest stuff</Msg><Username>davidphilip302</Username><Timestamp>1360260259061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:04:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360260294887-19</Id><Topic><Title>Colossal Advancement for Exxon Mobil Corporation. **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>kennethmcintyre60</Username><Timestamp>1360243721253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:28:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they all go up huge</Msg><Username>davidphilip302</Username><Timestamp>1360260294887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:04:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360260879895-20</Id><Title>Xom is a great co but BUY EWSI. Now</Title><Msg>Read the news can make serious money here !!! Stock was at 2 dollars and will climb back and hit 3 dollars</Msg><Username>davidrogers615</Username><Timestamp>1360260879895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:14:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360261720487-21</Id><Topic><Title>A Purified Elite America</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1356825754436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 19:02:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>elite they should be able to right the ship</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1360261720487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:28:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360263102317-22</Id><Title>EPA to issue climate change plan Friday</Title><Msg>EPA to issue climate change plan Friday By Ben Goad - 02/07/13 12:24 PM ET The Environmental Protection Agency is set to unveil a plan to counter the effects of climate change. The draft EPA Climate Change Adaptation Plan, to be published for public consideration in Friday’s edition of the Federal Register, is meant to guide the agency’s response to global warming, which it says is occurring at a rapidly increasing rate. “Until now, EPA has been able to assume that climate is relatively stable and future climate would mirror past climate,” reads a notice previewing the plan’s release. “However, with climate changing at an increasingly rapid rate and outside the range to which society has adapted in the past, climate change is posing new challenges to EPA’s ability to fulfill its mission.” The plan is designed to help EPA prepare for future changes in climate by incorporating them into the agency’s operations. The public will have 60 days to comment on the draft. Attempts to obtain more information about the plan froom EPA were not immediately successful. The plan is slated for release days before President Obama is to deliver his State of the Union address to a joint session of Congress this week. He is expected to address climate change, as he did during his second inaugural address last month. “We will respond to the threat of climate change, knowing that the failure to do so would betray our children and future generations,” Obama said. That response is likely to include new federal rules from EPA, cracking down on air pollution. The agency, for example, is weighing whether to propose new emission standards on existing power plants. Industry and opponents and congressional Republicans are vowing to fight those regulations, which could ultimately lead to litigation in the coming years. thehillDOTcom/blogs/regwatch/energyenvironment/281721-epa-to-issue-climate-change-plan-friday-</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360263102317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:51:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263105333-23</Id><Topic><Title>Colossal Advancement for Exxon Mobil Corporation. **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>kennethmcintyre60</Username><Timestamp>1360243721253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:28:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>must keep funds open for this play</Msg><Username>ivorysean279</Username><Timestamp>1360263105333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:51:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263594186-24</Id><Topic><Title>BYE BYE OIL</Title><Username>altrade65</Username><Timestamp>1360121481267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:31:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is a good one,cold fusion ENERGY for all those things. Is that like the King that had no coat?</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1360263594186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:59:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360265631227-25</Id><Topic><Title>Ethanol slowdown not enough, say mandate critics</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360182448426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:27:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Argentina will shortly begin to harvest the largest corn crop they've ever planted. American farmers will likely plant the largest corn crop ever this spring and the 2013 corn harvest will contribute to ethanol mandates for the last three months of the year. Corn glut is on the horizon!</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360265631227</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:33:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360266918372-26</Id><Title>screw job</Title><Msg>tell me why the stock price goes down and the pump price goes up! Yes, somebody is taking it in the rear.</Msg><Username>rallen_46038</Username><Timestamp>1360266918372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:55:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360270081599-27</Id><Title>CVU - Ready to Rally!</Title><Msg>Breakout!</Msg><Username>weinstein_s</Username><Timestamp>1360270081599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:48:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360274165077-28</Id><Topic><Title>screw job</Title><Username>rallen_46038</Username><Timestamp>1360266918372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:55:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you don't understand the lag time between old and new crude, you should study more about your subject. And, that's just the tip of the iceberg.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1360274165077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:56:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360281517210-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ethanol slowdown not enough, say mandate critics</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360182448426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 15:27:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Using food to run our cars doesn't sit well with me. Fracking is so efficient it seems immoral to use food to power my car. I like XOM's fracking business.</Msg><Username>iowababybass</Username><Timestamp>1360281517210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:58:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360286556010-30</Id><Title>Wyden: 'fracking' rule must include public safeguards</Title><Msg>Wyden: 'fracking' rule must include public safeguards By Ben Goad - 02/07/13 07:08 PM ET A hydraulic fracturing rule being revised by the Obama administration should include measures to protect public health and the environment, Sen. Ron Wyden said Thursday. The Oregon Democrat, chairman of the Senate Energy Committee’s subpanel on public lands and forests, sent a letter to outgoing Interior Department Secretary Ken Salazar, contending that a balanced regulation could serve as a model for states and international energy production interests. Hydraulic fracturing, known as “fracking,” involves high-pressure injections of water, chemicals and sand into shale formations to open seams that enable hydrocarbons to flow. Wyden supports the use of “new supplies of cleaner burning natural gas,” but said safeguards must be required as part of the process. “Production of oil and gas resources from our public lands is of great importance to our Nation’s energy supply,” Wyden wrote. “At the same time, residents of neighboring communities must have confidence that the water they drink and the air they breathe will be free of harmful pollutants.” To that end, Wyden is calling for provisions requiring firms to publicly disclose fracking activities and ensure the integrity of wells. He is also urging and monitoring requirements in the rule. The Interior Department issued draft rules last May but last month pulled those back, announcing it would take new comments and revise the proposal. thehillDOTcom/blogs/regwatch/energyenvironment/281865-wyden-fracking-rule-must-include-public-safeguards-</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360286556010</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:22:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>