<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357124572973-1</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi tells Boehner how to vote</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1357099720115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:08:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont worry the whole country going to collapse soon and the teabaggers will rebuild it with out the dumbocraps.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357124572973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 06:02:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357124687710-2</Id><Topic><Title>The newest board idiot = hanseteelyard</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1356983478975</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 14:51:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maxipad is a #$%$ POS that dosnt have a brain.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357124687710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 06:04:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357124830866-3</Id><Topic><Title>The newest board idiot = hanseteelyard</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1356983478975</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 14:51:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very soon maxi dopey the poor #$%$ slob wont be able to find food in the dumpster. He will have to pick the corn out of $hit at the sewer plant.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357124830866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 06:07:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357131410028-4</Id><Title>The Republicans had 1 chance to force a deal on spending....</Title><Msg>1... and they threw it away to appease the Wall Street gamblers who must have been burning up the phone lines 1 Jan after the Republican leadership announced it was against Obama's fiscal cliff bill. Now Obama will totally ignore them on the debt ceiling and use the Senate to flank them. Now he will totally ignore them on gun control and flank them there too. on immigration policy... on war spending... ... ... ... In 2014 the US government will be totally under the control of the Democratic Party when the Republican Party is swept out of the US House. Immigration and Obama ensures it. He owns the agenda and will take credit for what goes well, blame the GOP for what fails, and they will be crushed. The closest parallel for what America will become is probably Germany. The Progressives has been working for over a century to make America like Germany and in some ways the UK, but mostly Germany. When the transformation begins in earnest, after 2014, America will come out of its malaise, and rise powerfully. The 20 year road block of libertarian radicalism that was obstructing things, the road block inaugurated in the early 1990s with the end of the Cold War has been pushed aside...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357131410028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 07:56:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357131948618-5</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi tells Boehner how to vote</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1357099720115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:08:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wall Street on line 1....</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357131948618</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:05:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357132853282-6</Id><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Msg>Job creation? What job creation? Raises for fed workers and Congress? Why? If their pay is performance based, then on what is it based? Certainly not based on quality new jobs created in the private sector! If anything, pay reduction would be in order!</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357133282888-7</Id><Title>Hess Acquisition.</Title><Msg>Avis Kickz Off The New Trading Year With Zipcar (ZIP),for a 50% Premium. Cash Cowz,such as Exxon and Cheveron are rumored to be EyeBalling The Bakken,and it will most likely be Hess that gets taken over. Newz could come out any day,with Hess commanding a 43% surge over the 50 dollar price of recent months. Stench thinkz Hess will be near 67 within Q1,and with oil back above 100 this summer,and a takeover by XOM,We are expecting HES to fetch approximately 100 per share,which is off 20 buckz from all time highs.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1357133282888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:28:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357133788147-8</Id><Title>Real Estate in Imperial America...</Title><Msg>in the South, yes it will have to be there...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357133788147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:36:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357133864506-9</Id><Topic><Title>Hess Acquisition.</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1357133282888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:28:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what language is that? Another dialect perhaps? lol</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357133864506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:37:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357134011151-10</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The same should apply to all corporate leaders until jobs are created and 20 million or more people are no longer in need of public assistance.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357134011151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:40:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357135373276-11</Id><Title>Biodiesel gets big boost in ‘cliff’ vote</Title><Msg>Biodiesel gets big boost in ‘cliff’ vote 6:06 AM, Jan 2, 2013 | by Dan Piller Biodiesel producers in Iowa and elsewhere won a big victory Tuesday when the fiscal cliff compromise passed by congress included reinstatement of the $1 per gallon biodiesel blenders tax credit sought by the industry. Daniel Oh, chief execuive officer of</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357135373276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:02:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357135395261-12</Id><Topic><Title>Biodiesel gets big boost in ‘cliff’ vote</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357135373276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:02:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smyrna is first metro city with biodiesel program WSB Radio-2012-12-31 Smyrna becomes the first city in metro Atlanta to start a biodiesel program. Construction on the project, which makes its own fuel for its vehicles, began about a ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357135395261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:03:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357135916838-13</Id><Title>Iowa ethanol output held steady at 3.7 billion gallons in 2012</Title><Msg>Iowa ethanol output held steady at 3.7 billion gallons in 2012 By Iowa Renewable Fuels Association | December 31, 2012 JOHNSTON, IOWA – The Iowa Renewable Fuels Association announced that Iowa’s 41 ethanol plants produced 3.7 billion gallons during 2012, matching 2011 production. Iowa is estimated to account for roughly 28 percent of national ethanol production in 2012. This is the first time since 2002 where production did not increase year to year. “2012 will be remembered for the great drought,” said IRFA Executive Director Monte Shaw. “Due to Iowa’s incredible farmers, the state weathered the drought better than most. Iowa was fortunate not to have an ethanol plant shut down in 2012. Most plants pulled back on production due to the drought, but we had another plant operating for a full year that offset those reductions. In the end we held steady, but everyone is praying for rain and a trend-line corn yield in 2013 to really jumpstart the industry.” Iowa has 41 ethanol refineries capable of producing over 3.7 billion gallons annually, with one wet mill and two cellulosic ethanol facilities currently under construction. In addition, Iowa has 12 biodiesel facilities with the capacity to produce 315 million gallons annually. The association also pointed out that Iowa motorists could have saved $69 million in 2012 if E15 had been widely available to Iowans who drive 2001 and newer vehicles. The figure was based on gasoline sales data released Dec. 27 by the Iowa Department of Revenue. “$69 million buys a lot of Christmas presents,” Shaw said. “With E15, Iowans can spend less while boosting the Iowa economy. That’s a pretty good deal. IRFA is working with retailers across the state to make E15 access a reality. Until E15 is widely available, Iowans will continue paying more at the pump than they should.” The potential savings with E15, a fuel blend containing 15 percent ethanol, were calculated using 1,630 million gallons of Iowa gasoline use (extrapolated from Iowa Department of Revenue figures). Roughly 85 percent of the fuel sold goes into vehicles that can legally use E15, including all 2001 and newer passenger vehicles. Where E15 has been sold, it has averaged 5 cents per gallon lower than E10. ethanolproducerDOTcom/articles/9414/iowa-ethanol-output-held-steady-at-3-7-billion-gallons-in-2012</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357135916838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:11:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357136234160-14</Id><Topic><Title>Iowa ethanol output held steady at 3.7 billion gallons in 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357135916838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sugar Climbs in London on Economic Outlook; Coffee Also Advances By Claudia Carpenter on January 02, 2013 Sugar advanced in London on speculation that economic growth will boost demand. Coffee also climbed. U.S. lawmakers passed a bill that averted the so-called fiscal cliff. Manufacturing expanded in December in India and China, reports today and yesterday showed. Oil in New York advanced, boosting the appeal of ethanol as an alternative fuel that is made from sugar cane in Brazil. “If energy is supported, then you’re going to see ethanol supported in the U.S. and that would be supportive of sugar,” said Keith Flury, an analyst at Rabobank International in London. “If you assume the U.S. economy is going to grow, then energy prices would be supported based on demand.” White, or refined, sugar for March delivery climbed 1.1 percent to $529.30 a metric ton by 11:14 a.m. in London on NYSE Liffe. Prices dropped 13 percent last year. Sugar has climbed in January every year for the past five years. Buying by investment funds because of changes in the weightings of raw sugar in indexes boosted prices in January the past two years and probably will again this year, Flury said. Raw sugar is one of the 24 commodities in the S&amp;P GSCI gauge. Robusta coffee for March delivery climbed 0.3 percent to $1,929 a ton. Prices gained 6.3 percent last year. Cocoa for March delivery declined 0.1 percent to 1,433 pounds ($2,335) a ton. Prices rose 4 percent last year. businessweekDOTcom/news/2013-01-02/sugar-climbs-in-london-on-economic-outlook-coffee-also-advances</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357136234160</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:17:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357136777412-15</Id><Topic><Title>Iowa ethanol output held steady at 3.7 billion gallons in 2012</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357135916838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BRAZIL: BP invests in higher flexibility ethanol By Fernando Calmon | 2 January 2013 The ethanol market in Brazil remains under pressure after five years of nearly frozen petrol prices. Since biofuel production costs kept rising, its pump prices have been far from competitive for two years. However, BP Biofuels (a subsidiary of the BP oil company) has decided to pour in US$345m at Usina Tropical in Edeia, state of Goiás in the country’s mid-west. The move will create 7,600 direct and indirect jobs by 2014 when production at the refurbished distillery will top 500m litres/110m imperial gallons yearly. Investments, besides an output increase, will deliver more flexible ethanol and sugar production. The split may be 60%-40% for either product according to respective price competitiveness, as opposed to the usual 55%-45% seen here. BP Biofuels has also announced that electric power cogeneration at Tropical (fuelled by waste, crushed sugar cane bagasse) will improve. Up to now there was no such surplus for it was all used up in their own industrial activity. Once the process is completed, 340 GWh will be sold to the national, interlinked power network. Only sugar cane ethanol has the ability to reduce up to 90% of exhaust pipe CO2 emissions, according to Brazilian and foreign scientists. just-autoDOTcom/news/bp-invests-in-higher-flexibility-ethanol_id130251.aspx</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357136777412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:26:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357136974960-16</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sick and tired #$%$ like u wheres the private sector jobs WELL GO TO MCDONALDS , 7 ELEVEN, WALMART they are hiring because in MOST GOV'T jobs you need a COLLEGE DEGREE OR PHD !!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357136974960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:29:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357137308870-17</Id><Topic><Title>Bullish still</Title><Username>audrycusimanobbyz303</Username><Timestamp>1329696763000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-02-19 19:12:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Promised Profit</Msg><Username>charles.meadow</Username><Timestamp>1357137308870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:35:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357137539545-18</Id><Title>Production Tax Credit For Wind Power Saved, For One Year</Title><Msg>Production Tax Credit For Wind Power Saved, For One Year CleanTechnica-45 minutes ago Supporters of the production tax credit for wind power can breathe a little easier, at least for now. Whatever else anybody says about the “fiscal ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357137539545</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:38:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357137905700-19</Id><Title>Geothermal Industry Happy With Last-Minute Congressional Action</Title><Msg>Geothermal Industry Happy With Last-Minute Congressional Action January 2, 2013 Zachary Shahan After months and months of delay (what’s new with Congress these days), important clean energy decisions were finally made by our Congressional representatives just before midnight. The most notable was probably the extension of the wind power production tax credit (PTC) — an article on that is coming in a few moments. However, there’s also some important news regarding the geothermal industry. Here’s a full statement from the Geothermal Energy Association (GEA) on that: The Geothermal Energy Association applauds Congress for adopting today, as part of bi-partisan tax legislation, important changes in the underlying terms of the federal tax incentives for new geothermal and other renewable power projects. The modification adopted, which allows projects to qualify for the production tax credit based upon being under construction, represents an approach to renewable tax incentives that will work more effectively for geothermal and other renewable power technologies that have longer development lead times. “The Geothermal Energy Association estimates that new geothermal power projects in as many as a dozen states could be stimulated to move forward this year as a result of this change,” said GEA Executive Director Karl Gawell. “Congress’ action will spur significant new employment and sustain geothermal industry growth. Consumers and utilities will benefit, as well, because developers will have greater certainty about whether the credit will be available for their project.” Gawell continued: “We applaud the support demonstrated by Congress and the Administration for policies to support growth in geothermal power, and look forward to working with both as they examine longer-term policies to sustain innovation and growth in this emerging industry. In particular we wish to applaud the Senate Finance Committee and Senate Leadership for initiating this important change in the Production Tax Credit.” sDOTtt/1xRKb</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357137905700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:45:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357138129636-20</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Jobs thats why they extended the unemployment benefits for another year you dont need a job,, I am sure Obama has their address where to send the check.</Msg><Username>smkpit</Username><Timestamp>1357138129636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:48:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357138737137-21</Id><Topic><Title>Real Estate in Imperial America...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357133788147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:36:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Atlanta. I do hope I can bear the humidity...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357138737137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:58:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357139102622-22</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The jobs will come when the economy is reorganized. It will take a while. It took some time for the banking and housing speculators to ruin the economy after they set at form 1994-2008... It will take time to fix it. Jan 3, 2015 is when you can expect things to really get going. I guess things look different from the perspective of $82,000,000 in cash. All the same, things will turn around for you. Just you wait and see lol.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357139102622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:05:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357139288110-23</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It must mean they have no idea how they are going to get those people off the government dole by creating jobs. A total failure of our public servants to provide what this country needs to get back on it's feet again. Sure, just keep printing more money and inflating the dollar against foreign currencies from countries we have become so dependent upon for their foreign goods we no longer can afford. Obama's doing a wonderful job fulfilling his goal of destroying the USA. Isn't he?</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357139288110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:08:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357139555076-24</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jobs will come? Then what's been happening in the last 4 years of zero job growth? By 2015, it will be too late. What has changed from a few weeks ago? A few month ago? Nothing! We were still losing jobs three months ago and nothing has happened that will change that! Now has it?</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357139555076</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:12:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357139690699-25</Id><Topic><Title>Whats Wrong Now?</Title><Username>ferrellvqo881</Username><Timestamp>1342966052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:07:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great call!</Msg><Username>charles.meadow</Username><Timestamp>1357139690699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:14:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357140016299-26</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it 2015 yet? You are too impatient... The speculators are still running wild too, or I guess you didn't notice. The GOP sold you out last night to make the speculators richer. Blame them when you pay more for oil. The flood of foreign goods will keep coming in so you can still buy cheaply at Wal-Mart... The longer unemployment stays up the lower wages will go, at least for the people competing with the Chinese peasants... China's the big bonus as far as the strength of the dollar is concerned. They are the 51st US state now and a big one, and quite helpful in keeping down price levels, keeping down wages, breaking the power of unions, etc... The dollar is up quite a bit since 2007 against most currencies, and it will rise more too in the years ahead as they trends continue.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357140016299</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:20:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357140058913-27</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lefties are unreal. You say GOVERNMENT creates jobs! Now suddenly when govt is not creating jobs (except for fed payrolls of course!!) it's the fault of the COMPANIES? obama is taxing corp america to death, they are not GOING to hire if they can't afford to, due to paying taxes, STOOOOPID. get your head out of your a%%.</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1357140058913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:20:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357141274344-28</Id><Title>Trends in the government power</Title><Msg>Shifts in government power and influence in the economy and society across the ages, Western Civilization: Increasing (I+), not increasing (I-) Period 1, 1651-1713, I+ Period 2, 1714-1740, I- Period 3, 1740-1919, I+ Period 4, 1919-1932, I- Period 5, 1933-1991, I+ Period 6, 1992-2014, I- Period 7, 2015-????, I+ Periods 2, 4, 6 were marked by depressions, speculative bubbles, and many economic disasters. Periods 1, 3, 5 were marked by the building up government, education systems, nationalism, military power, big corporations, and expanding big government/big business partnerships in the sciences and industry - sometimes called the military industrial complex, sometimes called other things... 1651 is a convenient starting point because that was when England really began its Imperial career, and started extending the power of state massively. period 6 starts with the collapse of the Soviet Union and runs through the fad of free market, free enterprise ideology that followed it across America and Europe... period 7 will start when the GOP loses the next election</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357141274344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:41:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357141772358-29</Id><Topic><Title>Trends in the government power</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357141274344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:41:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then what happened in the last four years of bleeding more jobs? The Fed cannot hire enough people to offset the loss of jobs. Nothing Congress has done or is about to do in coming months will change the trend which has been set during the last four years. 73% of New Jobs Created in Last 5 Months Are in Government Jobs Are Being Sent To China And They Aren’t Coming Back Government Dependents Outnumber Those With Private Sector Jobs In 11 U.S. States Fix the trade deficit and create private sector jobs, industrial jobs!</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357141772358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:49:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357141999582-30</Id><Topic><Title>Trends in the government power</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357141274344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:41:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This train-wreck of an economy is solely the democrat party's and the republican party's. Total failures, both!</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357141999582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:53:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357142175761-31</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi tells Boehner how to vote</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1357099720115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:08:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no wonder govt spending is going up--having to buy boxes of diapers for the bush gop is getting out of hand</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1357142175761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:56:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357142268895-32</Id><Topic><Title>Trends in the government power</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357141274344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:41:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The government's power has not been increasing the past 4 years. There was a brief uptick in government 2009-2010 when the economy surged back, and then the GOP won control of the Congress and they have been obstructing non-stop ever since. The UK and Germany has been under minimalists government rule the past few years too. France is trying to switch the other way, but, on the whole, the past 4 years has not been marked by an expansion of government power in the economy. Wall Street is still running wild, the speculators are still in control, taxes are still low despite the tiny increase in the GOP's latest defeat. Increasing government power is the kind of thing that happened during the New Deal, Hitler's Germany, or during the Cold War... You don't know what big government on the rise even look like.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357142268895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:57:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357142727089-33</Id><Topic><Title>Trends in the government power</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357141274344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:41:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You don't know what big government on the rise even look(s) like." Oh? Yes we do know by witnessing it ourselves the last 4 years.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357142727089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:05:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357142890305-34</Id><Topic><Title>Trends in the government power</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357141274344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:41:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You don't know what big government on the rise even look(s) like." Oh? Yes we do know by witnessing it ourselves the last 4 years.-- wrong. You will see big government, but not yet. Nov 2014 elections. mark it down... I buy then. You can sell then. I don't really care...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357142890305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:08:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357143413811-35</Id><Topic><Title>Trends in the government power</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357141274344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:41:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does it really matter whether the jobs come from private enterprise or from the govt. - or both? The Scandinavians appear to be doing well compared to us.(USA). One has to do that which bears results and forget about religion or ideologies.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1357143413811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:16:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357143661080-36</Id><Title>Dudes; that 'Deal' will make the economy WORSE!!!</Title><Msg>No new tax income, higher expenditures, greater National Debt... Yeah Baby!! We went down the 'Monetary Manhole' !!</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1357143661080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:21:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357144544366-37</Id><Topic><Title>Trends in the government power</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357141274344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:41:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure, we'll see.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357144544366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:35:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357144640530-38</Id><Topic><Title>Dudes; that 'Deal' will make the economy WORSE!!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1357143661080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:21:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no IMMEDIATE cut to bloated military--worst outcome possible</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1357144640530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:37:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357145206727-39</Id><Topic><Title>Dudes; that 'Deal' will make the economy WORSE!!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1357143661080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:21:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Military Cuts ?? Reptards don't know what that means but grandma, disable,poor childrens LUNCH $$$ CUT CUT CUT !!!! OBAMA FIGHT THESE BASTERDS !!!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357145206727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:46:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357146901113-40</Id><Title>Dollar powering ahead, reversing losses on cliff deal passage...</Title><Msg>The market is a slow learner - having a powerful government (or Imperialistic government) is far better than the alternative of endless compromise, squabbling, etc... Economic problems are easy to solve when the nationalistic spirit is invoked - which is what unified government brings. The crushing defeat of the Boehner and his pack of guinea hens was a big step forward. Obama displayed real leadership in not compromising, and forcing their line to break.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357146901113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:15:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357147904889-41</Id><Topic><Title>Hess Acquisition.</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1357133282888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:28:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stinkbomb please, please #$%$ #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357147904889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:31:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357150773125-42</Id><Topic><Title>Real Estate in Imperial America...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357133788147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:36:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>greed - what now? i thought you were in brentwood. what is it now? why are you promoting atlanta? or is this more mockery?</Msg><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1357150773125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:19:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357152034412-43</Id><Topic><Title>Real Estate in Imperial America...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357133788147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:36:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mock Atlanta? No. Reason for buying there: investment. No. I'm not in Brentwood at the moment, and haven't been for some time now...Where could I be??? lol</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357152034412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:40:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357152270326-44</Id><Title>Could Chevron Jumpstart the North American Natural Gas Sector?</Title><Msg>Could Chevron Jumpstart the North American Natural Gas Sector? Wednesday January 2, 2013, 4:15am PST By Adam Currie - Exclusive to Gas Investing News The natural gas sector ended the year on a high note following the announcement that one of the world’s leading energy firms has agreed to operate — and buy a partial stake in — a proposed liquefied natural gas (LNG) project on Canada’s British Columbia coast. Kitimat LNG’s project moved a step closer to reality last week when Chevron (NYSE:CVX) announced that it will buy out the minority positions that Encana (TSX:ECA,NYSE:ECA) and EOG Resources (NYSE:EOG) hold in the endeavor. In doing so, Chevron has established itself as a 50-percent owner in a project that is ready for construction, but has fallen victim to a number of delays amid uncertainty surrounding sales contracts. Chevron also confirmed that it will take a 50-percent interest in approximately 644,000 acres of petroleum and natural gas rights in the Horn River and Liard Basins in British Columbia. Chevron and Apache (NYSE:APA) will now share ownership of the project, with Chevron operating the plant and related Pacific Trail Pipeline, which is set to transport oil from Northeastern BC. In October 2011, the National Energy Board granted Kitimat LNG a 20-year export license to serve international markets. The proposed project is currently in the resourceinvestingnewsDOTcom/48071-could-chevron-jumpstart-the-north-american-natural-gas-sector.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357152270326</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:44:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357152880738-45</Id><Title>Energy Year Ahead: Energy Lobbyists Gird for Tax Overhaul Fight</Title><Msg>Energy Year Ahead: Energy Lobbyists Gird for Tax Overhaul Fight By Jim Snyder - Jan 1, 2013 10:01 PM MT. 0 Comments A battle is brewing over a potential corporate tax overhaul in 2013, and the prospect fills oil and gas lobbyist Lee Fuller with dread. “As a whole, this industry really doesn’t see an advantage to these proposals that would lower the corporate rates and eliminate deductions,” said Fuller, the vice president for government relations at the Independent Petroleum Association of America. PHOTO Last year, Obama’s call to end the $4 billion in tax subsidies to oil companies died in the Senate for lack of support. Photographer: Patrick T. Fallon/Bloomberg. Translation: the energy industry is going to cling for life to its tax breaks. Repealing investment benefits -- including one that allows deducting the expenses of everything from roadwork to well repair -- will curtail investments that are lowering foreign oil imports and creating thousands of jobs, Fuller said. Critics -- including President Barack Obama -- say oil and gas companies can afford to give more. Tax issues this year will affect businesses here and abroad, from Exxon Mobil Corp. (XOM) to the U.S. unit of Iberdrola SA, a Spanish company that specializes in clean energy, if the White House and Congress get serious about cutting out the dozens of breaks and subsidies in favor of a lower rate. Obama’s call to end the $4 billion in annual tax subsidies to oil companies including Exxon Mobil, the biggest U.S. oil company, has failed to pass in either house of Congress. Green Tax Breaks Green energy interests are also ready to fight to continue their incentives. Wind companies, for example, are trying to protect a credit that shaves as much as a third off the costs of producing power, saying its disappearance will lead to significant job losses. The American Wind Energy Association, a Washington-based group whose members include General Electric Co., released a plan in December to phase out the credit in six years, a concession to growing concerns about the rising federal deficit. One way to raise revenue is to tax carbon dioxide emissions, which could also encourage the development of renewables to address the risks associated with climate change. The idea appears to have greater cachet off Capitol Hill than on it. Senator Ron Wyden, an Oregon Democrat and incoming chairman of the Energy and Natural Resources Committee, says a carbon tax would be a “big lift politically.” Reaching any agreement on energy has been hard to do in recent years. Congress hasn’t passed a major bill since 2007, when lawmakers agreed to raise the fuel-efficiency standards for cars and trucks and set biofuel production targets. Since then, the U.S. energy landscape has undergone a “transformational shift,” Wyden said in a recent interview. Fracking Boom Hydraulic fracturing has increased domestic production of oil and natural gas. That’s lowered imports, and cut gas costs to their lowest level in a decade. Chemical companies are planning to re-locate stateside because natural gas is an important ingredient for their products. Natural gas has also become the fuel of choice for utilities instead of coal. The switch is lowering carbon emissions, even though Obama couldn’t get through Congress a sweeping climate-change bill. Wyden said more direction from Washington could provide businesses with greater certainty over where to invest, expanding growth in an industry that’s already a bright spot in a sluggish economy. One issue he plans to examine is whether natural gas should be exported. Fifteen companies have applied to the Energy Department for permission to sell to markets in Asia and elsewhere. An Energy Department-commissioned study has offered an almost unqualified endorsement of exports. ‘Low-Carbon Economy’ Wyden said that in 2013 he’ll try to promote hydropower, biomass and geothermal power sources to help develop a “low- carbon economy.” On these issues, he said he hopes to find agreement with the top Republican on the panel, Senator Lisa Murkowski of Alaska, whose state shares some of the same resources. Paul Bledsoe, a Washington-based energy consultant, said he’s doubtful Democrats who control the Senate and Republicans in charge of the House can agree on a major bill. One possible way forward would be to couple an energy-efficiency bill with measures expanding offshore oil and gas production. “The real question is whether the parties would rather have a bill or a talking point,” Bledsoe, a former energy adviser to President Bill Clinton, said. ALSO WORTH WATCHING IN 2013: EPA: Lisa Jackson’s planned departure as head of the Environmental Protection Agency leaves President Barack Obama facing a confirmation war as regulators prepare to release final rules imposing the first limits on carbon dioxide emissions. Congressional Republicans have sought unsuccessfully to prevent the EPA from acting under the Clean Air Act to fight global warming. In 2013, a new administrator may come under fresh attacks if the agency acts to limit greenhouse gases from existing facilities. Now proposed rules are limited to new power plants. KEYSTONE: The State Department says it will make a determination about TransCanada Corp. (TRP)’s pipeline from Alberta’s oil sands to refineries in Texas early in 2013. Environmentalists oppose the project because they say it promotes development of tar sands mining, which releases more carbon dioxide than oil drilling. CONFERENCES: From solar panels to Canadian oil sands, there is no shortage of talking topics at various energy conferences tracked by the U.S. Energy Information Agency. bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-01-02/energy-year-ahead-energy-lobbyists-gird-for-tax-overhaul-fight.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357152880738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:54:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357154733162-46</Id><Title>Currency Trade III</Title><Msg>buying euro. 1.3168 $/€... 100% €. some real estate in Munich...and pocket cash. the euphoria over Boehner's defeat and the short covering rally in the US has run its course I think.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357154733162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:25:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357154766481-47</Id><Title>Oil industry urges court to scuttle offshore drilling challenge</Title><Msg>Oil industry urges court to scuttle offshore drilling challenge By Ben Geman - 01/02/13 10:29 AM ET The oil industry wants a federal court to dismiss a green group’s lawsuit against Interior Department plans to conduct new offshore oil-and-gas lease sales, alleging the environmentalists lack standing to bring the case. The American Petroleum Institute and other groups, in a Dec. 31 filing, say the Center for Sustainable Economy (CSE) can’t establish so-called representational standing because it’s not a membership organization. Industry groups also say CSE doesn’t have a sufficient stake as an organization, noting it has not suffered the “particularized injury” from Interior's action needed to clear the bar for standing to bring the case, among other arguments. CSE is challenging Interior’s 2012-2017 auctions for drilling blocks in the Gulf of Mexico and off Alaska’s coast, claiming the economic analysis underlying the leasing plan is “critically flawed, biased and incomplete.” Attorneys for the group say the plan should be redone because Interior failed to consider the economic value of not going ahead with leasing, in some cases. E2-Wire has more on CSE’s case against Interior’s plan here. API, the Independent Petroleum Association of America, the U.S. Oil &amp; Gas Association and the International Association of Drilling Contractors are seeking to intervene in the case on Interior’s side. The groups’ filing with the U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit makes several arguments against CSE’s ability to establish the legal standing needed to bring the case. Here’s a bit from the filing about why the industry groups argue CSE can’t show that it will suffer an injury from Interior’s plan: CSE as an organization plainly has not suffered any legally cognizable injury. By its self-description to this Court, CSE “works to speed the transition to a sustainable society through rigorous analysis of policy, programs, and projects, by developing creative solutions for government agencies, businesses, non-profits, and educators, and by providing expert support for legislative, administrative, and legal campaigns.” ... Nothing in the approval of the 2012-17 leasing program will impair CSE’s ability to continue to pursue that political agenda. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/275169-oil-industry-urges-court-to-scuttle-offshore-drilling-challenge</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357154766481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:26:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357155185916-48</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi tells Boehner how to vote</Title><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1357099720115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 23:08:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP speculators around here, the ones who like to pass themselves off as "investors," won't even show themselves today either. They must feel too ashamed to be profiting off what was a total rout and sellout of their party... sordid, very sordid. .. They will get an opportunity to feel miserable about both the sellout and the losses ahead which will only intensify as the GOP is not finished throwing wrenches in the works of the economy yet.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357155185916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:33:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357155784713-49</Id><Title>Three ethanol tax credits extended for 2013</Title><Msg>Three ethanol tax credits extended for 2013 Renewable Fuels Association | January 2, 2013 The American Taxpayer Relief Act of 2012, that was approved by both the Senate and House included extension of three key ethanol related tax credits, Bob Dinneen, president and CEO of the Renewable Fuels Association, noted. “The one year extension of the cellulosic producer tax credit and accelerated depreciation provides some measure of certainty to ensure that 2013 will be a year of growth and milestones for the advanced ethanol industry. “In addition, and equally significant, is the extension of the alternative fuel infrastructure tax credit which will accelerate E15’s entry into the marketplace this coming year. The extension of these important provisions demonstrates the Obama Administration’s stalwart support of biofuels and Congress’s belief in the promise of energy independence and job creation through domestic renewable energy resources,” claims Dinneen. agprofessionalDOTcom/news/Three-ethanol-tax-credits-extended-for-2013-185421912.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357155784713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:43:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357157046297-50</Id><Title>Chevron chief dismisses climate change concerns</Title><Msg>Chevron chief dismisses climate change concerns Last updated on 2 January 2013, 12:03 pm Climate change must come second to economic growth and the continued exploitation of fossil fuels according to Chevron CEO John Watson. In an interview with news agency AP published in the Washington Post, Watson argues oil, gas and coal are the only “affordable” sources of energy available to governments. Reports from the World Bank and accountants PwC published in November 2012 warned that the world is on a trajectory to warm 4-6°C by 2100, which scientists say would lead to catastrophic changes in the global climate, together with rising sea levels. But Watson, whose company is planning to invest $33 billion in oil and gas exploration this year, says efforts to take direct action to address climate change, such as putting a tax on carbon, are inappropriate as they will put pressure on energy process and the world economy. Chevron CEO John Watson: The company is the second largest investor-owned oil and gas business in the world, reportedly making a $24 billion profit in 2012 “It’s very difficult for the United States to go it alone. Watch what (other) governments do. The day-to-day decisions being made (show) that concern about climate change is less than other concerns that they have,” he said. “China is racing by the US in greenhouse gas emissions. Germany is shutting down their nuclear power, the only energy source with zero carbon emissions that can be produced at scale. Japan, much the same way. “Governments around the world are making the choice that the benefits of lifting people out of squalor are very important. And affordable energy is the way to get there. And that currently comes through oil, gas and coal.” Watson also appeared to dismiss renewable technologies such as wind and solar, arguing against “big subsidies on technologies that we know are more expensive and won’t necessarily solve the issue”. Instead he suggests instead governments should invest in energy efficiency and back “pre-commercial activity to try to advance some of these breakthrough technologies”, although these technologies were not named during the interview. A report from the International Energy Agency (IEA) released in 2011 revealed fossil fuel subsidies last year reached $523bn in 2011. Renewable energy subsidies during the same period totalled $88bn. The IEA say energy efficiency measures could keep the door to limiting warming to 2°C open for an additional five years. At present rates, this threshold of warming, beyond which scientists classify the changes as “dangerous”, will be reached in 2017, but efficiency could push this back to 2022. rtccDOTorgn/chevron-chief-dismisses-climate-change-concerns/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357157046297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:04:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357157726778-51</Id><Topic><Title>Currency Trade III</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357154733162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:25:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>selling for $, 1.3178, +0.075% 100% $</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357157726778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:15:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357158074148-52</Id><Topic><Title>Real Estate in Imperial America...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357133788147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:36:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MUNICH</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357158074148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:21:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357160737554-53</Id><Title>You Disgust Me, Christie Tells Boehner Over Aid</Title><Msg>Wow I agree for the first time with Christie. Is this progress ?? NO he's been Disgusting to me Boehner since 2010 !!! NY &amp; NJ PULL THAT $$$ OUT FROM THEIR COFFERS !!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357160737554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:05:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357160950067-54</Id><Topic><Title>You Disgust Me, Christie Tells Boehner Over Aid</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357160737554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:05:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did it take training for you to become a complete idiot, or were you just born that way?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1357160950067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:09:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357163069133-55</Id><Topic><Title>You Disgust Me, Christie Tells Boehner Over Aid</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357160737554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:05:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask your MOTHER who trains MENTAL MIDGET like u !!! People r suffering u #$%$!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357163069133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:44:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357163580451-56</Id><Title>LMAO Sean Hannity’s ratings have Plummeted !!! U r great American Voters saw his BS !!</Title><Msg>"Sean Hannity’s ratings have plummeted since Barack Obama’s second victory. Nielsen ratings show that Hannity’s audience is leaving in droves; approximately half in the weeks after the election with Rachel Maddow still leading the Fox host. NYDailyNews reports, “Bill O’Reilly — who steadfastly refuses to identify himself politically as a conservative — retained around 70% of his audience. After a stunned audience had to go to bed finding that President Obama was reelected, apparently the anti-Obama sentiment proved to be a colossal failure." COLOSSAL FAILURE !!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357163580451</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:53:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357163774358-57</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO Sean Hannity’s ratings have Plummeted !!! U r great American Voters saw his BS !!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357163580451</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:53:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont worry he still has like 5 Mental Midgets fans on this board !! The SMART ones had left long time ago !!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357163774358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:56:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357165907374-58</Id><Topic><Title>You Disgust Me, Christie Tells Boehner Over Aid</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357160737554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:05:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pra pra is a #$%$ POS. christie turned dumbocrap the rat traitor.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357165907374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:31:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357166039185-59</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After nobumba winning election jobs are leaving and never coming back. Hope its the #$%$ libs that cant work and then starve like the rats they are.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357166039185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:33:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357167940236-60</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the jobs?</Title><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357132853282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:20:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so what do you suggest "greedy" ?? Another PHONY war to overthrow daddys' nemesis ?? A tax cut to pay for your PHONY war ?? how about largest expansion of govt employees since FDR all employed by TSA?? how about FREE prescription drugs for medicare WITH NO negotiations for pricing how about bailing out AIG/Bear Stearns-Merrill/ how about making the USPS sponsor Lance Armstrongs bicycle team for a few million how about putting your head back up in your bung where you normally insert it it won't smell any worse than the gop stench of john boehners and the teabags dirty diapers--what a cowardly 4 year display of huff-puff-and stink the drawers no wonder someone like you admires a paul ryan and sarah palin--ignorant filth</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1357167940236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:05:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357177378030-61</Id><Topic><Title>Sold on the news today....</Title><Username>sushibn</Username><Timestamp>1357165313786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:21:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And so are the Myan Apocalypse. whoopsy, another miss prognostication. Listen up! This market is the best January new year run since 2009', and that was The last time Obama was elected. Getting the picture now?</Msg><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1357177378030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:42:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357177948750-62</Id><Title>Buffett to build world’s largest photovoltaic solar project</Title><Msg>Buffett to build world’s largest photovoltaic solar project Posted on January 2, 2013 at 1:30 pm by Bloomberg Solar panels are installed in Arlington, Ariz. (AP Photo/Ross D. Franklin, File) By Tina Davis and Amanda Jordan Jan. 2 (Bloomberg) — Warren Buffett’s MidAmerican Energy Holdings Co. agreed to spend as much as $2.5 billion to build two solar projects in California that are set to be the world’s largest photovoltaic development. MidAmerican acquired the 579-megawatt Antelope Valley projects in Kern and Los Angeles counties from SunPower Corp., according to a statement today. MidAmerican will pay San Jose, California-based SunPower $2 billion to $2.5 billion for the projects and a three-year contract to build them. SunPower also will operate and maintain the projects under a multiyear agreement with MidAmerican. Buffett has been increasing investment in wind and solar farms and last year formed a MidAmerican unit to support the projects it’s acquired, including the $2.4 billion 550-megawatt Topaz solar farm in California. Chief Financial Officer Patrick Goodman said in November the company favors bets on renewable energy amid high utility valuations. California is the biggest U.S. solar market. The sale gives panel-maker SunPower “a sizable captive demand channel for its modules which should help ensure the company maintains healthy factory utilization levels even if the oversupply conditions in the industry take longer than expected to be resolved,” Ben Kallo and Christopher M. Kovacs, analysts for Robert W. Baird &amp; Co., said in a note today. Ingrid Ekstrom, a spokeswoman for SunPower, declined to specify how much of the total amount being spent is construction costs and how much is the purchase price. SunPower is 66 percent owned by France’s Total SA, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. 2015 Completion Construction of the Antelope Valley project is due to begin this quarter, with completion by the end of 2015, SunPower said in a filing with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. “Together, the two combined projects will form the largest permitted solar photovoltaic power development in the world and will create an estimated 650 jobs during construction,” according to the statement. The projects will provide energy to Edison International under two long-term power-purchase contracts. MidAmerican Renewables, a subsidiary of MidAmerican Energy, has more than 1,830 megawatts of assets, including wind power, geothermal, solar and hydro, according to today’s statement. MidAmerican is owned by Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway Inc. SunPower rose 6.6 percent to $5.99 at 12:28 p.m. in New York. Berkshire, based in Omaha, Nebraska rose 3.4 percent to $138,653. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/01/02/buffett-to-build-worlds-largest-photovoltaic-solar-project/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357177948750</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:52:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357179021211-63</Id><Topic><Title>Buffett to build world’s largest photovoltaic solar project</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357177948750</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:52:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how much is obama giving him of our tax dollars? Must be an angle here from heir obama.</Msg><Username>eagle1776321</Username><Timestamp>1357179021211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:10:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357179926745-64</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO Sean Hannity’s ratings have Plummeted !!! U r great American Voters saw his BS !!</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357163580451</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:53:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ #$%$ #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357179926745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:25:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357180142368-65</Id><Topic><Title>Buffett to build world’s largest photovoltaic solar project</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357177948750</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:52:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They kept their tax break this round.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1357180142368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:29:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357180584545-66</Id><Topic><Title>You Disgust Me, Christie Tells Boehner Over Aid</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1357160737554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:05:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Christie did what most who followed the money " Big O "said was there and got the green W from the "Big O who is from the Big C town".</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1357180584545</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:36:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357184343958-67</Id><Title>2 JAN--Boehner already wins "Coward of Year" award</Title><Msg>showing ballsak the size of a hamster ; the spkr--John Boehner folded on every GOP talking point he has hidden behind for 4 years from the Hastert rule to grover pledges just the biggest "stink the drawers" in US Congress history and that took a lot--but he pulled it off</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1357184343958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:39:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>