<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372681809405-1</Id><Topic><Title>☛☛☛☛NOBAMA, Supreme Court, DEMOCRATS...Laughing stock of the world...</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1372575196408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 02:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just think, here it is JULY 4 and no NOBAMA in the USA. Oh I forgot he went home on our tax dollar (100 M).</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1372681809405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 08:30:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372684787589-2</Id><Title>Gas exporters to defend pricing as courts reject oil link</Title><Msg>Gas exporters to defend pricing as courts reject oil link Posted on July 1, 2013 at 7:07 am by Bloomberg The world’s biggest natural gas exporters will seek to defend linking prices to the cost of oil even after courts ruled they overcharged customers and rising output from the U.S. to Australia challenges their dominance. Tying gas costs to oil will dominate “in the long-term” as the system provides visibility and transparency for buyers, the Gas Exporting Countries Forum said before its second summit of heads of state today in Moscow. RWE AG (RWE) said June 27 an arbitration court ruled that Germany’s second-largest utility had paid Russia’s OAO Gazprom (GAZP) too much since May 2010 and forced the group’s biggest producer to add links to market prices in its formula. Utilities are challenging the 40-year-old system after European market prices slumped below oil-linked contracts as the debt crisis cut demand for energy. State-controlled Gazprom has earmarked as much as 200 billion rubles ($6 billion) for potential rebates to European utilities this year. The estimate is higher than the 114 billion rubles set aside in 2012 and enough to meet all necessary payments, Chief Financial Officer Andrey Kruglov said June 27 in Moscow. “This could well be the tipping point that ushers in a new commercial era for European gas,” Trevor Sikorski, an analyst at Energy Aspects Ltd. in London, said June 28 by e-mail. “If so, the impact will be felt wider than Europe, with Asian customers looking longingly at European and U.S. hub prices, and seeing that commercial arbitration might be one way of lessening the burden.” Sonatrach, RasGas Electricite de France SA, Europe’s biggest power producer, in April obtained lower gas prices for its Italian unit Edison SpA through arbitration with Sonatrach of Algeria, Europe’s third-biggest supplier after Russia and Norway. Qatar’s Ras Laffan Liquefied Natural Gas Co. has also lost an arbitration case related to oil-linked</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372684787589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 09:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372685050560-3</Id><Title>U.S. says oil market can cope with more Iran export cuts</Title><Msg>U.S. says oil market can cope with more Iran export cuts June 30, 2013|Fredrik Dahl | Reuters VIENNA (Reuters) - The top U.S. energy official said he believed the oil market could cope with any further reduction of Iran's oil exports from the tightening of sanctions on Tehran over its nuclear program. U.S. Energy Secretary Ernest Moniz also said on Sunday he expected a "fair amount of action" by his department in 2013 in evaluating applications by U.S. firms to export natural gas. Companies hoping to ship gas abroad have been frustrated by lengthy delays and rule changes as they await Department of Energy approval of their applications. "I'm planning to go through them as rapidly as I can," Moniz said in an interview in Vienna. As for Iran, U.S. lawmakers are embarking this summer on a campaign to deal a deeper blow to its diminishing oil exports, and analysts say the ultimate goal could be a near total cut-off. This could risk antagonizing China and India, the biggest remaining buyers of Iranian crude, and could push oil prices higher in a hit to the global economy. Moniz said Iranian exports were not now a "dominant player in the market", and was offset by increased production in the United States and in Iraq as well as substantial reserve capacity in some of the major OPEC producers such as Saudi Arabia. "So I would think that with further sanctions, the markets could be quite resilient to that," said Moniz, who took office last month. From a technical point of view, "we can certainly manage a further reduction of Iranian exports", he added. U.S. and European Union sanctions aimed at choking the flow of oil money into Iran and forcing Tehran to negotiate curbing its controversial nuclear program slashed its crude exports to 700,000 bpd in May, the lowest in decades, according to industry sources and tanker-tracking data. But crude prices are still lower than they were a year ago. Iran says its nuclear program is a peaceful bid to generate electricity.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372685050560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 09:24:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372685504536-4</Id><Title>ND drillers to get tax breaks natural gas usage</Title><Msg>ND drillers to get tax breaks natural gas usage Posted on July 1, 2013 at 6:53 am by Associated Press in Natural gas A drilling rig aims for oil in the Bakken Shale near Watford City, N.D. (AP Photo/James MacPherson) BISMARCK, N.D. — New legislation offers North Dakota oil drillers tax breaks beginning Monday if they stop burning and wasting natural gas. The Republican-sponsored bills passed the Legislature this year. They offer oil companies tax incentives for capturing and using the byproduct of the state’s booming crude production. Records show 275 million cubic feet of natural gas goes up in smoke each day in North Dakota, or enough to heat more than 1 million homes daily. Flaring also accounted for about 5 million tons of carbon dioxide emissions in North Dakota last year. That’s about the same amount that 945,000 automobiles would emit. About one-third of the state’s gas production is being burned off because development of the pipelines and processing facilities needed to handle it has not kept pace with production. fuelfix</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372685504536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 09:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372686848175-5</Id><Title>The Fiat 500e EV is sold out at all the Fiat dealerships in California.</Title><Msg>The Fiat 500e EV is sold out at all the Fiat dealerships in California.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372686848175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 09:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372687031354-6</Id><Title>GE’s Brilliant Wind Turbine — Wind Power Cheaper Than Coal Or Natural Gas (Part 3)</Title><Msg>GE’s Brilliant Wind Turbine — Wind Power Cheaper Than Coal Or Natural Gas (Part 3) July 1, 2013 Andrew This is Part 3 of a 3-part series on GE’s Brilliant 1.6-100 wind turbine. Check out Part 1 and Part 2 or the rest of our GE Brilliant Wind Turbine archives for more on the Brilliant 1.6-100 wind turbine. Big Data And The Industrial Internet Meet In The GE Brilliant 1.6-100 Impressively, everything spinning on the Tehachapi hills at GE’s Power &amp; Wind research site continues to supply clean, renewable electricity to the Southern California Edison (SCE) grid. This includes a prototype of the 1.6-100′s predecessor, the GE 1.5-77 wind turbine, which has been up, running, and supplying electricity to SCE customers in LA and other parts of southern California for well over a decade. “We’ve made incredible gains since acquiring the property,” Longtin stated, pointing out that today’s GE turbines are operating at close to 98% availability (97.6%), the same as a thermal coal plant. Furthermore, he continued, “with the introduction of the 1.6-100, we’ve also improved the capacity factor (a measure of energy efficiency) from 35% ten years’ ago to over 50% today.” Over 50% capacity factor is far above the capacity factor that most people think of when they think of wind turbines. Clearly, very significant strides have been made to get to such a high percentage. Contributing to the boost in turbine availability and efficiency, GE’s Brilliant 1.6-100 captures and converts more wind energy at lower (Class 3) wind speeds, which, by definition, blow at 7.5 meters per second (m/s). These and other wind turbine advances and enhancements translate into more clean, renewable, wind-generated electricity at far lower cost. Now 12 years old, GE’s 1.5-77 turbine has generated enough clean, renewable electricity to supply some 350 California homes with electricity. The Brilliant 1.6-100 doubles down on that, producing enough for 700. Moreover, GE has also made great strides in term</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372687031354</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 09:57:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372695703816-7</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You two clowns need to get a life........your posts are worthless and a nuisance.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1372695703816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 12:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372695748083-8</Id><Topic><Title>cut 'n paste bluecheese............</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1372122828910</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 21:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give it a rest, already !</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1372695748083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 12:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372695787623-9</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese is a walking encyclopedia.....</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370133089920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All he does it cut and paste #$%$.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1372695787623</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 12:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372695813090-10</Id><Topic><Title>Bluecheese: All his posts are "absolutely worthless" !</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371752941651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong answer !</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1372695813090</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 12:23:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372703001460-11</Id><Title>Moniz: CO2 could enhance US oil by millions of barrels a day (video)</Title><Msg>Moniz: CO2 could enhance US oil by millions of barrels a day (video) July 1, 2013 at 10:02 am by Jennifer A. Dlouhy The future of coal-fired power may lie in still-developing technology to capture the carbon dioxide it produces and put it to work in the oil field, Energy Secretary Ernest Moniz suggested. In an interview with Platts Energy Week, Moniz talked up the potential not just for capturing and storing the carbon dioxide produced by burning fossil fuels, but using more of it to glean oil from aging fields. Oil and gas companies are already using the method — known as enhanced oil recovery — around the United States, but Moniz sees it ramping up significantly. “We’re producing about 300,000 barrels per day using carbon dioxide to enhance oil recovery from older fields,” Moniz told the energy news show. “The estimates are that could increase by a factor of 10 to about 3 million barrels a day.” But that would require a whole lot more carbon dioxide — about 600 megatons per year. And according to Moniz, “we could only get that by capturing it from industrial sources, power plants.” CBO: Future bleak for carbon-cutting technology The Energy Department is working to accelerate some enhanced oil recovery technology and operations. For instance, it has provided about $431 million toward a project at Valero’s refinery in Port Arthur, Texas, where carbon dioxide is now being extracted from two steam methane reformers, then dried, compressed and shipped to the West Hastings oil field 20 miles south of Houston. Pumping the greenhouse gas underground has two benefits: Not only does it help pull more crude out of the site, but it also indefinitely stores the carbon dioxide underground. The Port Arthur project involves just 1 million metric tons of carbon dioxide a year — which puts the potential scale of future efforts in perspective. But carbon capture technology is still a long way from being commercially viable. The Energy Department is expected to play a major</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372703001460</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 14:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372703193474-12</Id><Title>EPA sends White House revised emissions rule for new power plants</Title><Msg>EPA sends White House revised emissions rule for new power plants Zack Colman 07/01/13 12:05 PM ET The Environmental Protection Agency on Monday sent its revised greenhouse gas emissions rule for new power plants to the White House, The Hill has confirmed. The contents of the proposed rule, which now rests in the White House Office of Management and Budget, remain sealed. While its substance is unknown, moving the rule puts the climate plan President Obama announced last week into motion. “EPA is moving forward on the President's plan to address carbon pollution from power plants using the same Clean Air Act tools that have protected Americans' health and environment from air pollution for a generation. For newly built power plants, the plan calls for EPA to issue a new proposal by September 20, 2013. As part of this process, EPA has sent the new proposal for interagency review,” the EPA told The Hill in an email. OMB and other agencies will now assess the revised rule and later return it to the EPA. The EPA had missed an April deadline for finalizing the rule for yet-to-be built plants. The agency said it needed time to review the 2 million public comments the rule invited, though insiders say the EPA pulled back to tinker with it in hopes of withstanding legal challenges from industry. The tweaked rule is expected to establish separate emissions standards for coal- and natural-gas fired power plants. The original version didn't differentiate between fuel sources, which rankled the utility industry. The original draft rule effectively barred construction of new coal-fired power plants unless they include state-of-the-art technology that traps and then stores carbon pollution underground. It earned plaudits from Democrats, greens and public health advocates who say it will stymie the effects of climate change and improve health. But Republicans, some coal-state Democrats and industry charge the rule is too harsh, contending it will cripple the econom</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372703193474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 14:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372708791487-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bluecheese: All his posts are "absolutely worthless" !</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371752941651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jojomaxi u commie POS idiot shut ur dumb mouth.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1372708791487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 15:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372711458568-14</Id><Topic><Title>EXOM- Cramers new Gold eom.</Title><Username>hedgecutter10</Username><Timestamp>1372178160571</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Hedge, I didn`t mean to come off disrespectful, but I did look up eom and I found over 150 acronyms (end of message included) . I apologize if I might have come across a little snippy but you`re right, being close to 70, there are a lot of little things I should learn but at this stage of the game I sometimes get short. Thanks for responding.</Msg><Username>gasspump</Username><Timestamp>1372711458568</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 16:44:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372714595242-15</Id><Topic><Title>EPA sends White House revised emissions rule for new power plants</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372703193474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 14:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coal..... how does this tie into XOM?</Msg><Username>ephrems_law</Username><Timestamp>1372714595242</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:36:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372731270779-16</Id><Title>O..l...a</Title><Msg>ki.....fer... 22.22</Msg><Username>boldchris</Username><Timestamp>1372731270779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 22:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>