<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370837332740-1</Id><Topic><Title>The King's of useless info:</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370821613927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The overriding theme of my posts is that the oil industry will be bankrupt sooner than you would like. At one time you thought I was one of your famous oil pigs and a Republican so I suppose bluecheese is an improvement. By the way, you will not get yourself invited to my Christmas Party at my new place in the Grunewald in Berlin with such posts as you’ve produced on this board. If you were hoping for more posts you could make money from, ones like the currency &amp; bond trades, that’s just too bad. My mind is occupied with Cinderella &amp; fairy theme décor and flowery wallpapers. Lombard Street trading combat mode would spoil my mood. Try it yourself. You will see rather quickly how nice it would be to have useful information &amp; genes, and just how much money you can lose in their absence.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1370837332740</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 00:08:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370837437951-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer presidency unraveling daily......I LOVE IT !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370798162113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:16:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Die Partie ist Obama!!! 4 More Years! 4 More Years! 4 More Years! 4 More Years! We couldn't hope for a better American Commander-in-Chief to run the ship aground... lol</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1370837437951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 00:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370841936749-3</Id><Title>US shale boom putting OPEC on the defense</Title><Msg>June 9, 2013 at 6:00 am by Harry R. Weber OPEC’s weakening grip on international oil markets is causing a lot of head scratching and hand wringing among countries that aren’t used to not getting their way. While the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries is studying the U.S. shale boom’s impact on the cartel, analysts say there is very little OPEC can do — and, some argue, should do — to turn the tide. “I imagine some members of OPEC may be flipping out over shale oil,” Morningstar analyst Jason Stevens said. That doesn’t mean U.S. consumers should expect the changing dynamic to cause a sharp drop in prices for crude and gasoline over the long-term. Analysts: Global oil boom will force Saudi Arabia to cut oil production At least for the time being, OPEC appears to be taking a measured approach, even as some of its 12 member countries pressure the group to be more aggressive in tightening production to prop up prices in support of government budgets that rely heavily on oil prices of $100 a barrel or higher. OPEC oil ministers opted last month at their most recent meeting to keep production steady at 30 million barrels a day. They said the relative steadiness of prices so far this year shows the market is adequately supplied. Brent crude, which is used to price oil from the North Sea and is the benchmark for world prices, traded around $100 a barrel last week while West Texas Intermediate, the U.S. benchmark, was about $94 a barrel. The spread has narrowed significantly in recent months. U.S. gasoline, meanwhile, averaged $3.65 a gallon for regular last week, up 3 cents over the same week in June of 2012, according to the U.S. Energy Information Administration. It averaged $3.370 a gallon in Texas Friday, according to AAA. Refined product prices are tied more to Brent crude than to West Texas Intermediate. So while higher U.S. oil production reduces imports, fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/06/09/opec-on-the-defense-amid-us-shale-boom/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370841936749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 01:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370842671781-4</Id><Title>INSIGHT-Ethanol lobby sees red over a yellow gas hose in Kansas</Title><Msg>Cezary Podkul NEW YORK, June 10 | Mon Jun 10, 2013 1:00am EDT (Reuters) - At a handful of gas stations in eastern Kansas, the intensifying fight between major oil refiners and the ethanol industry over the future of America's fuel supply has found a new focus: the color of the gas hose. Scott Zaremba, owner of Lawrence, Kansas-based Zarco 66, says he is being forced by his main fuel supplier, Phillips 66 , to stop selling gasoline blended with 15 percent ethanol, the maximum level currently allowed for use in normal car engines but higher than the 10 percent norm. Zaremba, the first retailer in the country to sell the so-called E15 fuel, has found himself caught in a fierce market-share battle between ethanol makers and oil companies that is also being fought in the courts and in the U.S. Congress. On April 1, Zaremba received a notice from Phillips 66, the nation's third-largest refiner, that he could no longer sell the E15 fuel from his regular black fuel hoses, as he had been selling it since last July. Instead, any gasoline with more than 10 percent ethanol has to be served from a separate, yellow hose, according to a copy of the Phillips 66 guidelines seen by Reuters. The aim is to distinguish E15 from other Phillips 66-branded gasolines with 10 percent or less ethanol. He has other options, but they aren't cheap - or very feasible. For example, it would cost $100,000 to $250,000 to install new stand-alone gas pumps for E15, Zaremba said. Or he can always pay a $412,000 fee to Phillips 66 to break his marketing contract - expensive options that have so far kept him in compliance with the Phillips 66 guidelines, the only way he said he could. In April, Zaremba began phasing out E15 sales, leaving only some two dozen stations in the country that sold the blend as of the end of May, when the last of his eight stations gave up the fuel. "They're just holding reutersDOTcom/article/2013/06/10/e15-rules-phillips-idUSL1N0EH2ES20130610</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370842671781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 01:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370846317442-5</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon positives</Title><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1370792271864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:37:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good post. I agree. one other item: they have been ramping investments over the past few years in a long lead industry. those investments may soon start to add to growth one of my favorites not a recommendation. do your own dd</Msg><Username>nli200808</Username><Timestamp>1370846317442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 02:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370857377398-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer presidency unraveling daily......I LOVE IT !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1370798162113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:16:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mr luck is a commie POS moron.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1370857377398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 05:42:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370870361021-7</Id><Title>Cool Planet Nears Commercial Production of Carbon Negative Biofuel</Title><Msg>June 10, 2013 Tina Casey California based Cool Planet Energy has just announced almost $30 million in funding toward a goal of $100 million to build its first commercial facility for producing low cost biofuel that is not just carbon neutral, it’s carbon negative. Yes, that’s what Cool Planet has promised: it will produce bio-gasoline at a cost of under $1.50 per gallon without government subsidy, along with a biochar coproduct that will increase crop yields while capturing carbon from the atmosphere. Sounds good, right? Well, let’s take a look and see what Cool Planet’s biofuel venture is all about. Cool Planet Energy’s Plan For Biofuel We first caught up with Cool Planet Energy just last fall, when the company announced that its pilot facility scale facility in Camarillo had passed muster, producing drop-in biofuel that is chemically identical to gasoline. The process is focused on miscanthus but can also work on other woody biomass including agricultural waste. Setting aside the carbon-negative claim for now, Cool Planet’s system combines a number of carbon-reducing elements that are common to next-generation biofuel strategies. That includes using non-food feedstocks including hardy perennials like miscanthus, and relying on feedstocks that require little preparation prior to processing. That would be miscanthus again, which can be air-dried in the field to reduce moisture content to the optimal level. Cool Planet has also compared its refining process to a “kitchen stovetop” in terms of its relatively low operating temperature and pressure. One interesting aspect of Cool Planet’s strategy is its focus on commercializing modular, transportable micro-biorefineries which can be located at or near biofuel croplands, which should help reduce carbon emissions related to feedstock transportation. The prefabricated micro-refinery approach is cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/06/10/cool-planet-nears-commercial-production-of-low-cost-biofuel/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370870361021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370873813229-8</Id><Title>Is anyone interested in 300-400% return in the next 2 months?</Title><Msg>Take a look at a beaten down jr. oil stock - IVAN (on Nasdaq). They're trading at an all time low, despite the fact that they're only a month away from getting an approval for their Tamarack project located in AB, Canada. That will add at least $4.50 per share to the stock price. They are also a month or two away from signing a deal with Ecuador to develop 20B barrels of heavy oil. Look at ivahnoe-energy web site for latest presentation. The stock price is going to go up 6-7 times within the next 2 months!</Msg><Username>her_vam_dam</Username><Timestamp>1370873813229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:16:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370875733807-9</Id><Topic><Title>The King's of useless info:</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370821613927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You actually have a Christmas party? Why would an atheist have a Christmas party? Remember it is Jesus Christ that puts the Christ in Christmas. Ironic, a bunch of green liberals discussing their wives, mistresses and girlfriends recent abortions, how to tax the rich and give it to the poor, gay rights, socialism, and animal cruelty at a Christmas party. What's wrong with this picture?</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1370875733807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370875791476-10</Id><Topic><Title>The King's of useless info:</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370821613927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Darn, I'm heartbroken...........</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370875791476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370875986294-11</Id><Title>Would like to see more move up</Title><Msg>XOM is rated buy at stoxline website with the 109.21 target price in six months.</Msg><Username>fyokuxco</Username><Timestamp>1370875986294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370876695715-12</Id><Topic><Title>The King's of useless info:</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370821613927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No the point of a Christmas Party is the company of people, not Jesus Christ. He will not be invited. He’s been dead for quite some time and irrelevant – as are you. I will celebrate the Christmas tree and other things...and make the right noises like a “good” Protestant. Frederick the Great was an atheist too, and made the right Protestant noises at parties and state functions. He's easily in the league of the Greatest of the Germans. I see your stock is down today. Enjoy your losses: You and the gay boy on this thread…Birds of a feather…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1370876695715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 11:04:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370882466721-13</Id><Topic><Title>The King's of useless info:</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370821613927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a surprise..........your posts would always indicate that you have absolutely NO spriritual values and are therefore, in my opinion, rendered utterly worthless.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370882466721</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 12:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370884520641-14</Id><Title>Will a plane crash into Las Colinas???</Title><Msg>Anything is possible.....</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1370884520641</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 13:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370888909230-15</Id><Title>Energy agency: US oil-and-gas reserves up 35 percent, thanks to shale boom</Title><Msg>Energy agency: US oil-and-gas reserves up 35 percent, thanks to shale boom By Zack Colman 06/10/13 01:30 PM ET The amount of technically recoverable United States oil-and-gas reserves is 35 percent greater than in 2011, the U.S. Energy Information Administration (EIA) said Monday. The report credited the spike to new geologic and well-drilling results, as well as the adoption of hydraulic fracturing. The U.S. clocked in at second behind Russia in global technically recoverable shale oil reserves, with 58 billion barrels. It registered fourth behind China, Argentina and Algeria, with 665 trillion cubic feet of technically recoverable shale gas. "Technically recoverable" refers to oil-and-gas reserves accessible with current technology. That differs from economically recoverable, which is when energy firms can develop the hydrocarbons at a profit. “The use of horizontal drilling in conjunction with hydraulic fracturing has greatly expanded the ability of producers to profitably produce oil and natural gas from low permeability geologic formations, particularly shale formations,” EIA said in its report. Hydraulic fracturing, or fracking, has spurred the uptick in global shale oil-and-gas production. The drilling method involves injecting a high-pressure mixture of water, sand and chemicals into tight-rock formations to tap hydrocarbons buried deep underneath. In all, the EIA surveyed U.S. shale formations as well as 137 shale formations in another 41 countries. The agency estimated there are 345 billion barrels of technically recoverable shale oil and 7,299 trillion cubic feet of technically recoverable world shale gas reserves worldwide. The EIA did not survey many potential shale resources in the Middle East and Caspian region. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/304495-eia-shale-boom-drives-us-oil-and-gas-reserves-up-35-percent</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370888909230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 14:28:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370889570769-16</Id><Title>Oil, Gas From Shale Seen Rising as More Nations Explore</Title><Msg>10 June 2013 June 10 (Bloomberg) — Global resources of oil and gas from shale formations are greater than previously estimated as more nations join efforts to explore for deposits following a burst of production in the U.S. The U.S. Energy Information Administration released a fresh assessment of worldwide resources of oil and gas in shale, which are tapped by hydraulic fracturing, showing tight oil resources could be 345 billion barrels. Shale gas estimates were increased by 10 percent from 2011, to 7,299 trillion cubic feet. “As shale oil and shale gas production has grown in the United States to become 30 percent of oil and 40 percent of natural gas total production, interest in the oil and natural gas resource potential of shale formations outside the United States has grown,” Adam Sieminski, the agency’s administrator, said today a statement. The report shows “a significant potential for international shale oil and shale gas.” The report doesn’t assess all prospective shale formations, leaving out those under the large oil fields in the Middle East and the Caspian region because of a lack of data. The report studied technically recoverable resources, and the agency says some of those might not be economically justified given current cost for drilling or fracking in different nations. Hydraulic fracturing, or fracking, in which water, sand and chemicals are shot underground to break apart rock and free natural gas or oil trapped in the shale, has led to a boom in energy production to Pennsylvania, Texas and North Dakota. It’s led to a drop in natural gas prices, and estimates that the U.S. could meet its energy needs for the first time in decades. The EIA studied shale formations in 41 nations, compared with 32 assessed in a similar report in 2011. That report didn’t include estimates of tight oil. Shale resources account for 32 percent of the global estimated aboutDOTbnefDOTcom/bnef-news/oil-gas-from-shale-seen-rising-as-more-nations-explore/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370889570769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 14:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370901366696-17</Id><Topic><Title>The King's of useless info:</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370821613927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ maxipad commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1370901366696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370901403010-18</Id><Topic><Title>The King's of useless info:</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370821613927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ur mother; oh thats right u dont know who she is.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1370901403010</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370909352188-19</Id><Title>FAA wants to wean private airlines off leaded fuel</Title><Msg>FAA wants to wean private airlines off leaded fuel By Keith Laing - 06/10/13 04:10 PM ET The Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) is asking fuel producers to submit ideas for types of gasoline that do not contain lead for small private airplanes. The gas currently used for airplanes that are powered by piston engines, which is known as AvGas, contains lead. The FAA is looking for a proposal for a new source of fuel for the planes, which are typical one or two-seaters and are flown for private individual uses. The agency's goal is to switch the noncommercial aviation industry completely to unleaded gas by 2018. Transportation Secretary Ray LaHood said on Monday that developing an alternative to AvGas was a critical step toward reaching that goal. “General aviation is vital to the U.S. economy and is an important form of transportation for many Americans,” LaHood said in a statement. “We need to work with industry to develop an unleaded fuel that advances aviation safety and improves the environment.” The deadline for submissions to the FAA is July 1, 2014. The FAA said it will then select 10 potential suppliers of the new unleaded fuel to test up to 10,000 gallons of gas. FAA Administrator Michael Huerta said the agency would be working with the noncommercial aviation industry and other agencies in the Obama administration on the development of the unleaded private airplane fuel. “The FAA knows the general aviation community and the Environmental Protection Agency are focused on this issue, and we look forward to collaborating with fuel producers to make an unleaded avgas available for the general aviation fleet,” Huerta said in a statement. thehillDOTcom/blogs/transportation-report/aviation/304535-faa-wants-to-wean-private-airlines-off-leaded-fuel</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370909352188</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 20:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370909485615-20</Id><Title>LaHood said in a statement. “We need to work with industry to develop an unleaded fuel that advances aviation safety and improves the enviro</Title><Msg>LaHood said in a statement. “We need to work with industry to develop an unleaded fuel that advances aviation safety and improves the environment.”</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370909485615</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 20:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370909845748-21</Id><Title>FAA wants unleaded airplane fuel</Title><Msg>FAA wants unleaded airplane fuel washingtonpostDOTcom/local/trafficandcommuting/faa-wants-unleaded-airplane-fuel/2013/06/10/bcbffe8e-d203-11e2-a73e-826d299ff459_storyDOThtml</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370909845748</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 20:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370909868534-22</Id><Title>FAA wants unleaded airplane fuel</Title><Msg>FAA wants unleaded airplane fuel</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370909868534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 20:17:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370922813743-23</Id><Title>LOOk for oil stocks to free fall here</Title><Msg>No real demand here. Prices will crash too many alternatives here. Fuel consumption way down . Its all been speculation on Wall Street as always.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1370922813743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 23:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>