<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-26"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369579076667-1</Id><Title>Germanic themed Prometheus story – told by Americans</Title><Msg>The American movie is very true to the spirit of the Germanic creation story. The story is most fitting for the further development of the scientific ethos of the modern world, and the wrapping of the story in science is very cleverly done. The creation of the scientific worldview is poison to the sort of irrationality that stands behind the traditionalism of the Republican Party, and poison as well to the oil industry… Scarlett Johansson (Danish name) could not be more Germanic looking or acting. Her hair, her bone structure, and her attire is very Nordic. She keeps in superb physical shape too to accentuate her traits. The supreme dominance of her character and her character’s supreme indifference to inferior views is singular. Her special apartment on-board her company’s starship is notable for its virtual reality Nordic forest scene, and of course everything she surrounds herself with has an excellent rational quality and purpose. Her logic is so precise, and her demeanor so rational, one character even suspects she may be a cyborg or not one of his kind. The distinction was deliberately made too. Of course the creator-humans the expedition encounters at the creator’s military storage facility are exactly the sort envisaged by the Germanic Greeks – white Titan like beings with mostly human DNA. They were given other names. There is also an allusion to Egyptian language, architecture, and design in the works of the master-creators they discover. The Pharaohs and their priests did not consider themselves from this earth and neither did the Egyptian common people consider them from it. There was nothing quite so close to a god on Earth as a Pharaoh in Egypt. Hollywood has been useful yet again – keep up the good work.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369579076667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 10:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369581488867-2</Id><Topic><Title>Germanic themed Prometheus story – told by Americans</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369579076667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 10:37:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I mixed the starlets Charlize Theron was in the recent movie. Scarlett Johansson possibly will be in sequels or other type roles. Charlize Theron is German-Dutch/Germanic from South Afrika... You can't get more Germanic than that, unless you are from Germany or the Nordic lands... Out of a common mold.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369581488867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:18:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369590672614-3</Id><Topic><Title>McCain is an open border socialist</Title><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1369514975171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 16:49:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US Chamber of Commerce calls it In sourcing.</Msg><Username>besttoyou1</Username><Timestamp>1369590672614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 13:51:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369592759795-4</Id><Title>Solar PV Market Set To Grow To $155 Billion In 2018</Title><Msg>Solar PV Market Set To Grow To $155 Billion In 2018</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369592759795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 14:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>