<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359442304350-1</Id><Title>***** HILLARY CLINTON 2016 ******</Title><Msg>Enjoy these 4yrs and then the next 8 yrs. with Hillary !!!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1359442304350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 01:51:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359455426228-2</Id><Topic><Title>***** HILLARY CLINTON 2016 ******</Title><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1359442304350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 01:51:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She is finished, more dirt then nobumba.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1359455426228</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 05:30:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359456651430-3</Id><Topic><Title>Israel Deploys Missiles as Netanyahu Sees Syria Collapse</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1359312363055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 13:46:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ stinkbomb</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1359456651430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 05:50:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359459554535-4</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese military</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359405325330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:35:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's their entitlement programs going? Any government freebies? Is there any government housing, foodstamps, welfare or a lower uneducated class that pays no taxes? Are they acting as policemen of the world? Do they have open borders and an influx of foreigners tapping into the governments entitlement programs?</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1359459554535</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 06:39:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359464832172-5</Id><Topic><Title>Trek back to $80 begins soon</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359065370898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:09:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How important is it to "beat" the estimate these days? I claim it is really meaningless. Just look at how the analysts scramble to lower estimates when a company warns a couple weeks before their announcement date, solely so the company can beat the "estimate". So, let's say XOM does "beat" the $2.02 quarterly and $7.91 annual estimates - what's a good amount to beat by - maybe 10% for the quarter? That would be huge. Let's give them a $2.20 for the quarter and what the heck, we'll give them $8.10 for the year. Mind you, gas prices at the pump have been down this past quarter. What is the justification for the stock to trade at a multiple higher than 10? There is none. The company is generating lower revenues and earnings even when buying back billions of shares annually. This is not a growth company/stock. It's not complicated at all - give it a PE of 10, and that's what your price target is. When the company begins turning in $10/share EPS again, maybe it will see a $100/share price. Over the past 10 years, even those when it was making $10/share it didn't hit $100/share.</Msg><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359464832172</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 08:07:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359469713048-6</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese military</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359405325330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:35:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a reason why the US Democrat Party does not implement a program of state funded University education for those with the best academic records as China has been doing since 1985 Germany has done for ages. The cultural minorities the Democrats pander to would never be able to meet the standards. So the USA relies on a hodgepodge of charity to fund a few scholarships which is totally inadequate. The US universities are full but not with an elite, except for in the very best schools, and even there the students are being burdened with costs retarding their advance...Of course if the USA then copied the German and (now the Chinese) way of using the power of the state to regulate the economy and reserve the best employment opportunities for the elite they cultivated (who really don't need much help anyway) that would exclude the minorities the Democrats count on to get elected.... The poorly run government and the bad choices that result is a symptom of a government that is not being run by highly educated elites... The Republicans do not understand right wing government either... I foresee no improvement in such attitudes. So the USA will get to feel the competition of a state of 1.35 billion people elevated to a similar plane as Germany... Germany itself will keep right on leading, while the US keeps up government of by and for the poor, ignorant, and culturally bankrupt.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359469713048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 09:28:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359470750150-7</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese military</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359405325330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:35:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh BTW...the oil gamblers should not be too enthusiastic about this future either... Beijing is fighting automobile pollution so bad it is forcing them to adopt European auto pollution regulations, and shut down parts of their economy on some days... The problem of oil has certainly been made aware to the System, and the System is not happy and is taking counter-measures... It will focus more intellect and money at the problem than the US companies and US government could even dream of.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359470750150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 09:45:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359473347941-8</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359379384997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 08:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold all gilts...0.971% yield to maturity.... Gain: +0.062%... sold £ for €...100% €.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359473347941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 10:29:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359473430734-9</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359379384997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 08:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...1.1696 €/£...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359473430734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 10:30:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359473500762-10</Id><Topic><Title>Chinese military</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359405325330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 15:35:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with your assessment. A hopeless situation for America.</Msg><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1359473500762</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 10:31:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359474274891-11</Id><Title>Wind Enegy Surpasses Nuclear As China’s 3rd Largest Source Of Electrical Power</Title><Msg>Wind Enegy Surpasses Nuclear As China’s 3rd Largest Source Of Electrical Power January 29, 2013Andrew Wind energy is now China’s third largest source of electricity, according to a report from People’s Daily Online. Wind power generation in China totalled 100.4 billion kilowatt-hours (kWh) in 2012, a 0.5% year-on-year increase and surpassing nuclear power generation, according to data presented over the weekend by the China Wind Energy Association (CWEA). Ambitious state renewable power targets and government support for wind energy manufacturers have fueled rapid development and growth of wind power capacity in China. China had 60.83 GW of installed wind power capacity online as of year-end 2012, according to CWEA. A national target calls for 100 GW of installed capacity by the end of 2015. The 2% total for 2012 indicates just how fast and far China has progressed in realizing the strategic renewable power goals set out in its latest Five-Year Plan, and just how much it continues to rely on thermal coal and large-scale hydro power to meet its fast-growing demand for electrical power. Image Source: Barton Merle-Smith, Wind Currents China Wind Power: Rapid Growth Amid Grid, Market Challenges In its 12th and latest five-year plan (for 2011–2015), China’s leadership again singled out renewable energy as a key, strategic economic sector targeted to receive even greater attention and support. Aiming to provide “a snapshot of China’s renewable energy market,” consulting firm Solidiance January 8 released a white paper that “demonstrates the challenges and opportunities faced by this important industry.” The presentation by CWEA also reveals hurdles to bringing wind and other renewable power generation online and on the grid. Though reaching a cumulative record-high in 2012, growth in wind power capacity additions actually slowed to 14 gigawatts (GW) in 2012 from 20.66 GW in 2011, according to data presented by CWEA chairman He Dexin. He identified wind turbine overcapacity, growing international trade protectionism, grid interconnection challenges, and wind power generation wastage as bottlenecks for bringing additional wind power capacity online. Nonetheless, CWEA forecasts wind power capacity in China will grow to 18 GW in 2013, as local governments have accelerated approval of wind power generation projects since the beginning of the year. The Development and Reform Commission of Hunan Province on January 9 approved three wind power projects, a total investment of 1.35 billion yuan ($217 million) alone. Government-led market-oriented reform is needed to address the problem of curtailment, whereby grid-connected wind-generated electricity is held back by grid operators, according to He. Some 20 billion kWh of wind-generated electricity was lost to curtailment in 2012, according to CWEA data. “Grid companies lack economic incentives to take in more wind power, as government-dictated on-grid wholesale prices of wind power are higher than those of thermal power,” Meng Xian’gan, secretary-general of the China Renewable Energy Society, was quoted as saying. sDOTtt/1z5h0</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359474274891</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 10:44:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359474969153-12</Id><Title>Can fossil-fuel tax benefits boost the renewable energy industry?</Title><Msg>Can fossil-fuel tax benefits boost the renewable energy industry? Posted on 01/29/2013 by Dan Haugen (Photo by BBC World Service via Creative Commons) Since the 1980s, U.S. oil and gas companies have benefited from a tax loophole big enough to build a pipeline through. By organizing as a type of partnership instead of a corporation, companies that extract, process or transport “depletable” natural resources have been exempt from corporate income taxes. That word — “depletable” — specifically excludes renewable energy, but a long-simmering effort to change that now appears to be gathering some steam in Washington. U.S. Sen. Chris #$%$, a Delaware Democrat, introduced a bill last year that would give wind, solar and other renewable projects the same tax benefit that fossil fuels have enjoyed for decades. The Master Limited Partnerships Parity Act has picked up bipartisan support, including Republicans from oil-rich states such as Alaska Sen. Lisa Murkowski and Rep. Ted Poe of Texas. But the bill also finds itself going against broader political momentum in Congress to eliminate loopholes and exemptions in order to raise revenue and lower tax rates. Leveling the playing field The first master limited partnership, or MLP, was devised in 1981 by a Minneapolis drilling and exploration company, Apache Oil Corp., now based in Houston. The structure offered a way to sell publicly tradable stock without being taxed as a corporation. The model quickly spread to other oil and gas firms, as well as other industries seeking the same tax advantages, including real estate, hotels and motels, and restaurants. By the time Congress intervened in 1987, even the Boston Celtics had formed an MLP. Worried that too many corporations would become MLPs to avoid taxes, Congress prohibited them except for companies that earn 90 percent of their income from specific investment, real estate and natural resource activities, including oil and gas operations. “It just doesn’t make any sense. It never made any sense why MLPs were available to them and not to us,” says Blake Nixon, president of Geronimo Wind, a Minnesota wind developer that has been lobbying for MLP changes since 2009. Allowing renewable companies to organize as MLPs is among a handful of tax reforms the industry and its supporters say will help level the playing field with fossil fuels. Others include allowing them to organize as real estate investment trusts, or REITs, and letting renewable tax credits be claimed by more types of investors. Need for financial innovation Setting up renewable projects as MLPs would make it easier to sell shares to individuals and institutional investors such as pension funds. Widening the pool of potential investors would inject new competition, which could lower the cost of financing projects, and ultimately lower the cost of renewable power. Currently, there are only about 20 large financial institutions that have large enough tax bills to claim the full value of federal credits awarded to renewable projects. Wind and solar developers that want to take advantage of the credits need to recruit one of these players to invest in every single project. “They basically get to set terms,” says Nixon. “Because there’s so few of them, there’s very little flexibility in the terms and in the costs of the money. There’s very little competition among them to drive those costs down.” Even though borrowing rates are at historic lows, these large renewable investors charge interest rates of 8 to 9 percent, after tax, per project, says Nixon, compared to 4 to 5 percent that’s common for MLPs. As the cost of wind and solar technology has fallen, financing costs have stayed high and become a bigger share of overall project costs, says Felix Mormann, an associate professor of law at the University of Miami and a fellow at Stanford’s Steyer-Taylor Center for Energy Policy and Finance. “It’s time for us to complement ongoing technology innovation with critical financial innovation,” says Mormann. Mormann co-authored a Brookings Institute report published in November called “Smarter Finance for Cleaner Energy: Open Up Master Limited Partnerships (MLPs) and Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) to Renewable Energy Investment.” Not a ‘magic potion’ MLPs aren’t a “magic potion,” however, warns Joe Condo, vice president and general counsel for Chicago renewable developer Invenergy, which has lobbied for MLP changes for several years. “One concern we have is that some folks who support MLP are saying maybe this is a replacement for [production tax credits],” says Condo. “We don’t agree with that.” The Bipartisan Policy Center, a Washington, D.C., think tank, agrees. In a 2011 policy brief it concluded, “Because MLP s would only increase the eligible investor pool … by themselves they would most likely not supplant the tax incentives currently in place.” #$%$’ bill is getting more attention than previous efforts to extend MLPs to renewables, but they’ve still been getting “a fair amount of pushback from Capitol Hill,” says Keith Martin, a lawyer and lobbyist with Washington, D.C., firm Chadbourne &amp; Parke. Martin is scheduled to speak about MLPs and REITs next week at the Wind Power Finance &amp; Investment Summit in San Diego. If the bill advances, it would likely move forward as part of a broader corporate tax reform bill that Congress is expected to take up either this year or next year, says Martin. Even if it succeeds, the impact could be muted if Congress decides to tax partnerships, as some have proposed. Martin says both parties want to lower the current 35 percent corporate income tax rate. Democrats want to lower it to 28 percent and Republicans are aiming for 25 percent. “It’s a monumental task to take the rate that low,” says Martin. Adding exemptions will make it tougher. A 2011 Congressional Research Service report estimated that extending MLPs to renewable energy firms would cost the U.S. Treasury about $2.8 billion between 2010 and 2014. An alternative, that report suggests, if the goal is a level playing field: close the loophole for oil and gas companies. midwestenergynewsDOTcom/2013/01/29/can-fossil-fuel-tax-benefits-boost-the-renewable-energy-industry-master-limited-partnership/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359474969153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 10:56:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359475269934-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359379384997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 08:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buying 5-Year German Bunds tomorrow... Bunds will become Deutsche marks if for some reason German leaves the Euro...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359475269934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 11:01:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359475851706-14</Id><Title>Canadian carbon project aims to prove 'clean coal' works</Title><Msg>Canadian carbon project aims to prove 'clean coal' works Mon Jan 28, 2013 9:26am EST * Boundary Dam power plant to trap carbon from 2014 * First commercial-scale CCS project at a coal-fired plant * SaskPower seeks to limit power output loss to 25 pct By Environment Correspondent Alister Doyle OSLO, Jan 28 (Reuters) - A technology that holds the hope for cleaner use of coal will be tested on a commercial scale for the first time in Canada next year, aiming to resolve big uncertainties about the vast amount of power it will need. Saskatchewan Power Corp. (SaskPower) hopes that a $1.24 billion refit of its 45-year-old Boundary Dam power plant to capture carbon dioxide emissions will make investors think twice about shifting to gas-fired plants from dirtier coal. "This will come in on time and on budget," Michael Monea, head of SaskPower's carbon capture and storage (CCS) initiatives, told Reuters in an interview. The company hopes that its carbon capture technology will reduce Boundary Dam's power output by only a quarter or thereabouts, making it the world's first commercially viable large-scale CCS project at a coal-fired power plant. Success could spur interest in CCS technology from China to the United States as an effective way to fight climate change. "We need this as an example of carbon capture and storage actually happening," said Camilla Svendsen Skriung, of the Norwegian environmental group Zero. The plant is designed to capture one million tonnes a year of the greenhouse gas carbon dioxide from April 2014. It will also trap the pollutant sulphur dioxide. SaskPower agreed last month to sell the carbon dioxide it captures to Canadian oil company Cenovus Energy - when injected into an oil well, the gas raises the pressure and forces more oil to the surface. Monea did not reveal the price agreed. Monea said that the key to proving that clean coal is possible is to limit the "parasitic load" - the amount of power needed to capture the carbon and sulphur. "The big deal for us is parasitic load. The old 140 megawatt plant will be new again, so will probably generate 150 to 155 megawatts. Then the capture plant may mean we lose 40 megawatts of power," he said. "I am hoping that we will net higher than 110 megawatts (after the carbon has been captured)." COSTS AND PENALTIES There are a few other commercial carbon capture projects, such as the one at the Sleipner natural gas field off Norway run by Statoil, which re-injects a million tonnes of carbon dioxide a year beneath the seabed. However, high costs and low penalties for emitting carbon mean that such projects have failed to catch on for coal-fired plants as part of efforts to slow climate change. "Once people hear that the economics are very good, maybe we won't have everybody dash to gas and throw out coal," Monea said. "We hope the rest of the world can learn from our plant." SaskPower says that the plant will reduce carbon emissions by about 90 percent - the equivalent, it says, of taking 250,000 cars off the roads in the province every year. Almost 200 nations have set themselves a deadline of end-2015 to agree a United Nations-led pact to combat climate change, with its implementation set for the start of 2020. But after past failures, there is little prospect of a global price on carbon emissions that would help to make carbon capture more viable. Monea said that lessons from the Boundary Dam refit, aided by a federal government subsidy of $240 million, will cut costs and mean that future refits can be completed without state aid. The costs of the Boundary Dam refit were comparable to those for replacing it with a new natural gas plant, Monea said. The plant has ready access to water, which might otherwise be a constraint. The cost of the refit means that power prices paid by SaskPower's clients will rise by a few cents from the 10 to 11 cents per kilowatt that they pay now, he said. The European Commission last month said that it failed to find a winner in a contest to fund EU carbon capture and storage projects, deepening doubts that the technology can soon emerge to help to reduce greenhouse gas emissions. reutersDOTcom/article/2013/01/28/climate-carbon-canada-idUSL5N0AX5X220130128?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=rbssEnergyNews&amp;utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed:+reuters/USenergyNews+(News+/+US+/+Energy)</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359475851706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 11:10:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359476902458-15</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359379384997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 08:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you look at what Iran started by selling oil for any and all currencies except the dollar is a doom for bonds as intrest rates go up.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1359476902458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 11:28:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359477011484-16</Id><Topic><Title>Canadian carbon project aims to prove 'clean coal' works</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359475851706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 11:10:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Inexpensive clean coal is coming, bringing a return to coal from natural gas. Peak natural gas consumption in America will be December 2013 through January 2014.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359477011484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 11:30:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359478011139-17</Id><Topic><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359379384997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 08:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$ rates will go over time, but not German rates. Germany has a surplus and the government will reduce the amounts bonds over time. The surplus is caused by Germany's superior education system, technology, and elite led government. Productivity will relentlessly advance and increase the surplus over time. Places like China, which Germany is actively cooperating with and helping advance, are no threat Germany, just as Japan which Germany elevated is not threat... Oil will be obsolete as an energy source eventually too. Germany and China are working on making that state a fact. Even for aviation it will become obsolete. Quantum physics is the reality, and it will eventually make things that seem impossible by classical mechanics and the public possible. Of course Germany introduced the world to Quantum mechanics (which defies the 2nd "Law" of Thermodynamics on entropy with a mathematical proof, via probability theory)...--see Ludwig Boltzmann...In other words what appears impossible only appears so because what is probable is what you see, as per the laws of mathematics. Making oil obsolete for land transportation is quite straightforward. Magnetic levitation, superconductors, and electric and fuel cells will destroy it... Iran is irrelevant…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359478011139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 11:46:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359479686789-18</Id><Title>Election is Past</Title><Msg>Oil is up - gas is up election is over never fails democrat or republican. But don't forget the democrats are for working middle class. Like groceries up 40-50% in 4 years.</Msg><Username>willstand99</Username><Timestamp>1359479686789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 12:14:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359481058239-19</Id><Topic><Title>Trek back to $80 begins soon</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359065370898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:09:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xom-is a strong buy-its above 200dmva in the daily,weekly,monthly,quarterly and yearly charts-i went back 10yrs-huge huge support-goint to 120 in near distant future!!!!!</Msg><Username>dale_rinderle</Username><Timestamp>1359481058239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 12:37:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359481993842-20</Id><Title>Stench Mentioned MidEast Unrest and 100 Dollar Oil.</Title><Msg>Time to move Hess profitz into the next big mover: XOM.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1359481993842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 12:53:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359483015817-21</Id><Title>Goldman will get their $150/barrrel oil as US dollar dies!!!</Title><Msg>Oil bulls going to make a killing.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1359483015817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 13:10:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359483094103-22</Id><Title>The Turdz Are Trukin Oil !!!!</Title><Msg>They are true hard working hustlers. Exxon is better off in the north. We are now poised like a coiled spring,ready to bust into the 100s,and oil is going thru the roof too.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1359483094103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 13:11:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359483261677-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Turdz Are Trukin Oil !!!!</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1359483094103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 13:11:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be such a gift ...... my birthday is on fri......</Msg><Username>mccafferty</Username><Timestamp>1359483261677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 13:14:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359486913858-24</Id><Topic><Title>If some guy figured out a technology to replace oil</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1359480854911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 12:34:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure the fools who invest in oil companies would like to believe that... The collective arrogance I've seen on this board would certainly be conducive to such attitudes and beliefs. Such people are like an ant peering at the walls of a fortress, thoroughly convinced that nothing is going on behind those walls...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359486913858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 14:15:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359488573198-25</Id><Title>The Bernack will print us over $100 easily</Title><Msg>Ben and Dudley are XOM's Best. Friends. Forever.</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1359488573198</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 14:42:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359492118068-26</Id><Title>Tomorrows big moves YTRV</Title><Msg>COULD EASILY TRIPLE!</Msg><Username>dstefaia</Username><Timestamp>1359492118068</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 15:41:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359492503730-27</Id><Title>SCHS THIS WEEKS NUMBER 1 GAINER STOCK IN THE STOCK MARKET</Title><Msg>Schs is going to be a monster this week dont miss this one folks</Msg><Username>stockexpertpro</Username><Timestamp>1359492503730</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 15:48:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359507094617-28</Id><Title>Oil-and-gas lobby might take ethanol fight to Supreme Court</Title><Msg>Oil-and-gas lobby might take ethanol fight to Supreme Court By Zack Colman - 01/29/13 02:21 PM ET The American Petroleum Institute (API) is "strongly considering" asking the U.S. Supreme Court to hear a case regarding sales of a high-ethanol fuel blend, API Group Downstream Director Bob Greco said Tuesday. The Supreme Court move would represent another escalation in API’s campaign to roll back rules and court decisions vital to the biofuels industry. Greco said API would need to file a petition for a rehearing by mid-April. In question is a U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia ruling that upheld the Environmental Protection Agency’s (EPA) decision to allow E15 fuel into the marketplace. EPA and the biofuels industry have said the fuel blend — which contains 15 percent ethanol, rather than the standard 10 percent — is safe for cars made in 2001 or later. But API and automakers contend E15 damages cars. API floated the Supreme Court option during a Tuesday press call announcing research that it and automakers funded showing E15 harms cars. The E15 court case is one part of the lobby group's congressional and legal battles to block E15 sales and to repeal a biofuel-blending mandate. Biofuels groups contend API and its oil-and-gas allies are concerned about losing market share. Currently, E15 is only available at a handful of gas stations across the country. But more of it is needed to meet the blending mandate’s accelerating targets, which calls for mixing 36 billion gallons of biofuel into traditional transportation fuel by 2022. “Oil companies are desperate to prevent the use of higher blends of renewable fuels,” Tom Buis, chief executive with biofuel trade group Growth Energy, said in a Tuesday statement. “They have erected every regulatory and legal roadblock imaginable to prevent our nation from reducing our dependence on oil.” thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/279885-oil-and-gas-lobby-considering-taking-high-ethanol-fuel-case-to-supreme-court</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359507094617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 19:51:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>