<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371031566177-1</Id><Topic><Title>The King's of useless info:</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370821613927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jojo idiot does sound like maxipad the commie POS.</Msg><Username>bluemax19</Username><Timestamp>1371031566177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371031628404-2</Id><Topic><Title>maxipad ???</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1369130857995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 06:07:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jojo gets all thumbs down just like the maxipad welfare bum.</Msg><Username>bluemax19</Username><Timestamp>1371031628404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 06:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371040471413-3</Id><Title>finally PWE is making a move.trades at under $11 bloomberg article says worth over $18</Title><Msg>Board says open to ALL options including a sale of entire company.</Msg><Username>green_lightning11</Username><Timestamp>1371040471413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 08:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371044204312-4</Id><Title>Denuding the Middle East of its wealth after the oil price crash…</Title><Msg>The fate of the oil price is basically a fait accompli at this point. OPEC is desperately striving to prop up the oil price by cutting production while supply expands in response to the high price. There is unlimited capital to develop the supply and unlimited capital to destroy the demand, which ensures the crash. For oil investors times will become very tough after the oil price crash. They will have to liquidate their non-oil assets to keep up their lifestyle. They will sell their stocks, bonds, gold and other assets to keep spending. The biggest oil investors of course reside in the Middle East – the Princes and other nobles of Arabia and the millions who feed off their largesse. The oil revenues they squander exceed by an order of magnitude the likes of Exxon Mobil and its executives, employees, and shareholders. Germany runs trade surpluses with all those places and will end up collecting the Arab’s wealth over time. Places in the USA that have a petroleum based economy will be similarly denuded of their wealth....</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371044204312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371044716898-5</Id><Title>Berrnanke sending your $$ to Israel...</Title><Msg>Fed Funds are being skimmed off and deported.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1371044716898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 09:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371052411896-6</Id><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending June 7, 2013</Title><Msg>U.S. crude oil refinery inputs averaged over 15.2 million barrels per day during the week ending June 7, 2013, 225 thousand barrels per day below the previous week’s average. Refineries operated at 87.5 percent of their operable capacity last week. Gasoline production decreased last week, averaging 9.2 million barrels per day. Distillate fuel production decreased last week, averaging 4.7 million barrels per day. U.S. crude oil imports averaged under 7.9 million barrels per day last week, up by 582 thousand barrels per day from the previous week. Over the last four weeks, crude oil imports have averaged about 7.8 million barrels per day, about 1.2 million barrels per day below the same four-week period last year. Total motor gasoline imports (including both finished gasoline and gasoline blending components) last week averaged 692 thousand barrels per day. Distillate fuel imports averaged 52 thousand barrels per day last week. U.S. commercial crude oil inventories (excluding those in the Strategic Petroleum Reserve) increased by 2.5 million barrels from the previous week. At 393.8 million barrels, U.S. crude oil inventories are above the upper limit of the average range for this time of year. Total motor gasoline inventories increased by 2.7 million barrels last week and are also above the upper limit of the average range. Both finished gasoline inventories and blending components inventories increased last week. Distillate fuel inventories decreased by 1.2 million barrels last week and remained in the lower half of the average range for this time of year. Propane/propylene inventories increased by 3.3 million barrels last week, and are in the upper half of the average range. Total commercial petroleum inventories increased by 12.8 million barrels last week. Total products supplied over the last four-week period have averaged under 18.5 irDOTeiaDOTgov/wpsr/wpsrsummary.pdf Data Overview (Combined Table 1 and Table 9) irDOTeiaDOTgov/wpsr/overview.pdf</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371052411896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 11:53:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371057257687-7</Id><Topic><Title>Best stock picks</Title><Username>cartermurphy914</Username><Timestamp>1371048588071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 10:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice</Msg><Username>wyattmack173</Username><Timestamp>1371057257687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371057349042-8</Id><Title>Can't beat free</Title><Msg>Awesome picks for free sent to your phone. What's not to love? Sign up now!! Text the word "stocks" without quotes now to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>gbutler668</Username><Timestamp>1371057349042</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371058299832-9</Id><Title>royl just struck gas well......rich.......pps zippin up</Title><Msg>good luck....................</Msg><Username>stringandtwocups</Username><Timestamp>1371058299832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371061604785-10</Id><Title>The EPA is scheduled to propose new ozone standards within the next year, and is considering toughening the limit to 60 particles for every</Title><Msg>The EPA is scheduled to propose new ozone standards within the next year, and is considering toughening the limit to 60 particles for every billion in the atmosphere, or parts per billion, down from the current standard of 75, set in 2008.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371061604785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371062401411-11</Id><Title>Renewable Fuels Association (RFA) is adding to its campaign arsenal to block Big Oil from winning the E15 battle.</Title><Msg>Renewable Fuels Association (RFA) is adding to its campaign arsenal to block Big Oil from winning the E15 battle.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371062401411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371066070840-12</Id><Title>$$$$ BUY PREFERREDS $$$$ 6-7% dividends..sleep at night !!</Title><Msg>A GOOD SLEEP...finally....</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1371066070840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:41:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371078766638-13</Id><Topic><Title>The EPA is scheduled to propose new ozone standards within the next year, and is considering toughening the limit to 60 particles for every</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371061604785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 14:26:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even if they managed to push through the limit of 60 particles, this won't effect XOM in the long run.</Msg><Username>jjbrooks52</Username><Timestamp>1371078766638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 19:12:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371082132382-14</Id><Title>The increase of the so-called social cost of carbon, to $38 a metric ton in 2015 from $23.80, adjusts the calculation the government uses to</Title><Msg>The increase of the so-called social cost of carbon, to $38 a metric ton in 2015 from $23.80, adjusts the calculation the government uses to weigh costs and benefits of proposed regulations. The figure is meant to approximate losses from global warming such as flood damage and diminished crops.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371082132382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 20:08:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371091153273-15</Id><Title>price of exxon</Title><Msg>classic head n shoulder pattern, for what that is worth ....puts Exxon down to $88 or $86 ..... let it roll. regards</Msg><Username>dvoowner</Username><Timestamp>1371091153273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 22:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371091382687-16</Id><Topic><Title>The King's of useless info:</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370821613927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least bluecheese has use of the English language........you on the other hand are just an obscene jerk.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371091382687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 22:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371094959610-17</Id><Title>British Bio-refining Proceedings; Deutschland Biofuels…</Title><Msg>Scientists working for the UK’s biofuels research program at the University of York have discovered how to produce an enzyme copied from a marine wood boring worm, and enzyme that is uniquely suitable for producing liquid biofuels from waste paper, wood, grass, and other cellulose materials. The enzyme offers many improvements in productivity and fuel production cost over older technologies. Once an industrial process is developed to produce and utilize the enzyme, bio-refineries will be constructed at major transportation hubs around Europe and globally. The products produced from such materials will be much greener than petroleum based products, and the tax regime will place Big Oil at a major competitive disadvantage against them. Such green industry is certainly part of industrial cluster development plans both at the urban/district and federal level. Places such as Hamburg, Berlin, and the Ruhr district offer many advantages as potential bio-refining locations. Railroad transportation capacity would simply be augmented from Hamburg and the Ruhr through Berlin and eastward to the Donbas and Moscow to move cellulose raw materials westward to Germany. Waste cellulose would be shipped to the refineries from across Germany and Europe. Railroads and shipping would move finished fuels to market. The forests and steppes of Eastern Europe and Russia are vast and only lightly developed at present. The amount of bio-fuels that could be derived from the area is enormous…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371094959610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 23:42:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>