<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358229121211-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama looked poised and spoiling for a fight on the debt ceiling</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358185453404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sadly for you Obama is very much in possession of his intellectual abilities. He has judged the extent of his power correctly, and judged the cowardice and weakness of his opposition correctly as well, and decided his opponents' opinions and attitudes are not worthy of further comment except to condemn them. Baiting a weak opponent and provoking an outburst and political battle is a good strategy, right in line with Sun Tzu teachings. "If your enemy is weak attack and annihilate him..." Giving the enemy time to evade and regroup is not good strategy. The annihilation of the Republican Party so that the collectivist agenda can be advanced is the goal. The inherent superiority of collectivism is the guiding light. The goal and means to achieve it are quite rational...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358229121211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 00:52:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358230866695-2</Id><Title>1st Part of Offshore Wind Power Line Moves Ahead</Title><Msg>1st Part of Offshore Wind Power Line Moves Ahead By MATTHEW L. WALD Published: January 14, 2013 WASHINGTON — An audacious plan to lay a multibillion-dollar wind power transmission spine under the seabed from southern Virginia to the New York City area will take a step forward on Tuesday with an announcement of plans for the first leg, a 189-mile segment running from Jersey City to a spot south of Atlantic City. The proposed backbone, first outlined publicly in October 2010, is intended to link future wind farms far offshore, sparing them the expense and regulatory problems of bringing power lines all the way to shore individually and to move power to land-based sources. The project’s backers, which include Google and other prominent investors, argue that the buried offshore spine, impervious to storms, could also come in handy in an emergency, providing a backup for hospitals and police stations and restarting power plants in blacked-out areas. The latter selling point has gained importance for the line’s promoters as interest in offshore wind has suffered setbacks, including the declining price of natural gas, a competing energy source. The Atlantic Wind Connection, the project’s sponsor, says the first segment would run from a substation called Cardiff, near Pomona, N.J., operated by Atlantic City Electric, out into the ocean 12 to 14 miles. That leg represents less than half of the 350-mile project, but the plan was always to build it in stages. Near the line’s southern end, it would tie into multiple wind farms in a region that the Obama administration has identified as prime territory for offshore wind. Executives at Atlantic Wind say they chose to begin with a segment solely in New Jersey because the project could level the big price differences for electricity within the state, yielding an economic benefit that could justify at least some of the first leg’s $1.3 billion construction cost. Remaining within one state simplifies the regulatory process, they added, and political support for offshore wind farms is relatively strong in New Jersey. The state has mandated that 22.5 percent of its electricity must come from renewable sources by 2021, and the bulk of that is expected to come from wind, some of which may come from outside New Jersey. Very few onshore sites in the state are suitable for wind, however. New Jersey’s Offshore Wind Economic Development Act calls for at least 1,100 megawatts of offshore wind, but backers say it could go as high as 3,000 megawatts. Atlantic Wind hopes to secure regulatory approval and get the financing in place by mid-2015 and to start construction at the end of that year. Laying cable under the seabed will be an inducement for wind developers to move ahead as well, it predicts. In 2011, 11 companies expressed interest in building wind farms, although progress all over the East Coast has been quite slow. Even if those farms do not materialize as fast as was once imagined, the sponsors argue that the transmission line is justified because it would allow faster recovery from crippling storms like Hurricane Sandy. “This is great for offshore wind, but it’s supergood for the grid itself,” said Robert L. Mitchell, the chief executive of the Trans-Elect Development Company, a transmission-line business based in Bethesda, Md., that proposed the venture. A report that the company commissioned from the Chertoff Group, led by Michael Chertoff, a former secretary of homeland security, asserts that in a blackout, the line would transport electricity from a faraway location to critical facilities like hospitals and police stations, or start up power plants in blacked-out areas. Not everyone agrees on the reliability benefit, though. Jersey Central Power and Light, which serves much of the Atlantic coast, lost 55 of its 75 transmission lines in Hurricane Sandy. But even if there had been an alternative, it would not have made much of a difference, because most of the distribution lines feeding buildings were also down. “It’s certainly an interesting concept,” said Todd Schneider, a spokesman for the utility. But he said the project would “not necessarily speed restoration work during a significant storm.” The project passed a major hurdle last May when the Interior Department, which controls the ocean floor, said that preparation of an environmental-impact statement could begin. The president of the State Senate, Stephen M. Sweeney, welcomed Atlantic Wind Connection’s proposal. “The potential jobs and economic benefit this could bring to New Jersey is definitely exciting, especially in a state with the fourth-highest unemployment rate in the nation,” he said. He added that he wanted to evaluate the costs before making a decision on whether to support construction. For the project to be built, New Jersey would have to submit a request to the regional grid operator, PJM Interconnection. The first step for PJM would be to determine how much money the line would save by importing cheap power from southern New Jersey into northern New Jersey. Another factor is how much prices in southern New Jersey would rise as a result of its exports. Such transfers are now limited by congestion on the grid. Once the economic value of the line had been established, a sum related to that value would be charged to all PJM customers, including those in New Jersey. If the estimated construction cost of an estimated $1.3 billion exceeded that, which seems likely, the balance would be charged to New Jersey ratepayers as an environmental project, to meet the state’s renewable energy goals. nytimesDOTcom/2013/01/15/business/energy-environment/an-offshore-wind-power-line-moves-ahead.html?_r=0</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358230866695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 01:21:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358231915533-3</Id><Title>Duke Energy Completes 402 Megawatts of Texas Wind Farms</Title><Msg>Duke Energy Completes 402 Megawatts of Texas Wind Farms By Ehren Goossens - Jan 14, 2013 9:16 AM MT. 1 Comment A unit of Duke Energy Corp (DUK), the largest U.S. utility owner by market value, has started producing power at wind farms in Texas with 402 megawatts of combined capacity. The 200-megawatt Los Vientos I project in Willacy County is selling power to CPS Energy Products Inc. and the 202-megawatt Los Vientos II project in Wilacy and Cameron Counties is selling power to Austin Energy, Charlotte, North Carolina-based Duke Energy Renewables said today in a statement. The projects will “boost economic development, support the local school districts, and be a source of dependable tax revenue for years to come,” Duke Energy Renewables President Greg Wolf said in the statement. Duke’s unit, with enough capacity to power half a million homes, now has more than 1,700 megawatts of wind and solar capacity, Wolf said. bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-01-14/duke-energy-completes-402-megawatts-of-texas-wind-farms.html ------------------------------------------------------ Pennsylvania Mehoopany Wind Farm Completed VIDEO January 14, 2013 Nicholas Brown BP Wind Energy and Sempra US Gas and Power completed their wind project called the Mehoopany wind farm, which we previously wrote about while it was still under construction. This wind farm has an electricity generation capacity of 141 MW (141,000 kW) and it spans 9,000 acres (36 square km), and is located 20 miles northwest of Scranton, Pennsylvania. This wind farm is powered by 88 General Electric (GE) xle wind turbines which each have an electricity generation capacity of 1.6 MW (1,600 kW). It wasn’t clear how much of this project was built locally, however, domestic electricity generation is a good thing as opposed to importing it. The larger the fraction of the project that was done in Pennsylvania, the greater the number of people that would be employed in Pennsylvania; unless the workers were imported from another state. The total investment in this wind farm was $250 million. This is supposed to be the largest wind farm in the state of Pennsylvania and created 400 temporary construction jobs during its peak construction period. Since construction was completed 10-15 people are permanently hired to maintain the facility. BP and Sempra already had the entire power output of the wind farm purchased by Old Dominion Electric Cooperative and Southern Maryland Electric Cooperative Inc. Although the project is a 50:50 joint venture between BP and Sempra it is operated by a wholly owned affiliate of BP Wind Energy. BP has infused about $8 billion for alternative energy development recently. The US BP Wind Energy is the usual owner and operator of BP wind farms in the United States, with an investment of over $4 billion. The US BP Wind Energy invested in 16 wind farms across the United States with a gross generation capacity of 2.6 GW (2,600 MW). sDOTtt/1yrL2</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358231915533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 01:38:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358248641709-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Bringing Constitutional Crisis to the USA</Title><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1358210987576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 19:49:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After the collapse of america all dems and #$%$ libs will be held responsible and after teabagers rebuild america there will be no lib or #$%$s. They will be shipped to greenland.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1358248641709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 06:17:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358248715413-5</Id><Topic><Title>60 degrees in New Jersey today (January).</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1358111833183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:17:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ POS snth had to many failed lobotomy's.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1358248715413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 06:18:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358252723030-6</Id><Title>Lennar Reports Fourth Quarter EPS of $0.56</Title><Msg>Lennar Reports Fourth Quarter EPS of $0.56 MIAMI, Jan. 15, 2013 /PRNewswire/ -- 2012 Fourth Quarter •Net earnings of $124.3 million, or $0.56 per diluted share, compared to net earnings of $30.3 million, or $0.16 per diluted share •Deliveries of 4,443 homes – up 32% •New orders of 3,983 homes – up 32% •Backlog of 4,053 homes – up 87%; backlog dollar value of $1.2 billion – up 107% •Revenues of $1.3 billion – up 42% •Gross margin on home sales of 23.5% – improved 410 basis points •S,G&amp;A expenses as a % of revenues from home sales of 11.3% – improved 250 basis points •Operating margin on home sales of 12.2% – improved 660 basis points •Lennar Homebuilding operating earnings of $106.0 million, compared to $25.2 million •Lennar Financial Services operating earnings of $33.2 million, compared to $9.1 million •Rialto Investments operating earnings totaled $4.6 million (net of $0.2 million of net earnings attributable to noncontrolling interests), compared to $8.0 million (including an add back of $2.0 million of net loss attributable to noncontrolling interests) •Lennar Homebuilding cash and cash equivalents of $1.1 billion •No outstanding borrowings under the $525 million credit facility •Issued $350 million of 4.750% senior notes due 2022 •Lennar Homebuilding debt to total capital, net of cash and cash equivalents, of 45.6% 2012 Fiscal Year •Net earnings of $679.1 million, or $3.11 per diluted share, which includes a partial reversal of the deferred tax asset valuation allowance of $491.5 million, or $2.25 per diluted share, compared to net earnings of $92.2 million, or $0.48 per diluted share •Revenues of $4.1 billion – up 33% •Deliveries of 13,802 homes – up 27% •New orders of 15,684 homes – up 37% Lennar Corporation (NYSE: LEN and LEN.B), one of the nation's largest homebuilders, today reported results for its fourth quarter and fiscal year ended November 30, 2012. Fourth quarter net earnings attributable to Lennar in 2012 were $124.3 million, or $0.56 per diluted share, compared to $30.3 million, or $0.16 per diluted share, in the fourth quarter of 2011. Net earnings attributable to Lennar for the year ended November 30, 2012 were $679.1 million, or $3.11 per diluted share, compared to $92.2 million, or $0.48 per diluted share, in 2011. Stuart Miller, Chief Executive Officer of Lennar Corporation, said, "During our fourth quarter, the housing industry took further steps toward a sustained recovery. Low mortgage rates, affordable home prices, reduced foreclosures and an extremely favorable 'rent vs. own' comparison continue to drive the recovery. Housing should continue to assume its traditional role in the broader economic recovery, driving employment upward, increasing consumer confidence and helping new homeowners accumulate wealth through home ownership, thus helping to accelerate economic growth." Mr. Miller continued, "Our fourth quarter reflects the recovery in housing with solid profitability in all of our business segments. Our homebuilding sales pace continued to grow with a 32% increase in new orders, while our homebuilding gross margin percentage increased 410 basis points over last year to 23.5% and our homebuilding operating margin percentage increased 660 basis points over last year to 12.2%. Our homebuilding machine continues to improve and be our primary driver of profitability, fueled by our opportunistic land acquisitions and increasing operating leverage due to higher absorption per community and overall deliveries." "Our financial services segment also had a strong fourth quarter with operating earnings of $33.2 million, compared to $9.1 million last year. This business segment continued to benefit from both our growing homebuilding operations and by participating in the robust refinancing market." "On the Rialto side of our business, in December 2012, we completed the first closing of our second real estate fund with initial equity commitments of approximately $260 million (including $100 million committed by Lennar Corporation). Rialto has continued to contribute directly to the profitability of the company while providing our homebuilding segment with unique opportunities to acquire attractive land parcels. We remain enthusiastic about Rialto's position in the market and its prospects for long-term profitability and value creation, which should be enhanced by continued economic recovery." "Two other longer term strategies have also continued to develop within the company and should benefit from economic recovery. We incubated a multifamily platform that is now maturing into the construction phase with a pipeline of over $1 billion to be developed over the next three years. Additionally, our FivePoint large community development program is well positioned to become a significant profit generator in the coming years." Mr. Miller concluded, "As we head into 2013, we are extremely well positioned to gain market share in a recovering market. We have a strong balance sheet and seasoned management team, and we will continue to benefit from our strategic land acquisitions and new community openings. With a beginning sales backlog value up more than 100% from the prior year, fiscal 2013 promises to be another year of strong profitability." RESULTS OF OPERATIONS THREE MONTHS ENDED NOVEMBER 30, 2012 COMPARED TO THREE MONTHS ENDED NOVEMBER 30, 2011 Lennar Homebuilding Revenues from home sales increased 41% in the fourth quarter of 2012 to $1,152.2 million from $816.5 million in the fourth quarter of 2011. Revenues were higher primarily due to a 32% increase in the number of home deliveries, excluding unconsolidated entities, and a 7% increase in the average sales price of homes delivered. New home deliveries, excluding unconsolidated entities, increased to 4,426 homes in the fourth quarter of 2012 from 3,359 homes in the fourth quarter of 2011. There was an increase in home deliveries in all the Company's Homebuilding segments and Homebuilding Other. The average sales price of homes delivered increased to $261,000 in the fourth quarter of 2012 from $243,000 in the same period last year. Sales incentives offered to homebuyers were $25,800 per home delivered in the fourth quarter of 2012, or 9.0% as a percentage of home sales revenue, compared to $33,900 per home delivered in the same period last year, or 12.2% as a percentage of home sales revenue, and $26,100 per home delivered in the third quarter of 2012, or 9.2% as a percentage of home sales revenue. Gross margins on home sales were $270.3 million, or 23.5%, in the fourth quarter of 2012, compared to $158.4 million, or 19.4%, in the fourth quarter of 2011. Gross margin percentage on home sales improved compared to last year, primarily due to a decrease in sales incentives offered to homebuyers as a percentage of revenue from home sales, an increase in the average sales price of homes delivered and lower valuation adjustments. Gross profits on land sales totaled $3.3 million in the fourth quarter of 2012, compared to $0.8 million in the fourth quarter of 2011. Selling, general and administrative expenses were $130.1 million in the fourth quarter of 2012, compared to $112.5 million in the fourth quarter of 2011. As a percentage of revenues from home sales, selling, general and administrative expenses improved to 11.3% in the fourth quarter of 2012, from 13.8% in the fourth quarter of 2011, primarily due to improved operating leverage and lower advertising costs. Lennar Homebuilding equity in loss from unconsolidated entities was $12.4 million in the fourth quarter of 2012, primarily related to the Company's share of operating losses of Lennar Homebuilding unconsolidated entities, which included $6.6 million of valuation adjustments primarily related to asset sales at a Lennar Homebuilding unconsolidated entity. This compared to Lennar Homebuilding equity in loss from unconsolidated entities of $69.2 million in the fourth quarter of 2011, which included the Company's share of valuation adjustments of $57.6 million related to an asset distribution from a Lennar Homebuilding unconsolidated entity as the result of a linked transaction. This was offset by a pre-tax gain of $62.3 million included in Lennar Homebuilding other income (expense), net, related to that unconsolidated entity's net asset distribution. The transaction resulted in a net pre-tax gain of $4.7 million in the fourth quarter of 2011. Lennar Homebuilding other income (expense), net, totaled ($2.2) million in the fourth quarter of 2012, compared to Lennar Homebuilding other income (expense), net, of $69.7 million in the fourth quarter of 2011, which included the $62.3 million pre-tax gain related to an unconsolidated entity's net asset distribution discussed in the previous paragraph. Lennar Homebuilding interest expense was $50.2 million in the fourth quarter of 2012 ($26.7 million was included in cost of homes sold, $0.5 million in cost of land sold and $23.0 million in other interest expense), compared to $43.2 million in the fourth quarter of 2011 ($20.9 million was included in cost of homes sold, $0.3 million in cost of land sold and $22.0 million in other interest expense). Interest expense increased due to an increase in the Company's outstanding debt and an increase in deliveries, partially offset by a lower weighted average interest rate. Lennar Financial Services Operating earnings for the Lennar Financial Services segment were $33.2 million in the fourth quarter of 2012, compared to $9.1 million in the fourth quarter of 2011. The increase in profitability was primarily due to increased volume and margins in the segment's mortgage operations and increased volume in the segment's title operations, as a result of a significant increase in refinance transactions and homebuilding deliveries. Rialto Investments Operating earnings for the Rialto Investments segment were $4.6 million in the fourth quarter of 2012 (which included $4.8 million of operating earnings offset by $0.2 million of net earnings attributable to noncontrolling interests), compared to operating earnings of $8.0 million (which included $6.0 million of operating earnings and an add back of $2.0 million of net loss attributable to noncontrolling interests) in the same period last year. Revenues in this segment were $36.0 million in the fourth quarter of 2012, which consisted primarily of accretable interest income associated with the segment's portfolio of real estate loans and fees for managing and servicing assets, compared to revenues of $46.5 million in the same period last year. Revenues decreased primarily due to lower interest income as a result of a decrease in the portfolio of loans. Expenses in this segment were $29.0 million in the fourth quarter of 2012, which consisted primarily of costs related to its portfolio operations, loan impairments of $5.4 million primarily associated with the segment's FDIC loan portfolio (before noncontrolling interests) and other general and administrative expenses, compared to expenses of $38.4 million in the same period last year. Expenses decreased primarily due to a decrease in loan servicing expenses. Rialto Investments other income (expense), net, was ($6.1) million in the fourth quarter of 2012, compared to $0.9 million in the same period last year. Rialto Investments other income (expense), net, includes expenses related to owning and maintaining real estate owned ("REO"), impairments on REO, gains from sales of REO, gains (losses) from acquisitions of REO through foreclosure and rental income. The segment also had equity in earnings (loss) from unconsolidated entities of $3.9 million in the fourth quarter of 2012, which primarily related to the Company's share of earnings from the Rialto Real Estate Fund (the "Fund") of $4.2 million. During the fourth quarter of 2012, a majority of the remaining securities in the investment portfolio underlying the AllianceBernstein L.P. ("AB") fund formed under the Federal government's Public-Private Investment Program ("PPIP") were monetized related to the unwinding of its operations, resulting in a $12.0 million liquidating distribution. Equity in earnings (loss) from unconsolidated entities was ($3.0) million in the fourth quarter of 2011, consisting primarily of $7.6 million of unrealized losses related to the Company's share of the mark-to-market adjustments of the investment portfolio underlying the AB PPIP fund, partially offset by $2.5 million of interest income earned by the AB PPIP fund and $2.0 million of equity in earnings related to the Fund. Corporate General and Administrative Expenses Corporate general and administrative expenses were $39.0 million, or 2.9% as a percentage of total revenues, in the fourth quarter of 2012, compared to $28.5 million, or 3.0% as a percentage of total revenues, in the fourth quarter of 2011. The increase in corporate general and administrative expenses was primarily due to an increase in personnel related expenses as a result of an increase in share-based and variable compensation expense. Noncontrolling Interests Net earnings (loss) attributable to noncontrolling interests were ($0.8) million and ($4.8) million, respectively, in the fourth quarter of 2012 and 2011. Net loss attributable to noncontrolling interests during the fourth quarter of 2012 was primarily attributable to noncontrolling interests related to the Company's homebuilding operations. Net loss attributable to noncontrolling interests during the fourth quarter of 2011 was attributable to noncontrolling interests related to the Company's homebuilding and Rialto Investments operations, of which the Rialto operations related to the FDIC's interest in the portfolio of real estate loans that the Company acquired in partnership with the FDIC. Income Taxes During the fourth quarter of 2012, the Company concluded that it was more likely than not that a portion of its deferred tax assets would be utilized. This conclusion was based on additional positive evidence including actual and forecasted earnings. Accordingly, during the fourth quarter of 2012, the Company reversed $44.5 million of its valuation allowance of which the majority was previously maintained to be utilized in remaining interim periods of 2012. This reversal was offset by a tax provision of $25.9 million primarily related to fourth quarter 2012 pre-tax earnings. Therefore, the Company had an $18.6 million net benefit for income taxes in the fourth quarter of 2012. Debt Transaction During the fourth quarter of 2012, the Company issued $350 million of 4.750% senior notes due 2022 in a private offering under SEC Rule 144A. The net proceeds of the sale will be used for working capital and general corporate purposes, which may include the repayment or repurchase of its senior notes or other indebtedness. phxDOTcorporate-irDOTnet/phoenixDOTzhtml?c=65842&amp;p=irol-newsArticle_print&amp;ID=1774494&amp;highlight=</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358252723030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:25:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358252911943-7</Id><Topic><Title>Lennar Reports Fourth Quarter EPS of $0.56</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358252723030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:25:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LEN Chart bigchartsDOTmarketwatchDOTcom/advchart/frames/frames.asp?show=&amp;insttype=Stock&amp;symb=len&amp;time=6&amp;startdate=1%2F4%2F1999&amp;enddate=1%2F8%2F2012&amp;freq=1&amp;compidx=aaaaa%3A0&amp;comptemptext=&amp;comp=&amp;ma=4&amp;maval=9+15+50&amp;uf=7168&amp;lf=1&amp;lf2=4&amp;lf3=2&amp;type=4&amp;style=320&amp;size=3&amp;timeFrameToggle=false&amp;compareToToggle=false&amp;indicatorsToggle=false&amp;chartStyleToggle=false&amp;state=11&amp;x=0&amp;y=0 Analyst Estimates marketwatchDOTcom/investing/stock/len/analystestimates</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358252911943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:28:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358255512199-8</Id><Title>Scientists: Backing Keystone pipeline would ‘undermine’ Obama’s climate legacy</Title><Msg>Scientists: Backing Keystone pipeline would ‘undermine’ Obama’s climate legacy By Ben Geman - 01/15/13 06:00 AM ET A group of prominent climate scientists say President Obama’s legacy is on the line as he mulls whether to approve the Keystone XL oil sands pipeline. “We hope, as scientists, that you will demonstrate the seriousness of your climate convictions by refusing to permit Keystone XL; to do otherwise would be to undermine your legacy,” the 18 scientists wrote in a public letter to Obama released Tuesday. Scientists signing the letter include James Hansen of Columbia University and NASA, Stanford University’s Ken Caldeira, Scripps Institution of Oceanography emeritus professor Richard Somerville, and Penn State’s Michael Mann. The full list is available here. Environmentalists are pressing the White House to scuttle TransCanada Corp.’s proposed pipeline to bring oil from Canadian oil sands projects to Gulf Coast refineries. They oppose Keystone due to greenhouse gas emissions from oil sands production and use, damage to forests from the massive projects, and fears of spills along the route. Business groups and a number of major unions are pressing the White House to approve Keystone. They call it a way to create jobs and improve energy security by strengthening ties to Canada, which is already the biggest supplier of oil to the U.S. The letter, organized by the environmental group 350.org, cites recently unveiled federal data showing that 2012 was the hottest year on record in the contiguous U.S. “You take office for the second time at a critical moment. As you may know, the U.S. has just recorded the hottest year in its history, beating the old mark by a full degree; the same year that saw the deep Midwest drought, and the fury of Hurricane Sandy, also witnessed the rapid and unprecedented melt of the Arctic ice pack,” they write. The State Department is weighing whether to grant TransCanada a permit for the project, but Obama has indicated that he will ultimately be the decider on Keystone. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/277149-scientists-backing-keystone-pipeline-would-undermine-obamas-climate-legacy</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358255512199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 08:11:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358260079730-9</Id><Title>Ethanol’s Discount to Gasoline Strengthens on Corn Supplies</Title><Msg>Ethanol’s Discount to Gasoline Strengthens on Corn Supplies By Mario Parker - Jan 14, 2013 2:43 PM MT 0 Comments Ethanol’s discount to gasoline strengthened to the narrowest in four weeks as smaller corn supplies signaled higher costs. The spread contracted 2.44 cents as ethanol extended its longest streak of gains since July on signs of higher feedstock prices. An Agriculture Department report on Jan. 11 showed corn stockpiles in the U.S. on Dec. 1 totaled 8.03 billion bushels, 17 percent less than a year earlier. “The corn market’s strong so ethanol’s trying to follow along with it,” said Mike Blackford, a consultant at INTL FCStone in Des Moines, Iowa. “Ethanol’s got to stay with corn to make sure the plants stay on.” Ethanol was 42.41 cents a gallon below the price of gasoline, based on prompt-month contracts for both commodities. That was less than the 44.85 cents on Jan. 11 and the smallest gap since Dec. 17. Denatured ethanol for February delivery rose 3.9 cents, or 1.7 percent, to settle at $2.33 a gallon on the Chicago Board of Trade, the highest price since Dec. 11. Prices have advanced 9.9 percent in the past year. Corn for March delivery advanced 15.25 cents, or 2.2 percent, to $7.24 a bushel in Chicago, the highest price since Dec. 17. The futures have risen 21 percent in the past year. Losing Money Based on March contracts for corn and ethanol, producers are losing 28 cents on each gallon of the fuel made, up from 27 cents on Jan. 11, according to data collected by Bloomberg. The figures exclude the revenue that can be made from the sale of dried distillers’ grains, a byproduct of ethanol production that can be fed to livestock. In cash market trading, ethanol on the West Coast jumped 6 cents, or 2.5 percent, to $2.45 a gallon and in the U.S. Gulf the additive increased 6 cents, or 2.6 percent, to $2.385, data compiled by Bloomberg show. Ethanol in New York gained 3.5 cents, or 1.5 percent, to $2.40 a gallon and in Chicago the biofuel rose 2.5 cents, or 1.1 percent, to $2.30. Gasoline for February delivery increased 1.46 cents, or 0.5 percent, to $2.7541 a gallon on the New York Mercantile Exchange. The contract covers gasoline that’s made to be blended with ethanol before delivery to filling stations. bloombergDOTcom/news/2013-01-14/ethanol-s-discount-to-gasoline-strengthens-on-corn-supplies.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358260079730</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:27:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358260223572-10</Id><Topic><Title>Ethanol’s Discount to Gasoline Strengthens on Corn Supplies</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358260079730</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:27:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New owner says Pratt ethanol plant to reopen in late spring By Dan Voorhis The Wichita Eagle Published Monday, Jan. 14, 2013, at 6:08 p.m. 2 Comments An ethanol plant in Pratt closed since 2008 will reopen in late spring, an official with the Scoular Co. said Monday. Omaha-based Scoular bought the shuttered 55 million-gallon-a-year ethanol plant, plus the adjacent railroad track and grain elevator, from Gateway Plant, LLC in 2011. On Monday, Scoular announced that it had sold most of its interest in the plant to Pratt Biofuel Investors, a company newly formed by the investors behind a Pixley, Calif., ethanol plant, Calgren Renewable Fuels. Lyle Schlyer, president of Calgren Renewable Fuels, was named president of ethanol plant, Pratt Energy. Scoular retains full ownership of the track and elevator and a minority stake in the ethanol plant. It will procure all feedstock for the plant and market and ship the ethanol and distillers grains produced there. Terms of the transaction were not announced. John Heck, senior vice president with Scoular, said the plant closed in 2008. Gateway later declared bankruptcy. Although ethanol production in the U.S. has leveled off in the last few years, Heck said the market for ethanol isn’t bad. “There is good demand for ethanol out of Kansas plants today,” he said. “If you look at the plants selling ethanol, they’re all busy. We think the long-term prospects for the plant are good.” Scoular started work on the plant in the summer, but Pratt Biofuel has now taken over. Jerry Schroeder, formerly with Calgren and now with Pratt Biofuel, is managing the renovations and will become plant manager when it becomes operational. Heck said Pratt Biofuel is looking for a few construction-related employees who might eventually become plant employees. More staff is expected to be hired closer to the plant re-opening. Located on the Union Pacific Railroad, the plant can load 100-car trains of grain, dried distillers grains and ethanol. Scoular said the operation is part of its grain marketing network. Scoular has eight facilities in Kansas, including shuttle train loading facilities at Coolidge, Downs, Salina and Wellington. It employs more than 150 people in Kansas. kansasDOTcom/2013/01/14/2635981/new-owner-says-pratt-ethanol-plant.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358260223572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 09:30:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358263165388-11</Id><Title>Apple is symptomatic of the entire stock market bubble</Title><Msg>The stock has now crashed 30% in just a few months. The basic laws of economics and common sense dictate that no company is going to be able to earn high rates of return in a competitive industry for long. Competition will emerge to reduce the profit margin. Without the high rates of return the $700 stock is worth a tiny fraction of that. The same situation exists for other bubbles like energy. There is no shortage of energy and the ability of society to generate new technology to lower prices is infinite. When real estate rises higher and higher in a place like the United Kingdom, nearly reaching the 2006 highs even as the economy languishes in a recession, one has to wonder about the sanity of markets. Across Europe the same thing has been going on and now real estate is priced to yield only a few percent. It gets that way because central banks have driven long term interest rates to only a few percent or less. The same money herded into a stocks in a desperate gamble to get return chases houses and land. Unfortunately for the dreamers, real estate generates one of the lowest rates of economic return in the economy, and cannot generate long run economic output to justify the prices. For many areas like land speculation and housing it is difficult to identify any return at all - it just absorbs capital and produces absolutely nothing.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358263165388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:19:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358264592873-12</Id><Title>Why doesn't Fracking Industry use Bio-Diesel/Ethanol blends to frac with?</Title><Msg>Gas Frac can viscosify natural gas to carry the frac sand. What is wrong with using the Bio-Diesel/ethanol blends? If it is messing up Auto Industry and requiring a huge re-tooling to make the autos. Use it all there. Farmers win and the government mandates win.</Msg><Username>metalfluid</Username><Timestamp>1358264592873</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:43:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358265079235-13</Id><Topic><Title>Oil sands and cancer clusters.</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1358224860847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 23:41:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A friend of mine told me he knows a guy that leased his land to an oil company for fracking. All his cows stop giving milk...</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1358265079235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:51:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358266310346-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama looked poised and spoiling for a fight on the debt ceiling</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358185453404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hansesteelyard is absolutely correct. The Republicans are clearly too weak to respond. Either too weak, or on board with Obama's mission. Sadly, they don't even attempt to disguise it. Marx would have reveled in Obama. Well done, my good and faithful servant follower.</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1358266310346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:11:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358266883537-15</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hanse, why are you wanting to be taxed? do you work? i'm serious, i ask in sincerity, since when do citizens WANT more taxes? what is the thinking?</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1358266883537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:21:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358267932203-16</Id><Topic><Title>Oil sands and cancer clusters.</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1358224860847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 23:41:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... and then they started forming crop circles!</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1358267932203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:38:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358268206815-17</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Higher taxes reduce the US deficit and increase the strength of the dollar. I own a large amount of dollars. I would own Deutsche Marks for a permanent store of value if I could but the dollar is the next best thing. I'm a German citizen so US taxes do not concern me. While I will be married to an American shortly I will still be German. If I did choose to become American I would still support higher taxes. A strong currency, growing human capital from taxes and government, and a growing economy is a better environment to prosper in than limited government...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358268206815</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 11:43:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358270578791-18</Id><Title>Red hot GSX</Title><Msg>Already doubled this week and will triple.</Msg><Username>van12</Username><Timestamp>1358270578791</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:22:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358272771065-19</Id><Topic><Title>XOM - Important Update!</Title><Username>paulwhitford56</Username><Timestamp>1358253535933</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:38:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yest it is</Msg><Username>ragsdale_robert</Username><Timestamp>1358272771065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 12:59:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358272804159-20</Id><Topic><Title>XOM - Important Update!</Title><Username>paulwhitford56</Username><Timestamp>1358253535933</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:38:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shorts taking over lol</Msg><Username>ragsdale_robert</Username><Timestamp>1358272804159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:00:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358275101324-21</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The U.S. rebuilt your country after your leaders tore it down and now continue to subsidizes it. What a parasite...</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1358275101324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:38:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358275268622-22</Id><Topic><Title>XOM - Important Update!</Title><Username>paulwhitford56</Username><Timestamp>1358253535933</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:38:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>listen to people who got it right befote</Msg><Username>eugenewindsor</Username><Timestamp>1358275268622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:41:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358276193552-23</Id><Topic><Title>XOM - Important Update!</Title><Username>paulwhitford56</Username><Timestamp>1358253535933</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:38:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow some many people interested i signed up</Msg><Username>luis.goodman</Username><Timestamp>1358276193552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 13:56:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358276606323-24</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The U.S. rebuilt your country after your leaders tore it down and now continue to subsidizes it." Wrong. The US looted many tens of billions of dollars worth of German technology after World War II by appropriating German patent rights for US companies. It then appropriated the fruit of many thousands of German scientists and engineers in 'Operation Paperclip' and other programs to pursue jet aircraft, rocketry, and spaceflight, and various DOD tape computing and electronic systems etc… The American university and public school systems were copied from Germany as well, and without them the US would have been on par with Mexico by the time the world wars came around. As for industrialization without knowledge, that is just laughable, and knowledge without those German institutions would have been quite sparse. You'd still be living off the sweat of slaves if not for German institutions. As for German industrial capital - it was in quite good shape in 1945 and not needing of "rebuilding." Within a few years Detroit was run out of business by German companies, not to mention many other industrial fields. Germany subsidized America today to the tune of many tens of dollars yearly, buy its debt and propping up its currency, as do other countries. American succeeds despite your parasitic party and creed, and will do much better when they are swept away.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358276606323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:03:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358277018778-25</Id><Topic><Title>XOM - Important Update!</Title><Username>paulwhitford56</Username><Timestamp>1358253535933</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 07:38:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are awesome</Msg><Username>williammiller840</Username><Timestamp>1358277018778</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:10:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358277364611-26</Id><Title>Currency Purchase...</Title><Msg>100% £...1.6055 $/£ This is not a trade but a permanent move until at least after the debt ceiling negotiations are completed.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358277364611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:16:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358278900709-27</Id><Topic><Title>Currency Purchase...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358277364611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:16:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% 30 Year UK Gilts...3.24% yield.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358278900709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358280525377-28</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some people know their social responsibilities. The wealthy benefited the most from the Gov. bailouts.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1358280525377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:08:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358280964628-29</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The US looted many tens of billions of dollars worth of German technology after World War II" That's known as the spoils of war. A war which your leaders were responsible for. It came at a great expense of U.S. lives and treasure to put your goose-steppers back in the box. "As for German industrial capital - it was in quite good shape in 1945 and not needing of "rebuilding."" In 1945 most of Germany looked liked a moonscape, there was no economic structure and very little food. Again, which your leaders were responsible for. Germany couldn't support its people let alone industry. "Germany subsidized America today to the tune of many tens of dollars" Wow, many tens of dollars... I got many tens of dollars in my back pocket. "You'd still be living off the sweat of slaves if not for German institutions." Do you mean these German institutions? Bergen-Belsen Börgermoor Buchenwald Dachau Dieburg Esterwegen Flossenburg Gundelsheim Neuengamme Papenburg Ravensbruck Sachsenhausen Sachsenburg As my granddaughter would say "Oh snap". You are so funny.</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1358280964628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:16:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358281193330-30</Id><Title>Inflation of American GDP numbers...</Title><Msg>If you compare the UK to the US you will notice that US GDP is about 20% higher per person. There are several reasons for that none of which reflect greater real income on the part of Americans: 1) The majority of UK residential housing is masonry while America emphasizes wood-frame, and masonry requires far less upkeep and replacement over time than wood-frame, and incurs lower heating expenses. Higher expenditures on upkeep, replacement, and heating to maintain the inferior American housing stock increase American GDP as they are counted as final goods. 2) The US healthcare system delivers equivalent medical services, but at a higher cost, than the UK's socialized system. American GDP counts the higher American cost (in other words the increment of waste) as higher output, adding 8-10% to American GDP. 3) Americas burn more oil to perform equivalent economic tasks because of poor urban planning and the lack of any systematic national transportation policy. The waste of energy shows up as higher American GDP. In the end such waste does not increase American wealth at all however which is why UK citizens have on average the same level of wealth as American citizens. So we see two societies with equivalent wealth and income and one with a far bigger government than the other. America faces many challenges with its flawed system of checks and balances. Germany, of course, is richer than both America and the UK on a per person basis... Income figures are similarly skewed downward by the greater efficiency and less waste counted as GDP, but even so they match US levels...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358281193330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:19:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358281240726-31</Id><Topic><Title>Oil sands and cancer clusters.</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1358224860847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 23:41:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a good one!</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1358281240726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:20:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358281256462-32</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waste of time... Go find a goat to fornicate with - it might improve your genetic line.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358281256462</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:20:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358283026653-33</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go boink a goat!? That's all you got? LOL</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1358283026653</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:50:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358283427181-34</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time is running short and the goat is the best I can think of to entertain you. Wall Street is getting ready to close and the only reason I bother "observing" your country is it. I will be "boinking" much finer American this evening. Enjoy your goat. I hope it inspires you. ...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358283427181</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358287122381-35</Id><Title>Oil industry escalates attacks on biofuel mandate</Title><Msg>Oil industry escalates attacks on biofuel mandate By Zack Colman - 01/15/13 12:16 PM ET The oil industry on Tuesday escalated its attacks on the federal biofuel mandate as it rolled out a national ad campaign aimed at promoting the nation’s refineries. The ad blitz from the American Petroleum Institute will be an “all hands on deck” effort across TV, print, radio and online, Cindy Schild, the lobby's senior manager, said Tuesday in a call with reporters. She said getting Congress to axe the biofuel rule is "one place to start" to strengthen the domestic refining industry. “EPA [Environmental Protection Agency] has been unable and sometimes unwilling to make it workable. That is why we need Congress to scrap” the renewable fuel standard, Schild said. Schild said also said API plans “to be devoting a lot of resources” to getting the Keystone XL pipeline approved. “We certainly have been touting those benefits and the job potential,” Schild said of the project, which would bring Canadian oil sands to Gulf Coast refineries. The Obama administration has final say on the pipeline’s northern leg because it crosses into Canada. API CEO Jack Gerard said last week that the Keystone decision would serve as a bellwether for how Obama plans to work with the oil-and-gas industry in his second term. But environmentalists have kept pressure on Obama to reject the pipeline, saying its approval would be out of step with the president's recent comments about making climate change a priority in his second term. API declined to release a spending figure for the commercials, which will run nationally for a month, but the group did detail its concerns about the biofuel mandate. After years of pressing EPA for piecemeal changes, the powerful industry group in November shifted to gunning for an outright repeal. API has said ending the fuel rule is one of its top priorities in 2013. Patrick Kelly, downstream policy adviser with API, said the lobby group is waiting for the right opportunity to float a repeal bill. “We are encouraging Congress to take it up this year. We have not seen specific legislation that we are pursuing at this time, but we are open to exploring avenues with congressional staff,” Kelly said in a call with reporters. The rule requires refiners to blend 36 billion gallons of biofuel into traditional transportation fuel by 2022. So far, the House Energy and Commerce Committee has said it plans to hold a hearing to look into claims that a high-ethanol fuel blend might damage cars. Fiscally conservative detractors say the rule interferes with energy markets by propping up the biofuels industry. And some lawmakers have argued the domestic oil-and-gas boom makes the mandate unnecessary. But theodds of getting a total repeal through Congress look long. Support for the fuel rule is predominantly regional, getting strong backing from rural GOP and Democratic lawmakers who view it as a boon for their economies. Many lawmakers also defend the rule as a way to reduce dependence on foreign oil. The biofuels industry vehemently defends the rule, and says any modifications would chill investment in “advanced” biofuels from non-edible feedstock. Some of those facilities are just now starting to reach commercial production levels. Biofuels groups also contend API and its members are gunning for the rule because it cuts into the oil industry’s profits by requiring biofuel use. “We agree that in order for the United States to achieve greater control over fuel and lower prices for consumers, we need to increase domestic production of energy. But what is ‘unworkable’ is a continued oil monopoly over our nation’s transportation fuel: we need not only the energy security that renewable fuel provides, but fuel diversity and savings that the industry is delivering to consumers,” Fuels America, a lobbying effort that includes several biofuels trade groups, said in a statement. Kelly said API is concerned refiners would hit a “blend wall” this year. Crossing that threshold would require blending higher concentrations of ethanol fuel to meet accelerating targets established by the mandate. Currently, most gasoline contains 10 percent ethanol. But EPA has approved sale of a 15-percent ethanol blend — known as E15 — for cars made in the model year 2001 or later. API, along with motor club AAA, has pushed back against EPA’s determination — and the biofuels industry's assertions — that E15 is safe for cars. They say the higher ethanol fuel blend damages cars and gasoline pumps, noting EPA tested E15’s impact on only vehicle emissions systems. Kelly said that API’s “concern is [going] beyond 10 percent” ethanol in fuel blends. When asked whether API could support a change that locked fuel blends in at 10 percent ethanol instead of a full repeal, Kelly said, “I don’t think we’d recommend an E10 mandate.” thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/277243-api-ad-campaign-to-push-for-biofuel-rule-repeal</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358287122381</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 16:58:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358287700160-36</Id><Title>Court rules against Big Oil in dispute over ethanol blend</Title><Msg>Court rules against Big Oil in dispute over ethanol blend Posted on January 15, 2013 at 3:44 pm by Zain Shauk Comments(0) | An ethanol plant in Missouri (AP file photo/Southeast Missourian, Aaron Eisenhauer) Despite protests from the oil industry, a federal appeals court on Tuesday refused to allow a challenge to an Environmental Protection Agency decision encouraging more ethanol to be blended into gasoline. The American Petroleum Institute, AAA and food producers, including the Grocery Manufacturers Association and Tyson Foods, all have opposed the agency’s move to allow up to 15 percent ethanol in gasoline blends. Nearly all gasoline sold in the country is blended with up to 10 percent ethanol. The EPA in 2010 approved the sale of E15 in the United States, and the fuel is currently safe for use in vehicles with model years 2001 and later, according to the agency. But opponents argue that the fuel is unsafe for vehicles that weren’t designed to use E15 and that ethanol production creates enormous new demand for corn, driving up food prices for humans and animals. Opponents had challenged the EPA’s ruling in court, but the case was thrown out by a federal judge because the parties involved had not detailed how they were affected by the E15 decision. Their argument for another hearing was refused Tuesday for the same reason by a three-judge panel in for the U.S. District Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia. “We’re disappointed in the court’s decision not to hear the case, and we are weighing our legal options,” API spokesman Carlton Carroll said in an email. “EPA approved E15 even though research by automakers, the oil industry and the government showed potential mechanical and infrastructure problems with E15 that could also lead to serious safety and environmental problems.” The Department of Energy and the EPA argue that research on E15 backed by the oil industry and automakers has been flawed and has insisted that the fuel is safe to run in vehicles made since 2001. E15 currently is available for sale at fewer than a dozen refueling stations nationwide, according to the Renewable Fuels Association. U.S. Circuit Judge Brett Kavanaugh, who wrote a dissenting opinion on the appeals court decision, argued that the case should be heard because E15 had substantial implications for both food and fuel producers. Kavanaugh said “the food producers’ economic interests are directly affected by the increased demand for corn caused by EPA’s E15” decision. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/01/15/court-rules-against-big-oil-in-dispute-over-ethanol-blend/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358287700160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 17:08:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358298364281-37</Id><Title>EPA says new air quality revisions will slash industry costs, health risks</Title><Msg>EPA says new air quality revisions will slash industry costs, health risks By Ben Goad - 01/15/13 12:09 PM ET The Environmental Protection Agency on Tuesday issued final revisions to a 2010 air quality rule, saying the changes would reduce costs associated with the regulations while also protecting public health. The revisions stem from settlement agreements reached between the agency and industry groups that mounted a legal challenge following release of the original rule. The rule imposes air pollution standards for</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358298364281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:06:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358298456532-38</Id><Topic><Title>EPA says new air quality revisions will slash industry costs, health risks</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358298364281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:06:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>url.. thehillDOTcom/blogs/regwatch/legislation/277247-epa-says-new-air-quality-revisions-will-slash-industry-costs-health-risks</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358298456532</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 20:07:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>