<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366097169859-1</Id><Topic><Title>Offshore Ireland</Title><Username>whynagg</Username><Timestamp>1366050454896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:27:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weather very stormy all around Ireland today, but the four service vessels are where they are planned to be awaiting arrival of the deep sea rig. The boys on board will be pretty seasick at this stage?</Msg><Username>whynagg</Username><Timestamp>1366097169859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 03:26:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366097493061-2</Id><Topic><Title>Maxipad</Title><Username>max_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1366073325854</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:48:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More like commie stroker the half pint commie runt.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366097493061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 03:31:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366097565948-3</Id><Topic><Title>library closed.</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366005465106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 01:57:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is the miserable commie #$%$ runt.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366097565948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 03:32:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366101341423-4</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have started a thread here titled "Offshore Ireland"...if any shareholder of XOM cares to pop over and say hello...I shall be posting updates on the impending drill site for Exxon's Irish adventure, where the Erik Raude is moving to drill the DUNQUIN prospect in deep water. Charlie</Msg><Username>whynagg</Username><Timestamp>1366101341423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 04:35:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366104665971-5</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have started a new thread Offshore Ireland here in Yahoo and I invite longs and shorts over to join in the excitement of the Exxon drill at Dunquin offshore SW coast of Ireland, the deepest drill program ever in European waters.The prospect is aimed at proving up a billion barrels or recoverable oil &amp; gas, their partner Providence already having set Irish oil prospects on fire with an internationally proven 400m barrels now seeking a partner which may be Exxon after bthey drill Dunquin. Those of you that want to see the Exxon share price go up, may find it's recovery is centred Offshore |Ireland...cm'on over and say hello...Charlie</Msg><Username>whynagg</Username><Timestamp>1366104665971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 05:31:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366105481591-6</Id><Topic><Title>library closed.</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366005465106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 01:57:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe someone made him think about being a traitor to his country.</Msg><Username>bluemax19</Username><Timestamp>1366105481591</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 05:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366105520516-7</Id><Topic><Title>Maxipad</Title><Username>max_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1366073325854</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:48:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He must know what he is by now.</Msg><Username>bluemax19</Username><Timestamp>1366105520516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 05:45:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366105635035-8</Id><Topic><Title>problem w/ gun control is---who controls the guns ???</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365953077535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 11:24:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The communist liberals. And the crooks includung the dems.</Msg><Username>bluemax19</Username><Timestamp>1366105635035</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 05:47:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366110364579-9</Id><Topic><Title>Maxipad</Title><Username>max_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1366073325854</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:48:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He knows exactly what he is.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366110364579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 07:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366110438237-10</Id><Topic><Title>library closed.</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366005465106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 01:57:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No that commie POS will never change as someone can not grow brains.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366110438237</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 07:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366116114605-11</Id><Title>Universal Bioenergy Inc. (UBRG)</Title><Msg>little company, but looks like a huge future</Msg><Username>ubrg_1</Username><Timestamp>1366116114605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366117075407-12</Id><Topic><Title>EU policy: nearly eliminate fossil fuels by 2050</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365778020508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:47:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366117075407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366117656869-13</Id><Topic><Title>Stock</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1366069810743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 19:50:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your presumption seems to be that oil &amp; gas is a good investment the potential of which the management of Exxon is undermining. That is wrong. The oil &amp; gas industry is headed for bankruptcy in the coming years. It is irrelevant how it manages its investments when the investments are based on what will be an obsolete products. What remnant of the industry which manages to survive will be in places like Saudi Arabia and state owned.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366117656869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366118122779-14</Id><Title>Nearly 300 EV Charging Stations At Kroger Stores</Title><Msg>Nearly 300 EV Charging Stations At Kroger Stores April 16, 2013 Zachary Shahan The rollout of EV chargers at big box stores actually makes me somewhat thankful for big box stores (but no, I’m not forgetting that they ruin cities and local economies). The exposure is tremendous, and this of course helps EV drivers who shop at these stores. So, it’s with great joy that I share the post below from EV Obsession about Kroger’s big step forward in support EV drivers and the electric revolution: I recently highlighted the fact that public EV charging stations are blowing hydrogen fueling stations out of the water, and that there are now well over 5,000 public EV charging stations across the US. There are actually about 200 public charging stations being added in the US each month. Some well known big box stores (e.g. IKEA, Walmart, Kohl’s) have been early leaders in bringing EV charging stations to the public. The latest such announcement comes form Kroger. Kroger last week announced a massive new rollout of charging stations in partnership with ECOtality. They announced “an expanded partnership including over 200 level 2 (quick charge) charging stations, and 25 DC Fast Chargers, to be installed across key markets through the EV Project,” as the press release stated. “This multimillion dollar expansion will bring the total number of Blink chargers at the Kroger Family of Stores to almost 300.” Kroger invested $1.5 million to install these chargers. They were installed at 125 locations in key markets (such as Phoenix, San Diego, and Los Angeles). Kroger and ECOtality previously teamed up to install 60 charging stations in Oregon and Washington, and 14 in Texas. cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/04/16/nearly-300-ev-charging-stations-at-kroger-stores/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366118122779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366119007505-15</Id><Title>Tax writers warm to giving renewables parity with fossil fuels</Title><Msg>Tax writers warm to giving renewables parity with fossil fuels Posted on 04/16/2013 by Environment and Energy Daily midwestenergynewsDOTcom/2013/04/16/tax-writers-warm-to-giving-renewables-parity-with-fossil-fuels/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366119007505</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:30:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366124898909-16</Id><Topic><Title>White House extends aviation biofuel program</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366072467145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:34:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just get your biofuels out of the ground. I have not studied it but I would not be surprised if you have to burn more energy making man made biofuels than you get in return and how many people will die in airplane crashes when the biofuels cause engine failure. Just askin'.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366124898909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366126027274-17</Id><Title>'suspicious package' at Las Colinas??</Title><Msg>I guess it could happen anywhere...</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1366126027274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366126367545-18</Id><Topic><Title>Nearly 300 EV Charging Stations At Kroger Stores</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366118122779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:15:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kroger is installing about 200 "level 2" charging stations, which in an hour can give a car enough power to drive 12 to 25 miles, Jader said. Twenty-five DC Fast Chargers — which can fill up to 40% of a battery in about 20 minutes — will also be installed. I am not surprised you left this bit of information out. What are you going to do while you are roasting in the heat waiting for your batteries to charge?</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366126367545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:32:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366127026365-19</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels make liberals feel good</Title><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366125624214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong, wrong, and wrong, and irrelevant. It is not necessary to produce the energy input products with oil &amp; gas. The net energy balance to go to liquid fuel using an alternative energy source as the energy input could be net energy negative for the process and still be profitable, as the economic cost of the energy and process, not the net energy balance determines economic viability. Solar &amp; wind will be the primary energy supply mechanism, and the cost is plummeting being driven along by the power of quantum chemistry backed by government. The difficulties this causes for American manufactures is a sign of your peril. The German government wants the cost down, as do its allies, and it does not care how much losses it causes for its competition- indeed if it can run it out of business so much the better... The poor organization of US institutions is irrelevant. Germany's systems are networked and capable of being controlled, and Germany is not the only player. You might as well argue that because the Bundeswehr operates at a net loss to the economy that it will disappear as to argue that the establishment developing alternative energy will disappear. I doubt seriously grain crops will be the bio-feed Germany's scientists have in mind either. There are very large tracts of land that are best suited to forest and woodlands...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366127026365</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366129166937-20</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels make liberals feel good</Title><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366125624214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you are going to cut down and kill trees that consume CO2 (green house gas) and consume energy to convert it to biofuels instead of pulling out natural biofuels out of the ground that are already converted to hydrocarbons? Or are you going to consume more and more land that could be used to grow food crops so that the cost of groceries goes up so that the poor can no longer buy enough food. Tell me how that is smart.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366129166937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:19:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366130489187-21</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels make liberals feel good</Title><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366125624214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your analysis is wrong. Try harder. It is should be obvious to you how wrong it is too if you think back to a time when there were no fossil fuel inputs and all energy was coming from agricultural, forestry, wind, etc. Such systems were very inefficient, but that was a function of the low level of knowledge not the potential of the system to produce net energy without net C02 output. First produce a complete picture of the system correctly analyzed from the point of view of C02 and other emissions output. If this is beyond your ability - too bad. Second imagine what will happen to the efficiency if you just throw money at it, and scientific talent at it, just as was done to improve armaments... Scientists can think about more than war. If you consider the situation for a country like the Netherlands which would disappear if sea levels rose perhaps you can consider why they do no care what it costs to prevent that outcome. Germany considers Netherlands and ally, too...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366130489187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366134044469-22</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels make liberals feel good</Title><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366125624214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry, the Netherlands are not going to disappear no matter. Scare tactics are used to keep cult members in line. Biofuels, when combusted create CO2 just like "fossil" fuels and you have to burn way more ethanol than octane to get a certain amount of energy. Biofuel production uses energy and causes the price of food to increase if grains are used. What is to like unless there is some profit motive behind it?</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366134044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:40:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366137237722-23</Id><Title>Warning to right-wing militia types.</Title><Msg>You have gone to far this time. Big crack-down coming.</Msg><Username>jerrym30711</Username><Timestamp>1366137237722</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:33:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366137511080-24</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels make liberals feel good</Title><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366125624214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Biofuels, when combusted create CO2 “ A plant takes carbon the out of the atmosphere to create biomass. When the fuel is burned the C02 goes back to the atmosphere. Obviously you do not understand that. This indicates you are operating at the level of less than an elementary school student. “Scare tactics are used to keep cult members in line…” Oh the people have been indoctrinated to support the view. In the end it is irrelevant whether there is a real danger. For the right-wing Hegelians this is a useful end in itself, as it allows the government to tax, spend, conduct industrial policy, and redistribute income to a middle class. This is something the German government has been doing for centuries, and the Dutch and Swedish government before it. There is no better tax payer than a willing tax payer. The difference now is energy is a useful product, while the outputs of a military-industrial complex are far less so. Still both are better than for society than mindless consumerism. As Hegel said: “the state is the power of reason actualizing itself as will.” The state has decreed the extinction of your industry. Carry on with your arrogance and ignorance and see where it gets you… The EU is 500 million people, and the healthy Germanic portion 300 million; and we outweigh the entire USA in income &amp; wealth.... Your industry doesn’t stand a chance…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366137511080</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366138625996-25</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels make liberals feel good</Title><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366125624214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am originally from Germany so I would not put it down but they have their share of stumn den kopf. Was looking around and found a cellulosic ethanol company that makes 40 gallons of ethanol per ton of wood. How much fuel do you think they burned to get that ton of wood to the plant? If they would spend all of those billions of wasted tax dollars on the development of better CO2 scrubbers that would make more sense.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366138625996</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366139724880-26</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels make liberals feel good</Title><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366125624214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...and let's not forget that those fragments of wood used to make ethanol there came from trees that did actively scrub CO2 from the air before it was cut down. Just insane.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366139724880</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366143320715-27</Id><Topic><Title>Down she goes....AGAIN!</Title><Username>tsobie</Username><Timestamp>1366036749710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:39:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AGREE . The underperformance of this stock over the last 5 years is astounding. Look at a chart.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1366143320715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366143555724-28</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>WOW recovered a whole 12 cents today after losing $2.50 yesterday. Five years of this daily drastic underperformance . Things will just get worse under the Tillerson wrecking crew and the supine somnolent board of directors.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1366143555724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366144041225-29</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>I've been a shareholder in several different companies. I have never seen a company screw its shareholders a viciously as Exxon. This latest raise for Tillerson in light of the horrendous relative performance of the stock and puny dividend is just another slap in the face.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1366144041225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366144365202-30</Id><Title>Buy backs by Xom hurt those looking for dividend s</Title><Msg>Buy back increases the hidden value in Xom, People want dividends,, the Ageing Americans want more dividends, as threats of cuts in future pensions and social security benefits making them look for better paying stocks and Xom is not known as a high yield dividend company.</Msg><Username>smkpit</Username><Timestamp>1366144365202</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:32:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366152819216-31</Id><Title>Bought XLE at 75.05 as a play on XOM and CVX</Title><Msg>Targeting XOM back to 88.50. Should 3-5 days. What do you guys think?</Msg><Username>jc18630</Username><Timestamp>1366152819216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366153514315-32</Id><Title>BCCI to triple in week..YAHOO NEWS HEADLINES</Title><Msg>HUGE SUCCESS$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>tra.peace</Username><Timestamp>1366153514315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366157869870-33</Id><Title>Sen. Whitehouse: Obama could use Keystone approval to tackle climate change</Title><Msg>Sen. Whitehouse: Obama could use Keystone approval to tackle climate change By Ben Geman - 04/16/13 11:23 AM ET If President Obama insists on approving the Keystone XL pipeline, he should tether the decision to measures that help fight climate change, according to one liberal senator. Sen. Sheldon Whitehouse (D-R.I.) strongly opposes construction of the pipeline, and argued that any decision in favor of it should not come in isolation. “If they are determined to go down that path and they can’t be dissuaded, then the important thing is to make sure that they surround that decision ... [with] a whole formidable array of environmental and anti-carbon measures that can not just offset the harm that they do by approving [Keystone] ... but actually turn the whole package into a very strong, anti-carbon pollution suite of strategies,” Whitehouse told reporters Tuesday. Whitehouse wants to see measures including Environmental Protection Agency carbon emissions standards for existing power plants. He spoke to reporters after remarks at “Good Jobs, Green Jobs,” a conference that brings together several labor unions and environmental groups. Asked if he thinks Obama will approve Keystone XL, Whitehouse replied: “I think it is a very realistic prospect.” The State Department is leading the federal review of TransCanada Corp.’s proposed pipeline, which would bring oil from Canadian oil sands projects across the border en route to Gulf Coast refineries. The oil-and-gas industry has made approval of the project a top priority, and are clashing with environmentalists who want Obama to reject it. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/294133-sen-whitehouse-to-obama-keystone-pipeline-approval-cant-come-alone</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366157869870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366158661645-34</Id><Title>High costs slowing new liquid natural gas plants</Title><Msg>Posted on April 16, 2013 at 5:20 pm by Emily Pickrell in LNG, Natural Gas, North America Higher capital costs for new liquefied natural gas projects and government barriers may be holding back the industry from providing needed resources to new markets, a panel of industry experts said Tuesday afternoon at the LNG17 conference in Houston. While natural gas has become abundant in the United States, the technology needed to transform it into a liquid that can be transported is still an expensive proposition and the federal government has been slow to approve export facilities. “We are trying to stem the increase (in costs) so that we can become competitive and meet our needs for a reasonable rate of return,” said Richard Guerrant, vice president for ExxonMobil gas and power marketing. Guerrant explained that in order for LNG exports to Asia to be profitable, the international price of LNG must cover the cost of processing and transportation, a differential that is pressuring Exxon to invest in the most advanced processing technologies. Exclusive: Shell’s Odum is optimistic on liquefied natural gas for transportation But these technology advancements are making new projects stunningly expensive. Chevron recently raised its estimate of its Gorgon project in Australia to $54 billion, saying that labor shortages and bad weather were continuing to raise costs. “The types of projects are an order of magnitude more expensive and the cash flow profile is different,” Guerrant said, explaining that many of these projects must be financed upfront because of their unconventional and risk nature. Net imports of liquefied natural gas decreased by 1.9 percent in 2012, which panel experts... fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/04/16/high-capital-costs-slows-increase-of-additional-liquid-natural-gas-plants/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366158661645</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:31:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366158892492-35</Id><Topic><Title>Sen. Whitehouse: Obama could use Keystone approval to tackle climate change</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366157869870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Environmentalists are jobs killers that let their paranoia about global warming cloud good thinking. Just plant a tree and be done with it.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366158892492</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:34:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366166428584-36</Id><Topic><Title>Sen. Whitehouse: Obama could use Keystone approval to tackle climate change</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366157869870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:17:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anti Carbon Messages? Al Gorus did his film and made school children watch it over and over in different school classes. Unfortunately............or fortunately, his Carbon Trading firm collapsed after the exposure of his role ............He &amp; his Limited Partnership 'buddies' in the Carbon Scam lost their #$%$ ets.</Msg><Username>basherbuste_r</Username><Timestamp>1366166428584</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 22:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>