<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358312486563-1</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation of American GDP numbers...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358281193330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:19:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More BS - boring as always</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1358312486563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:01:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358313613011-2</Id><Title>Atlantic Wind Connection Outlines Plans For First Phase Of Offshore Wind Transmission 'Backbone'</Title><Msg>Atlantic Wind Connection Outlines Plans For First Phase Of Offshore Wind Transmission 'Backbone' by NAW Staff on Tuesday 15 January 2013 The companies behind the Atlantic Wind Connection (AWC) - an offshore wind transmission "backbone" planned by independent transmission company Trans-Elect and developer Atlantic Grid Development, and backed by Google, Bregal Energy, Marubeni Corp. and Elia - have revealed some of the details for the first phase of the project. The group has selected New Jersey for the project's first phase, which will be called the New Jersey (NJ) Energy Link. According to the companies, the selection was based on the state's commitment to developing an offshore wind energy industry and the large potential for renewable energy that exists off its shoreline. The NJ Energy Link, which will be built in three phases, will be a subsea offshore electrical transmission cable linking energy resources and end users in northern, central and southern New Jersey. The cable will span the length of New Jersey and carry 3 GW of electricity. According to AWC, the NJ Energy Link will help support the goal of developing offshore wind by reducing the cost of offshore wind energy; creating a superhighway for wind farms; and providing ratepayers with a transmission line that works 100% of the time, not just when the wind is blowing. AWC expects that construction on the NJ Energy Link will begin in 2016 and that the first phase will enter service in 2019. nawindpowerDOTcom/e107_plugins/content/contentDOTphp?contentDOT10970</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358313613011</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:20:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358313722701-3</Id><Topic><Title>Atlantic Wind Connection Outlines Plans For First Phase Of Offshore Wind Transmission 'Backbone'</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358313613011</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:20:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Breaking New Ground on Grid Rules By MATTHEW L. WALD January 15, 2013, 12:48 pm1 Comment Among the “firsts” being tried by the Atlantic Wind Connection, the venture seeking to build an electric transmission line from southern Virginia to northern New Jersey, is negotiating the regulatory system. The problem is that the cable, which would be buried under the seabed, is what grid officials call a “multidriver project,” or a project that is undertaken for more than one reason — something that those officials have little experience with. To be built, the project must win the approval of the regional grid association, the PJM Interconnection. (The letters used to stand for Pennsylvania-Jersey-Maryland, but the organization now extends into all or part of Virginia, West Virginia, Delaware, Ohio and Illinois.) And PJM has three different systems for approving lines and apportioning their costs. The Atlantic Wind Connection project fits into at least two of these categories. The regulatory complications help explain why so little transmission capability is built these days in this country, even when there is growing agreement that the United States should be moving toward low-carbon energy sources like wind power. Often wind turbine technology operates best in places lacking transmission capability. PJM has the authority to approve a line and add the cost to the bills of all the customers in its territory, or just to some, depending on the line’s function. Other regional transmission organizations, like the New York Independent System Operator or ISO New England, which covers that six-state area, have similar provisions. If the line is judged to be important for the reliability, then a socialization principle is applied and everybody pays a little bit. The developer would borrow money to build the line and be paid back through revenue over the years, using a rate of return on its investment approved by the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission. The rates tend to be generous by comparison with typical investment returns today because the commission wants to encourage construction of new transmission. A second reason for building the line is that if electricity is expensive at one end of the line are high and far cheaper at the other, the new connection would help lower the price of electricity. Steven R. Herling, vice president for planning at PJM, said that if that was the assumption, his organization would run a computer simulation of anticipated prices in both areas, taking into account planned new generation and retirements of power plants. Then it would run a second simulation with the new line in place. The calculation includes how much prices will fall in the expensive area and how much they will rise in the area from which power will be taken. The difference is judged to be the benefit to the economy, and the ratio of benefit to cost must be at least 1 to 1.25. That, too, could be billed to all participants. The third reason to build the new line is to support a state policy related to encouraging renewable energy. New Jersey has a cluster of such policies; one requires that 22.5 percent of the state’s electricity be generated from renewable sources by 2021, and the bulk of that is expected to come from wind, some of it possibly from outside New Jersey. Another policy sets aside part of that total for solar power. A third calls for at least 1,100 megawatts of wind power generation within the state (or offshore), as opposed to imported from places that are better suited to wind power than most of New Jersey, like Pennsylvania ridge tops. The developers are claiming a reliability benefit for the Atlantic Wind Connection, but it is far from clear that the line would qualify. Still, it appears to meet an economic need, with prices in southern New Jersey generally far lower than those in northern New Jersey, plus a policy goal. The catch, Mr. Herling said, is that grid operators like PJM “really don’t have a track record” for approving projects undertaken for more than one reason, although procedures for doing so are now on file at the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission. “The line is not realistically going to make it as simply a transmission corridor in the water,’’ he said. “As the means of satisfying significant amounts of renewable requirements, it may very well be a very strong project.,’ he said. But that, he and others point out, depends partly on those offshore wind farms finally getting built. greenDOTblogsDOTnytimesDOTcom/2013/01/15/breaking-new-ground-in-grid-rules/?partner=rss&amp;emc=rss</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358313722701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:22:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358313803130-4</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That's known as the spoils of war"- that's what is known as theft, and while the theft is irrelevant at this point, the fact that it did occur disproves both your premise and the theory that the US was very helpful in "rebuilding." "A war which your leaders were responsible for." - they are not my leaders, and the Federal Republic of Germany is organized under a different system of government than the flawed Wiemar System imposed by the beloved American and "allies." "In 1945 most of Germany looked liked a moonscape, there was no economic structure and very little food. Again, which your leaders were responsible for. Germany couldn't support its people let alone industry." Wrong. 80% of German housing was intact in 1945 and German industrial capital was 125% of the 1939 level in 1945. Agriculture was barely scratched. Administrative chaos from several occupying powers did contribute to much disruption however especially in the banking sector and the movement of goods from producers to consumers. The capital itself was quite intact and restarting the economy when the incompetence of the foreign military governments was pushed aside by leaders in Deutsche Bank and industry was straightforward. "Germany subsidized America today to the tune of many tens of dollars" -tens of billions - and hundreds of billions over the years... If not for foreign investment your currency would be a ruin. "Do you mean these German institutions?" - you can thank American meddling in the first world war for that, and the transformation of Europe into an economic mad house when the house of cards constructed after the world came crashing down... It provoked a most severe outburst by some people who are better left not in power... Just ill bred trash...typical though.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358313803130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:23:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358313836725-5</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation of American GDP numbers...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358281193330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:19:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% fact -as always. More trash...as always.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358313836725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:23:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358314540194-6</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation of American GDP numbers...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358281193330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:19:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"More BS - boring as always" -one can only hope you live long enough to see the end of your company. Cheers, and GFY!</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358314540194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 00:35:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358341332696-7</Id><Topic><Title>Currency Purchase...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358277364611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:16:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold 30 Year UK Gilts...3.22% yield. Change in price +0.60% 100% £.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358341332696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:02:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358342040391-8</Id><Topic><Title>Currency Purchase...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358277364611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:16:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% £ short term: LIBOR rate, 0.5%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358342040391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:14:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358342657180-9</Id><Topic><Title>Currency Purchase...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358277364611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 14:16:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold for $ 1.5992 $/£ loss of 0.4% on the currency and gain of 0.6% on the bonds. Net: +0.20%. 100% $</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358342657180</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:24:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358347017403-10</Id><Topic><Title>Scientists: Backing Keystone pipeline would ‘undermine’ Obama’s climate legacy</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358255512199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 08:11:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder if these guys are protesting the transport &amp; export of oil sands crude to China?</Msg><Username>commishfree1</Username><Timestamp>1358347017403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:36:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358347320855-11</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't know what economic school of thought you attended but raising taxes and reducing the deficit will not increase the strength of the dollar. If I were you I would sell your large amounts of dollars and buy tangible assets. All fiat currencies have risk associated with them when issued by central banks. Higher taxes is not the answer. Lowering taxes and allowing business to keep the capitol to create jobs is the answer. More jobs = more taxpayers. The only way to increase the strength (value) of the dollar is to raise interest rates and make it more expensive to borrow. Money is like any other commodity - the more of it that exists the more the current pool is diluted thus devalued - this equals inflation. "growing human capital from taxes and government" does not grow economies it stifles economies and encourages central economic planning which only leads to social engineering. You appear to be quite the Keynesian - good luck with keeping those dollars!!!!</Msg><Username>cgw3431</Username><Timestamp>1358347320855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:42:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358348376096-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obama looked poised and spoiling for a fight on the debt ceiling</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358185453404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yes - "the superiority of collectivism" is working quite well for the European Union. Apparently the German people are most happy to give their money away to the failing EU states.....................</Msg><Username>cgw3431</Username><Timestamp>1358348376096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:59:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358349001734-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama looked poised and spoiling for a fight on the debt ceiling</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358185453404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a reason I do not own euros. The EU is an idiotic concept too and will fail. Collectivism with alien cultures does not work. Collectivism refers to nationalism and the means to advance it, as per Hegel, and nationalism and multiculturalism are contradictory concepts. Nationalism, aka cultural collectivism, is of course advanced by government. The Germanic cultures of Europe are doing quite well and a northern euro, or new Deutsche Mark, and Greater Reich - including the UK if it wanted - would work well as there is a common culture to support it. Southern Europe is totally alien and forcing the two into a common currency and banking system and political "union" is a receipt for absolute disaster for Southern Europe as capital flees the weakness there.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358349001734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 10:10:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358349614133-14</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your theories are total nonsense. I've been through the concepts before and will do it again until I see a reason. You don't even know what human capital means. As for your claim that the theory I espouse - which is German supply side economics - is somehow Keynesian that is total nonsense as well. Keynesians believe in the value of "animal spirits" or the benevolent speculator coming to the economy's rescue. Germany supply side economics is somewhat different. The speculator is the problem, and the high prices and distortions they cause are the problem. You obviously know nothing about banking either. Most of the assets of banks are government bonds and government bonds derive all their value from taxes. The currency value is nothing more than a reflection of the value of those bank credits backed by the government debt. The strength of the banking system and confidence in the currency is much more important than the self-interested goals of the speculators. Increasing taxes will most certainly make the $ stronger, and in turn the US economy.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358349614133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 10:20:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358351022398-15</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It truly must suck being German, no matter hard you try to take the moral high ground some schmuck always brings up the Nazis. Seriously Adolf, blaming the U.S. for the Holocaust, have you no shame?</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1358351022398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 10:43:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358351042754-16</Id><Title>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending January 11, 2013</Title><Msg>Summary of Weekly Petroleum Data for the Week Ending January 11, 2013 U.S. crude oil refinery inputs averaged 15.1 million barrels per day during the week ending January 11, 2013, 156 thousand barrels per day below the previous week’s average. Refineries operated at 87.9 percent of their operable capacity last week. Gasoline production increased last week, averaging 8.6 million barrels per day. Distillate fuel production decreased last week, averaging about 4.6 million barrels per day. U.S. crude oil imports averaged over 8.0 million barrels per day last week, down by 312 thousand barrels per day from the previous week. Over the last four weeks, crude oil imports have averaged about 7.9 million barrels per day, just under 1.2 million barrels per day below the same four-week period last year. Total motor gasoline imports (including both finished gasoline and gasoline blending components) last week averaged 375 thousand barrels per day. Distillate fuel imports averaged 186 thousand barrels per day last week. U.S. commercial crude oil inventories (excluding those in the Strategic Petroleum Reserve) decreased by 1.0 million barrels from the previous week. At 360.3 million barrels, U.S. crude oil inventories are well above the upper limit of the average range for this time of year. Total motor gasoline inventories increased by 1.9 million barrels last week and are also well above the upper limit of the average range. Finished gasoline inventories decreased while blending components inventories increased last week. Distillate fuel inventories increased by 1.7 million barrels last week and are near the lower limit of the average range for this time of year. Propane/propylene inventories decreased by 1.6 million barrels last week, but remained well above the upper limit of the average range. Total commercial petroleum inventories increased by 3.4 million barrels last week. Total products supplied over the last four-week period have averaged about 18.4 million barrels per day, up by 1.7 percent from the same period last year. Over the last four weeks, motor gasoline product supplied has averaged about 8.4 million barrels per day, down by 0.6 percent from the same period last year. Distillate fuel product supplied has averaged just under 3.4 million barrels per day over the last four weeks, down by 5.2 percent from the same period last year. Jet fuel product supplied is 1.1 percent higher over the last four weeks compared to the same four-week period last year. irDOTeiaDOTgov/wpsr/wpsrsummary.pdf Data Overview (Combined Table 1 and Table 9) PDF irDOTeiaDOTgov/wpsr/overview.pdf</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358351042754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 10:44:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358351909442-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama looked poised and spoiling for a fight on the debt ceiling</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358185453404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Collectivism can be divided into horizontal collectivism and vertical collectivism. Horizontal collectivism stresses collective decision-making among relatively equal individuals, and is thus usually based on decentralization. Vertical collectivism is based on hierarchical structures of power and on moral and cultural conformity, and is therefore based on centralization. A cooperative enterprise would be an example of horizontal collectivism, whereas a military hierarchy would be an example of vertical collectivism. In political economy, horizontal-collectivism is often associated with the economic theories of socialism, which call for some form of co-operative or collective ownership of the means of production and collective decision-making or worker's self-management within economic enterprises. In essence collectivism is the 21st century buzzword for socialism which requires big government to control every aspect of one's life. Unfortunately your Prime Minister Angel Merkle supports the EU and will continue to drain the German economy to bailout failing member nations.</Msg><Username>cgw3431</Username><Timestamp>1358351909442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 10:58:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358352970294-18</Id><Title>What happens if you follow Republican low-tax ideology to its ruinous conclusion...</Title><Msg>Historical Example: Imperial Germany Imperial Germany's economic policy was very similar to the current American Republican Party's policy. The Kaisers' government pursued a policy of high spending on the military and government in general. They refused, however, to raise taxes to finance the spending. Instead the government just started borrowing. From 1900 to 1914 the German government's debt spiraled up. When World War I came along the government's credit went into free fall. It refused to raise taxes to pay of the war, believing it could borrow its way to prosperity. To make matters worse, the German banking system had relatively few bank deposits and short term reserves that the Reichsbank could borrow to subsidize the government's borrowing spree. The German banking system was an investment banking system which borrowed large sums to finance long term industrial and commercial lending, not a short term credit based system on the Anglo-American model. The German banking system was well suited to financing industrialization but very poor at financing a spendthrift government. With a small amount of deposits and liquid savings capable of being loaned to the government, interest rates climbed higher and higher as the government borrowed from 1914 to 1923. What the Reichsbank could not borrow from its banks, which was just about everything by 1916, it just printed and used the printed notes to buy government debt. Interest rates climbed from a few percent, to 25%, to 80%, to around 1 quadrillion percent, annualized, by 1923. The currency was arbitrarily set at 1 quadrillionth the value of 1913 when it was finally replaced. People in short term credits - in practice lending to finance daily call loans- maintained most of their value as they rode the wave of interest rates higher and higher, but anyone in long term bonds, or equities was obliterated. The economy collapsed as the currency's value fell and capital fled to the short term - by 1923 hourly loans - or fled the country entirely. The British government, facing similar strains to the German Reich, borrowed, but taxed as well, and faced no such difficulties maintaining the value of its currency... The US government taxed and borrowed to cover its commitments. Now the US government has chosen the irresponsible policy of the Reich of old. Borrow and spend and see what happens...Thankfully for the United States the irresponsible policy of the Republican Party is ending will end entirely as they are driven from power...If the Democrats revert to Republican ways the result will be an interest rates spiral just as confronted Imperial Germany. It will take longer to happen as the American banking system has vast reserves of deposits to borrow, but those reserves are not infinite.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358352970294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:16:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358352986277-19</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would strongly suggest you do some economic studies. Maybe read some Murray Rothbard or Henry Hazlet's "Economics in One Easy Lesson". If that doesn't work then perhaps some perusing of the Mises Institute website to read about economies and currencies. With fiat currency's the norm in a global economy it is doomed to failure. In all of human history their has never been a fiat currency that has not been debased to worthlessness. The power to tax is the power to destroy. Excessive taxation destroys economies it does not add value to currencies. Human capital is the stock of competencies, knowledge, social and personality attributes, including creativity, embodied in the ability to perform labor so as to produce economic value. It is an aggregate economic view of the human being acting within economies, which is an attempt to capture the social, biological, cultural and psychological complexity as they interact in explicit and/or economic transactions. In other words you are merely a tool - I think I consider myself a little more than that........</Msg><Username>cgw3431</Username><Timestamp>1358352986277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:16:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358353387779-20</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I would strongly suggest you do some economic studies." I would strongly suggest you observe the realities of the world and how the economy really works. I'm well past the point of tiresome reading and lectures from people and authors who neither know how the economy works, or how to make money from it. If you want to read and believe such twaddle go ahead. It is irrelevant.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358353387779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:23:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358356695473-21</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If most of the bank assets are government bonds then where did the banks get the money to buy the bonds??? Where do the corporations and businesses store their capital?? Why would banks put the bulk of their assets in bonds ( which pay less then +/- 3%) when they can loan at upwards of 6 - 29% and borrow from the FED at .25%. Excess bonds held by banks is merely a result of the "carry trade" due to the low borrowing rates from the FED. Borrow at .25% invest at 3% that's a deal I would take.... With a fiat currency the value is a mere reflection of the global economy's faith in the currency - the dollar gets its value as the "global currency of reserve" and nothing else. If the global oil market did not require the purchase of oil in $ the $ would be pretty much worthless. We export our inflation to our trading partners but this will be changing. Russia, China, India and Brazil are already trading oil in gold and other currencies and have pretty much come to the conclusion that the dollar will eventually become worthless. Once other nations realize that their purchase of Treasury bonds will be devalued through inflation the dollar will be toast.</Msg><Username>cgw3431</Username><Timestamp>1358356695473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:18:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358357795857-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama looked poised and spoiling for a fight on the debt ceiling</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358185453404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:44:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Government without a common culture is a failure and will never work. Supranational institutions that attempt to combine alien cultures flows directly out of the tradition of aristocratic governance that dominated Medieval Europe. It failed then and will fail wherever it is tried. The aristocrats owned lands in many cultural areas and attempted to govern them as one. The Plantagenet Kings, and the Habsburgs specialized in such lunacy. One reason Spain, and the rest of Southern Europe, was so backward until just recently is the utter failure of the Habsburgs and the fools who called themselves leaders in Spain etc to form nations. The Spanish "Empire" was nothing of the sort, and just a jumble of cultures divided geographically and dominated by local grandees and destinated to failure; of course the place is still a failure. England was the first country to discover the superiority of the nation and the collectivist society. The Netherlands, then France, then Germany came along. Germany was an economic failure until it discovered the principle of nationalism and collectivism. If Germany attempts to subvert its sovereignty to the EU I will leave...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358357795857</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:36:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358357889389-23</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are such a economic expert how come you don't write a financial blog? Just because your economic theory can be debunked doesn't mean we can't learn something from you. Don't be so close minded.</Msg><Username>cgw3431</Username><Timestamp>1358357889389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:38:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358358045638-24</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read Hegel. There is right thinking and there is wrong thinking. Open mindedness to wrong ideas is a useless thing... You can prove it through the methods of philosophical logic - the ultimate source of truth.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358358045638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:40:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358359139415-25</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Marx was a disciple of Hegel and adopted his theoretical thesis of dialectic reasoning in order to affect change in a society. Marx's goal was socialism. Problem + Reaction = Solution. Unfortunately, problem + predicted reaction are carefully planned to produce the desired outcome (Solution). This is how the elitists have molded societies for the last 100 years - where ever societies or cultures are headed it is always the result of our 'overlords' desire to control us........ That is the real truth!!!</Msg><Username>cgw3431</Username><Timestamp>1358359139415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:58:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358359841030-26</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Marx wrote a critique of Hegel denouncing most his ideas. Marx did not believe in cultural collectivism but rather international socialism. Internationalism socialism seeks to find a common ground among different class groups such as the "proletariat" across cultures. The groups are total theoretical garbage designed to appeal to the rabble Marxist ideologues needed to gain power. Dividing a society up as Marx does to attempt to combine its pieces with culturally alien classes from other cultures does not advance national collectivism, it does the reverse. Such an attitude is wrong thinking as per Hegel and quite useless to be broad minded about. Cultural Marxism is another name for the modern day vision of such twaddle. Small government ideologues do the work of Marxists for them as only a powerful central government can counter their ideas. Doing nothing and allowing individuality to run rampant is very useful for them...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358359841030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:10:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358360779523-27</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Open mindedness to wrong ideas is an opportunity to educate and debate the virtues of differing philosophical logic. As long as man has free will to think and do as he/she pleases the "ultimate source of truth" will be skewed by bias and level of education............... Only facts can provide truth not philosophical logic.</Msg><Username>cgw3431</Username><Timestamp>1358360779523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:26:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358360788145-28</Id><Title>More taxes = more spending</Title><Msg>If we all gave 50% in taxes, they would spend all of it and want 80%. This country is divided now more than ever before. Liberals and conservatives are like baking soda and vinager or like potassium and water. Refusing to CUT...means eager to TAX. There's no other way to put it. EOM</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358360788145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:26:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358360892344-29</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wrong. Wrong ideas are wrong in the first instance and wrong always. They do not gain value by being considered...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358360892344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:28:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358361241645-30</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The right way to approach wrong ideas is to allow someone who is high educated to filter the mass of ideas that are out there and summarily condemn and extirpate from mass discussion the wrong ones. Presenting wrong ideas to uneducated people is not wise. That is one of the key principles of right wing government - government by the Principles of Right... The "Universal Class",consisting of the wealthy and those with time for serious thought are the natural candidates to do the filtering of ideas... I</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358361241645</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:34:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358361801031-31</Id><Topic><Title>More taxes = more spending</Title><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358360788145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:26:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is high time we ask Obama about his end-game. What is he trying to achieve?? A rational person knows that there is fat that has to be cut. He refuses to cut or to negotiate. Why? Not for the overall good of the nation, clearly. To pay off his base? Transfer to them salary and pork and free bennies? It appears that way. Anything else? To truly BK the nation? Maybe. Maybe it woul help him achieve political aims.</Msg><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1358361801031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:43:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358361952389-32</Id><Topic><Title>What happens if you follow Republican low-tax ideology to its ruinous conclusion...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358352970294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:16:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you want a successful model look to Estonia and modern Sweden (last 15 years). Taxes were cut. Public salaries were cut. Freedom was expanded and the economies flourished. Then again we have Greece and other PIG countries.... that serve as disastrous examples.</Msg><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1358361952389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:45:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358362442819-33</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, well it appears that you are quite the global socialists. You would best be served in the company of Henry Kissinger and David Rockefeller as they espouse the same political idealism. Damned the masses and their auto-determination. The wealthy and intellectual elite know what's best for all of us - including you. You will eventually get what you sow. Apparently you disdain the thought of being a free man. Your wish may come true sooner then you think!!!!! It's no wonder you get such scorn on this message board........</Msg><Username>cgw3431</Username><Timestamp>1358362442819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:54:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358363561738-34</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Well, well it appears that you are quite the global socialists." A global socialist believes in collectivism across cultures. I believe in collectivism within a single culture. The ideas a mutually exclusive and contradictory. You might as well claim that up is down and down is up to equate them. The reason I believe in cultural collectivism is simple: the concept explains the historical record of the economy, and society, and the record of successes and failures. The outcomes of history occur they way they do for a reason and are rational. Right thought should be able to explain them and it can. "What is rational is actual and what is actual is rational."- Hegel. You are just taking blind shots into a dark room, forcing things to fit your opinions, just as you did above and have been doing all along.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358363561738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:12:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358364038511-35</Id><Topic><Title>More taxes = more spending</Title><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358360788145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:26:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reality is you have a deficit, and the deficit will destroy you if you do not get rid of it. A further reality is you are up against an ideology you cannot defeat and which will not relent in its quest for a bigger government. The rational choice for you is to accept the tax increase. The irrational choice is to ignore reality and attempt to make the world as you would like it rather than accepting what is.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358364038511</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:20:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358364612543-36</Id><Topic><Title>What happens if you follow Republican low-tax ideology to its ruinous conclusion...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358352970294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:16:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Greece's example is object. A country that did not raise enough taxes to pay its bills. One more example of a spendthrift land failing. How useful. Sweden has been run by collectivist principles for about 350 years now. It has a central bank the Riksbank and expanding government for even longer than England. When productivity improves enough from sound collectivist governance tax cuts are possible. The irrational option of deciding you do not like taxes and do not like government and then deciding to run the experiment of not raising sufficient taxes to pay for the government you have is not a wise one.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358364612543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:30:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358366733331-37</Id><Topic><Title>PLEASE SEND THIS TO THE CEO OF EXXON</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1358364751421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:32:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey dude--this coming Monday--High of zero, low of -15, no warming climate in Eau Claire,WI! Luv, JFM</Msg><Username>franco5</Username><Timestamp>1358366733331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:05:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358367062932-38</Id><Title>Middle East And North Africa To Reach 3.5GW Solar Power Capacity By 2015</Title><Msg>Middle East And North Africa To Reach 3.5GW Solar Power Capacity By 2015 January 16, 2013 Mridul Chadha According to a recent report published by GTM Reserach the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region will be installing nearly 3.5 GW of solar capacity by 2015. The study was conducted in collaboration with the Emirates Solar Industry Association (ESIA). The study also forecasts that the solar market in the MENA region could represent 8% of total demand globally by 2015. The GTM Research report states that Saudi Arabia and Turkey are expected to have the highest demand, with 70% of the total MENA demand by 2015. Saudi Arabia is expected to be the region’s first gigawatt-scale market by the end of 2015. The report forecasts Turkey to be the second strongest market in the region in 2015 and beyond, due to its favourable renewable energy policies, and its prior wind projects installation experience is expected to translate into greater solar demand. The study predicts that the overall regional outlook calls for more than 10 GW of solar power demand through 2017, but the majority of this demand is expected to come by 2015. “In terms of solar energy, it is clear that the MENA region is set to experience significant change over the next five years,” said Scott Burger, GTM Research analyst and the report’s author. “While Saudi Arabia will likely be the largest market in the long-term, there will be significant opportunities throughout the region. With strategic planning and a solid development of local partners and supply chains, savvy companies will be able to capitalize on all of the opportunities in the region.” Drivers For Renewable Energy In MENA Region For oil-producing nations in the MENA region, renewable energy can substitute domestically for subsidised oil-generated electricity and thus help in freeing oil for export at higher prices. Renewable energy can play a significant role in the diversity of the energy supply backed up by the vast renewable energy sources in some countries. There is also a need for greater regional security of supply in terms of interconnection and utilisation of renewable electricity from strong resource areas across the region. GTM Research states in its report that the MENA region is set to experience significant change over the next five years and attractive investment opportunities will arise in the region. Renewable Energy Plans In MENA Region Several countries have announced ambitious plans for deployment of renewable energy infrastructure in the MENA region. Qatar has announced plans to install 1.8 GW of PV capacity by 2014 and Dubai aims to source 5% of its power supply from solar by 2030. Abu Dhabi will soon commission Shams-1, a 100MW concentrating solar power plant (our Site-Director took a tour of the Shams-1 which is also the world’s largest single-unit solar power plant). Saudi Arabia has also announced a renewable energy strategy that will include 16 GW of solar power facilities and 25 GW of concentrating solar power facilities by 2030. Additionally, there is the massive DESERTEC project backed by EU being planned in the MENA region. sDOTtt/1yvGC</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358367062932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:11:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358367250099-39</Id><Topic><Title>More taxes = more spending</Title><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358360788145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:26:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hans, . As an investor, as a businessman, as a father, and as a citizen, I am truly thankful that I don't have your "give-up" attitude, or your false sense of self importance.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1358367250099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:14:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358368054977-40</Id><Topic><Title>More taxes = more spending</Title><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358360788145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:26:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm just telling you what logic says is rational and best for you. Philosophy and logical thought is not a self-interested actor and has no claims to self-importance. If you wish to attach to me the theory I espouse that is amusing but rather pathetic on your part. I told you where it came from - Hegel. If you want to understand the Progressives you are up against, you should read him. Sometimes the white flag is the best strategy. Germany did surrender to the other-self it created in its image in 1945 and also in 1918 - the Progressives of the USA, of course. So surrender is a rational option. "If a battle can't be won don't fight it..."</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358368054977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:27:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358368610563-41</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation of American GDP numbers...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358281193330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:19:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm dead sure it will around for a long long time - long after you are gone.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1358368610563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:36:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358368638756-42</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation of American GDP numbers...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358281193330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:19:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% your opinion - as always.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1358368638756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:37:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358368917885-43</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation of American GDP numbers...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358281193330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:19:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Statistisches Bundesamt - for German figures... Federal Reserve flow of funds for US figures on wealth and income World Bank... A chimp could discover the facts on housing just by typing the key words I used into google. Tiresome</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358368917885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:41:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358369330378-44</Id><Topic><Title>Debt Ceiling Fight</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358177258216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 10:27:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't seem to have worked for your mother.</Msg><Username>sandysonar44</Username><Timestamp>1358369330378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:48:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358369693709-45</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation of American GDP numbers...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358281193330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:19:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes you are.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1358369693709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:54:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358370019135-46</Id><Topic><Title>Inflation of American GDP numbers...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358281193330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 15:19:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yes you are." So like a parrot. Totally ignorant as always too, and vacant of any factual or logical ability. just sad I will be around for another 50 years ,at least, judging just by actuarial life tables, which is more than enough time to watch your company die... The market is closed and the evening games commence... ta ta</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358370019135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 16:00:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358372978985-47</Id><Title>On the heels of Newtown</Title><Msg>With O Reilly, Krauthammer, Ed Schultz and Pierce Morgan constantly promoting weapons restrictions, the best the spinmeisters can poll is 55% for restrictions and 45% against. The Neocon Trotskyites love the USA flooding the world with weapons and keeping the US borders wide open. Wall Street's Manhattan media are desperate to confiscate weapons as American taxpayers awaken to increasingly suffocating debt. Wall Street rapes Main Street</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1358372978985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 16:49:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358373781376-48</Id><Title>Only 1 reason why a new approach is attacked...</Title><Msg>....when it is known to work. The NRA spent quite a bit here in Australia to campaign against the ban a automatic and semi-automatic weapons. An approach new only to the US. The ban worked in Australia. Australians were shown the recent NRA commercial. They ask why Americans don't know that there was an armed guard at the Columbine High School.</Msg><Username>hypno_hype</Username><Timestamp>1358373781376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 17:03:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358374318690-49</Id><Topic><Title>More taxes = more spending</Title><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358360788145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:26:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes "Hans" 1. you are advocating capitulation. 2. almost certainly any new revenue will be spent and not used to reduce defects 3. revenue collection alone will NOT reduce the defect. cuts are necessary, though you fail to acknowledge that 4. you have not persuaded me that "bigger govt" will translate to a better US society, despite any positive outcome under Bismarck or Gladstone. 5. at what point does big government become oppressive and indeed totalitarian and Socialist? 6. Obama is violating the constitution in many of his actions. you are not considering the founding document for our country.</Msg><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1358374318690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 17:11:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358374373902-50</Id><Topic><Title>More taxes = more spending</Title><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358360788145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:26:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>7. at what point does open revolt to Mr. Obama become a reality. are you factoring that into your calculus?</Msg><Username>doyoulikeneruda</Username><Timestamp>1358374373902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 17:12:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358378080003-51</Id><Topic><Title>More taxes = more spending</Title><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358360788145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:26:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The right has the propensity to see their beliefs as fact. Or is it just deceit? Like, calling certain Gov. spendings they don't approve of (while the majority do), fat?</Msg><Username>stenchengineer</Username><Timestamp>1358378080003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 18:14:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358382932200-52</Id><Title>DO NOT BACK ANY Gun Control....period ! ***(because of 6 NUTS ??).</Title><Msg>ridiculous......</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1358382932200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 19:35:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358387132953-53</Id><Title>Capitol Hill gas-export backers ready new pressure on DOE</Title><Msg>Capitol Hill gas-export backers ready new pressure on DOE By Ben Geman - 01/16/13 02:34 PM ET Lawmakers that favor expanding U.S. natural-gas exports are preparing to increase political pressure on the Obama administration to greenlight industry export plans. Reps. Bill Johnson (R-Ohio) and Tim Ryan (D-Ohio) are gathering colleagues’ signatures for a letter to Energy Secretary Steven Chu that urges quick review of a federally commissioned study that called expanding exports a net economic win for the U.S. The Energy Department (DOE) is taking comment on the study as it weighs 16 applications to export liquefied natural gas (LNG) to nations that do not have a free-trade deal with the U.S. Time is of the essence, the lawmakers say in the letter, slated for delivery next week. It states: The United States is not the only nation with abundant shale gas reserves. However, we do have significant advantages that will take competitors many years to overcome, such as best-in-class technology, gas processing and pipeline infrastructure developed over decades, a financial system that matches capital with promising investment opportunities, well defined mineral ownership, and a mature legal system. Other nations are already at work trying to duplicate the success of America’s shale industry. These advantages won’t last forever. In the wake of the DOE report and the realities of today’s natural gas market, we believe now is the time to expand domestic exportation of LNG. We respectfully urge the Administration to advance without delay through the comment period and toward approval of export permits to non-Free Trade Agreement (FTA) countries. The lawmakers have thus far gathered 39 signatures from a bipartisan, nationwide group of lawmakers, according to an aide. The letter is part of a wider political and lobbying battle over gas exports and the DOE-commissioned report, which was conducted by NERA Economic Consulting. The oil-and-gas industry and other export advocates are pressing for approval, calling expanded exports a way to wring more economic benefit out of the nation’s natural-gas boom. But the study, which predicts some price increases but an overall economic benefit, has drawn pushback from a pair of senior Capitol Hill Democrats: Sen. Ron Wyden (D-Ore.) and Rep. Edward Markey (D-Mass.). They say NERA underestimated the impact of expanded exports on consumers and energy-thirsty manufacturing industries that have benefited from low-cost domestic gas. A few big chemical and manufacturing companies, including Alcoa and Dow Chemical, that are wary of large-scale exports are also attacking the report. But the letter that Johnson and Ryan are circulating say U.S. gas consumers will continue to see a price advantage even if exports go forward. It states: We note that the Department has already indicated that it intends to monitor the market so that “natural gas exports do not subsequently lead to a reduction in the supply of natural gas needed to meet essential domestic needs.” As supplies tighten and prices adjust to sustainable levels, less gas would be exported. Further, the NERA report estimates the total cost to transport gas to an export terminal, liquefy, ship, and then regasify it overseas would range from $6.30 to $8.39. In other words, the difference between the price of gas in the U.S. and internationally would need to be at least that much higher in order to justify its export. That price differential is a significant cushion against domestic prices climbing to a “world price.” thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/277571-capitol-hill-gas-export-backers-ready-new-pressure-on-doe</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358387132953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 20:45:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358395601101-54</Id><Topic><Title>why are exmilitary coworkers act so stupid</Title><Username>demsenate4obama</Username><Timestamp>1358389098360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 21:18:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glancing over your reply message subject.... and your message, I wouldn't talk about anyone else's English teaching skills.</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358395601101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 23:06:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358397554835-55</Id><Title>China Targeting 10 GW of New Solar Capacity In 2013</Title><Msg>China Targeting 10 GW of New Solar Capacity In 2013 By Adam Johnston We are two weeks into the new year and China continues its march towards clean energy dominance. The Asian giant is aiming to have up to 10 gigawatts (GW) of new solar capacity this year. According to PV Magazine, if successful, will more than double its total capacity currently at 7GW. Image Credit: Chinese Flag via Shutterstock Meanwhile the country envisions having a total of 21GW by 2015. Seven gigawatts is pretty impressive for solar capacity for any country, especially China, and how rapidly they have gotten there. In 1999, China only had 16 megawatts (0.016 GW). Ten years ago in 2003 that number sat at 42MW (0.042GW), while in 2008, Chinese solar capacity grew to 140MW(0.14GW). The recent announcement has been apart of a string of positive news within China’s solar industry. Yingli Green Energy also became the largest solar company in the world, beating out Suntech. Yingli shares have also jumped up within the past month from its month low on December 17th at $2.31/share to its most recent high of $3.05/share on January 9th. Share prices at the end of trading on January 15th were $2.90/share. How Far Can China Continue to Move Up the Solar Ladder? There is no doubt China continues to move its way up the renewable energy ladder in solar and wind. If China’s economy continues to rebound, furthering the need for cleaner energy, solar energy capacity targets now targeted for China, could easily be beaten. sDOTtt/1yz8k</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358397554835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 23:39:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>