<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358658090592-1</Id><Topic><Title>Algeria is it turning into another Nigeria?</Title><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1358529510832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 12:18:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Global appetite for oil is such a moving target since economy slowed. The increased sales of gas and diesel vehicles in China and India is just starting. Once the world economy starts to recover oil demand resumes with great strength. It might be a surprise to many when Saudi comes face to face with a major decline in production from one of the elephant size fields. It will happen one day.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1358658090592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:01:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358663928558-2</Id><Title>Northern Gateway oil pipeline: Vancouver hearings overwhelmingly opposed to project</Title><Msg>Northern Gateway oil pipeline: Vancouver hearings overwhelmingly opposed to project Published on Friday January 18, 2013 Petti Fong Western Canada Bureau 9 Comments VANCOUVER—Supporters of the controversial Northern Gateway pipeline project do exist, but in Vancouver at least they are remaining completely silent. During its hearings in Vancouver, the consensus has been unanimous: Of the dozens of speakers appearing before the National Energy Board panel reviewing the proposed Enbridge oil project, not a single person has spoken in support of it. Speaker Marc Eliesen looked as if he was going to break the trend as he told the panel about his credentials. A former chairman of Manitoba Hydro, former CEO of B.C. Hydro and former senior executive in the public and private sectors, Eliesen appeared to be markedly different than the speakers before him in his crisp white shirt and dark business suit. The two speakers before him were a former environmental lawyer and a nurse who spoke about the jeopardy to salmon streams. But Eliesen too spoke against the project. “The public benefit test is not being met and therefore the project is not in the public interest,” said Eliesen. “It’s bogus economics being utilized to justify this pipeline project.” The speakers in Vancouver, the latest stop in the months-long public hearings touring B.C. and Alberta, included medical doctors, public sector executives, politicians, rabbis, teachers and students. Some speakers have been overcome by emotions, breaking into tears during their presentations. The panel will ultimately #$%$ the environmental effects of the proposed project and release its recommendation report by Dec. 31 this year. After that the federal government must decide whether or not the project should be approved. The first speaker last Monday night, W.M. Cakette, was just beginning his comments when drum beats outside from protesters nearly drowned him out. Anticipating the protests, the panel had arranged to have public viewing rooms in a separate building from the hearings. The panel made the same arrangements in Victoria. In Vancouver, the distance between the hotels where the public was allowed to attend and where speakers appeared was more than two kilometres apart. That didn’t stop protesters from showing up at the hearings, including five of them with whistles who burst in on the second day of hearings and were arrested. Panel member Sheila Leggett called the disruption, which shut down the hearing for nearly an hour, a “huge disappointment. “It’s important for us to hear these oral statements. It’s why we’re here. To have the discussion jeopardize other people’s days is very unfortunate,” she said. Leggett, a biologist and former board member with the Natural Resources Conservation Board, is one of three panel members who have been hearing speakers. The other two are Kenneth Batement, an energy lawyer and former senior executive in the energy sector, and Hans Matthews, a professional geologist and former mining executive. Also in the room beside the speakers who are rotated in through groups of three are legal and public affairs representatives of Enbridge, the Calgary-based energy transport and distribution company which employs 6,000 people in North America. The company wants to build the pipeline from Edmonton to a marine terminal on B.C.’s northern coast of Kitimat. Company spokesman Ivan Giesbrecht said he’s not surprised at the deep emotion many of the speakers displayed. “People have become very emotional about this. It speaks to the importance of the project,” said Giesbrecht. As for the lack of supporters of the project at the hearing, Giesbrecht said he remembers a man a few months ago when the panel was in Comox, B.C., who told him he supported the project. The Canadian Federation of Independent Businesses polled its members a year ago about whether the association should support the pipeline. “We got a very split opinion with members with very strong opinions on the issue,” said Kimball Kastelen, policy analyst with the federation. “If our members all line up, we represent their opinion but where we find there is conflict or strongly expressed diverging views, we will not express an opinion.” The business community has done a poor job of showing its support said Philip Hochstein, president of the Independent Contractors and Business Association of B.C., the non-union representatives for construction work. “I’m as guilty as the next one. I represent the construction industry, lots of jobs and service jobs that will continue on after the construction of the pipeline is completed,” said Hochstein. “We should be out there saying it’s a good thing, but I’m not out there making the case and I should be.” A poll from Angus Reid found that of 800 people sampled, nine per cent of British Columbians completely support the project it while 27 per cent support the pipeline but could change their minds based on economic or environmental considerations. One third say they completely oppose the pipeline. thestarDOTcom/news/canada/article/1317268--northern-gateway-oil-pipeline-emotions-erupt-at-vancouver-hearings</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358663928558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:38:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358664447585-3</Id><Title>US sees record numbers of wind farms in 2012, but it's not the only country expanding</Title><Msg>US sees record numbers of wind farms in 2012, but it's not the only country expanding By Dan Seiferton January 18, 2013 04:29 pm The US installed a record number of wind farms in 2012, totaling 13.2 gigawatts of capacity, according to a report from Bloomberg New Energy Finance. The surge in production is attributed to two factors, namely falling costs for wind power and a production tax credit that was due to expire on December 31st. As a result in the surge in production, the US now produces 60 gigawatts of wind energy, which is about six percent of the nation's total energy outout. Though wind energy accounts for a small fraction of the US's total energy production, in states such as Texas, wind energy is as plentiful as energy produced from natural gas. California, Kansas, and Texas comprise the top three states in terms of wind energy production, while Pennsylvania is the only state in the North East in the top ten (number nine). US growth likely won't continue through 2013 While wind farms exploded in 2012, the report notes that the growth likely won't be sustained through 2013, even though the production tax credit was renewed by Congress through the rest of the year. The uncertainty about the tax credit has already put a damper on new wind farm construction, as companies did not plan ahead for the credit to be available in 2013. The US may have had a record year in wind farm expansion, but it's not the only country looking to wind as a new energy source. Just this week, Japan revealed plans to build the world's largest offshore wind farm starting in July, as reported by New Scientist. The project includes construction of 143 turbines on platforms a mere 16 kilometers off the coast Fukushima, where the Daiichi nuclear reactor suffered devastating damage from an earthquake and subsequent tsunami in March 2011. The new wind farm is expected to produce one gigawatt of energy when it is completed in 2020. Fukushima hopes to be completely reliant on renewable energy sources by the year 2040, using a combination of wind and solar energy. Fukushima hopes to completely rely on renewable energy by 2040 Reliance on alternative forms of energy has been a hot button topic for decades, as many have looked to various options to reduce the use of fossil fuels for energy. While we are still a long ways away from fully replacing fossil fuels in our modern society, the expansion of wind farms and solar collection sites does help to lessen the impact that burning fossil fuels has on the earth's environment. thevergeDOTcom/2013/1/18/3891714/us-record-number-wind-farms-2012-japan-worlds-largest-offshore</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358664447585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:47:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358665114034-4</Id><Topic><Title>US FERC chairman urges Texas to increase grid connections to rest of US</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358645208399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:26:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>KCP&amp;L identifies potential power line routes The second in a series of informational meetings between Kansas City Power &amp; Light Co. officials and Nodaway County landowners with regard to construction of a proposed high-voltage power line will take place from 3-7 p.m. Tuesday, Jan. 22, at the American Legion hall in Maryville. By Tony Brown Jan. 17, 2013 6:40 am The second in a series of informational meetings between Kansas City Power &amp; Light Co. officials and Nodaway County landowners with regard to construction of a proposed high-voltage power line will take place from 3-7 p.m. Tuesday, Jan. 22, at the American Legion hall in Maryville. A sort of dress rehearsal for that session was held Wednesday at the Northwest Technical School, where KCP&amp;L staffers filled Nodaway County Commission members and other officials in on how the project is progressing. The initiative, undertaken in partnership with the Omaha Public Power District, will lead to construction of a 170-mile-long, 345-kilovolt line running from southeastern Nebraska to KCP&amp;L's existing Sibley (Mo.) Substation in Jackson County. Plans also call for construction of a new KCP&amp;L facility — the Mullen Creek Substation — in Nodaway County west of Highway 71 and about seven miles south of Maryville. The utility is holding a series of similar meetings this month across the 13 northwest Missouri counties to be affected by the project. These meetings differ from the first round of informational sessions last August in that KCP&amp;L has now filled in its once-blank map with dozens of proposed routes. Over the next six months, KCP&amp;L plans to winnow those alternatives down to three or four options prior to selection of a final route next summer. Construction is to begin in 2015, and power company officials hope to put the new line in service by summer 2017. The purpose of this week's meeting was to prep county officials so they'll be prepared to answer constituents' questions as the process moves forward. The new map shows a half-dozen or so possible routes crossing a wide swath of Nodaway County before narrowing to a single point at the substation, then spreading out again between northern Andrew County and Conception. No formal program is planned for Tuesday's public information session, rather participants will walk through a number of stations featuring maps, GIS computer terminals and information about environmental impacts, real estate, routing and construction. When completed, the transmission line will consist of large H-pole structures standing up to 100 feet high and supporting 1,000-foot spans of high-voltage cable. Landowners over whose property the line passes are to receive one-time cash payments in exchange for granting easements ranging in width from 100 to 160 feet. Partnership officials estimate construction cost at $400 million, and say the effort will create between 50 and 70 construction jobs. The investment is to be recouped from electricity customers throughout the Southwest Power Pool, which embraces utilities in parts of nine states: Arkansas, Kansas, Louisiana, Mississippi, Missouri, Nebraska, New Mexico, Oklahoma and Texas. The Missouri portion of the line — by far the biggest part of the project — will be constructed and owned by Transource Energy, an entity formed last year by Great Plains Energy, KCP&amp;L's holding company, and power giant American Electric Power, which owns a controlling interest in Transource. maryvilledailyforumDOTcom/article/20130117/NEWS/130118963/1003/NEWS</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358665114034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 01:58:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358692391913-5</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Filth and Glenn Beckistan...</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1358472714325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 20:31:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hanes u r a #$%$ POS #$%$ face.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1358692391913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:33:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358695095270-6</Id><Topic><Title>End of the road for the dollar...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358546428808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:00:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I mean by "the end of the dollar" is that it is the end of the dollar for me, and that I now expect it to fall against the £ and €, not that I expect it to fall against goods and services in general. My allocation as of Monday morning will be 75% 5-Year German Bunds (€) at 0.60% and 25% UK pounds at 0.50%. Americans are grossly under-taxed so it would take a truly extreme policy to cause any difficulty for the US tax base. The dollar will probably gain value relative to US goods and services even as it loses value against European currencies as the flood of Chinese imports continues, a flood which will combine with still cheaper Japanese imports from the devaluation of the yen, and the pressure of lower wages from the tens of millions of Mexicans. Higher dollar interest rates to compensate foreigners for a weakening dollar going forward (caused by the US recession I foresee), and the collapse of the stock and energy bubble will be deflationary for US consumers. Higher interest rates will lower US real estate values and reduce lending. I expect oil prices to fall from $110 to around $40 as oil supplies buildup globally and break the OPEC cartel. That will be deflationary as well. At the rate the Federal Reserve is going it would take it about 10 years to reach the point where it actually ran out bank reserves to borrow and had to resort to the printing press. So actual dollar inflation is not relevant, although factors that play on dollar interest rates and exchange rates are. While it disappoints me that Obama has not pushed for more tax increases there will be plenty of time for that after 2014 or after 2016. I don't see how the Republican Party will ever win another Presidential election with the increasing Mexican vote on the scale - that augurs well for higher US taxes going forward.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358695095270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:18:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358696180801-7</Id><Title>Sheeple of odd colors</Title><Msg>In Roman times the upper class reserved one day of the year "Saturnalia" 17-December when masters would provide table service to their slaves. There was much partying, many orgies, and the roman ladies would become quite wild with drink...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358696180801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:36:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358697539742-8</Id><Topic><Title>Algeria is it turning into another Nigeria?</Title><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1358529510832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 12:18:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are wrong about oil prices and will lose a lot of money. China's purchases of oil are limited by how many exports they can sell and at what price. They are their own worst enemy on the prices. Those are what are know as terms of trade. It is not safe to assume them to be a constant, which is where the erroneous projections of Chinese demand for oil and other items comes from.... Tight oil has changed the equation on oil supply There are several Saudi Arabia's worth in the Eastern European and Russian shales thanks to the new technologies. This always happens with high prices and is why commodities never have been able to sustain high prices before... Projections about Saudi Arabia are all guess work too... They no doubt are benefiting from improvements in oil extraction technology and obviously can produce more than they are now</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358697539742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:58:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358699608201-9</Id><Title>The Tale of 8 Energy Price bubbles</Title><Msg>Energy Price Bubbles in the past - 200%+ increase in price 1. peak 1812. Continental Europe. Depression ensued till about 1819. 2. peak February, 1873. Europe and UK. Global depression by October 1873. 3. peak May, 1920. US and Europe. Global depression by fall 1920. 4. peak January, 1974. Global. Global depression within weeks. 5. peak July, 1980. Global. Global Depression within months. 6. peak September, 1980. Global. Global recession within months. 7. peak July, 2008. Global. Global depression till 2009. 8. peak March, 2012. Global... Recession across Southern Europe, UK, and global weakness building.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358699608201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:33:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358699933288-10</Id><Topic><Title>The Tale of 8 Energy Price bubbles</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358699608201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:33:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*6. September 2000...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358699933288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:38:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358705427375-11</Id><Title>Truck Stops Are Gearing Up For Natural Gas Fueling</Title><Msg>Cummins and Westport are developing a new engine for 18 Wheelers. Believe Exxon knew this was coming quite sometime ago, they will benefit greatly.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1358705427375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358712929370-12</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Filth and Glenn Beckistan...</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1358472714325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 20:31:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahleee makes a poor excuse of a turd. His mother tried to donate him to science at birth.</Msg><Username>ihategooks</Username><Timestamp>1358712929370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:15:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358717732721-13</Id><Title>First Turbines In Place For Tasmanian Wind Farm</Title><Msg>First Turbines In Place For Tasmanian Wind Farm by Energy Matters SUNDAY 20 JANUARY, 2013 Construction of Musselroe Wind Farm in Tasmania is well under way, with last week seeing the final international shipment of components for turbines reaching the Apple Isle's shores and the first fully complete wind turbine and tower constructed on site. All components were lifted into place to "top out" the 80-metre high turbine tower and it appears a couple of other towers have also had turbines set in place since. The task of installing 80 tonnes of nacelle was no mean feat. According to Project Director Andrew Hickman, highly specialised equipment was used. "Lifting of the top sections, nacelles and blades requires a unique type of crane. The 1200 tonne crane we are using is the largest model telescopic crawler crane in the world." Turbine placement hasn't been the only challenge - parts of the 48 kilometre transmission line to Derby needed to traverse some inaccessible terrain. Mr Hickman said the most efficient and cost-effective way to string the line through those sections is by helicopter. Situated at Cape Portland in north-east Tasmania - approximately 100 kilometres north-east of Launceston - the $395 million, 168 megawatt Hydro Tasmania facility is to be completed and operational by 1 July 2013. Tasmania’s Energy Minister Bryan Green said the first turbines will be generating electricity and exporting power to the mains grid in March. "Once it’s fully operational in the middle of this year, the wind farm will meet the electricity needs of up to 50 000 homes, equivalent to the residential power needs of the people of Burnie and Devonport," he said. Hydro Tasmania also operate an advanced hybrid power system on King Island that utilizes wind, solar, diesel and innovative energy enabling technologies. Tasmania enjoys world-class wind energy resources as it lies directly in the path of the roaring 40s, the prevailing westerly winds that circle the Earth’s high southern latitudes. energymattersDOTcomDOTau/indexDOTphp?main_page=news_article&amp;article_id=3558</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358717732721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:35:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358722656335-14</Id><Title>Big bet on Wyoming wind: Phil Anschutz's latest $9 billion idea</Title><Msg>Big bet on Wyoming wind: Phil Anschutz's latest $9 billion idea</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358722656335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:57:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358722964803-15</Id><Topic><Title>Big bet on Wyoming wind: Phil Anschutz's latest $9 billion idea</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358722656335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:57:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>windactionDOTorg/news/37071</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358722964803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:02:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358724716399-16</Id><Topic><Title>Truck Stops Are Gearing Up For Natural Gas Fueling</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1358705427375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nat gas as a transportation fuel is just starting and will take some time to grow, but one can expect things like lng powered ships, and some nat gas/lng powered heavy equipment. Air pollution concerns in some major ports like China, Hong Kong are likely going to prefer lng and nat gas powered ships, perhaps they will give some sort of incentive. bottom line is nat gas has probably seen its bottom and while it might not rise fast it probably will rise steadily. xom will benefit regardless.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1358724716399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:31:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358725280159-17</Id><Topic><Title>Algeria is it turning into another Nigeria?</Title><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1358529510832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 12:18:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While advances in extraction technology are important its not likely frac and horizontal well technology will do for oil what it did for nat gas. How much more oil and at what price and what decline rate new technology for shales remain to be determined. And while one must agree new technology in enhanced oil recovery will help the Saudi, they still face a decline in reserves. time will tell. If the world can continue to grow and abundant supply of oil its going to help the world economies and economic recovery. From my point of view there are fewer and fewer big oil fields to be found and enhanced recovery will only do so much. expect higher and higher oil prices in the future. jmho</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1358725280159</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:41:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358725535705-18</Id><Topic><Title>Truck Stops Are Gearing Up For Natural Gas Fueling</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1358705427375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Air pollution concerns in some major ports like China With little or no pollution this should be a winner. Cummins says this new engine will be 25% more efficient.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1358725535705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:45:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358726251287-19</Id><Topic><Title>The Tale of 8 Energy Price bubbles</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358699608201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:33:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems like the housing bubble was the time bomb, it took the $150 oil prices to help light the fuse.</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358726251287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:57:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358730358576-20</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Filth and Glenn Beckistan...</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1358472714325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 20:31:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better yet, do away with those housing units. the public owes them nothing</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1358730358576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:05:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358730466176-21</Id><Topic><Title>US FERC chairman urges Texas to increase grid connections to rest of US</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358645208399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:26:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perhaps Texas plans to succeed as per their original entry agreement?</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1358730466176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:07:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358730520035-22</Id><Topic><Title>Enbridge Losing Bakken Oil Business to Railroads, Refiner Says</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358623687125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:28:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rails are economical</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1358730520035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:08:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358730577913-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama officials delay ‘fracking’ rules</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358555325107</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 19:28:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's a good thing, we have NG glut anyways. price is low</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1358730577913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:09:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358730754256-24</Id><Title>Connie Hedegaard: Clean Energy Revolution Is Critical, Do-Able, &amp; Good For Jobs &amp; The Economy (VIDEOS)</Title><Msg>Connie Hedegaard: Clean Energy Revolution Is Critical, Do-Able, &amp; Good For Jobs &amp; The Economy (VIDEOS) January 20, 2013 Zachary Shahan Connie Hedegaard, the European Commissioner for Climate Action in the European Commission since February 2010, gave a great keynote speech at the World Future Energy Summit (part of Abu Dhabi Sustainability Week) a few days ago. Below are two videos of her speech and a text summary of the key points ---------------- -------------- ------------- ------------ ------------ Exclusive Interview: Connie Hedegaard On EU 2020 Renewable Energy Target &amp; Climate Change Messaging (VIDEO) January 20, 2013 Zachary Shahan In addition to the videos I recorded of Connie Hedegaard’s keynote speech at the start of the World Future Energy Summit (part of Abu Dhabi Sustainability Week, hosted by Masdar), I also got to sit down with her after her speech, ask her a few questions, and videotape it all. My initial question (not included in the video) was about the EU’s 2020 CO2 emissions reduction target — in particular, whether or not the push for an increase in the target from 20% to 30% might soon meet success; if it seemed that it might be possible to soon convince some of the blocking countries (most notably Poland) to get on the bandwagon. As mentioned in the</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358730754256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:12:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358738254708-25</Id><Topic><Title>Truck Stops Are Gearing Up For Natural Gas Fueling</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1358705427375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flying J/Loves truck stops are installing nat gas units right now. Within 90 days they will have units in coast to coast on main Interstates. This is the fuel of the future.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1358738254708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:17:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358739853844-26</Id><Topic><Title>Truck Stops Are Gearing Up For Natural Gas Fueling</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1358705427375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Catterpillar says its going to make large equipment nat gas engines as avaiable option, think they have some joint agreement with westport. Think for some large open pit machines like in oil sands and for electricity generators there could be a market.</Msg><Username>manylumen</Username><Timestamp>1358739853844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:44:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358740811234-27</Id><Title>3000 babies aborted daily in the US</Title><Msg>Is it safe to assume the majority of the aborting physicians are of the same ethnicity as Clinton Secretary of State Madeline Albright. Albright informed a stunned Leslie Stahl in a 60 Minutes interview that the Iraqi sanctions that had resulted in over a half a million dead Iraqi children were worth it. The LA Times notes that over a million civilians are dead as a result the US invasion in Iraq. Obama, Feinstein and Boxer can't drone to death enough Afghan and Pakistani children. With cops out gunned and way overmatched in most US cities the leftists are hellbent on arming Mexican cartels via Fast and Furious and facilitating the Mexican cartel hench men's re entery into the United States by insisting on wide open US Borders.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1358740811234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:00:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358744313261-28</Id><Topic><Title>Truck Stops Are Gearing Up For Natural Gas Fueling</Title><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1358705427375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>think they have some joint agreement with westport From what I've heard, Cummins and Westport have not merged but have an agreement on these engines. Cummins will take the lead. I've recently added to my CMI, check it out with your Broker. I'm also a strong supporter of CAT, they too will do fine with nat gas engines.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1358744313261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:58:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>