<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373434847178-1</Id><Topic><Title>Attention longtime XOM posters.....</Title><Username>reality_gerald</Username><Timestamp>1373407703451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 18:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey troll B I T E M E</Msg><Username>jok_sonu</Username><Timestamp>1373434847178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 01:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373450422680-2</Id><Topic><Title>52 week high approaching</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373416309738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 20:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better off accumulating AA @ $8,, new cars built with aluminum are 40% lighter than steel,, 10% better on gas,, and now VW offers a car with 2.6 gas tank +120v plug with 620 range===========80% drop in oil needs. all of these oil companies are about 80% over priced for the new future.</Msg><Username>tagthatstock</Username><Timestamp>1373450422680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 06:00:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373451676457-3</Id><Title>VW car with 2.6 gal gas tank +120v plug with 620 range===========80% drop in oil need</Title><Msg>its like when bush signed into law that all govt lights had to be converted to LED by 2014==88% savings (ps--funny an oil guy did that haha)</Msg><Username>tagthatstock</Username><Timestamp>1373451676457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 06:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373458864154-4</Id><Topic><Title>Yankeedom USA</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369925701757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 10:55:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold United Kingdom t-bills. sold £ for € at 1.1628 €/£. War on Fossil Fuels Allocations (%): German Real Estate {urban upper/middle class, large city}: 78.5% German t-bills : 21.5%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373458864154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 08:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373460634072-5</Id><Title>House rejecting most amendments to energy and water bill</Title><Msg>House rejecting most amendments to energy and water bill By Pete Kasperowicz - 07/09/13 11:10 PM ET The House late Tuesday accepted just two amendments that would tweak an energy and water spending bill for 2014, but rejected several others, most of which came from Democrats looking to boost funding in various areas of the bill. In a voice vote, the House accepted a bipartisan amendment from Rep. Adam Schiff (D-Calif.) that would boost funding for the Advanced Research Projects Agency-Energy (ARPA-E) program, which helps fund advanced energy projects. Schiff's language would increase ARPA-E funding by $20 million, and would take that funding by reducing Department of Energy (DOE) administration funds by the same amount. In another voice vote, the House accepted language from Rep. Tom Reed (R-N.Y.) to increase the non-defense environmental cleanup fund in the bill by $19 million, paid for by cutting the administrative budget. Passage of those amendments meant many other related amendments to boost ARPA-E funding, or increase funding for science or renewable energy programs, were destined to be rejected. The House also rejected three GOP amendments aimed at cutting speeding beyond the cuts already in the bill. Rep. Tom McClintock (R-Calif.) proposed eliminating the entire renewable energy development program at DOE in order to save $1.5 billion, but his language was turned away in a 115-300 vote — 115 Republicans supported it, more than the 109 Republicans who opposed it. Another, from Rep. Paul Broun (R-Ga.), would have cut $4.7 million from the renewable energy program and moved it to the deficit reduction account, to reduce a House-approved increase in that account. The House killed this in a 158-256 vote. Broun had another proposal to cut $9.5 million in DOE salaries, and this was defeated by voice. Other amendments that either failed in a voice vote or were disposed of in other ways were from:</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373460634072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 08:50:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373461327351-6</Id><Title>OPEC Sees U.S. Shale Boom Eroding Demand for 2014 Crude VIDEO</Title><Msg>OPEC Sees U.S. Shale Boom Eroding Demand for 2014 Crude VIDEO By Grant Smith - Jul 10, 2013 4:45 AM MT The Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries forecast the world will need less of its crude next year, even as global oil demand growth rebounds to its strongest pace since 2010, amid competing supply sources. Amrita Sen Sees Crude in $90-$100 Range Long Term VIDEO 3:37 Demand for OPEC’s crude will slip by 300,000 barrels a day next year to 29.6 million a day next year, or about 2.6 percent less than the 12-member group is pumping now, the organization said in its first set of forecasts for 2014. The need for OPEC’s crude will diminish even as global oil demand growth recovers to 1 million barrels a day in 2014, from 800,000 a day this year, amid rising output in the U.S. (DOETCRUD) and Canada. “The strong growth trend seen in 2013 is expected to continue in 2014” for production from outside OPEC, the organization’s Vienna-based secretariat said in its monthly market report today. Dependence on OPEC’s crude is slipping as the U.S. and Canada unlock unconventional oil supplies from deep underground shale deposits with new drilling techniques. Brent crude futures have slipped 2.7 percent this year, trading at about $108 a barrel on the London-based ICE Futures Europe exchange today, amid signs of slowing growth in China and uneven recovery in the U.S., the world’s biggest oil consumers. World oil consumption will advance by 1 million barrels a day, or 1.2 percent to 90.7 million next year as emerging nations expand and developed economies continue to recover, the organization said. Demand estimates for 2013 were kept mostly unchanged, with an anticipated growth rate of about 800,000 barrels a day, or 0.9 percent, to 89.6 million. U.S. Growth “Higher growth in the U.S. and a recovery in the euro zone are the main drivers behind the forecast,” OPEC said. “Emerging economies continue to expand at levels below the high rates seen in past years.” Su</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373461327351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 09:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373463943213-7</Id><Topic><Title>Yankeedom USA</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369925701757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 10:55:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bond purchase: 15-Year German government bonds at 2.137% ytm War on Fossil Fuels Allocations (%): German Real Estate {urban upper/middle class, large city}: 78.5% 15-Year German government bonds: 12.5% German t-bills : 9.0%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373463943213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 09:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373464506678-8</Id><Title>Getting Ready to Explode to Upside!</Title><Msg>CCUR, currently $7.89, has 8.754mm s/o, a market cap of $69.07mm, cash of $22.37mm, no debt, and an enterprise value of $46.7mm. CCUR's enterprise value is only 0.74X revenues of $63.23mm, 6.55X operating cash flow of $7.13mm, and 8.34X free cash flow of $5.6mm. CCUR's EPS was up 175% last quarter and it just raised its dividend by 100% to $0.48 per share for a yield of 6.1%. CCUR leads the video on demand (VOD) delivery business with over 2.4mm VOD streams shipped globally and 4 of America's 6 largest cable TV operators as clients. The #2 VOD technology vendor SEAC is currently trading for $11.50 and has an enterprise value of $262.4mm or 1.68X revenues of $156.11mm, 15.05X operating cash flow of $17.43mm, and 19.32X free cash flow of $13.58mm. An enterprise value of 1.68X revenues would value CCUR at $14.69. An enterprise value of 15.05X operating cash flow will value CCUR at $14.81. An enterprise value of 19.32X free cash flow will value CCUR at $14.91. In addition, CCUR provides the #1 Big Data Analytics software solution for cable TV operators. CCUR tracks the customer behavior of 35 million cable TV subscribers across linear TV, VOD, and nDVR and has already processed 15 billion media transactions. Big Data Analytics is the #1 hottest industry on Wall Street. DATA recently had its IPO at $31 and hit a new 52-week high Monday of $63 for a gain of 103%. DATA's enterprise value is currently 25X revenues vs. CCUR's enterprise value of only 0.74X revenues! CCUR's business is booming big time as cable TV service providers upgrade their systems to provide new Network DVR, start-over, and look-back services. CCUR is also powering multi-screen video delivery to tablets, smartphones, and other IP connected devices for major cable TV operators like TWC! Plus, CCUR provides content delivery network (CDN) video solutions and just signed a major CDN contract with Virgin Media, the #1 pay-TV operator in the UK!</Msg><Username>jowslir632</Username><Timestamp>1373464506678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373466808902-9</Id><Topic><Title>Yankeedom USA</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369925701757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 10:55:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold German 15-years at 2.133% ytm, +0.05%...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373466808902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 10:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373469611498-10</Id><Title>(GLBH) is the next big gainer</Title><Msg>Have you checked out the chart on (GLBH). It looks prime to make a huge run to atleast double its current price.</Msg><Username>wliam681</Username><Timestamp>1373469611498</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:20:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373469817708-11</Id><Topic><Title>(GLBH) is the next big gainer</Title><Username>wliam681</Username><Timestamp>1373469611498</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am buying this now</Msg><Username>lmorin217</Username><Timestamp>1373469817708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:23:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373470596697-12</Id><Topic><Title>stock splits are good</Title><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1369765772412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah RB, I understand all that. But if you look at the performance of stocks that split as opposed to those that don''t, the perfomance of the stocks that split is better. Why? I don't know why. May be an emotional thing. Paul</Msg><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1373470596697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373470687795-13</Id><Topic><Title>Be careful..........bluecheese is tainted and dangerous to your health</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373397655392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 15:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tainted by salmonella posioning of the brain.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373470687795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373470749660-14</Id><Topic><Title>stock splits are good</Title><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1369765772412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how can stock split not be a great thing? yes, so stock price &amp; divvvy halves. but generally in the case of xom, stock prices rise going forward, &amp; you have 2x as much. the only way a split is not a positive, is if the stock value never rises. which XOM historically does. am i missing something here? please enlighten me.</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1373470749660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:39:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373472761135-15</Id><Title>All signs point to a huge run in (GLBH)</Title><Msg>Hearing a rumor that (GLBH) is about to get pumped</Msg><Username>blakewolfe603</Username><Timestamp>1373472761135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 12:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373474666824-16</Id><Topic><Title>stock splits are good</Title><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1369765772412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gee, I agree with you 100%. Paul</Msg><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1373474666824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 12:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373478656449-17</Id><Title>Texas regulators begin aerial surveys of oil and gas facilities</Title><Msg>Texas regulators begin aerial surveys of oil and gas facilities July 10, 2013 at 10:42 am by Jeannie Kever Several weeks into an assessment of air quality at oil and gas production facilities in South and West Texas, officials with the Texas Commission on Environmental Quality say it’s too soon to say whether the survey will lead to action against companies working there. No citations will be issued based on the fly-over monitoring, said Keith Sheedy, technical advisor in the commission’s office of air. But the monitoring, which is scheduled to continue through mid-August, could prompt the commission to send field inspectors to production facilities for follow-up, he said. Producers, meanwhile, said they are ready for the heightened scrutiny. “It’s the world we live in today,” said Alex Mills, president of the Texas Alliance of Energy Producers. “It’s a changing world. With the federal regulatory arena we’ve been in since 2009, it’s created a lot more regulations, more paperwork, more compliance. People in the oil and gas business in Texas have to be on their toes.” The monitoring will cover 22 counties and will use a helicopter equipped with an infrared camera to take video images of volatile organic compounds and other hydrocarbons. Volatile organic compounds can combine with nitrogen oxides to form ozone. Eagle Ford: Texas county combats rise in oil field waste dumping The camera doesn’t quantify how much of the compounds are present, Sheedy said, but simply alerts the commission staff to their presence. Using the helicopter allows the monitoring to covering more ground. When the monitoring is completed, he said the agency will began to assess which companies are working in areas where emissions were reported and send inspectors for follow-up. The targeted counties include Andrews, Atascosa, Bee, Crockett, De Witt, Dimmit, Ector, Gaines, Howard, Irion, Karnes, La Salle, Live Oak, Martin, McMullen, Midland, Reagan, Reeves, Upton, Ward, Webb and Winkler.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373478656449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 13:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373479422034-18</Id><Title>US, China unveil joint climate initiatives</Title><Msg>US, China unveil joint climate initiatives By Ben Geman - 07/10/13 12:29 PM ET China and the U.S., the world’s top greenhouse gas emitters, on Wednesday pledged to deepen bilateral cooperation with efforts to curb carbon emissions from heavy-duty vehicles and advance carbon storage technology. The plan also calls for expanded cooperation on energy efficiency, greenhouse gas data collection and deployment of “smart grid” technologies for electricity. The plans were laid out at a high-level meeting on climate Wednesday that drew an array of Cabinet-level and White House officials, signaling the Obama administration’s elevation of climate in recent months. The secretaries of State, Energy, Treasury, Transportation and Commerce all attended the session at the U.S.-China Strategic and Economic Dialogue, according to Todd Stern, State’s special climate envoy who briefed reporters Wednesday. Other attendees included Gina McCarthy, who is EPA’s top air quality official and the White House nominee to run the agency, as well as U.S. Trade Representative Michael Froman, U.S. Export-Import Bank President Fred Hochberg, and Deputy National Security Advisor Caroline Atkinson, said Stern, who also noted high-level Chinese participation. A joint “working group,” which was announced in April, presented a plan to U.S. and Chinese officials gathered in Washington, D.C., this week for the high-level U.S.-China Strategic and Economic Dialogue. The working group will develop “implementation plans” on the subjects by October, the State Department said in a summary of the initiative. The five “action initiatives” will expand on various existing, voluntary bilateral green energy and climate cooperation agreements between the two nations. The stepped-up bilateral collaboration does not create any binding requirements or emissions targets. It’s the latest phase of efforts to work with China to spur wider use of technologies to curb emissions of carbon and other</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373479422034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 14:03:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373480299093-19</Id><Topic><Title>Be careful..........bluecheese is tainted and dangerous to your health</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373397655392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 15:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bluecheese is the copy 'n paste king of the world...........what junk !</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373480299093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 14:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373480715580-20</Id><Title>Call the savings plan</Title><Msg>and buy your stock back. 2 trades a month</Msg><Username>everyday092155</Username><Timestamp>1373480715580</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 14:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373500269766-21</Id><Title>Rail chief blames employee in Quebec train crash</Title><Msg>Rail chief blames employee in Quebec train crash Posted on July 10, 2013 at 1:48 pm by Associated Press LAC-MEGANTIC, Quebec (AP) — The head of a railway company whose train crashed into a Quebec town, killing at least 15 people, blamed the accident on an employee who he said had failed to properly set the brakes. Edward Burkhardt, president and CEO of the railway’s parent company, Rail World Inc., made his comments Wednesday during his first visit to the town where some 60 people remain missing following Saturday’s fiery crash. “It was questionable whether hand brakes were put in place at this time,” Burkhardt said. “I don’t think any employees removed brakes. They failed to set the brakes.” He said a train engineer has been suspended without pay. “I think he did something wrong. It’s hard to explain why someone didn’t do something. We think he applied some hand brakes but the question is did he apply enough of them,” Burkhardt explained. “He said he applied 11 hand brakes we think that’s not true. Initially we believed him but now we don’t.” Investigation: Quebec oil train derailment sparks criminal probe Burkhardt, who arrived with a police escort and was heckled by angry residents, said that he had stayed in Chicago to deal with the crisis in his office, where he was better able to communicate with insurers and officials in different places during what he described as 20-hour work days. The railway boss promised an energetic response to the humanitarian crisis. At a press conference, shortly before Burkhardt was due to arrive in Lac-Megantic, Quebec Premier Pauline Marois faulted the company’s response in the wake of the disaster. “We have realized there are serious gaps from the railway company from not having been there and not communicating with the public,” Marois said. She also announced a $60-million fund to help victims in Lac-Megantic and to rebuild the town. Quebec police inspector Michel Forget said they were pursuing</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373500269766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 19:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373504592846-22</Id><Topic><Title>stock splits are good</Title><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1369765772412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dividend is half what it was unless raised.Pay-off is if XOM is in an uptrend you will have twice as many shares that will appreciate over time.</Msg><Username>jazz9650</Username><Timestamp>1373504592846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 21:03:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373505301239-23</Id><Title>Bernanke won't stop until oil $200/bbl</Title><Msg>With Lew in Treasury, Geithner's 'legacy' will be extended as the Fed prints the deficit forever. Ben is XOM's Best. Friend. Ever!</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1373505301239</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 21:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373514142410-24</Id><Title>$30B energy, water spending bill passes House, 227-198</Title><Msg>$30B energy, water spending bill passes House, 227-198 By Pete Kasperowicz - 07/10/13 10:32 PM ET The House late Wednesday approved the third of 12 annual spending bills for 2014, passing the Department of Energy (DOE) and water projects spending bill in a 227-198 vote. Democrats have argued throughout the week that the $30.4 billion spending bill cuts too deeply into renewable energy and science research. Those complaints led all but eight Democrats to oppose the bill in the final vote. President Obama has also threatened to veto the bill because of these cuts, and Senate consideration of a bill that spends more means the House version is not likely to survive the upper chamber. Still, House passage allows Republicans to set down a marker on their priorities if and when a final 2014 spending agreement is reached. Republicans admitted that the legislation focuses on what they see as the nation's top priorities — maintaining the U.S. nuclear stockpile, and maintaining U.S. waterways. But even national security-related funding is cut by nearly $400 million compared to 2013 levels. Non-security funding is cut even more, by $2.5 billion. That includes a $100 million cut to civil works programs in the Army Corps of Engineers, another $100 million cut to the Department of the Interior and the Bureau of Reclamation, and a $2.1 billion cut to the Department of Energy. Democrats took several shots during the week at restoring that funding, but they were rejected by the Republican majority. In particular, Democrats sought to restore funding to the Advanced Research Projects Agency-Energy (ARPA-E) program, which was gutted by an 81 percent cut to just $50 million in 2014. The House did agree to one amendment from Rep. Adam Schiff (D-Calif.) to restore $20 million to ARPA-E, but other proposals failed. Republicans also took a few shots at reducing spending further than the 9 percent cut already in the bill. One of these was from Rep. Tom McClintock (R-Calif.) to sa</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373514142410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 23:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>