<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367062203676-1</Id><Title>xom</Title><Msg>xom has fallen below s&amp;p and the dow i think its time to sell this stock is dead in the water!!</Msg><Username>hd7227</Username><Timestamp>1367062203676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 07:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367062331557-2</Id><Topic><Title>Man, Cramer really HATES Exxon !!!!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1366991686449</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>look at exxon chart this stock is doing nothing for the past 5-10 years</Msg><Username>hd7227</Username><Timestamp>1367062331557</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 07:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367065621168-3</Id><Topic><Title>xom</Title><Username>hd7227</Username><Timestamp>1367062203676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 07:30:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XOM has a long history that tells you to buy on the drops and sell the RIPs.... We are closer to the bottom then then the top right now. I think we get a chance to buy at $85 this quarter ..... And by year end we can sell it closer to $95.... Been doing it since 1970. Selling and leaving now is statically a risky move IMO. Where would you go? AAPL ?</Msg><Username>ah673000</Username><Timestamp>1367065621168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 08:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367071367162-4</Id><Title>NC Renewable Energy Standard Scores Surprise Win</Title><Msg>To the shock and horror of its backers, a bill attempting to gut North Carolina’s renewable energy standard fails in committee. Earthtechling, Pete Danko: April 26, 2013 Maybe state renewable portfolio standards aren’t quite so fragile after all. On Wednesday in North Carolina, an RPS thought to be among the most vulnerable withstood attack. A broad assault on these laws, which operate uniquely but in general terms require utilities to source a growing amount of renewable energy, is being waged by thoughtful free market devotees or ruthless corporate interests, one or the other. (You can decide which; just know that the American Legislative Exchange Council has been right in the middle of it all in most states, as it was in North Carolina, along with the Heartland Institute, Grover Norquist, the John Locke Foundation and others, all with fossil fuel backing, according to the Center for Media and Democracy’s PR Watch.) Remarkably, the bill to gut the RPS failed even to get out of the committee chaired by its sponsor. With six Republicans voting against it, the tally in the Committee on Public Utilities and Energy was a resounding 18-13 against moving the bill forward. The anti-RPS folks were aghast. The News &amp; Observer quoted Dallas Woodhouse, North Carolina director for the anti-tax, anti-government Americans for Prosperity, thusly: “This was a horrible vote by Republicans, and they need to be held accountable. And that’s all I’m going to say.” Renewable energy advocates in the Tar Heel State had a slightly different take. “The vote’s outcome and the fact that it occurred in the Committee chaired by the bill’s own sponsor, Chairman Mike Hager, not only helps to secure a path forward for continued economic development in the renewable energy sector, it also showed the strength of the voices from across the state that spoke out against the greentechmediaDOTcom/articles/read/nc-renewable-energy-standard-scores-surprise-win</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1367071367162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 10:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>