<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366171270576-1</Id><Topic><Title>Offshore Ireland</Title><Username>whynagg</Username><Timestamp>1366050454896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:27:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surf's up for sure offshore at Dunquin, but rig due anytime</Msg><Username>whynagg</Username><Timestamp>1366171270576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 00:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366171525102-2</Id><Title>Offshore Ireland</Title><Msg>Four or five heavy icean service vessels coming into place</Msg><Username>whynagg</Username><Timestamp>1366171525102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 00:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366171663859-3</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels make liberals feel good</Title><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366125624214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don’t like the docile sheep we’ve made? They are very white and well behaved. Maybe you didn’t fit in, or were rejected by the others. That’s so sad. But then I brought an American over in the oppose direction so that more than makes up for the loss. Of course such a bright, golden haired, intelligent angel could never be a sheep. No, no, no, I would have a rebel on my hands if I entertained anything like that. So she has become a Master German, and keeps sheep for herself. She has everything her way which is for the best. I find no objections in the 19th century German Romantic literature to such an arrangement, or for that matter on the keeping and training of sheep, or to Green politics either. Now Marxism, which has been driven out and expunged by good Germans, strongly objects to such arrangements, but that is a compliment as I see it. You would do well not to mix up your sheep and Masters when commenting on abilities. Keep in mind who is driving the agenda you obviously despise. The bio-fuels assault has not been launched yet, and what you are commenting on is the work of skirmishers not the Field Marshal directing his battalions in a full attack. It takes planning and preparation for assaults.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366171663859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 00:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366174179594-4</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels make liberals feel good</Title><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366125624214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hate to bust your bubble nbut unless you think of the "W" as a "hair brain liberal" (that requires a brain) you might check his record on corn ethanol--of course it was nothing but billions tax wasted to ADM and Koch but hey if gop does it--its not on fox--and idiots like you will never know</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1366174179594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 00:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366174328429-5</Id><Topic><Title>Buy backs by Xom hurt those looking for dividend s</Title><Username>smkpit</Username><Timestamp>1366144365202</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:32:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but help the EPS so share price goes up want big divvy--quit the complaints--sell buy elsewhere get a box of diapers with your 1st big divvy</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1366174328429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 00:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366182840851-6</Id><Topic><Title>Warning to right-wing militia types.</Title><Username>jerrym30711</Username><Timestamp>1366137237722</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:33:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more like commie lefties.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1366182840851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 03:14:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366204649192-7</Id><Title>Al Gore warns of climate devastation in Dublin visit VIDEO</Title><Msg>Al Gore warns of climate devastation in Dublin visit VIDEO Louise Hogan– 17 April 2013 FORMER US Vice-President Al Gore didn't mince his words as he painted a vivid portrait of the worldwide devastation being caused by the invisible, tasteless and odourless greenhouse gases. Climate change is causing devastation like that depicted in the Bible's book of 'Revelations', he told delegates, including Tanaiste Eamon Gilmore, at the Hunger, Nutrition, Climate Justice international conference at Dublin Castle. "We have to win the conversation about climate change – when you hear denial speak up," he said. "We cannot continue sleep walking towards the edge of history's cliff," he added. Former President Mary Robinson, whose foundation co-hosted the event, said they must ensure those at the 'grassroots' – the fishing and farming organisations on the ground – are listened to as they attempt to work together to tackle the problem. independentDOTie/irish-news/al-gore-warns-of-climate-devastation-in-dublin-visit-29201711.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366204649192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366205258250-8</Id><Topic><Title>Buy backs by Xom hurt those looking for dividend s</Title><Username>smkpit</Username><Timestamp>1366144365202</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:32:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lots of quality dividend stocks out there besides XOM.</Msg><Username>rogernusbaum</Username><Timestamp>1366205258250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:27:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366205435791-9</Id><Title>California Wind Power Blows Away Production Record</Title><Msg>California Wind Power Blows Away Production Record New all-time high for wind energy set Sunday April 08, 2013 05:25 PM Eastern Daylight Time FOLSOM, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Wind power is gaining speed. The California Independent System Operator Corporation (ISO) reports a new record was set when turbines spinning within the ISO power grid combined to produce a new record of 4,196 megawatts (MW) at 6:44 p.m. on Sunday. The ISO is the main operator for the state’s high voltage network, serving about 80 percent of the Golden State. “With these impressive wind production levels, California is well positioned to meet the 33 percent by 2020 green power goal” . On Friday, total wind levels surpassed the 4,000 MW milestone when 4,095 MW helped to power California. Previously, the all-time record peak output for wind energy was 3,944 MW on March 3, 2013. “With these impressive wind production levels, California is well positioned to meet the 33 percent by 2020 green power goal,” said ISO President and CEO Steve Berberich. “Our control center operators are tracking a steady increase in renewable energy and we are leveraging the latest forecasting technology as well as complementary flexible resources to capture and optimize this carbon-free power supply.” There is a total of 5,899 megawatts of wind plant capacity installed within the ISO grid. Not all of the wind power was available yesterday as a result of routine generation and transmission outages. California is now the second largest producer of wind power next to Texas. The independent system operator ERCOT, which serves about 80 percent of the Lone Star State, reports 10,407 MW of wind generation installed and achieved a record peak of 9,481 MW on February 9, 2013. businesswireDOTcom/news/home/20130408006725/en/California-Wind-Power-Blows-Production-Record</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366205435791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366206852137-10</Id><Title>Quantum batteries...</Title><Msg>Quantum batteries can store and release energy on demand almost perfectly, provided they are entangled. The efficiency of a system designed using the rules of quantum mechanics is entirely different than one based on the rules classical mechanics. The efficiency of a entangled battery system can be made arbitrarily close to the thermodynamic limit, as per the laws of physics. So there is no reason why a battery cannot be designed that is far superior to current technology. Keep in mind the physics to build nuclear weapons was around before the devices. The scientists working on America's Manhattan Project were not guessing. They knew exactly what they were doing. .....</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366206852137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:54:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366207756872-11</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore warns of climate devastation in Dublin visit VIDEO</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366204649192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:17:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Al Gore must have some serious mental issues. He now is a fully delusional limousine liberal burning all kinds of fossil fuels to tell us not to. Where are all his cat 5 hurricanes? Why is there still snow still on Mt Kilimanjaro? He is more interested in intimidating "deniers" and scaring the paranoid than educating.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366207756872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366208178853-12</Id><Topic><Title>Quantum batteries...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366206852137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:54:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this more pie in the sky? What are they waiting for. Don't tell me...government funding. Of course. We fund and develop. The Chinese then steel it and manufacture it dumping pollutants everywhere then sell it back to us.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366208178853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366208602563-13</Id><Topic><Title>California Wind Power Blows Away Production Record</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366205435791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's build some more dams too.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366208602563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:23:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366208739479-14</Id><Topic><Title>California Wind Power Blows Away Production Record</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366205435791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Total System Power for 2011: Changes from 2010 In 2011, Total System Power for California was marginally higher by half of a percent from 2010. The two primary reasons are the ongoing recession and continued mild temperatures. The effects of the recession resulted in a peak demand that was 5 percent less than the forecast. As for temperatures, they were lower than normal during the spring, near normal temperatures during the summer, and above normal temperatures during both the fall and winter.1 By design, California's electric generation system delivers electricity quickly to match peak air conditioning load conditions in the summer... energyalmanacDOTcaDOTgov/electricity/total_system_power.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366208739479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366209082336-15</Id><Topic><Title>Biofuels make liberals feel good</Title><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366125624214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:20:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never agreed with everything W did nor do I just get info from Fox. I read your post so there ya go.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366209082336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366209543252-16</Id><Topic><Title>California Wind Power Blows Away Production Record</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366205435791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am all for wind power but we are foolish if we try to completely rely on it. Of course you are talking about California.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366209543252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366210778170-17</Id><Title>see oil prices collapsing here</Title><Msg>Oh yes game is over. Fundamentals say oil prices plunge. Shale will over take oil here big time. Prices will free fall.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1366210778170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:59:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366216842074-18</Id><Title>will test last summer lows of $78</Title><Msg>In the not too distant future....</Msg><Username>texasbroker2000</Username><Timestamp>1366216842074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:40:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366216975177-19</Id><Title>☛☛☛Market SHOULD BE @ DOW=4400....at best</Title><Msg>sell everything asap boys !</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366216975177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366222570976-20</Id><Title>Senior House Dem blasts Energy and Commerce chief on climate change</Title><Msg>Senior House Dem blasts Energy and Commerce chief on climate change By Zack Colman - 04/17/13 09:50 AM ET Rep. Bobby Rush (D-Ill.) made a Wednesday pit stop at a Washington, D.C., conference to rip House Energy and Commerce Chairman Fred Upton (R-Mich.) on climate change. “He also believed in climate change. But now all of the sudden, since he became the chair, he’s had a new reorientation. He thinks that climate change now is a hoax,” Rush, a senior Democrat on the Energy and Commerce Committee, said at the Good Jobs, Green Jobs Conference. Rush was on his way to a House Energy Commerce Committee mark up for a bill that would expedite approval of the Keystone XL oil sands pipeline by removing the need to get a cross-border permit from the State Department. It is expected to pass with support from Republicans and some centrist Democrats. The veteran Illinois Democrat opposes the Canada-to-Texas pipeline, which he says would devastate the climate by encouraging production carbon-intensive oil sands. Rush and Rep. Henry Waxman (D-Calif.), the Energy and Commerce Committee’s top Democrat, have tried pushing Upton to hold hearings on climate science. The chairman and committee Republicans have rebuffed those efforts. Rush said he would not relent in attempting to force the committee to address climate change. “I’m on my way to a mark up … But I wanted to stop by here not just to get an award, but to get some new energy and to be refreshed,” Rush said, to applause. “We’ve got a relentless battle that’s going on in the U.S. House of Representatives, and we’ve got to shake that place up.” thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/294431-senior-house-dem-rips-energy-and-commerce-chief-on-climate-change</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366222570976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366223260307-21</Id><Title>As fuel efficiency standards drive gasoline taxes down, who pays to fix the highways?</Title><Msg>Julia Pyper, E&amp;E reporter ClimateWire: Tuesday, April 16, 2013 As the federal Highway Trust Fund inches closer to empty, toll operators are promoting user fees as the solution to America's infrastructure woes. The federal gas tax, which supports the highway fund, hasn't been raised since 1993. Meanwhile, vehicle fuel economy has continued to increase, spurred by market demand and new federal fuel efficiency standards. Collectively, these have kept tax revenue low while the need to repair the nation's aging roadways has increased. According to a recent report by the American Society of Civil Engineers, the United States needs to spend $3.6 trillion by 2020 to restore and upgrade the nation's infrastructure. Roads alone need $170 billion in capital investments per year to improve their condition and performance so the United States can stay economically competitive. Current federal, state and local investments total $91 billion per year. "Without a viable revenue stream, the status of our nation's surface transportation will continue to deteriorate," said Steve Morello, tolling expert at D'Artagnan Consulting and chief organizer of a symposium hosted yesterday by the International Bridge, Tunnel and Turnpike Association (IBTTA) in Philadelphia. "The transition to some alternative to the current gas tax ... with a user-based principle is picking up steam and is no longer a pipe dream," Morello added. Rebuilding the interstates IBTTA and its supporters are looking to inject tolling and other user fees into the national conversation about surface transportation funding with current federal highway legislation set to expire in September of next year. "One of our major goals is to ensure that as Congress considers funding options for surface transportation, tolling should be an option for state and local governments. They should have the flexibility to fund and finance America's... eenewsDOTnet/public/climatewire/2013/04/16/2</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366223260307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366223501273-22</Id><Title>Copenhagen Carbon Neutral By 2025, Danish Capital Moving Towards Ambitious Goal</Title><Msg>April 17, 2013 Nathan Copenhagen’s ambitious plan to be 100% carbon-neutral by the year 2025 continues to move forward. This plan, once achieved, will make Copenhagen the world’s first carbon-neutral capital. The City Council there, acting on the plan approved last August, will soon begin the first of several large-scale changes. These changes include: replacing coal power with biomass, adding more wind and solar energy to the grid, improving energy efficiency, increasing bike use/improving infrastructure, and improving public/mass transportation systems. Copenhagen, and more broadly Denmark, already possess substantial renewable energy infrastructure and capacity, and of course a strong cycling culture, but there is still a lot of room for improvement. With regards to cycling, 36% of all trips taken to work or school are currently via bike. These trips are taken over a 249-mile expanse of bicycle tracks. And during peak travel times, more than 20,000 cyclists, on average, enter the city every day. That’s all pretty impressive, but with some infrastructure improvements, those numbers could likely rise much higher. By the year 2025, the city is aiming for 75% of all trips to be made either by foot, bicycle, or public transit. To achieve this goal, the city is implementing a variety of new infrastructure improvements/changes: “green wave” traffic signals set to the speed of oncoming bikes, 44 miles of new bicycle tracks (paved paths separated from cars and pedestrians by curbs), “angled footrests that enable cyclists to rest without dismounting at intersections,” improvements to existing tracks — making them wider, smoother, and better lit, and the creation of “bicycle superhighways.” The first of these 26 planned bicycle superhighways opened just last year — an 11-mile link connecting Albertslund with Copenhagen. Two more are currently under... cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/04/17/copenhagen-carbon-neutral-by-2025-danish-capital-moving-towards-ambitious-goal/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366223501273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366230931758-23</Id><Topic><Title>As fuel efficiency standards drive gasoline taxes down, who pays to fix the highways?</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366223260307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:27:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals just cannot help it. They just love taxes. What about all those shovel ready projects that got stimulus money? I am sure a lot went to roads and bridges.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366230931758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 16:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366231581836-24</Id><Topic><Title>Copenhagen Carbon Neutral By 2025, Danish Capital Moving Towards Ambitious Goal</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366223501273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:31:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about all that carbon dioxide all those bicyclists are exhaling. I think there are serious flaws to all this carbon neutral push but politicians are good these days at not thinking things through.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366231581836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 16:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366232463595-25</Id><Title>Chinese are Polluting the World</Title><Msg>And to my knowledge no liberal environmentalist person in Congress is requiring them to comply with our standards to allow them to trade with us. So the result is that they are killing our jobs and nothing is getting better globally but liberals feel better I suppose.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366232463595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366235302942-26</Id><Title>Better ideas than carbon neutral policies can be found that would not hurt freedom and living standards.</Title><Msg>New CO2 Sucker Could Help Clear the Air by Robert F. Service on 9 January 2012, 5:23 PM | 0 Comments Researchers in California have produced a cheap plastic capable of removing large amounts of carbon dioxide (CO2) from the air. Down the road, the new material could enable the development of large-scale batteries and even form the basis of "artificial trees" that lower atmospheric concentrations of CO2.</Msg><Username>boyhowdie365</Username><Timestamp>1366235302942</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366239116838-27</Id><Title>Beat AAPL in market cap</Title><Msg>today.</Msg><Username>tshih_90630</Username><Timestamp>1366239116838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 18:51:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366241573257-28</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH XOM Analyst Report</Title><Username>andersonmike961</Username><Timestamp>1366234733099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Key Logger site from India............see the source? .in</Msg><Username>basherbuste_r</Username><Timestamp>1366241573257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 19:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366244464673-29</Id><Title>Oil-and-gas lobby talks biofuel rule with White House, EPA, senior lawmakers</Title><Msg>Zack Colman - 04/17/13 05:35 PM ET The head of a powerful oil industry lobbying group met with top White House officials and senior lawmakers Wednesday about stripping a federal biofuel rule. “We’re talking about the renewable fuel standard (RFS). It’s a hot topic,” American Petroleum Institute (API) chief executive Jack Gerard told reporters at the Capitol. “We’re just making some visits, making people understand the importance of repealing the RFS.” API wants to repeal the biofuel rule, which requires refiners to blend 36 billion gallons of biofuel into conventional petroleum by 2022. A list of Gerard’s meetings obtained by The Hill showed the lobbyist met with a power group of Washington, D.C., figures, underscoring the intensifying lobbying and political battle surrounding the biofuel mandate. Gerard met with several top Obama administration officials, including: Heather Zichal, President Obama’s top climate adviser; Gina McCarthy, director of the Environmental Protection Agency’s (EPA) Office of Air and Radiation, who is Obama’s pick to run EPA; Bob Perciasepe, acting EPA administrator; and Gene Sperling, Obama’s chief economic advisor. For his part, Obama has been a staunch supporter of biofuels. His fiscal 2014 budget plan proposes major increases for alternative fuel research, and he also is pushing an alternative fuel and vehicle research fund. McCarthy, who could end up leading EPA, also has touted the impact biofuels have had on reducing greenhouse gas emissions. With the administration proving a possible roadblock to its goals, API also has focused on the legislative route. It formally backed a bill introduced last week by Rep. Bob Goodlatte (R-Va.) that would repeal the renewable fuel standard, and has been busy lobbying lawmakers to oppose the rule. Noting that, Gerard's Wednesday trip to the thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/294623-oil-and-gas-lobby-talks-biofuel-rule-with-white-house-epa-senior-lawmakers</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366244464673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 20:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366244951183-30</Id><Title>States, cities, environmental groups demand EPA emission rules</Title><Msg>Neela Banerjee April 17, 2013, 3:05 p.m. WASHINGTON -- A dozen states and cities and three major environmental groups have notified the Environmental Protection Agency that they plan to sue the regulator unless it issues final rules limiting greenhouse gas emissions from new power plants. On Monday, the EPA confirmed that it had missed an April 13 deadline to issue final rules curtailing emissions of carbon dioxide from power plants, the country’s single biggest source of heat-trapping gases that drive climate change. The jurisdictions and the environmental groups sent separate letters to the EPA. But each letter notified the regulator of the groups’ plan to sue after 60 days, if the EPA did not expedite the rules. In a reply, the EPA declined to set a deadline for releasing the final regulations on the plants. “We are working on the rule and no timetable has been set. We continue to review the more than 2.7 million comments we have received on the rule,” spokeswoman Alisha Johnson said. The EPA proposed the rule for power plants in March 2012, and under the Clean Air Act, it must issue the final version of the rule within a year of receiving public comments, the New York attorney general’s office said. But the EPA failed to meet that deadline. It has yet to give the final rule to the Office of Management and Budget at the White House, where it could be reviewed for another 120 days and, based on the progress of some other EPA rules, might be delayed indefinitely. By finalizing the rules, the EPA would partially fulfill commitments it made in a 2011 agreement with New York Atty. Gen. Eric Schneiderman and a coalition of states to issue greenhouse gas emission standards for new and existing power plants. The EPA has to finalize rules for new plants before it can propose limits on carbon dioxide at existing plants. Said Schneiderman, “Climate change is a real and latimesDOTcom/news/politics/la-pn-epa-emission-rules-demand-20130417,0,7927668DOTstory</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366244951183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 20:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366246569853-31</Id><Topic><Title>California Wind Power Blows Away Production Record</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366205435791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And we need more Power Plants. Nucs, Coal, Peaking Gas power plants, and yes, DAMS.....if there is enough water to make a dam DAM worthwhile.</Msg><Username>dai_gul_dai</Username><Timestamp>1366246569853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 20:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366247773187-32</Id><Title>★★★★ KABOOM !!! ★★★★</Title><Msg>ENTIRE market CRASH coming boys......</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366247773187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 21:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366249088474-33</Id><Title>★★★★ KABOOM !!! ★★★★ GOLD market crashing..-$35 now</Title><Msg>paper next men.....</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366249088474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 21:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366249208996-34</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore warns of climate devastation in Dublin visit VIDEO</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1366204649192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:17:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did he fly there on a private jet? Most likely.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1366249208996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 21:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366249735946-35</Id><Topic><Title>Just wondering if Exxon CEO will want his life back after Texas Fire.....remember what he said about BP's Macondo??</Title><Username>spcrash</Username><Timestamp>1366233436858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:17:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How old were you when your father repeatedly slammed your head against the wall?</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1366249735946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 21:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366253168797-36</Id><Topic><Title>Fire at Exxon's Beaumont, Texas, refinery injures 12 workers</Title><Username>spcrash</Username><Timestamp>1366232855749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:07:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm truly sorry for the injured workers but crude has taken a pretty significant dive in the last 2 weeks. This should cause a shut down of the refinery which will lower out put nationwide for gasoline which should raise prices then next week they will report the inventories are down and were moving into the high driving summer months and there's a problem with inventories being too low.</Msg><Username>ravasaur</Username><Timestamp>1366253168797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 22:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366257529466-37</Id><Title>Artificial Photosynthesis, major new threat for oil &amp; gas</Title><Msg>Using the investigative methods of Quantum Chemistry, the Max Planck Institute has determined the precise structure of the oxygen evolving complex, the catalyst used by plants for photosynthesis. This could not be done with prior spectroscopic techniques. Proceeding as of the past 4 months, the scientists have been working on determining the mechanism of water oxidation at an atomic level. The purpose is the production of bio-fuels at a far lower cost than has been possible with past techniques. The processes which result will eventually be commercialized by a German corporation at some future date, just as has been done with countless other products. There is what was possible with antiquated, imprecise knowledge, and what is possible with precision which can only really be described as God-Like. The difference is substantial, and will be telling when such God-Like knowledge is introduced into markets…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1366257529466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>