<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359004127162-1</Id><Topic><Title>Apple is symptomatic of the entire stock market bubble</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358263165388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-15 10:19:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359004127162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 00:08:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359005340291-2</Id><Title>UBS: Boom in unsubsidised solar PV flags energy revolution</Title><Msg>UBS: Boom in unsubsidised solar PV flags energy revolution By Giles Parkinson on 23 January 2013 The revolution in energy markets caused by the growing impact of rooftop solar PV is about to take a dramatic leap in scale. According to analysts from the global investment banking giant UBS, the arrival of socket parity – where the cost of installing solar is cheaper than grid-sourced supplies – is about to cause a boom in un-subsidised solar installation in Europe, and the energy market may never be quite the same again. Such forecasts have long been the province of environmentalists, climate activists, university researchers, and the occasional industry leader, such as David Crane, the head of NRG, the largest generator of electricity in the US. Now, the team of energy analysts from UBS, writing in response to plunging power prices in Europe, has issued a stunning report entitled “The unsubsidised solar revolution” – suggesting that investing in solar will become a “no brainer” for households in several European countries, and will have profound implications for the incumbent energy industry. “Solar has turned from a heavily-subsidised marginal technology into a mainstream source of power generation,” the UBS analysts write. ” “Thanks to significant cost reductions and rising retail tariffs, households and commercial users are set to install solar systems to reduce electricity bills – without any subsidies.” Here’s a graph to illustrate what they mean. It shows the light blue line at the top, which indicates where grid-based electricity costs are heading. The dark blue line indicates the cost of solar PV – it’s now at an inflection point in southern Germany and will get cheaper. But PV with battery storage, while more expensive now, will cross over in 2014 and ultimately deliver the biggest savings. UBS says this means utility customers will effectively become utility competitors. It estimates there could be 80GW of unsubsidised solar installed in Germany alone. This is on top of the 32GW already installed through subsidised installation, and the 52GW cap put on subsidised installations. “We are at the beginning of a new era in power markets,” the UBS analysts write. ”Purely based on economics, we believe almost every family home and every commercial rooftop in Germany, Italy and Spain should be equipped with a solar system by the end of this decade.” It says up to 18% of electricity demand could be replaced by self-produced solar power in these markets, at the expense of centralised generation. Even as soon as 2020, up to 43GW of unsubsidised solar could be installed in Germany, Italy and Spain, replacing up to 9 per cent of electricity demand. This is on top of reduction in demand caused by energy efficiency measures and weak GDP growth. The impact on utilities will be profound, and will be made worse by the emergence of cheap battery storage, which would allow households – and businesses – to consumer more of their own energy, and effectively remove the morning and evening peak in pricing, as well as the midday peaks, as we revealed in a dramatic graph in our article last May of Why generators are terrified of solar. Without any peaks, the profit margin of generators is removed. UBS calculates the EBITDA profit pool of the conventional generators will shrink by around 50 per cent. “Households will be able to use the electricity stored in batteries during the evening, which means pressure on spot prices during the evening hours. So far, solar has only been shaving the midday peak. Even worse, batteries installed in family homes or commercial buildings could also reduce the morning peak as they could be charged with low-cost electricity from the grid during night hours,” UBS notes. It says residential customers, on average, could provide 29 per cent of their own energy needs by 2020. Individually, a house with a 3kWh battery and a 4kW PV system could to lower its electricity consumed from the grid by 50-60 per cent. Commercial businesses could cut even greater amounts, and even a car manufacturing giant like BMW could produce 490MWh of solar electricity per year using its own land, or 29 per cent of the group-wide electricity demand. The impact on the generation industry will be severe. Here’s what UBS estimates the combination of solar PV and battery storage will do to the tariff curve by 2020 – the full impact of their predictions will result in an even greater flattening of the curve. (Please click on graph if it is not totally visible). UBS predicts that by 2020, power prices will fall another 10 per cent, and coal-fired generators, once the major providers of baseload power, will be reduced to the role of filling the gaps between renewable. UBS estimates that the load factor of lignite (brown coal) plants in Germany drops from 72% to 59%, while the load factor of hard coal plants drops from 47% to 31% by 2020. That will give them a lower load factor than many wind or solar farms. UBS says that the explosion of solar will have a cascading effect – as noted by AGL Energy in Australia, and the local utility in Hawaii. AGL used the circle of death as an argument to reduce feed in tariffs. But the significance of unsubsidised solar is that the proliferation of solar is unstoppable – unless, of course, it is halted by regulation, or fixed tariffs. Given the rising costs of fossil fuels, this would be a PR nightmare for the generation industry, but UBS raises the possibility, echoing our story last year about how electricity business models and markets are effectively broken. “At some point, we think this will trigger a political debate about how the grid fees and renewables subsidies should be paid for. It could lead to a flat-fee pricing model,” the UBS analysts write. The UBS analysis does not extend beyond Europe. It says there is no immediate prospect of unsubsidised solar in other European countries, either because retail tariffs are lower (France), or because of lousy sun (northern Europe). But it clearly has implications for other countries, particularly Australia, which has high retail tariffs and excellent solar resources, and which already has a near 10 per cent penetration rate of rooftop solar on available households. reneweconomyDOTcomDOTau/2013/ubs-boom-in-unsubsidised-solar-pv-flags-energy-revolution-60218</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359005340291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 00:29:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359006123653-3</Id><Title>Jeffrey Sachs: Natural Gas Is “Absolutely Not Clean Enough”</Title><Msg>Jeffrey Sachs: Natural Gas Is “Absolutely Not Clean Enough” January 23, 2013Zachary Shahan Dr Jeffrey Sachs, Director of The Earth Institute at Columbia University and Special Advisor to the United Nations Secretary‐General on the Millennium Development Goals, gave one of the strongest presentations of the first-ever Abu Dhabi Sustainability Week and the 6th Annual World Future Energy Summit — it might have been the strongest presentation, in my opinion. His goal definitely seemed to be to wake us up to the urgency of addressing global warming and global climate change, and I think he did a good job of that. He also focused quite a bit on the shortcomings of natural gas. Here’s a video of his speech, followed by what I think were some of the highlights / key points: In my opinion, the messages or quotes in bold below were some of Dr Sachs’ most compelling points: 1. Natural gas production is not sustainable — it’s also harmful to our climate. “The hydrofracking revolution that is bringing shale oil and shale gas to many parts of the world is very profitable, but it is not putting the world on a trajectory that is sustainable by any stretch of the imagination.” Later in the speech, he added: “while we are in the middle of our new ‘gold rush’ of hydrofracking, and we tell ourselves conveniently that natural gas is clean, it is cleaner than coal, but it is absolutely not clean enough to divert us from a trajectory of grave damage on the environment — let’s be clear about that. We use rhetoric, which lulls us to complacency, to say that natural gas is a clean energy source. It is not a low-carbon energy source. It’s low-carbon only in comparison to coal. But it is high-carbon in comparison to what our climate can take.” This triggers an excellent analogy Karl-Friedrich Lenz recently made (which I shared in a news roundup yesterday): “Using gas is like smoking a ‘light’ cigarette. It may contain slightly less harmful substances, but it will still kill you. That’s why the European Union has a ban in place on using words like ‘light’ or ‘mild’ in connection with cigarettes since 10 years ago.” That’s the sad truth. And while natural gas could help renewable energy technologies power the majority of the grid without any support from nuclear or coal power plants, the truth is that we don’t currently need it (at today’s renewable energy saturation levels), and it is far too overhyped. Of course, even with optimistic assumptions about natural gas, it is not clean enough to be a significant part of our energy mix: However, due to uncontrollable and perhaps grossly underestimated natural gas leakage, the scary thing is that natural gas might be even much worse than we tend to assume. 2. Climate change is already hitting us. It is already a challenge. And this is just the beginning. “And I do think we are seeing, if we care to open our eyes, a rather alarming reality about climate change. It’s not news anymore, but I’m going to say it anyway, and that is — the issue of climate change used to be talked about as a problem of the future, and it is now a problem of the immediate present. In every part of the world, in every year, there are a number of calamities that vastly outnumber anything that we experienced even 20 years ago. The global climate system is simply changing a lot faster than our minds are changing, our institutions are changing, or our energy systems are changing.” In reference to that point just above, he had this great quote: ”I come from New York City. It’s a place that considers itself pretty sophisticated. It’s a place that couldn’t get the power supply on millions of people for a month after a major hurricane hit in November, and the city was unprepared, as was the East Coast unprepared, for a massive amount of flooding, which has come from the fact that the sea level has increased/risen by about a foot over the past century, and so when a massive storm hit, the amount of flooding was of an unprecedented character. “But the United States was actually hit by pre-shocks this past year — the warmest year in the instrument history of the United States; the massive drought that hit more than 60% of the US, and caused a huge damage to the food supply, and sent wheat and soybean and maize prices worldwide soaring once again; and the hurricane, Hurricane Sandy, which struck in early November. “But if you look in almost any part of the world, the story is the same. The size of the shocks, the droughts, the floods, the extreme events are coming at an alarming rate.” What more is there to say about all of that? The catastrophes of global warming and climate change are already hitting us… and they are only projected to get worse. 3. “I don’t think that our discussion is adequate yet. We do not have a solution trajectory that is, first of all, even identified. The United States, for example, does not have an energy plan. We have no policy that is agreed in the United States, not even a policy that has been put forward clearly in the United States, to explain how we will get on a low-carbon trajectory.” Again, not much to add there. 4. “And in the United States, for various reasons, we have not been able to create a framework that describes to the American people, for example, what is a trajectory to reach a low-carbon economy. Even less do we have a public policy. We don’t have a carbon tax. We don’t have a permit system. We have no agreement on this. “And if you look around at the major economies of the world, this is basically true, with the partial exception of Europe.” A bit chilling. For those of us aware of this, I think all we can do is keep pushing as hard as we can to change things in the countries, communities, and circles where we live. sDOTtt/1yQpZ</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359006123653</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 00:42:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359007280199-4</Id><Topic><Title>UBS: Boom in unsubsidised solar PV flags energy revolution</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359005340291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 00:29:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Goodbye, coal, natural gas and nuclear power! Expensive and dirty! Just my opinion</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359007280199</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 01:01:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359036571337-5</Id><Title>Out Of Apple And Into Exxon In Droves!</Title><Msg>Money Flows into the real Number One Today,as investors flee Apple and turn to Big Div Paying,and King of The Dog Run! Look for new highs in oil,partialy due to China,and also watch XOM as it nears new all time highs. A Div Hikez is just around the corner for Exxon Longz!</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1359036571337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:09:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359037369599-6</Id><Title>Money Flowing Out Of Apple Into Exxon Today!</Title><Msg>Watch the money flow leader today,as investors flee Apple into Exxon,which is The Real Big Dog in The Dog Park. Savy Investors as well as longtime Longz are also aware of impending Div Hikez in near future,and oil could break above 100.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1359037369599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:22:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359037389048-7</Id><Topic><Title>Reversing my short... well?</Title><Username>christinadeojay814</Username><Timestamp>1307853338000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-06-12 00:35:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just added my email... thx</Msg><Username>monicamoras490</Username><Timestamp>1359037389048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:23:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359038168796-8</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon, the most profitable corporation in the history of the planet.</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1359037216777</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:20:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saudi Aramco is the most profitable corporation in the history of the planet. Both of them will be bankrupt within 20 years...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359038168796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:36:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359038792351-9</Id><Title>The United States of Europe</Title><Msg>The idea is so nauseating it makes me want to put my house in Munich on the market right away, and buy a replacement in London. The UK has lower taxes than Germany too.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359038792351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:46:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359039485760-10</Id><Title>Bond Purchase</Title><Msg>30 Year UK Gilt 3.25% yield to maturity... 100% allocation.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359039485760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:58:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359039491575-11</Id><Title>viva E</Title><Msg>2000 years ago Europe was united under the Italians. It was destroyed by illegal immigrants who kept pushing west and are now in Hawaii 2000 years later.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1359039491575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:58:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359040259744-12</Id><Topic><Title>Reversing My Short</Title><Username>danieletreyz895</Username><Timestamp>1325517787000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-01-02 10:23:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great trading tool</Msg><Username>monicamoras490</Username><Timestamp>1359040259744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:10:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359040302768-13</Id><Topic><Title>viva E</Title><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1359039491575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:58:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everywhere you look in Europe that is not Germanic you find failure. Everywhere you look in Europe that is Germanic from Germany to the Frankreich, to England you find wealth... -- Southern Italy (as opposed to Germanic northern Italy which is rich) -- Spain -- Greece -- Portugal -- Romania -- Hungary -- Pannonia -- all the countries of former "Yugoslavia" -- all Roman in times past -- Turkey - Byzantine Empire North Africa was poor when the Roman ruled it, it was poor when Mussolini occupied parts of it, and it is still poor. The fasces is a mark of slavery, and tyranny - and very Italian and Roman.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359040302768</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:11:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359040490695-14</Id><Topic><Title>viva E</Title><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1359039491575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:58:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>American is being overrun the by Roman filth too. Its wealth is draining fast and will become a third world country...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359040490695</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:14:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359040868090-15</Id><Topic><Title>viva E</Title><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1359039491575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:58:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read your history. The Romans didn't do so badly for a thousand years.. I bet you use some of their roads and bridges in Germany besides that alphabet. Lots of Germans have dark hair and they are nicknamed "Roemer" Anyway they do that in Bavaria. As far as Italy is concerned, the North is perhaps the richest region in Europe and the south is scenic.By the way, if you want a big Fascist, the chubby Frau running the Deutschland today is an outstanding example.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1359040868090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:21:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359041230984-16</Id><Topic><Title>viva E</Title><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1359039491575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:58:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hansi, Hansi, our days in the sun are numbered. The great nations of Asia, China, India and Japan, to name a few, have wrenched the eagle standard from our hands- or soon will.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1359041230984</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:27:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359041830449-17</Id><Topic><Title>viva E</Title><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1359039491575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:58:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've forgotten more history than you ever knew. The Romans did well as long as they could find someone else's income to appropriate for themselves. Rome itself was nothing but a parasite of a million people drawing tribute from across Europe to feed it as were the other Roman cities. The system was very much like a the Mafia system of gang rule - organized with nice names like Senate and Legion - imposed across every land they occupied. Read Usher - Industrial History of England to learn the truth about their parasitic system of slavery and tribute. There are many other sources for facts but a Professor of history and economics from an Ivy League institution serves well enough. Northern Italy is Germanic too. It was conquered by the Ostrogoths - Germans - and never retaken by the Romans. The Roman filth you glorify did take Southern Italy back however, and the Papal States, Naples, and Sicily were governed in the Roman way for those many centuries. The Romans did not invent the alphabet either, and the Germanic languages have very few Latin influences. What culture the Romans had they appropriated from Greece, a country they occupied and lived like a parasite off of for many centuries... Your views are simply infantile....</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359041830449</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:37:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359042073214-18</Id><Topic><Title>Bullish still</Title><Username>myonghurlbut2315</Username><Timestamp>1321760655000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-11-19 22:44:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. So in theory.</Msg><Username>monicamoras490</Username><Timestamp>1359042073214</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:41:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359042155027-19</Id><Topic><Title>viva E</Title><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1359039491575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 09:58:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eagle standard? More Roman filth... You mean your days are numbered, and the culture that is being drug down by the Romanism you embrace day's are numbered. Germanic Europe having few difficulties. It is richer than all Eastern countries you mention. Germany itself has a surplus and very little unemployment. German industrial technology is the best in the world.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359042155027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:42:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359043157591-20</Id><Title>Rotten Apple!</Title><Msg>Get into Exxon,Ladys and Jerkz,while it trades under 95.. Goes X in 10 Dayz.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1359043157591</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:59:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359043392019-21</Id><Topic><Title>UBS: Boom in unsubsidised solar PV flags energy revolution</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359005340291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 00:29:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good - please stop using these immediately.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1359043392019</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 11:03:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359046697576-22</Id><Title>Lombards...</Title><Msg>The Lombards were a Germanic people, who originated in southern Scandinavia, and who later occupied the areas of modern Hamburg, Bremen, areas along the Rhine, parts of Bavaria, and Austria. After the wars between the Ostrogothic Kingdom in Italy (the German replacement of the annihilated Roman Western Empire) and the Eastern Roman Imperial forces under Belisarius and Justinian in the 6th century, Italy was very severely depopulated. To defeat the Imperial Roman armies the Germans brought in their Frankish German allies. The bloodbath in Italy was almost total. Eventually Constantinople could not sustain the expense, and turned tail back to the East, focusing their tyrannical government and tributes on the Balkans and Near East. Syria etc...another failed land today. The Lombard Germans then swept in from Germany and Austria and occupied Northern Italy, seizing the depopulated lands for themselves. Lombardy in Northern Italy is named for them. Lombard Street in London is also named for them as well. London banking was much influenced by the Germanic Lombards from Northern Italy, as were other areas across Germany, the Netherlands, etc...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359046697576</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 11:58:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359046973586-23</Id><Topic><Title>Rotten Apple!</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1359043157591</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 10:59:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love XOM, it's my key holding. You can't really go wrong buying it at any time if you intend to buy and hold. That said, I tend to add to it when crude prices are low as the stock price dips. Crude is fairly high right now. Summer tends to be a good time, esp. whenever there are US elections. Generally, that's when it hits its 52 week low. If you're not DCAing (generally makes more money anyhow), you may as well buy when it's red. Also, with AAPL and tech's recent volatility a lot of people will be rebalancing their portfolios into large cap blue chips like XOM and the better parts of the dow30.</Msg><Username>rwilson31781</Username><Timestamp>1359046973586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 12:02:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359050035368-24</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation UPDATED CHARTS!</Title><Username>rosalselawendy</Username><Timestamp>1359044946110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 11:29:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok cool. Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>mordversuchshauna</Username><Timestamp>1359050035368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 12:53:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359051427979-25</Id><Title>Italian elections and future of euro and EU...</Title><Msg>The Italians are set go to the polls next month, and the outcome will decide the fate of the euro, and indeed the EU as well. You can rest assured that Germany and the rest of Germanic Europe is not going to write a check to bail out Italy, and if Italy elects a government that cannot balance its budget there will be no more euro. Germany itself is likely to just abandon it at some point, and change its banking credits and bond payments from euros to Deutsche Marks. The loss of the German buttressed currency would absolutely obliterate Southern Europe's economy. It would be like going back to Roman times, or the economic state of places like Mexico....Italy itself would probably be reorganized into north and south Italy at some point...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359051427979</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:17:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359052990551-26</Id><Topic><Title>UBS: Boom in unsubsidised solar PV flags energy revolution</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359005340291</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 00:29:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bluecheese, goodbye to you, freak. I now have your anti-science, illogical and unreasonable #$%$ on Iggy.</Msg><Username>iitriumvirate</Username><Timestamp>1359052990551</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 13:43:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359054073665-27</Id><Title>What the economic collapse of Southern Europe will bring...</Title><Msg>The assets owned by the people of Spain, Italy, Portugal, and Greece amounts to about 15 trillion euros. Without the economic power of Germany and other Germanic economies behind the Euro, the value of those Southern European assets will be substantially less. Interest rates on whatever currency replaced the euro with in those lands would be quite high, and the governments would be forced to balance their budgets or print their new currencies away to nothing. Either way they would generate far less $ demand for goods including oil and many other items. US banks have many bets on Southern Europe too and will sustain much damage, as will many major US corporations... The Chinese economy is built on exports and Southern Europe is major cash cow for them. They have much difficulty competing with German manufacturers for markets but in backward places like Southern Europe they are much more successful.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359054073665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:01:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359054627627-28</Id><Title>Waxman: Keystone XL 'small' piece of climate puzzle</Title><Msg>Waxman: Keystone XL 'small' piece of climate puzzle By Zack Colman - 01/24/13 12:31 PM ET A top Democratic global warming advocate said Thursday that President Obama’s decision on the Keystone XL pipeline is a “small” part of battling climate change. Rep. Henry Waxman (D-Calif.) said he hopes Obama nixes the project to bring Canadian oil sands to the Gulf Coast. But he stressed that Keystone is just one piece of the whole climate picture. “This is only a small issue compared to the overall objective that the president and we want to achieve,” Waxman, the top Democrat on the House Energy and Commerce Committee, said during a news conference Thursday. But Green groups have made the Keystone project the centerpiece of recent pressure on Obama to tackle climate change. Those groups are organizing a Feb. 17 demonstration urging Obama to axe the pipeline, which is under review by the State Department. The White House has final say on the pipeline’s northern leg because it crosses into Canada. Waxman said he would be “disappointed” if Obama approves the project, but he acknowledged the president has more than just the climate angle to consider. “I know there are a lot of different factors, including our relationship with Canada, that’s on his mind,” Waxman told reporters. Some members of Obama’s party have lined up in support of the project as well. A handful of Senate Democrats joined a group of 53 senators Wednesday that called on Obama to greenlight the project. They said the pipeline would be a boon for the economy in the handful of states along its planned route. And some unions want the project to go forward, because it could provide jobs for many of their members. Waxman said he has made his disagreement to the Keystone pipeline known. But he also said he must be practical about the battles he picks. “Well I should ask you what would you like me to do? Should I say to the president, ‘If you don’t agree with me on Keystone, I’m not going to work with you on solving the climate change issue’? That would be a little bit childish and counterproductive,” Waxman said. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/279081-waxman-keystone-xl-small-piece-of-climate-puzzle</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359054627627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:10:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359055407401-29</Id><Title>North America’s Largest Wind Energy Storage Facility Fires Up In Texas</Title><Msg>North America’s Largest Wind Energy Storage Facility Fires Up In Texas January 24, 2013 Tina Casey 38Share Where else to site the nation’s biggest wind energy storage facility but in Texas, the state known for its extra bigness? Duke Energy has fired up the new 36 megawatt energy storage and management facility, which is linked to the Notrees Windpower wind farm in the western part of the state. Aside from showcasing some nifty new energy management bells and whistles, the new storage facility blows a Texas-sized raspberry in the direction of renewable energy nay-sayers, whose complaints about the “unreliable” nature of wind power are now, well, blowing in the wind. We Built This Gigantic Wind Energy Storage System! The new facility was commissioned by North Carolina-based Duke, through its Duke Energy Renewables division. It was the recipient of one of the early publicly funded energy projects approved under the Obama Administration’s Recovery Act in 2009, with Duke matching a $22 million grant from the Department of Energy’s ARPA-E advanced energy research funding arm. For its investment, the U.S. taxpaying public gets to use the new system as a knowledge base leading to widespread adoption throughout the national grid, firmly cementing clean, renewable, low cost wind power into the mainstream of the U.S. energy landscape. Other partners in the effort include the Electric Power Research Institute, which will analyze the system’s performance and #$%$ its potential for broader application, and the Energy Reliability Council of Texas, which is working with Duke Energy to optimize the system’s ability to increase or decrease the frequency of electricity traveling through the grid. Small Batteries for Big Energy Storage The storage system itself was engineered by the Texas-based company Xtreme Power, which counts the Bloomberg 2012 New Energy Pioneer Award and an R&amp;D 100 Award among its recognitions. Xtreme’s Dynamic Power Resource™ energy storage system is already in use elsewhere in the U.S., one example being a 15 megawatt system for the Kahuku Wind project in Hawaii which previously held the title of North America’s largest when it went online in 2011. The system consists of a scalable assembly of thousands of Xtreme Power’s PowerCell™ battery, which is a a 12 volt, 1 kWh, dry cell battery based on a proprietary formula of alloys including copper, lead and tellurium. The system stores energy like a conventional battery but it also has the quick “stop-and-go” capabilities of a capacitor, and that enables it to function as a high performance energy management system as well as a storage system. Among other advantages, Xtreme Power notes that the materials in the PowerCell are not classified as hazardous and are easily recycled, for which purpose the company has established a recovery system. Many Paths to Renewable Energy Storage Battery-based storage systems are just one avenue of exploration for renewable energy storage. Among the other up-and-coming options is the flywheel, updated from its Neolithic roots with high-tech materials and space-age lubricants. Pumped hydro energy storage is another promising resource, in which excess wind power is used to pump water uphill, then gravity takes over when more energy is needed. Along similar lines, researchers at the University of Nottingham are looking into inflating giant undersea bags with compressed air, by using excess power from offshore wind farms. When more energy is needed, water pressure from the sea will force air out of the bags to run turbines. Meanwhile, researchers at the North Carolina State University are working on semiconductor “nanoflowers” with an enormous surface area relative to their size, which could lead to the development of cheaper, more efficient lithium-ion batteries. Speaking of the Biggest… Duke’s recent merger with Progress Energy has made it the largest utility company in the U.S., so this looks to be just the beginning of its impact on future energy generation, storage and distribution nationwide. The company has been making headlines lately for a variety of reasons, not all of them necessarily positive, but we’ve also taken notice of the company’s leadership position on renewable energy. Aside from wind power, Duke has been in the vanguard of new distributed solar power systems, and last fall former CEO Jim Rogers went out on a limb to make a clean energy case for the re-election of President Obama. Duke is also involved in an electric vehicle research partnership with the Department of Energy, Ford and Siemens, and it has formed clean tech partnerships with energy companies in China. Image (cropped): Raspberry by Muffet sDOTtt/1yT18</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359055407401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:23:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359056273802-30</Id><Topic><Title>Waxman: Keystone XL 'small' piece of climate puzzle</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359054627627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sen. Kerry keeps cards close to vest on Keystone pipeline By Ben Geman - 01/24/13 01:12 PM ET Sen. John Kerry (D-Mass.), President Obama’s nominee for Secretary of State, offered little indication Thursday of whether he would endorse construction of the Keystone XL oil sands pipeline. “It will not be long before that comes across my desk and at that time I will make the appropriate judgments about it,” Kerry said at his nomination hearing before the Senate Foreign Relations Committee. The State Department is leading the federal review of TransCanada Corp.'s proposed pipeline to bring Canadian oil sands to Gulf Coast refineries. The White House faces heavy and competing pressures: Business groups and some unions are lobbying hard for approval, while climate-change activists have made rejection of Keystone a priority. Kerry has been one of Capitol Hill’s most prominent advocates of curbing greenhouse gas emissions, and Thursday noted that American foreign policy is “defined by leadership on life-threatening issues like climate change.” He said during the hearing that he will be a "passionate advocate" at State on climate change, and noted extreme weather that took a toll on the U.S. over the past year. “I will be a passionate advocate about this, but not based on ideology, but based on facts, based on science,” Kerry said. Kerry, during the hearing, framed addressing climate change in the context of development of green energy technologies, casting it as a major economic opportunity for the U.S. “The solution to climate change is energy policy,” Kerry said. “This is a job-creator. I can’t emphasize that strongly enough” Kerry, who is widely expected to be confirmed, would lead State at a time when the U.S. is participating in United Nations-led talks aimed at crafting a new global emissions accord. State also with other nations through bilateral green energy and climate partnerships. But Kerry has not tipped his hand on Keystone, either in his Senate role or, on Thursday, as a Cabinet nominee. “We are responsible for the environmental review, and there are specific standards that have to be met with respect to that review. I am going to review those standards and make sure they are complete,” Kerry said of State’s review. Kerry said he would try and complete the review by the end of March, but did not promise it, noting he would check back in with State on the status. “It is happening in the appropriate due course of business. We will try and get it done as soon as we can,” Kerry said of the pipeline review. The State Department has said it hopes to complete the review by the end of the first quarter of 2013, but a department spokeswoman this week hinted that the timeline might slip. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/279093-kerry-keeps-cards-close-to-vest-on-keystone-pipeline</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359056273802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:37:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359057381812-31</Id><Title>Report: Lack of consistent policy holding back clean energy industry</Title><Msg>Report: Lack of consistent policy holding back clean energy industry Posted on 01/24/2013 by Dan Ferber Workers assemble a wind turbine blade at a factory in Grand Forks, North Dakota, in 2006. (Photo by tuey via Creative Commons) The Midwest has the potential for a thriving clean energy industry, but only if coherent policies are enacted at the state and federal level, clean-energy experts say. Experts on the Midwestern clean-energy sector say the region stands to benefit because of its research universities, strong supply chains and a high level of manufacturing know-how. But whether it does or not depends largely on policy-makers. According to a report issued last week by Pew Charitable Trusts, hurdles to an expanded U.S. clean-energy sector include a lack of a national clean-energy standard and longstanding tax breaks for oil, gas and coal producers. Unless these and other issues are addressed, they could lead to billions of dollars of economic activity moving overseas, the analysis concluded. “The Midwest looks to me like a great place for clean energy,” said Phyllis Cuttino, director of Pew’s Clean Energy Program. But, she added, clean-energy leaders in the Midwest and nationwide “all said the same thing: The thing that makes it really hard for us is that we can’t plan.” These conclusions come from two lines of investigation Pew undertook to prepare the report. They commissioned a detailed analysis of clean-energy trends by Pike Research, industry analysts who specialize in global clean-technology markets. Pew also conducted five regional roundtables of clean-energy business leaders, including researchers, manufacturers, companies deploying solar and biomass, and investors, as well as one national roundtable, all to get the industry’s take on how current policy was affecting them, and which policy changes would help. Pew found that the industry was at a tipping point in the United States and globally. Investment is on the rise, prices for clean energy are falling, and more and more clean energy is being deployed. “Clean energy is here to stay. It’s not niche. It’s quickly becoming cost-competitive and going into the next phase,” Cuttino said. Indeed, investment rose six-fold between 2004 and 2011 and was projected to continue to rise. Clean-energy installations—installations of solar photovoltaics, onshore and offshore wind, marine and hydrokinetic energy, geothermal, concentrating solar thermal, and biomass—will create $1.9 trillion in revenue globally and $269 billion in the United States between 2012 and 2018, the Pike Research analysis concluded. “We’re at a moment that looks like the auto industry at the turn of the 20th century or the early days of computers,” Cuttino said. “A whole bunch of actors are rushing in; we have an oversupply of production capacity, and more investments are coming because of the perception it’s going to take off.” As a result, the race is on between nations seeking to become global leaders in clean energy technology, the Pew analysis concluded. That race will not last forever, business leaders warn, and it’s not yet clear whether the United States in general, and the Midwest in particular, is going to win. Good news, bad news There are some encouraging signs for the industry, both in the Midwest and nationally, Pew found. The United States attracted a record $48.1 billion in private clean-energy investments in 2011, and the nation remains a leader in clean-energy innovation. But the Pew report pointed to signs of trouble. While U.S. solar installations have doubled each year since 2009, both Germany and Italy installed more than three times as much new solar last year. And China installed three times more wind in 2011 than the United States. “These trends are worrisome because these are technologies that we really invented and we used to manufacture and export,” Cuttino said. “Now we’re finding that we’re not playing at the same levels as other countries. Of the top 10 wind and solar companies in the world, we only have one of each,” she pointed out. The reasons for this include fierce international competition, including tariffs, tight credit markets, and policies that favor established fossil-fuel-based power over clean energy in the United States. What’s more, in other nations clean energy has not become the political football it has become here, said Aaron LeMieux, the founder and CEO of Tremont Electric, a six-year-old Cleveland-based company that specializes in harvesting kinetic energy. “When we go to other countries like Japan, there’s a compelling understanding of what clean energy is and the need to have new [energy] technology alongside existing technology,” LeMieux said. In the United States, in contrast, “renewable energy technology tends to be a partisan argument between Democrats and Republicans.” “At our business roundtables, they were kind of shocked that this had become a politicized issue,” Cuttino added. “They’d seen government engage in support for new and emerging industries—computers, trains, railroads and others. They couldn’t understand why not this sector.” Investment without rewards? As a result of our policy confusion, “we continue to innovate, but we don’t necessarily reap the rewards of our innovation and risk taking,” LeMieux said. “That’s passed to other countries to be able to build, manufacture, and deploy these technologies.” In Pew’s roundtables, business leaders like LeMieux named the U.S. clean-energy industry’s biggest obstacles as policy uncertainty, global oversupply, international competition, access to credit and private investment, and the uneven playing field with established fossil-fuel-based energy. But new national policies would create opportunity as well. A national Clean Energy Standard could stimulate demand for renewable energy. Such a standard would be broader than state renewable energy standards in that it might include natural gas and nuclear. The nation could invest more in basic energy research, which lags dramatically behind comparable investments in the health-care and defense sectors, Cuttino said. Effective policies to facilitate private sector investment in the industry could help, business leaders told Pew. For example, the Advanced Energy Manufacturing Tax Credit, which was established as part of the 2009 Recovery Act, provided a 30 percent tax incentive for investments of clean energy manufacturing. Far more companies applied than received funds, and it was documented to create 17,000 jobs at 180 facilities in 43 states, Cuttino said. The tax credit has expired but could be renewed. Clean-energy business leaders also suggested such measures as getting rid of special tax credits for oil and gas industries. Some suggested getting rid of all subsidies, or taxing the health and environmental costs incurred by burning gas, oil and coal, Cuttino said. “Now is the time for our policy makers to really level the playing field so that entrepreneurs and business leaders can compete with our competitors throughout the world,” LeMieux said. We also need a clear national policy aimed at phasing in more clean energy, LeMieux said. “Quite a few other countries are leading the charge in terms of clean energy. All have a national energy strategy.” That strategy should include a clean energy standard, the business leaders assembled by Pew concluded. Although 33 states have renewable portfolio standards, the lack of a federal standard harms the industry and keeps it from growing, LeMieux said. “We’re trying to tell people in Washington, D.C., that this is a big issue.” A manufacturing powerhouse With effective policy changes, the Midwest could become a national leader in clean energy manufacturing, technology and R&amp;D, LeMieux said. “The Midwest is the manufacturing powerhouse of the nation. It always has been,” he said. And more clean energy could mean more good jobs in the region, said Laura Arnold, president of the Indiana Distributed Energy Alliance, an Indianapolis-based nonprofit that promotes distributed renewable energy. The real economic development potential is not just building wind farms, Arnold said. “The real potential is in the manufacturing, not just buying and installing and producing renewable electricity. That’s where the middle-class manufacturing jobs come from.” Companies producing those jobs could make renewable energy components for export as well as domestic markets, Arnold said. Abound Solar, a Colorado-based company, was planning to create 800 jobs in Tipton, Indiana, to manufacture solar photovoltaic panels and they were planning to export 90 percent of what they made. In that case the plans were canceled, but they showed what’s possible, Arnold said. The United States in general, and the Midwest in particular, “has the manufacturing know-how to put out a quality product,” Arnold said. States matter, too The policy changes Pew suggests could go a long way, but changes at the state level are also essential, Arnold said. Germany and Italy, for example, have feed-in tariffs, which reward people for installing solar panels by ensuring a long-term, steady, and high price for the electricity they generate. If Midwestern states chose to establish such policies, markets would grow, helping the region’s clean-energy industry flourish, Arnold said. In Indiana, in contrast, “you can’t buy electricity from anyone other than your friendly electric utility,” she said. Policies that allow more choice would grow the market for renewable energy, she emphasized. Other state and local policies could spur demand for renewable energy in the region. Today, there are people in urban neighborhoods who might want to install solar panels but don’t have good exposure to the sun. If a church in the neighborhood has an annex with a great rooftop, they could provide solar power to their neighbors, but only if local and state policies allow for community energy systems, Arnold said. “I’m not sure how to do that with national legislation. I think it has to be done at the state level to permit more creative ways for people to own a piece of a small distributed system,” she said. “Yes, there’s an overriding need for national policy, Arnold concluded. “but the real nitty-gritty work still has to take place at the state level.” midwestenergynewsDOTcom/2013/01/24/report-lack-of-consistent-policy-holding-back-clean-energy-industry/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359057381812</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:56:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359057863003-32</Id><Title>Where's that arrogant little nut Maxwiz?</Title><Msg>I do believe he bragged about being a big apple shareholder... His XOM has gone nowhere since the Apple bubble peaked either. Dumpster boy - indeed.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359057863003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:04:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359058342996-33</Id><Title>This Week In Petroleum</Title><Msg>This Week In Petroleum Released: January 24, 2013 Next Release: January 30, 2013 Scroll over labels below to see different charts. Retail Prices (Dollars per Gallon) Retail Prices Change From Last 01/21/13 Week Year Gasoline 3.315 0.012 -0.074 Diesel Fuel 3.902 0.008 0.054 Heating Oil 3.984 0.011 0.047 Propane 2.455 0.019 -0.409 Futures Prices (Dollars per Gallon*) Futures Prices Change From Last 01/18/13 Week Year Crude Oil 95.56 2.00 -2.90 Gasoline 2.797 0.057 0.013 Heating Oil 3.053 0.044 0.065 *Note: Crude Oil Price in Dollars per Barrel. Stocks (Million Barrels) Stocks Change From Last 01/18/13 Week Year Crude Oil 363.1 2.8 28.3 Gasoline 233.3 -1.7 6.1 Distillate 132.9 0.5 -12.6 Propane 60.883 -3.073 10.131 Released: January 24, 2013 Next Release: January 30, 2013 After Late-2012 Declines, Gasoline Prices Stabilize in Early 2013 The U.S. average retail price for regular gasoline fell steadily through the end of 2012, to $3.25 per gallon on December 17 from $3.88 per gallon on September 17. After rebounding slightly in the final weeks of 2012, prices have held relatively steady through the first three weeks of 2013, increasing less than two cents per gallon to $3.32 per gallon. The stable prices in 2013 reflect Brent crude oil prices that have traded in a relatively well-defined range since the beginning of the year, and gasoline crack spreads that are largely unchanged, on average, from December. However, the stable national average does not capture the significant regional variation in gasoline prices, with the highest average prices for any Petroleum Administration for Defense District (PADD) on the West Coast (PADD 5) at $3.50 per gallon and the lowest average prices in the Rocky Mountains (PADD 4) at $2.88 per gallon (Figure 1). Gasoline prices fell in fourth-quarter 2012 as a result of modestly decreasing crude oil prices and narrowing gasoline crack spreads throughout the United States. Brent crude oil, the crude that U.S. product prices generally track, fell from a September 2012 average of $112.86 per barrel to an average of $109.49 per barrel in December 2012, a decrease of 8 cents per gallon. Most of that decline was in October, and Brent prices remained in a fairly well-defined range from late October through the end of the year. However, decreasing gasoline crack spreads contributed most of the late-2012 price decreases. Refineries have been running at high levels in response to strong distillate fuel crack spreads and low crude oil input costs in some regions, particularly the Midwest (PADD 2) and Rocky Mountains. The high refinery runs have led to increases in gasoline production, at a time when gasoline demand in the United States has been stagnant. This situation is reflected in high gasoline inventory levels. In four of the five PADDs, inventory levels are above their five-year average, PADD 1 being the only exception. As of January 18, U.S. total gasoline inventories stood at 233.3 million barrels, 8.3 million barrels (4 percent) above their five-year average level and 37.8 million barrels (19 percent) above early-October levels. Some of this inventory build is attributable to typical seasonal patterns. In anticipation of spring refinery maintenance season, market participants will often build inventories in the fourth quarter and early first quarter while demand is lower. However, the 37.8-million-barrel inventory build between the first week of October and mid-January was 17.3 million barrels above the five-year average. After declining during the fourth quarter of 2012, the wholesale gasoline market has not seen large price movements in recent weeks, and the changes that have occurred have been generally offsetting, with crack spreads increasing somewhat on the Gulf Coast and in Los Angeles, while remaining relatively stable in New York and decreasing further in Chicago. As a result, U.S. average retail gasoline prices have increased less than two cents per gallon since December 31, 2012, averaging $3.32 per gallon on January 21. As the major U.S. refining center, the Gulf Coast is a key market for gasoline and ships gasoline to regions throughout the country. While Gulf Coast gasoline markets have strengthened in January, they are still extremely weak. Crack spreads (measured here as the difference between the conventional gasoline spot price and the Brent crude oil spot price) in the region have been persistently negative since November. In January, they have thus far averaged -4 cents per gallon, an increase from the -13 cents per gallon they averaged in December. In December, crack spreads for conventional gasoline were also negative in Los Angeles but have since recovered, averaging 8 cents per gallon in January as several refineries have undergone maintenance on gasoline-producing units. New York crack spreads in January have been largely unchanged, up just a penny from the 12 cents per gallon they averaged in December. Chicago is currently the weakest market. Crack spreads in the area have been negative since November, but in January they have become even more negative, averaging -24 cents per gallon compared to -19 cents per gallon in December. Note that the Chicago crack spread is shown using Brent crude oil to be consistent with other regions; however, refineries in the Chicago market are more likely to have access to lower-priced West Texas Intermediate (WTI)-linked crudes, meaning refiners could be seeing small positive margins for gasoline. In this market structure, some refineries in the Midwest can access cheaper WTI-linked crudes and sell gasoline into a Brent-priced product market. This is because the Midwest has to attract some gasoline from the Gulf Coast. Similar to the situation in wholesale markets, stable retail gasoline prices at the national level mask regional variation. The most notable exception to the trend of stable prices has been in the Rocky Mountains. On November 5, Rocky Mountain prices were 12 cents per gallon higher than the U.S. average, but they fell to $2.88 per gallon by January 21, 44 cents per gallon lower than the U.S. average. While there are no observable spot prices for the Rocky Mountains, a similar dynamic is occurring there, where refinery runs are high because refineries in the Rockies seek to capture margins from the region's lower crude oil costs. Because the Rockies are a relatively isolated market with few significant pipeline connections to other U.S. markets, high levels of gasoline production can sometimes depress retail prices in the region compared to the U.S. average; a similar situation occurred last year. Looking forward, EIA forecasts gasoline prices to rise moderately through the first half of 2013. This increase is partly related to the switch to summer-grade gasoline during the spring that typically encourages widening crack spreads at that time of year. Increasing wholesale gasoline prices are expected to be partially offset by declining Brent prices. EIA forecasts U.S. average regular gasoline retail prices will peak in May at $3.59 per gallon. Regional variation is expected to continue, with West Coast prices expected to average $3.79 per gallon in May and peak a month later than the national average at $3.82 per gallon in June. On the low end, Gulf Coast prices are expected to return to their typical position as the lowest in the country, peaking at $3.45 per gallon in May. Gasoline and diesel fuel prices both up a penny The U.S. average retail price of regular gasoline increased one cent to $3.32 per gallon, down seven cents from last year at this time. The East Coast and Gulf Coast prices both decreased, while prices in all other regions increased. The East Coast price is $3.42 per gallon, down three cents from last week, and the Gulf Coast decreased a cent to $3.15 per gallon. The Midwest price increased seven cents to $3.22 per gallon, while the Rocky Mountain and West Coast prices both increased one cent, to $2.88 per gallon and $3.50 per gallon, respectively. The national average diesel fuel price increased a cent to $3.90 per gallon, five cents higher than last year at this time. Prices increased in all regions of the nation expect the East Coast, where the price decreased less than a penny to remain at $4.00 per gallon. The Rocky Mountain and West Coast prices both increased two cents, to $3.68 per gallon and $4.00 per gallon, respectively. The Midwest price is $3.85 per gallon and the Gulf Coast price is $3.83 per gallon, both an increase of one cent from last week. Propane inventories decline U.S. propane stocks fell 3.1 million barrels to end at 60.9 million barrels last week, 10.1 million barrels (20 percent) higher than a year ago. Midwest regional inventories dropped by 1.5 million barrels, while Gulf Coast inventories declined by 0.9 million barrels. Rocky Mountain/West Coast stocks dropped by 0.4 million barrels, and stocks in the East Coast region declined by 0.3 million barrels. Propylene non-fuel-use inventories represented 5.0 percent of total propane inventories. Residential heating fuel prices rise Residential heating oil prices increased during the period ending January 21, 2013. The average residential heating oil price increased by a penny to $3.98 per gallon, 5 cents per gallon higher than the same time last year. Wholesale heating oil prices increased by nearly 4 cents to just under $3.18 per gallon, 10 cents per gallon higher than last year at this time. The average residential propane price rose by 2 cents to almost $2.46 per gallon, 41 cents per gallon lower than the same period last year. Wholesale propane prices increased by 3 cents to nearly $0.93 per gallon for the week ending January 21, 2013, 31 cents per gallon lower than the January 23, 2012 price. eiaDOTgov/oog/info/twip/twip.asp</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359058342996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:12:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359065057264-34</Id><Topic><Title>Secret XOM Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>ashley.haggerty</Username><Timestamp>1359055637792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:27:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DANGEROUS SCAM VIRUS REPORTED !</Msg><Username>alphonite</Username><Timestamp>1359065057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:04:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359065370898-35</Id><Title>Trek back to $80 begins soon</Title><Msg>Likely right after the earnings are announced next week. Look at EPS trend - nothing to get excited about. XOM has no business trading at a PE of 12, not with declining earnings, even when buying back so many shares. Stock has had a good run, but it's not justified to be at/above this level.</Msg><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359065370898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:09:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359065416836-36</Id><Title>Where's the PARTY ? XOM back to the top !</Title><Msg>Came over here for some Apple Pie...Apple Fritters...and some upside down Apple Cake with some Apple Cider. cheers</Msg><Username>beat_the_market_everytime</Username><Timestamp>1359065416836</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:10:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359066880519-37</Id><Topic><Title>Secret XOM Info REVEALED!</Title><Username>ashley.haggerty</Username><Timestamp>1359055637792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 14:27:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow! surprisingly good one, thanks</Msg><Username>johnbussell595</Username><Timestamp>1359066880519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:34:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359079802156-38</Id><Topic><Title>Trek back to $80 begins soon</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359065370898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:09:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Relucantly,I concur. Todays build,the usual post earnings sell off,the likelyhood of 80 dollar oil in March,and the list goes on,all point to a 10 to 15 percent correction for entire oil patch,with Hess I'm afraid taking the hardest hit,followed bt XOM and probably see low 90s for CVX, I'm going to bailout tomorrow. The heck with the 50 cent Div Date coming up next week. We may see 75 dollar oil before memorial Day,and NG could drop lower also,given the glut.</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1359079802156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 21:10:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359080072628-39</Id><Title>OVERPRICED LOOK</Title><Msg>Market contraptions only work for so long untill a card is pulled then the house of card falls</Msg><Username>voxguitarplayer</Username><Timestamp>1359080072628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 21:14:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359082226560-40</Id><Topic><Title>Where's that arrogant little nut Maxwiz?</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359057863003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:04:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was last seen living in a cardboard box outside of Vegas. Lost everything on bingo.</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1359082226560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 21:50:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359085641138-41</Id><Title>Federal court won’t review decision that struck down EPA pollution rule</Title><Msg>Federal court won’t review decision that struck down EPA pollution rule By Ben Geman - 01/24/13 05:34 PM ET A federal court won’t reconsider a decision that nullified major Environmental Protection Agency rules to cut soot- and smog-forming power plant emissions that cross state lines. The U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit denied the Obama administration’s request for en banc, or full court, review of an August 2012 ruling that struck down the Cross-State Air Pollution Rule. A three-judge panel ruled 2-1 in August to toss out the rule, and on Thursday the court announced that a majority on a wider panel of judges voted against a full-court rehearing. “EPA is disappointed that the Court did not grant EPA's petition for rehearing. The agency is reviewing the decision and will determine any appropriate further course of action once the review is complete,” EPA said in a statement late Thursday afternoon. One environmentalist called the court's action a “terrible day for clean air in America.” “It is extremely disappointing that the court declined to reconsider a terrible judicial ruling that trampled on the court’s own legal precedent and marked a major setback for clean air for many years,” said John Walke, an attorney with the Natural Resources Defense Council, one of the groups that defended EPA’s rule in the litigation. The decision not to review the August ruling is a victory for several coal and power companies and allied industry groups, some states and GOP lawmakers. They alleged the rule would create economic burdens and force the closure of substantial numbers of coal-fired power plants. The rule has come under attack from House and Senate Republicans, but the Senate in 2011 turned back Sen. Rand Paul’s (R-Ky.) resolution to nullify it. The 2-1 decision in August instructs EPA to continue administering a less aggressive George W. Bush-era rule called the Clean Air Interstate Rule pending the creation of a "valid replacement." “EPA's Clean Air Interstate Rule remains in place and no immediate action from States or affected sources is expected at this time. EPA remains committed to working with States and the power sector to address pollution transport issues as required by the Clean Air Act,” EPA said Thursday. Walke said the court's action leaves EPA in a bind. “The original sharply divided 2-1 ruling leaves in its wake a muddle of conflicting court precedents for EPA to sort out, delaying and burdening the need to deliver clean air to tens of millions of Americans in the eastern half of the U.S.,” he said. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/279203-federal-court-wont-review-decision-that-struck-down-epa-pollution-rule</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359085641138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 22:47:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359086611921-42</Id><Title>Gov. McCrory embraces offshore wind power as energy alternative</Title><Msg>Gov. McCrory embraces offshore wind power as energy alternative Submitted by John_Frank on 2013-01-24 13:05 Republican Gov. Pat McCrory asserted his political independence on energy policy this week by throwing his support behind developing wind farms in North Carolina. Not just any wind farms, but offshore wind farms, which are considered among the most expensive forms of electricity, and generally denounced by conservatives and libertarians as a subsidy-dependent boondoggle. McCrory notified the feds that he endorses the Obama Administration's efforts to develop offshore wind power. The newly installed governor is making his pro-wind overture at a time that his Republican allies in the state legislature are making plans to roll back North Carolina's 2007 energy law that requires electric utilities to use wind power and other renewables. McCrory's letter, written Tuesday, to the U.S. Bureau of Ocean Energy Management is causing a stir among green energy advocates. "During the campaign he focused on offshore and onshore drilling," said Molly Diggins, the Sierra Club's North Carolina director. "So we are very encouraged that the governor recognizes that North Carolina has some of the best wind resources in the United States." The letter comes a month after the federal agency announced in December that about 1,900 square miles of Atlantic Ocean are available for offshore wind farm development. "This is an important step to develop North Carolian's world-class wind energy resources," McCrory wrote to the feds. "Development of commercial wind farms off North Carolina's coast could stimulate factory development in the state to provide the necessary equipment and bring jobs in that sector." McCrory's letter cited several major industrial companies with roots in the state that stand to benefit from wind power expansion. ABB makes cables for power transmission, Nucor makes steel plates used in turbine towers, and PGN makes fiberglass for the blades. The bureau is within the U.S. Department of Interior, which oversees ocean leasing for offshore wind farm development. In December the bureau said it would accept proposals this year from potential wind developers to gauge interest, the first step in offshore wind development. Along the East Coast other states are farther ahead in the process, with several projects approved. Getting one built, however, has proven more difficult, as the projects have run into public opposition and legal challenges. Those who support the renewable industry have said that if North Carolina takes an anti-subsidy stand on wind, solar and other renewables, other states will jump ahead in line and reap those benefits, such as federal support and economic development. McCrory campaigned as an advocate of energy drilling as well as fracking for shale gas, but his reputation is that of a practical moderate. His letter states that he believes in a comprehensive energy policy and is working on establishing a partnership with other states on offshore energy development. "Development of North Carolina's offshore wind energy resources is not just good for this state's economy, but it will continue to fulfill work toward an 'all of the above' strategy to move our nation toward greater energy independence." projectsDOTnewsobserverDOTcom/node/26820</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359086611921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:03:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359087505058-43</Id><Topic><Title>This Week In Petroleum</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359058342996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 15:12:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weekly U.S. Fuel Ethanol/Livestock Feed Production ethanolrfaDOTorg/pages/weekly-ethanol-feed-production</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359087505058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:18:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359087820802-44</Id><Title>Bills seek to reduce or remove ethanol from Maine gas</Title><Msg>Bills seek to reduce or remove ethanol from Maine gas Scott Thistle, State Politics Editor Maine | Thursday, January 24, 2013 AUGUSTA — A pair of bills introduced Thursday by state Rep. Jeff Timberlake, R-Turner, could have a significant impact on what goes into the gas tank of your car, lawnmower or snowblower. One of Timberlake's bills would cut the percentage of corn-derived ethanol in Maine gasoline from 10 percent to 5 percent. The other measure would allow the state to form a coalition with other New England states to create an ethanol-free gasoline market for Canadian petroleum-vendor Irving. Timberlake said Irving has offered to deliver ethanol-free gasoline to customers in New England if it has a minimum of three states willing to eliminate ethanol from the gas supply. New Hampshire has passed similar legislation, Timberlake said. He said he suspects that bill would be amended so gas stations would have the choice of offering either product, with or without ethanol. A farmer and the owner of a hardware store, Timberlake called ethanol one of the worst "government boondoggles" of his lifetime. He said the additive wreaks havoc with fuel lines in small engines, especially those that sit unused for any period of time. "It's really hard on engines and really affects our fuel mileage," Timberlake said. "Ethanol doesn't like small engines; it doesn't like fuel lines, chain saws, weed whackers, anything with fuel lines." He noted that federal farm subsidies paid to those growing corn for ethanol have contributed to a sharp increase in the price of corn and subsequently, in all products made with corn. Everything from feed grain for cattle and dairy cows to most of the food products consumed by humans have corn-based ingredients in them, Timberlake said. He said getting New England to move away from ethanol could be the first step in a national movement to remove the additive from American gasoline and cut the subsidies to Midwestern farmers growing corn for biofuel. sunjournalDOTcom/news/maine/2013/01/25/bills-seek-reduce-or-remove-ethanol-maine-gas/1311768</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359087820802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 23:23:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>