<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372056115632-1</Id><Title>Shorts coming again</Title><Msg>here we go</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1372056115632</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 02:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372080474881-2</Id><Title>Propelling Alternative Fuels Forward</Title><Msg>Propelling Alternative Fuels Forward Jun 21, 2013 By Brian Berk REDWOOD CITY, Calif. -- The U.S. fuels landscape is slowly changing. Although experts debate whether alternative fuels can truly make a dent in gasoline's dominance, there's no question ethanol, natural gas, diesel and electric are garnering more media headlines than ever before. Retailer Propel Fuels Inc. believes in the future of alternative fuels and is devoted to being a better steward to the earth -- something it says its E85 and biodiesel offerings can provide. The company offers both fuels at 38 fueling stations in California and Washington State. At 36 of the locations, Propel partners with existing gas station retailers to operate its renewable fuel pumps at their stores. These pumps, which Propel calls a “Clean Fuel Point,” reside under a single canopy and are branded with the Propel name. Propel pays rent to the station owners in return for the fuel sales from its pumps. Since Propel offers pay-at-the-pump technology, once a consumer turns on its pump to buy E85 or biodiesel, Propel -- not the convenience store operator -- accepts the payment and processes the transaction. All other fuel transactions at these 36 stores are handled by the c-store operator. "The thinking in America is changing. The vehicles we have are changing as well. Those two things together helped with the idea to form a different type of fuel company that's focused on bringing renewable fuels to the marketplace," Chris LaPlante, director of marketing for Propel, told CSNews Online. As for the other two locations, Propel owns them outright and has dubbed each a “Clean Mobility Center.” Located in Fresno and Fullerton, Calif., they offer free air for vehicle tires, as well as recycling capabilities at the fuel islands. These Clean Mobility Centers even have a Bike Station where cyclists and other riders can tighten or fill up their tires and grab a drink before venturing back on the road. These two locations do sel</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372080474881</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 09:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372080622343-3</Id><Title>US Credit Breaking Down Badly...</Title><Msg>It will require large cuts in the US Military budget and large tax increases just to cover the higher interest costs. Well over 10% of US GDP could easily go to serving the debt run up thanks to the monetary polices of Greenspan and Bernanke, and the wild spending of Bush and Obama. All the bad debt run up by the US housing agencies to subsidize US consumers spending should simply be added to the US government's total. US welfare spending is far too high and that should be cut as it has been across the bankrupt countries in Southern Europe. The US Veterans program is costing you more than China and Russia spend on their military combined - that's a legacy of Bush &amp; Obama's wars. That needs to be cut. The cuts in spending and higher taxes will hit US oil demand hard which is bad for Big Oil. Many countries around the world will probably just nationalize Big Oil's assets as the US military pulls back and retrenches.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372080622343</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 09:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372081100805-4</Id><Topic><Title>DARPA’s Black Credit Card – a slashing device aimed at XOM’s throat</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371570906914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Helmholtz Association has on display on its websites a glimpse of Germany's laser development programs.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372081100805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 09:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372081259767-5</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1372081259767</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 09:40:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372084173897-6</Id><Topic><Title>Forschungszentrum Jülich</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371959531379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 23:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I looked up this Westphalian research center and was very impressed. I doubt if the Republicans would allow us a similar scientific complex. I am sure the Russians and Chinese are keeping up with Germany.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1372084173897</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 10:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372084349644-7</Id><Title>War on Fossil Fuel Allocation - Bond Purchase</Title><Msg>10 Year German government bonds at 1.833% ytm, 8% allocation German t-bills and euros 2% allocation Residential Real Estate 90% allocation</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372084349644</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 10:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372085924711-8</Id><Title>Bernanke now looks like a complete IDIOT !!</Title><Msg>Right.. keep lowering rates and pumping $$ into the economy, then quickly switch gears and screw all the stockholders and pension funds. When there is no fundamental reason to increase rates.... BEN.... ugh.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1372085924711</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 10:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372087270359-9</Id><Topic><Title>War on Fossil Fuel Allocation - Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372084349644</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 10:32:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10 Year German government bonds at 1.816% ytm. Gain in price +0.15% 10% t-bills &amp; euro 90% real estate</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372087270359</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 11:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372087304967-10</Id><Topic><Title>War on Fossil Fuel Allocation - Bond Purchase</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372084349644</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 10:32:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>---SOLD-- 10 years</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372087304967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 11:21:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372087599063-11</Id><Topic><Title>Forschungszentrum Jülich</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371959531379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 23:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The website for the Helmholtz center in Berlin is good too. --- Helmholtz-Zentrum Berlin für Materialien und Energie, near Wannsee. Some German research groups such as Helmholtz work with the Russians, although not on all programs. The Republicans should be ashamed of themselves for what they have done to the USA.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372087599063</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 11:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372090427783-12</Id><Title>Get ready.....S&amp;P 500 next stop 1500 or 1400 by August.....</Title><Msg>on front page of Marketwatch!!! XOM under $85 next??? So, as we complete this a-wave over the next week or so, and begin a b-wave rally, I still maintain that we will likely only be setting up a larger crash-like scenario into August, wherein we will likely see the low 1500 region, and potentially drop to as low as the mid 1400 region before we can set up for one more rally taking us over 1700 by the first quarter of 2014.</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1372090427783</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 12:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372091945432-13</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA is THE strongest momentum stock on the market</Title><Username>momentum_train</Username><Timestamp>1370355813302</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Bloomberg video today talked about Google may buyout the fastest growing car company Tesla because Tesla has synergy with Google driverless car concept. The Fast and Furious Tesla has so much incredible potential.</Msg><Username>momentum_train</Username><Timestamp>1372091945432</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 12:39:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372103060417-14</Id><Title>TECO penny stock is running !</Title><Msg>TECO penny stock is running !</Msg><Username>texasholdempros</Username><Timestamp>1372103060417</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 15:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372103341222-15</Id><Title>Big FED POMO tomorrow</Title><Msg>Can they get the market up again like they have before on Tuesdays?</Msg><Username>tfmvance</Username><Timestamp>1372103341222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 15:49:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372105769082-16</Id><Title>Stock</Title><Msg>Again this stock crumps at the end of the day. Dow comes back 100 points and this stock just goes down. This stock has underperformed day after day literally ever since the present CEO took office over 5 years ago. There is little hope of improvement unless this company gets better management at the top but this does not seem likely.</Msg><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1372105769082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 16:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372110807827-17</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke now looks like a complete IDIOT !!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1372085924711</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 10:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least he won't be there much longer.</Msg><Username>gold_investing</Username><Timestamp>1372110807827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 17:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372111284905-18</Id><Title>Supreme Court will not take up E15 challenge</Title><Msg>Supreme Court will not take up E15 challenge By Erin Voegele | June 24, 2013 The U.S. Supreme Court has decided not take up the petroleum industry’s E15 appeal. The appeal, filed by the American Petroleum Institute, Grocery Manufacturers Association and a consortium of other organizations in February, challenged the D.C. Circuit Court’s decision to reject the its challenge of the partial waiver granted by the U.S. EPA to allow E15 use. The E15 waiver request was originally filed with the EPA by Growth Energy in March 2009. The EPA approved a partial wavier for the use of E15 in 2001 and newer light duty vehicles in January 2011. Since then, several legal challenges have been filed against the EPA by Big Oil and Big Food. The decision of the Supreme Court not to hear the appeal “marks the end of these baseless challenges,” said Growth Energy CEO Tom Buis. “The highest court in the land has spoken—they have unequivocally rejected the attempts of Big Oil and other opponents of ethanol to challenge the EPA’s sensible decision to permit the sale of E15,” Buis continued. “Now that the final word has been issued, I hope that oil companies will begin to work with biofuel producers to help bring new blends into the marketplace that allow for consumer choice and savings.” Bob Dinneen, president and CEO of the Renewable Fuels Association, noted that the Supreme Court’s action ends a long, drawn out effort by the petroleum industry to derail the commercialization of E15. “The uncertainty created by this lawsuit has chilled commercial activity that would provide American consumers more affordable choices at the pump,” he said. “With this decision, E15 can finally become a meaningful option for more Americans.” Brian Jennings, executive vice president of the American Coalition for Ethanol, pointed out that oil companies have spent more time and money trying to stop E15 in the courts then they have on complying with the renewable fuel standard (RFS).” During this time, ACE</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372111284905</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 18:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372114227136-19</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke now looks like a complete IDIOT !!</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1372085924711</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 10:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>except to put his friends into more power ahem.</Msg><Username>ryugo82</Username><Timestamp>1372114227136</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 18:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372122828910-20</Id><Title>cut 'n paste bluecheese............</Title><Msg>Really dude, do you think you have to constantly reprint the "news" ??? Get a life.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1372122828910</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 21:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>