<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373805843828-1</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jojomo owes a lot of money for his racist trash mouth.</Msg><Username>bluemax19</Username><Timestamp>1373805843828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373808914405-2</Id><Title>is Madoff Fool just a world war 2- like propaganda service? National Enquirer like illusion service?</Title><Msg>Perhaps should be sued. A farce like service this service has no business in the investment world.</Msg><Username>green_lightning11</Username><Timestamp>1373808914405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373809634775-3</Id><Title>Law &amp; Order &amp; FDI</Title><Msg>The Zimmerman verdict is a good indication that the white population of the South has steel in its spine, especially the ladies. Of course a strong man like Zimmerman has the right and duty to defend them with his strength in what way he knows how. This chivalrous principle was affirmed. So the trip to Hamburg to start buying houses is canceled. We go to Charleston a couple weeks sooner. Tomorrow I will buy $ to 12.5% allocation and put it in US t-bills. That money came out of the US anyway last week, from my Greenwich inheritance, and it shall go back to it, although not into the culturally Marxist Northern US – a label justly earned and affirmed by Obama’s recent policies. His outrageous conduct toward the EU and lying about it Merkel, is just another example of his character and motives. I think he's hostile to Germany and the EU (the German EU President called his behavior the act of an enemy) because we are white, and Germany is right-wing. That is the same reason he went after your "Tea Party" Theme: the Elf Kingdom of Germany, a land of purity, whiteness and science, will provide the technology to build a Solar Kingdom in the Southern United States. It’s just a fact the South gets more sun than Germany so our technology will work even better there. The South will become purer and much richer. As for the board,,, At best we have one black supremacist here and he’s probably living in a box now and unable to even speak. That’s very boring. The oil runts are few and barely speak. So in fall I will return, probably…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373809634775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373811631650-4</Id><Title>Alaska set for vote on oil-tax cut after lobby group submits petition</Title><Msg>Alaska set for vote on oil-tax cut after lobby group submits petition ANCHORAGE, Alaska | Sun Jul 14, 2013 4:53am EDT (Reuters) - Critics of an oil-industry tax cut handed a petition with 50,000 signatures to Alaska state officials on Saturday, more than enough to force a referendum that would overturn a new oil tax law. The bill, approved by the legislature three months ago, replaces taxes tracking oil prices with a cap on tax at 35 percent of net profits. Expectations for the new system were for a likely tax range from about 14 percent to about 20 percent. "This bill that they passed is against the interests of Alaska," Vic Fischer, a former state senator and one of two surviving authors of the Alaska constitution, told a group of about 50 banner-waving tax-cut opponents gathered outside government offices in Anchorage. Referendum supporters, organized in a group called "Vote Yes - Repeal the Giveaway", needed 30,169 signatures of registered voters - 10 percent of the total turnout in the last statewide election - to qualify their measure for the 2014 ballot. Leading oil producers in Alaska include BP Plc, ConocoPhillips and Exxon Mobil Corp. Governor Sean Parnell, sponsor of the new tax, argued that steep cuts in oil taxes were needed to lure industry investment away from North Dakota and other booming oil-producing areas. He dubbed the bill the "More Alaska Production Act". Opponents say the tax cuts are too steep, will cost the state $4.5 billion in lost revenues over five years, and do nothing to reverse North Slope production declines that they say are inevitable as the area's main oil fields age. reuters</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373811631650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:20:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373812790338-5</Id><Topic><Title>Reid confident he has votes to trigger nuclear option in Senate</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373742781187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 15:13:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@SenatorReid TWITTER Key fact about GOP obstruction: Pres. Obama has had 16 filibusters of his nominees, compared to 20 by all previous presidents. #EndGridlock ------------------------------------------------------------------------------ @SenatorReid TWITTER Unprecedented obstruction in the Senate: LBJ faced 1 filibuster as majority leader, I've had to deal with 420. #EndGridlock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373812790338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373844025356-6</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiots like you need to be locked away in an asylum. And take bluecheese with you ! Jerk !</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373844025356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:20:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373860736845-7</Id><Title>Very bullish for oil tonight. WTI oil moving on upwards. Gonna break old levels.</Title><Msg>Oil on a run.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1373860736845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>