<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365567357473-1</Id><Topic><Title>MTBE liability...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365527968207</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:19:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was not referring to US court action. US law is irrelevant outside the US, and there are other ways of getting justice than in courts. Read Iron Kingdom: the rise and downfall of Prussia 1600-1947...You will get some idea of what the government machine you are up against now is capable of... Prussia has been reborn in full force, and is directing the EU now with a similar zeal to Calvinism, under the guise of the Green movement and Christian Democrat Union...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365567357473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 00:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365579941196-2</Id><Topic><Title>ref_steve = ignorance personified</Title><Username>maxwizard68</Username><Timestamp>1364674108192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:08:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am just afraid where he might insert it.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1365579941196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 03:45:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365580058070-3</Id><Topic><Title>Socialism works---for those that don'e want work---for a time....</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365439509381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 12:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds like the commie coward #$%$ runt maxi pad.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1365580058070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 03:47:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365599633065-4</Id><Title>Goldman upgrrades XOM to BUY</Title><Msg>benziga</Msg><Username>xman34luv</Username><Timestamp>1365599633065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365601292244-5</Id><Title>13G FILED BANKS BUYS 33 MILLION SHARES OF -YTRV-- MONSTER MOVE</Title><Msg>HUGE UPSIDE</Msg><Username>tra.peace</Username><Timestamp>1365601292244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365601760221-6</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job.</Msg><Username>brandibuckley234</Username><Timestamp>1365601760221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365603682839-7</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing.</Msg><Username>hopephillips63</Username><Timestamp>1365603682839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 10:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365604535239-8</Id><Topic><Title>MTBE liability...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365527968207</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:19:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raising the dividend at this time would be a cocky move for the XOM CEO.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1365604535239</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 10:35:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365605136871-9</Id><Title>'Teen Mom' star Farrah Abraham: Yes I made a porno</Title><Msg>We have crossed a new frontier: the first official fake sex tape. Former "Teen Mom" star Farrah Abraham has admitted she was filmed having sex with adult-film star James Deen. Damn dude...what has America boiled down to??</Msg><Username>jack_kerouac</Username><Timestamp>1365605136871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 10:45:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365605303487-10</Id><Title>Start your DD on STBV ASAP</Title><Msg>Put STBV on your radar. It looks like it is about to run</Msg><Username>chart933</Username><Timestamp>1365605303487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 10:48:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365606046418-11</Id><Title>Is XOM acquiring GNE?</Title><Msg>Something to do with Israel rights GNE has.</Msg><Username>take_down_the_ask</Username><Timestamp>1365606046418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 11:00:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365608685380-12</Id><Title>STBV is the next big gainer</Title><Msg>Have you checked out the chart on STBV. It looks prime to make a huge run to atleast double its current price.</Msg><Username>gavincoleman234</Username><Timestamp>1365608685380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 11:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365608735641-13</Id><Topic><Title>'Teen Mom' star Farrah Abraham: Yes I made a porno</Title><Username>jack_kerouac</Username><Timestamp>1365605136871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 10:45:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>C-O-N-S-U-M-E-R-I-S-M Whether it is bidding a house worth 200,000 to 500,000, or selling a peek at the breast of a "celebrity" to sell movies or garbage to fill landfills it is the same mentality. I don't mind...Keep spending. The more wealth that is transferred to places like Germany and the Netherlands the better. We can take IT ALL...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365608735641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 11:45:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365609069929-14</Id><Title>Global recession off the table...</Title><Msg>.... Japan has joined the club of consumerism now, trying to mimic America. It's currency devaluation is just the start. What discipline they once possessed from their Samurai days is long gone. They do have a huge store of wealth to unload however... As societies (US, Japan, UK) dissipate their capital to keep up spending there is not going to be a recession, just a slow bleed lower in wealth and living standards for those places.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365609069929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 11:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365609127540-15</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>sanromanwiliam</Username><Timestamp>1361547275275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:34:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>raetab</Msg><Username>radisonfernando</Username><Timestamp>1365609127540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 11:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365611261282-16</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one!</Msg><Username>wood.jennifer</Username><Timestamp>1365611261282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 12:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365611299238-17</Id><Title>Universal Bioenergy Inc. (UBRG).................. Maybe Warren Buffet</Title><Msg>What do you people think??????????????????</Msg><Username>ntwk_2277</Username><Timestamp>1365611299238</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 12:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365612167792-18</Id><Topic><Title>'Teen Mom' star Farrah Abraham: Yes I made a porno</Title><Username>jack_kerouac</Username><Timestamp>1365605136871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 10:45:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whether it is bidding a house worth 200,000 to 500,000, or selling a peek at the breast of a "celebrity" to sell movies or garbage to fill landfills it is the same mentality. Good grief, do you think Obama will blame Bush for this too!</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1365612167792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 12:42:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365614842913-19</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome report!</Msg><Username>leroy_newman</Username><Timestamp>1365614842913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 13:27:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365617847183-20</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome report!</Msg><Username>daryl_kern</Username><Timestamp>1365617847183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 14:17:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365620868822-21</Id><Title>HEAVY DIP BUYING = GET YOURS TOO</Title><Msg>on the road to$100</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1365620868822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 15:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365621144762-22</Id><Title>after Texas stab massacre---WE NEED KNIFE CONTROL !!!</Title><Msg>PAY HEED</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365621144762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 15:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365628654918-23</Id><Topic><Title>after Texas stab massacre---WE NEED KNIFE CONTROL !!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365621144762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 15:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ban all knives including kitchen knives. Lets go fuked up Cali. freaks start screaming.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1365628654918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 17:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365631211642-24</Id><Title>★★★★SHORT ALL DOW STOCKS NOW ...easy JACK... Jack.</Title><Msg>short almost ANYTHING !!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1365631211642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 18:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365638922250-25</Id><Title>White House proposes royalty, permitting changes on energy development</Title><Msg>White House proposes royalty, permitting changes on energy development By Zack Colman - 04/10/13 01:11 PM ET The fiscal 2014 White House budget proposal released Wednesday seeks to raise Interior Department revenues through higher royalty rates on energy production and bolstering enforcement of lease terms. The Obama administration has put a renewed emphasis on the $2.5 billion it predicts the alterations would raise through 10 years. That’s because a portion of those funds would go toward President Obama’s plan for a research fund for alternative fuel and vehicle technology, which faces an uphill slog against Republican opposition. Interior Secretary Ken Salazar called the so-called "Energy Security Trust" a "critical proposal by the president." The trust would create a dedicated basic research fund designed to spur innovations to wean the transportation sector off oil. The administration wants $2 billion from offshore oil-and-gas revenues through the next decade for the trust, which Salazar said would be offset by other revenues. Those funds would come from the proposed permitting and royalty changes, already scheduled offshore leases and anticipated oil-and-gas price increases. Despite Salazar's promise of offsets, Republicans are unlikely to agree to let those funds go to the trust rather than the general Treasury, which is their current destination. The GOP would probably require the administration to expand federal oil-and-gas drilling as a condition for approving the trust. But the White House has said it won't do that, even as a compromise to secure approval for the trust. The budget reiterated that by touting the president’s five-year offshore leasing plan, which the administration says makes 75 percent of recoverable resources available for drilling. Overall, Interior’s budget would hit $11.7 billion, a 4 percent... thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/292987-white-house-proposes-raising-fees-on-federal-energy-production</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365638922250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 20:08:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365639530236-26</Id><Topic><Title>after Texas stab massacre---WE NEED KNIFE CONTROL !!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365621144762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 15:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what you need is sum MEAT... HOT DOG LOVER.. YEP WEINERS</Msg><Username>max_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1365639530236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 20:18:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365639857090-27</Id><Title>Arkansas Fish Kill Fish Kill Arkansas Fish Kill</Title><Msg>Yummy yummy Arkansas oil spill</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1365639857090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 20:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365639976849-28</Id><Title>Last turbine comes online at London Array offshore wind farm</Title><Msg>Last turbine comes online at London Array offshore wind farm Green energy news – by GreenWise staff 10th April 2013 London Array, the world’s largest offshore wind turbine, is now fully operational with the last of the 175 turbines at the Thames Estuary site, now generating clean electricity. Power from the final turbine of phase one of the London Array came online on Tuesday and was described by the UK wind industry as "a monumental feat of green engineering". Phase one of London Array covers a 90 km2 area and has a combined capacity of 630 megawatts (MW), enough to power half a million homes. It is the culmination of more than two years of offshore construction work by the joint owners of the farm, #$%$ Energy, E.ON and Masdar. It is claimed it will reduce carbon dioxide emissions by over 900,000 tonnes a year. "Britain has a real achievement to celebrate here – the largest operational offshore wind farm in the world is generating clean electricity for British homes and businesses," RenewableUK’s Chief Executive, Maria McCaffery, said. Construction on the London Array began in July 2009 with the start of the erection of the onshore substation at Cleve Hill. Offshore construction started in March 2011, when the first foundations of the project were installed. The first turbine was installed in January 2012 and the final turbine was installed in December last year. "This is the final major milestone of the construction phase and the culmination of more than two years' offshore construction work which began in March 2011 with the installation of the first foundation," London Array project director Richard Rigg said. Leading offshore wind development The London Array announcement follows the news that the final turbine was installed at Lincs 75 turbine-strong offshore wind farm on March 31. The 270MW project off the coast of... greenwisebusinessDOTcoDOTuk/news/last-turbine-comes-online-at-london-array-offshore-wind-farm-3891DOTaspx</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365639976849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 20:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365641596311-29</Id><Title>Breakthrough In Microalgae Oil Production, Accelerated Ability To Produce Variety Of Different Oils</Title><Msg>April 10, 2013 Nathan A breakthrough in microalgae oil production has been made by researchers at Solazyme. The new technology accelerates the ability of microalgae to produce a variety of different types of renewable oils in the same location; for use in fuels, food, personal-care products, or in the chemical industry. The improvements are possible simply as a result of utilizing standard industrial fermentation (as opposed to open ponds) in combination with Solazyme’s new patented microalgae strains. We’ve covered the continuing developments of Solazyme’s biotechnology a lot here on CleanTechnica, from its pioneering 2011 100% biofuel-powered US passenger jetliner flight, to the opening of its first commercial scale algae bio refinery in Peoria last year (and a lot in between). It seems to be continuing its growth at an impressive pace — it’ll be interesting to see what comes next. “Solazyme’s breakthrough biotechnology platform unlocks the power of microalgae, achieving over 80% oil within each individual cell at commercial scale while changing the triglyceride oil paradigm by their ability to tailor the oil profiles by carbon chain and saturation,” a press release from the American Chemical Society notes. “The ability to produce multiple oils in a matter of days out of one plant location using standard industrial fermentation is a game-changer.” “For the first time in history, we have unlocked the ability to completely design and tailor oils,” says Walter Rakitsky, Ph.D and employee of Solazyme. “This breakthrough allows us to create oils optimized for everything from high-performance jet and diesel fuel to renewable chemicals to skin-care products and heart-healthy food oils. These oils could replace or enhance the properties of oils derived from the world’s three dominant sources: petroleum, plants and animals.” cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/04/10/breakthrough-in-microalgae-oil-production-accelerated-ability-to-produce-a-variety-of-different-oils/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365641596311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 20:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365642486607-30</Id><Title>Google Satellite Maps Shows Oil Spill Spreading Throughout Arkansas</Title><Msg>XOM has anti-US Constitution news blackout.</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1365642486607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 21:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365645087194-31</Id><Topic><Title>HEAVY DIP BUYING = GET YOURS TOO</Title><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1365620868822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 15:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No rush. I think it has finally gotten thru to even the most obtuse investor how badly the XOM board treats its shareholders. This has been a lousy investment under Tillerson and there's no hurry to get in...maybe a hurry to get out.</Msg><Username>tsobie</Username><Timestamp>1365645087194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 21:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365648803720-32</Id><Topic><Title>Outlook</Title><Username>dlavine78</Username><Timestamp>1365549976605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree 100%. Tillerson is THE problem here. They need to throw the bum out, stop the share buybacks, and lift the dividend immediately by 40%. See published analysis today (4-10-13): Shares of ExxonMobil (NYSE: XOM ) lost 0.1% of their value today, after a Morgan Stanley analyst changed the stock's rating and gave investors a better option. Exxon was cut from an "equal weight" rating to an "underweight" rating this morning, in addition to having its target price cut from $90 per share to only $85. The new target price would indicate that shares are worth less than their current price of $88.68. Morgan Stanley also stated that Exxon competitor and fellow Dow component Chevron(NYSE: CVX ) will outperform Exxon by 55% over the next five years. Furthermore, Morgan Stanley slapped a price target of $135 per share on Chevron. Reports have cited that higher production growth and improving returns will give Chevron an advantage in the long run.</Msg><Username>perho</Username><Timestamp>1365648803720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 22:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>