<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370599513208-1</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese is a walking encyclopedia.....</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370133089920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and u r god, u r a POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1370599513208</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 06:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370599583665-2</Id><Topic><Title>If you place bluecheese on ignore...........</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370481884639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:24:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clown clown max is a commie rat.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1370599583665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 06:06:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370609852551-3</Id><Title>Wow, heard there is a massive promo coming to MISM</Title><Msg>All of the recent developments in MISM make me think that a big move is about to happen</Msg><Username>gfry679</Username><Timestamp>1370609852551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 08:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370614637252-4</Id><Title>U.S. orders new safety upgrades at nuclear plants</Title><Msg>U.S. orders new safety upgrades at nuclear plants</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370614637252</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370614795162-5</Id><Title>......................................................Time To Get Out? What The Cult Of Bernanke Is Telling Us</Title><Msg>It’s always a bit amusing to meet an investor making money in the markets right now who actually thinks it’s because he’s smarter than everyone else. Everyone knows the Fed’s quantitative easing program calls for them to buy $85 billion worth of bonds and mortgage backed securities each and every month. And the connection to market performance is clear. To put this figure in perspective, $85 billion is DOUBLE the annual profits of Exxon Mobil. It’s also equivalent to ALL the money Chinese tourists spent overseas on holidays last year. It’s also just over $1 trillion annually… which coincidentally is the headline budget deficit that the US federal government squanders each year. With so much money being pumped into the market, stock investors should all have busts of Ben Bernanke next to their trading screens. With few exceptions, analysis, street smarts, and fundamentals have practically been thrown out the window in favor of a tiny banking elite’s control over the PRINT button. However, it now looks to me as though we may have entered a new phase. Institutional investors are beginning to look ahead and worry what will happen when that money is no longer being pumped into the market. It may be 6 months away. It may be 18 months away. Only Ben Bernanke knows. But, while the markets have short memories looking back, they do tend to discount future events 12-18 months ahead of time. And that’s beginning to happen. We’re already seeing many stock markets coming off their highs. Plus most emerging market currencies have been struggling lately. Even the Australian dollar, New Zealand dollar, and Canadian dollar have been weak. All of this indicates that the leveraged investing herd seems to be squaring positions, going to cash, and paying back some of the USD-denominated debt they’ve borrowed. So far it’s all been an orderly move lower. And herein lies the trouble. Few investors are spooked right now because there is so much calm in the markets. But that calm</Msg><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370614795162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:19:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370614858789-6</Id><Topic><Title>......................................................Time To Get Out? What The Cult Of Bernanke Is Telling Us</Title><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370614795162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:19:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Few investors are spooked right now because there is so much calm in the markets. But that calm can quickly turn into anxiety, which can quickly turn into all-out panic. It’s taken years (since 2008) to print so much money. This means that a market panic will unwind years’ worth of liquidity in a matter of weeks. It’s a financial tsunami that no investor should underestimate.</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370614858789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:20:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370614900222-7</Id><Topic><Title>......................................................Time To Get Out? What The Cult Of Bernanke Is Telling Us</Title><Username>techanalyst_trader</Username><Timestamp>1370614795162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:19:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice article thanks!!!</Msg><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1370614900222</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370615248257-8</Id><Title>Lower corn prices could boost E85 use, infrastructure still short</Title><Msg>Susanne Retka Schill | June 06, 2013 Starting with the question, “What price of corn will make E85 competitive?” University of Illinois economists Scott Irwin and Darrel Good examined the breakeven prices of E85, ethanol and corn. While $7 corn at current retail gasoline prices doesn’t favor E85 expansion, if the 2013 corn crop comes through, they write, “it is feasible that corn prices could decline below the breakeven price for E85 if retail gasoline prices remain near current levels. If so, expanding E85 consumption could help expand the ethanol blend wall and add to the demand for corn to be processed into ethanol.” The two agriculture economists have been publishing an ongoing series of FarmDocDaily posts examining multiple issues around the renewable fuels standard. In this post they look closely at the retail price of gasoline, price variations and the relative value of E85. “While the logic for an energy breakeven level of E85 pricing is straightforward, there is uncertainty about whether consumers will in fact require a higher or lower discount to incentivize greater use of E85,” they add. The economic model factors in the wholesale-retail spread, the wholesale price of ethanol at Chicago need for a breakeven wholesale price of E85, plus the breakeven price of corn at an ethanol plant. “For a change of 10 cents per gallon in the retail price of gasoline, then, the breakeven price of corn changes by 26.5 cents per bushel.” On June 3, the average retail price of gasoline on June 3 was $3.88 per gallon, implying a breakeven price of corn of $5.24 per bushel. “In other words, if the price of corn is $5.24 and the pump price of gasoline is $3.88 then E85 can be priced at its energy equivalent value and everyone from ethanol producers to gasoline consumers just breaks even.” While a drop in corn prices from a good corn crop would favor more E85 ethanolproducerDOTcom/articles/9924/lower-corn-prices-could-boost-e85-use-infrastructure-still-short</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370615248257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370615679908-9</Id><Topic><Title>Best way to invest in Advanced Energy...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361540776959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 08:46:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New allocation residential real estate – 89%: Berlin – 20% (upper primary, and middle rental) all other middle: Stuttgart – 25% München – 14% Frankfurt am Main - 20% Ruhrgebiet: Duisburg &amp; Essen – 5% Ludwigshafen am Rhine – 5% Bonds &amp; deposits – 11% 3 month German government treasury bills @0.02% – 10% euro deposit – 1%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1370615679908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:34:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370615752107-10</Id><Topic><Title>Best way to invest in Advanced Energy...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361540776959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 08:46:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1370615752107</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370616006040-11</Id><Title>United planes to fly on advanced biofuel</Title><Msg>United planes to fly on advanced biofuel Jennifer A. Dlouhy Jun 04 at 3:11 pm United Airlines on Tuesday announced it has committed to buy at least 15 million gallons of cleaner-burning renewable jet fuel from a Los Angeles-based refinery, marking a potentially major breakthrough in the commercial aviation industry’s quest to pare carbon dioxide emissions. United is planning to use the advanced biofuel on flights out of its Los Angeles hub beginning next year. Under the deal, AltAir Fuels will retrofit idled portions of a Los Angeles petroleum refinery to produce the low-carbon renewable jet fuel and other products from non-edible natural oils and agricultural wastes. Once the project goes online, it is expected to be the first refinery in the nation capable of in-line production of both diesel and drop-in replacements for petroleum-based jet fuels. “This project demonstrates the practical efficiencies these fuels allow by fully integrating into an operating petroleum refinery,” said AltAir’s president Bryan Sherbacow in a statement. “The industry is delivering on the promise of commercial production of advanced biofuels that move beyond additives, like ethanol and biodiesel, to drop-in replacement low-carbon fuels.” Study: Climate change trend likely to thwart biofuel goals AltAir will produce the biofuel using technology developed by Honeywell UOP. The product is engineered to provide the same performance as conventional, petroleum-based jet fuel, allowing it to be dropped in to existing equipment and used by factory-standard engines without modifications. According to United, the renewable jet fuel supplied by AltAir is expected to slash greenhouse gas emissions in half over its entire lifecycle, from production to combustion. Jimmy Samartzis, United’s managing director for global environmental affairs and sustainability said the agreement underscores the company’s http://blog.sfgate.com/energy/2013/06/04/united-planes-to-fly-on-advanced-biofuel-2/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370616006040</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370616094229-12</Id><Title>New Allocations, War on Fossil Fuels Investments</Title><Msg>Berlin – 20% (upper primary, and middle rental) all other middle class rental: Stuttgart – 25% München – 14% Frankfurt am Main - 20% Ruhrgebiet: Duisburg &amp; Essen – 5% Ludwigshafen am Rhine – 5% Bonds &amp; deposits – 11% 3 month German government treasury bills @0% – 10% euro deposit – 1%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1370616094229</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 10:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370617728658-13</Id><Title>If you haven’t checked out MISM what are you waiting for</Title><Msg>I just found out that MISM is about to be promoted by some of the biggest IR groups. Grabbing some now</Msg><Username>alexander.beck495</Username><Timestamp>1370617728658</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370619566490-14</Id><Title>ZAZA Insiders Buying Volume Up HOT New Energy Stock</Title><Msg>This is going to the highs on solid earnings</Msg><Username>hitstocks</Username><Timestamp>1370619566490</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 11:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370628525232-15</Id><Title>New E85 blender pump location opens in Nebraska</Title><Msg>New E85 blender pump location opens in Nebraska By Nebraska Ethanol Board, Nebraska Corn Board June 07, 2013 New flex fuel pumps are now open in David City, Neb., at the RB’s Corner Stop on Highway 15. This is the 83rd retail location with E85/flex fuel pumps that offer ethanol blended fuels such as E85 for flex fuel vehicles. RB’s Corner Stop is offering E10, E20, E30, and E85. There is an ethanol blend for everyone. These pumps were paid for in part by a grant provided by the Nebraska Corn Board. The location is supporting the local economy by offering a homegrown, locally produced fuel, ethanol. “We have been working hard to get flex fuel pumps across Nebraska,” said Kim Clark director of biofuels development for the Nebraska Corn Board. “Over the last year we have doubled the number of locations that offer E85 and other ethanol blended fuels.” Todd Sneller, administrator of the Nebraska Ethanol Board said, “Ethanol saves motorist money at the pump. Last year, ethanol saved Americans in the Midwest over $1.60 per gallon. A consumer’s choice and ethanol availability are high on consumer’s priority list with today’s gas prices.” One in 10 Nebraska motorists currently own a flexible fuel vehicle which can run on any blend of ethanol and gasoline, up to E85, and many don’t even know it. ethanolproducerDOTcom/articles/9926/new-e85-blender-pump-location-opens-in-nebraska</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370628525232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370643520739-16</Id><Title>Edison will shut down the San Onofre nuclear plant for good VIDEO</Title><Msg>Joseph Serna and Abby Sewell June 7, 2013, 7:11 a.m. Southern California Edison announced Friday it would shut down the troubled San Onofre nuclear power plant. The move comes 17 months after the San Onofre plant was closed because of problems in steam generator systems. The plant powered about 1.4 million households in Southern California before the outage. Until now, Edison had vowed to restart the plant. But the company released a statement Friday saying it would stop the process to fire up the plant. Q&amp;A: Why is it closing and what will it cost? "We have concluded that the continuing uncertainty about when or if [the plant] might return to service was not good for our customers, our investors, or the need to plan for our region’s long-term electricity needs," said Ted Craver, chairman and chief executive of Edison International, parent company of SCE. SCE President Ron Litzinger said in a statement: "Looking ahead, we think that our decision to retire the units will eliminate uncertainty and facilitate orderly planning for California’s energy future.” In February, Edison estimated the closure had cost the company $400 million. FROM THE ARCHIVES: San Onofre Nuclear Generating station San Onofre was shuttered after a tube in the plant's replacement steam generator system leaked a small amount of radioactive steam on Jan. 31, 2012. Eight other tubes in the same reactor unit later failed pressure tests, an unprecedented number in the industry, and thousands more tubes in both of the plant's units showed signs of wear. The wear was blamed on tube vibration caused by excessively dry and high-velocity steam and inadequate support structures, particularly in one of the plant's two units. Tube vibration and wear has been a problem at other plants, but the specific type of vibration at San Onofre had not been experienced in the industry. latimesDOTcom/local/lanow/la-me-ln-edison-closing-san-onofre-nuclear-plant-20130607,0,7920425DOTstory</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370643520739</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 18:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>