<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368594822654-1</Id><Title>Is US Poised to Back Kurdish Independence From Iraq?</Title><Msg>Oil Deals Could Be Strong Incentive for Administration Shift by Jason Ditz, May 14, 2013 The US military may have withdrawn from Iraq, but the biggest US policy decision on the nation may be yet to come, in the form of a potential administration endorsement for Kurdish secession. Dispute between the increasingly unpopular Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki and the Kurdistan Regional Government (KRG) have gotten ever closer to outright military conflict. Kurdish leaders have suggested the only reason Maliki is still buying arms from the US is because he envisions attacking Kurdistan and eliminating its semi-autonomous status, and needs better gear to stand up to the KRG’s Peshmearga fighters. The US has always supported Kurdistan, to a point. The shift to openly backing secession would be a big one, but the financial incentives for such a shirt could be significant, with the central government and KRG fighting over oil revenue, and the KRG’s deals increasingly benefiting US corporations at the expense of Iraqi contracts. That may seem cynical but is not out of keeping with historical US policy in the region, which has centered around oil. Maliki’s role as an ally of Iran might provide yet another excuse to cut him loose in favor of an independent Kurdistan and lucrative deals for Exxon-Mobil. The interventionist American Enterprise Institute has also issued a policy paper suggesting they believe the time for such a shift is nearing, saying that a successful transition of power after the next Kurdish elections could be presented as proof the Kurds “deserve” independence in the estimation of the US. The prime mover against Kurdish independence has always been Turkey, but with peace talks progressing with the PKK, that obstacle may well be removed soon as well, setting the stage for the US jumping on board the break-up of Iraq after spending massive amounts of money and antiwarDOTcom/2013/05/14/is-us-poised-to-back-kurdish-independence-from-iraq/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368594822654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 01:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368605783915-2</Id><Topic><Title>When will Exxon up dividend?</Title><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1368552012073</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:20:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whipde #$%$ doo.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1368605783915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 04:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368611317858-3</Id><Topic><Title>buybacks</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1368566441861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:20:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does 2018 become the magic number?</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1368611317858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 05:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368623934472-4</Id><Title>Paper: drilling waste setting off radiation alarms</Title><Msg>Paper: drilling waste setting off radiation alarms Posted on May 15, 2013 at 6:42 am by Associated Press in Natural gas PITTSBURGH — Gas drilling waste is setting off more radiation alarms at Pennsylvania landfills. The Pittsburgh Tribune-Review reports that the alarms went off 1,325 times in 2012, with more than 1,000 of those from oil and gas waste, according to Department of Environmental Protection data. DEP spokesman Kevin Sunday tells the paper that all the data so far indicates that public health is protected. After an alarm workers flag the waste for special treatment. The state began requiring radiation monitors at landfills in 2002 because of medical waste. But oil and gas drilling brings up mineral fragments containing naturally occurring radiation. DEP says past research has shown problems are unlikely. DEP started a review in January to examine radioactivity in drilling waste and on all the equipment that handles it. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/15/paper-drilling-waste-setting-off-radiation-alarms/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368623934472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:18:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368624444757-5</Id><Title>Obama’s failed second term</Title><Msg>Already he’s embroiled in scandals. The Fed pumped stock and bond market is enriching a small sliver of the US population (until it collapses) and doing nothing for the economy. His healthcare policy does nothing to deal with the Medicare problem which will destroy the US economy if it is not resolved – and it won’t be resolved. People with the means to pay more taxes will renounce their citizenship to avoid them, and those who cannot find a way out will see their living standards crushed under the rollers of the IRS. A GOP win in 2014 will cap the failure, and ensure two more years of no leadership in what is fast becoming a failed state - temporarily propped up borrowing, speculation, and delusions... Meanwhile 50% of children born in the USA are coming from non-white groups, groups with negligible net wealth or negative net assets, and no record of achievement in education, and the sciences. The US government does not have programs to pay for University either, even if they knew how to reach that level and most of them do not know how anyway. The US government is certainly counting on such people to carry the US economy forward, however, making all sort so projections of labor productivity for them assuming they will behave as white Americans born in the 1950s, 1960s, 1970s, 1980s …etc. That is not going to happen…. The US does not exist in isolation either. While it consistently fails to educate scientists, and falls behind in technology (except war technology) other countries continue ahead... The US automobile industry is an abject failure having long since been conquered by German and Japanese companies. The US energy industry is targeted for destruction, as is petrochemicals. Electronics and other fields will be dominated by German and Chinese companies.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368624444757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:27:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368624522150-6</Id><Title>... could “directly threaten the centralised utility model”</Title><Msg>... solar PV and battery storage were two technologies (along with fuel cells and storage from electric vehicles) that could “directly threaten the centralised utility model” ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368624522150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368625951385-7</Id><Topic><Title>... could “directly threaten the centralised utility model”</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368624522150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:28:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... can now claim bragging rights as being the second city in California where all newly built homes — commercial buildings and major residential remodels/additions, too — must be equipped with solar systems ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368625951385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 09:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368626983273-8</Id><Title>Clinton machine taking down Obama?</Title><Msg>Those two never liked each other. Obama scandals are becoming hard to hide from</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1368626983273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368629787966-9</Id><Title>The World Order of the Future</Title><Msg>I foresee an alliance between Germanic Europe, Russia, and possibly China. Russia is becoming very elitist in its approach to education. They are of course very white and their nationalism is strong. They know what it means to be Russian, and they want that to mean European as the Tsars and their nobility did. Putin makes many friendly visits to Europe these days. Egalitarianism is not part of their program now. The foreign cancer brought in by Lenin and the Bolsheviks is gone. China is becoming an elitist, scientific country too. They are copying German methods of education now which is why they are doing so well, having disposed of their egalitarian Marxist educational system in the 1980s. The Chinese really love WHITE too. Their elite women try as best they can to be as white as any German or Nordic person. So with common interests and beliefs it is likely that some sort of alliance takes shape. The Beijing-Berlin maglev railroad with stops in Russia would be a useful symbol project...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368629787966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:56:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368630399907-10</Id><Title>☛☛☛HEY NUTJOBs ...just KEEP ON BUYING !! Bwhahahahahaha!</Title><Msg>shorties dream......</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1368630399907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 11:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368636072749-11</Id><Topic><Title>The World Order of the Future</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368629787966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I foresee you in a padded cell. Enjoy.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368636072749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368636348856-12</Id><Title>Wind farms get pass on eagle deaths</Title><Msg>Obama administration allows wind farms to kill eagles, birds, despite federal laws AP story which yahoo will not let me quote - typical.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368636348856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 12:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368641128718-13</Id><Title>XOM would wind up the company to look at this year.</Title><Msg>We simply wanted to share this website with everybody under the sun. This service has an article with detailed info of hot small cap stocks. moourlDotcom/b59wb [Use . AND Remove Dot]</Msg><Username>garciaalvarado423</Username><Timestamp>1368641128718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368641506112-14</Id><Title>Sequester will cut oil and gas drilling leases, Democrats say</Title><Msg>May 15, 2013 11:04 am by Jennifer A. Dlouhy The across-the-board cuts to federal spending will translate to fewer oil and gas drilling leases — and some $150 million in lost government revenue — congressional Democrats warned Wednesday. In a new report on the effects of the so-called sequester budget cut, Democrats on the House Appropriations Committee, say the oil and gas industry is poised to take a big hit. “Instead of saving money, the sequester is costing Americans money and job opportunities, as the Bureau of Land Management is forced to slow down approval of oil and gas drilling permits and cancel lease sales to meet the (required) spending reductions,” the report says. The conclusion dovetails with other analyses and dire warnings from Obama administration officials who say the broad $85 billion cut gives agencies relatively little flexibility to target spending to the most pressing needs. Drawing on her more than three decades of private sector experience, Interior Secretary Sally Jewell has been vocal in criticizing the sequester as unwise. “We would never do something like the sequester in business,” said Jewell, the former chief executive of Recreational Equipment Inc., while at the Offshore Technology Conference in Houston last week. “It is a really dumb way to run a budget because it requires line-by-line item cuts.” When it comes to the Interior Department’s management of oil and gas development on public lands and waters, the effects will be more acute onshore. The fees tied to offshore energy development are helping to insulate activity tied on the outer continental shelf, officials have said. Still, Jewell said it’s a difficult balancing act. “When you’ve got (government workers) trying to keep up with demand for permits and you’re requiring that those folks work less hours, you have to adjust, and you have no choice,” Jewell said. “You fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/15/sequester-will-slash-oil-and-gas-drilling-leases-democrats-say/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368641506112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368641949706-15</Id><Title>Oil CEO: Humans are involved with climate change</Title><Msg>May 15, 2013 at 1:00 am by Zain Shauk The leader of one of the world’s largest energy companies said this week that humans are accelerating climate change and the global community should take action to address the problem. While speaking with reporters following the annual shareholders meeting of ConocoPhillips, the world’s largest independent oil company, its CEO said there was no doubting the role of humans in warming the planet. “As a company we recognize the impact that humans are having on the environment and that CO2 is having an impact on what’s happening in the climate,” ConocoPhillips CEO Ryan Lance said. The company’s stance is similar to that of other companies, like Exxon Mobil Corp., though other executives have so far been less explicit about the role of humans in causing a warming of the global climate. Exxon Mobil has acknowledged that the climate is changing and has encouraged action to address the problem, even favoring a carbon tax over cap-and-trade efforts when singling out potential policy changes to reduce greenhouse gas emissions. “If governments consider the adoption of regulatory frameworks (to address climate change), we believe a well-designed, revenue-neutral carbon tax mechanism provides a cost-effective policy approach,” according to a statement on Exxon Mobil’s website. Climate: Obama talks tough and proposes ‘drilling for clean energy’ program Lance was asked about climate change following reports over the weekend that a major climate change measure had “passed a long-feared milestone,” according to the New York Times. As with many other energy giants, he said ConocoPhillips is taking action to reduce its effects on the climate. “We know there is a lot of disagreement on both sides of that argument, but we think it’s the smart thing to do for the company to recognize that there is an impact and we’re trying to do the right things within... fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/15/no-doubts-on-need-to-act-on-climate-change/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368641949706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368642060453-16</Id><Topic><Title>XOM would wind up the company to look at this year.</Title><Username>garciaalvarado423</Username><Timestamp>1368641128718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:05:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is so flat Im feeling gidddy</Msg><Username>hayesrichard69</Username><Timestamp>1368642060453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368642516468-17</Id><Topic><Title>XOM would wind up the company to look at this year.</Title><Username>garciaalvarado423</Username><Timestamp>1368641128718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:05:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tight top</Msg><Username>marionmartin3</Username><Timestamp>1368642516468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368643455096-18</Id><Title>Logos Technologies Closer to Commercial Cellulosic Ethanol Biofuel</Title><Msg>May 15, 2013 Biofuel company Logos Technologies and partner Edeniq have completed more than 1,000 hours of continuous operation at their corn-to-cellulosic migration (CCM) pilot plant in Visalia, Calif., the companies say. Employing Edeniq’s proprietary technology, the plant converts 1 metric ton per day of non-food corn stover into ethanol. Performed on a commercial scale, this conversion process would result in a domestically produced, renewable and competitively priced biofuel with low greenhouse gas emissions and a small carbon footprint, according to the companies. Supported by funds from the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act of 2009 and the Department of Energy’s BioEnergy Technology Office, Logos Technologies managed the design, construction and 1,000-hour demonstration of the CCM plant. Located at Edeniq’s headquarters, the facility first started producing ethanol in March 2012. Operations include mechanical pretreatment, saccharification, fermentation, distillation, liquids-solids separation and integrated process water recycling. Edeniq contributed technology including the Cellunator for mechanical pretreatment and advanced saccharification and fermentation biochemistry. The Cellunator technology produces sugars by milling corn and other plant materials into “right-sized” particles of feedstock that can be more easily converted. The companies say they plan to commercialize the technology demonstrated at the CCM plant and develop other concepts with the goal of initiating large-scale cellulosic facilities. Cellulosic ethanol is on track be cost competitive with corn-based ethanol by 2016, a development that could drive the fuel’s production, according to an industry survey published in March, conducted by Bloomberg New Energy Finance. Cellulosic ethanol cost 94 cents a liter to produce in 2012, about 40 percent more ... environmentalleaderDOTcom/2013/05/15/logos-technologies-closer-to-commercial-cellulosic-ethanol-biofuel/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368643455096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368648451002-19</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester will cut oil and gas drilling leases, Democrats say</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368641506112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 14:11:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will have a hard time slowing them down any more than Obamao has already ordered them to.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368648451002</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 16:07:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368652826899-20</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton machine taking down Obama?</Title><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1368626983273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:09:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea lots of people died under clintons.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1368652826899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:20:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368654043213-21</Id><Title>Commentary: US NGLs to crowd OPEC Asian exports</Title><Msg>May 15, 2013 at 2:40 pm by Amy Myers Jaffe Out in the Middle East, more than just Qatar is starting to feel the pinch of the US shale revolution. Saudi Arabia will find new competition for its liquefied petroleum gas (LPG) and other feedstock exports from U.S. exports of NGLs. The trend is likely to accelerate in the next few years, according to new studies. Tremendous market changes in petrochemical feedstock prices and trade flows are on the horizon due to the emerging tight oil play in the United States. The United States is poised to become a larger exporter of NGLs to Asia, with large ramifications for Middle East export refining and petrochemical businesses. Natural gas liquids (NGLs) represented nearly half of “oil” liquids production from US shale formations in 2012, according to a new study. A new report from the Baker Institute by author Alan Troner concludes that NGL production could soon hit a near-term limit of how much condensate can be blended into localized light crude streams or shipped to Canada to facilitate oil sands shipments, leaving a possible “NGL hell” where price differentials could collapse significantly. Troner argues in his study that the growing U.S. NGL surplus, which might extend out at least to 2018, could become the ying to Asia’s demand yang, potentially changing the previously attractive economics of Saudi LPG exports and regional naphtha trading. Energy Intelligence Group’s Barbara Shook agrees, noting in a recent presentation that ethane will be cheaper than naphtha for petrochemical manufacturing, prompting the announced construction of five new ethane crackers to be built on the US Gulf coast in the second half of this decade. Just as the upstream potential of shale gas is bumping up against infrastructure constraints on natural gas exports, the US tight oil play may also be held back by the timing of key infrastructure development. Several fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/15/us-ngls-to-crowd-opec-asian-exports/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368654043213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:40:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368654808914-22</Id><Title>Interior pressed to allow Indian tribes to develop oil and gas</Title><Msg>Julian Hattem - 05/15/13 04:40 PM ET A Senate Indian Affairs Committee hearing quickly turned into a referendum on energy development on Indian lands on Wednesday. As Republicans on the panel pressed Interior Secretary Sally Jewell to allow Indian tribes to develop oil and natural gas resources, the department chief reiterated the administration's commitment to developing renewable energy alongside fossil fuels. In her prepared testimony, Jewell said "the Department is committed to assisting tribes in expanding on Indian lands renewable, low cost, reliable and secure energy supplies as well as safe and responsible oil and gas development in accordance with tribal objectives." On some Indian reservations, claimed Sen. John Barrasso (R-Wyo.), "oil and gas and coal reserves held in trust by the United States for the tribe, for its members, represent by far the number one best opportunity for prosperity for that tribe in that location." Barrasso, the committee's top Republican, added, "We should be asking the tribes, not the Sierra Club or the policy wonks in some think tank or some university, what they want to do with their homelands." "I think our government needs to work with native people in developing their resources, managing their resources in a responsible manner so that they can grow their economies and help their citizens as well as grow their communities," said Sen. Deb Fischer (R-Neb.). "I think that's vitally important." "There's a lot of potential for renewable energy in Indian country," retorted Sen. Al Franken (D-Minn.), who advocated for a distributed generation model that generates electricity from small sources not connected to a larger grid. "Those technologies are good for the environment," he added. In coming days the Interior Department is thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/300007-interior-secretary-pressed-on-oil-and-gas-on-indian-lands-</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368654808914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:53:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368654829086-23</Id><Topic><Title>Interior pressed to allow Indian tribes to develop oil and gas</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368654808914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:53:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... In coming days the Interior Department is expected to propose a rule on hydraulic fracturing, or fracking, the method by which a high-pressure mix of water, sand and chemicals is injected into rock formations to release hydrocarbons. The rule, which has already been criticized by Republicans, will likely require energy producers to disclose the chemicals they use and impose standards on integrity of wells and water that returns to the surface after the process. Republican lawmakers questioned the effect of the impending regulations on Indian tribes. "I just hope you realize that any new regulations are likely to exacerbate delays and costs and hinder tribes," Barrasso told the secretary. The new fracking rule "is really important to tribes," added Sen. John Hoeven (R-N.D.). "They need to be able to hydraulically fracture. So how these rules will come out will be very important, and I want your commitment that you will work with the states and the tribes on a rule that works." After the hearing, Jewell, in just her fifth week on the job, told reporters "it's still weeks, not months" until the proposal is released. Legislators also expressed concern to the secretary about the effect of cuts from sequestration on Indian reservations and problems stemming from a 2009 Supreme Court ruling that restricted the federal government from taking tribes' land into trust. Jewell called the state of government-run schools on reservations "an embarrassment" that would not be helped by sequestration. She told reporters afterwards, "We have a number of schools that are identified as in poor condition. That's not what we aspire to be in our responsibility for Indian education."</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368654829086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 17:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368663647841-24</Id><Title>Price-fixing probe in Europe targets BP, Statoil, Shell, others</Title><Msg>Price-fixing probe in Europe targets BP, Statoil, Shell, others May 14, 2013 at 11:49 am by Harry R. Weber Several major oil firms, including BP, Statoil and Royal Dutch Shell, have been caught up in a price-fixing probe in Europe. The European Commission said that on Tuesday it raided the workplaces of companies that provide services to the crude oil, refined oil products and biofuels sectors. While the commission didn’t name the companies involved or the countries where the unannounced inspections took place, BP, Statoil and Shell confirmed that they are among the subjects of the probe. Statoil said one of the inspections occurred at its office in Stavanger, Norway, while Shell said its offices in London and Rotterdam, in the Netherlands, received visits. BP, based in Britain, and Statoil, based in Norway, said they are cooperating with the probe. Shell is based in the Netherlands. In a statement on its website, the European Commission said the companies may have colluded in reporting distorted prices to a price reporting agency to manipulate the published prices for a number of oil and biofuel products. The commission also alleges that the companies may have prevented others from participating in the price assessment process, with a view to distorting published prices. Read more: Industry executives expect regulatory costs to soar European antitrust rules prohibit cartels and restrictive business practices and abuses of a dominant market position, the commission said. The commission said even small distortions of assessed prices may have a huge impact on the prices of crude oil, refined oil products and biofuels purchases and sales, potentially harming consumers. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/14/price-fixing-probe-in-europe-targets-bp-statoil-others/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368663647841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 20:20:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368676455202-25</Id><Topic><Title>The World Order of the Future</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368629787966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The State of the World: Germany's Strategy.... It's interesting that yahoo deletes every message with the text in it. Probably the US government has ordered the censorship. The fact is Germany does not need the US, has no use for what is mostly inferior US technology, and as soon as a more useful partner comes along that meets Germany's interest we will join them. Russia has much to offer. The US nothing.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368676455202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 23:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368676573312-26</Id><Topic><Title>The World Order of the Future</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368629787966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 10:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Du lieber Gott! Mein Führer lebt!</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1368676573312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 23:56:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>