<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-23"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361595805304-1</Id><Title>Saudi Arabia invites companies to bid for colossal renewables contracts</Title><Msg>Saudi Arabia invites companies to bid for colossal renewables contracts Government publishes white paper detailing plans to install 54GW of clean energy capacity by 2032 By Jessica Shankleman 22 Feb 2013 Green businesses have welcomed the official launch of Saudi Arabia's massive renewable energy procurement programme, which could see 54GW of new capacity added to the grid by 2032. The government-backed K.A. CARE (King Abdullah City for Atomic and Renewable Energy) yesterday unveiled a white paper detailing the tender processes for new solar PV and solar thermal power plants, wind farms, geothermal facilities and waste-to-energy plants. FURTHER READING Global solar farm capacity doubles inside 12 months Financial markets inherently biased against clean energy, warn analysts The first three rounds of contracts are now expected to be awarded before 2015, with a view to creating more than 7GW of new capacity, the majority of which will come from solar power. A smaller introductory round will be launched in the first half of this year solely focusing on concentrated solar power. It will be followed by two larger tendering rounds over the period to 2015 for a range of technologies. Germany clean tech consulting firm Apricum told BusinessGreen the three tender rounds for solar alone could account for more than $10bn (£6.5bn) of investment. The rounds form part of Saudi Arabia's colossal program to procure 54GW of new renewable energy capacity by 2032, which would see the oil-rich kingdom become one of the largest green energy generators in the world. According to K.A. CARE, Saudi will continue to source the majority of its power from hydrocarbons, with a further 17.6GW of nuclear energy, but it will also establish itself as a leading renewables hub. Under the new plans, the vast majority of new green capacity will be solar – 16GW of which come from photovoltaic cells and 35GW from concentrated solar thermal. A further 9GW will come from wind power, 3GW will be provided by waste-to-energy, and 1GW will come from geothermal power. Developers will be invited to bid for power purchase contracts and the government's Sustainable Energy Procurement Company (SEPC) will buy the electricity generated. K.A. CARE maintained this mix will allow nuclear, geothermal and waste-to-energy to provide a baseload night-time supply of power, while solar with storage will contribute to the daytime demand alongside gas and oil. Speaking to BusinessGreen, Matthias Kittler, project manager for Apricum, predicted the programme would offer a massive boost to green industries. Bidders will be invited from around the world. However, the tendering process will also aim to encourage the creation of local production and jobs. He said the first rounds will offer a bonus to bidders with local sourcing arrangements while rounds after 2015 will include a mandate for local content. Kittler forecast significant interest from local energy companies seeking to expand into renewables, as well as international firms. "We also expect a lot of top-notch solar players, such as Suntech Power, will be eager to provide their panels," he added. "[But] we think that for international companies to be successful bidders, they need to find Saudi project partners." The Emirates Solar Industry Association (ESI) hailed the news as a major milestone for Saudi Arabia and the Middle East solar market as a whole. "ESIA will continue to work closely with K.A. CARE to make sure this program becomes a resounding success and a benchmark for excellence." said ESI president Vahid Fotuhi. businessgreenDOTcom/bg/news/2249977/saudi-arabia-invites-companies-to-bid-for-colossal-renewables-contracts</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361595805304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 00:03:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361597084804-2</Id><Title>O'Malley's wind bill passes in House</Title><Msg>O'Malley's wind bill passes in House Submitted photo Steve Hershey Steve Hershey questioned many factors of Gov. Martin O'Malley's wind energy bill before the bill was passed in the House on Friday. Posted: Friday, February 22, 2013 2:30 pm | Updated: 7:08 pm, Fri Feb 22, 2013. By Josh Bollinger Staff Writer ANNAPOLIS - Gov. Martin O'Malley's Maryland Offshore Wind Energy Act of 2013 passed in the House of Delegates by a 86-48 vote on Friday, much to the chagrin of some Eastern Shore delegation members. The bill proposes to build an offshore wind energy facility at least 10 miles off the coast of Ocean City. In the bill's fiscal note, it states most estimates say offshore wind turbines can generate only 38 percent of its maximum power. Also, the fiscal note states local energy expenditures will increase minimally in fiscal year 2014, but increase significantly in 2018, and the total net cost for the wind project expected to be recovered from taxpayers is $1.73 billion over 20 years. The fiscal note estimates individual ratepayers might pay up to an extra $1.50 per month on their electric bills to subsidize the project. Del. Steve Hershey, R-36-Queen Anne's, questioned whether utility ratepayers will ever see a return on their investment in offshore wind. "We are continuing to fight for the ratepayers. They should not be asked to financially back the governor's, or for that matter, the president's high-risk pet projects," Hershey said. Another problem in the bill for Hershey is the way building the facility will be carried out. Basically, a private company will get the chance to build the facility, but will be subject to requirements usually set aside for public works projects that the government has funding in, before the private company sells the electricity back to the grid. "We appear to be headed down a slippery slope that could lead to any private business regulated by the state being subject to prevailing wage, living wage and Maryland Business Enterprise requirements," Hershey said. "That's a big step this bill crosses over, too." Hershey said one reason this bill shouldn't be pushed forward is because offshore wind an inefficient form of energy. Also, offshore wind energy technology hasn't been proven or built in the U.S., Hershey said. "Do we really need to go forward through with this at this time?" said Hershey, who added it would be better to wait until offshore wind is a proven technology. Sen. Jim Mathias, D-28-Lower Shore, said he believes now is the right time to go forward with building renewable, offshore wind farms. Mathias said offshore wind isn't a new issue, as this is the third year variations of this bill have been introduced, nor is pushing offshore wind forward an irrational decision. He said offshore wind isn't meant to be the sole producer of energy in Maryland, as the state needs other sources of energy to survive, like natural gas facilities. "If we can add this to our portfolio as we see our population density going forward, it's absolutely the right thing to do," Mathias said. Plus, offshore wind farms will become more efficient as time progresses, he said. "You look at solar, what solar was ... and what solar is now. We have some of the largest solar farms in Maryland on the Eastern Shore," Mathias said. As for the price of this project, Mathias said it's going to take some time to refine, and that once offshore wind energy gets set up and advertised, the price will be predictable. This is also an environmental issue for Mathias, who said this project will help build Maryland's renewable energy portfolio to better the environment in a time when severe, unseasonable weather events are common. Once Maryland's offshore wind facility is established, the farms also will be able to be linked elsewhere, like if farms are built off the coast of Delaware of New Jersey, "and string them together to add even more electricity to the grid for the area," Mathias said. For now, Mathias said it's vital that incentives are made to encourage investment in offshore wind. myeasternshoremdDOTcom/news/queen_annes_county/article_bb286a90-7d4c-11e2-aedb-001a4bcf887a.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1361597084804</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 00:24:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361623774992-3</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>sanromanwiliam</Username><Timestamp>1361547275275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:34:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome</Msg><Username>connorarmando</Username><Timestamp>1361623774992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 07:49:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361630685070-4</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome!</Msg><Username>coreypeterson181</Username><Timestamp>1361630685070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 09:44:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361630697116-5</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome!</Msg><Username>coreypeterson181</Username><Timestamp>1361630697116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 09:44:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361631422329-6</Id><Title>COP</Title><Msg>XOM shoud buy COP</Msg><Username>philbrown1000</Username><Timestamp>1361631422329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 09:57:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361633873966-7</Id><Title>A new front opens up 2015.</Title><Msg>The Republican Party should be swept away then and the Democrats will be in a position to push through a comprehensive advanced energy program. In California, the state with the largest minority population in America, Democrats now have super majorities. The fossil fuel industry has no influence there at all. High taxes on oil, gas, coal, and nuclear will help speed those energy sources to extinction, and the share prices of the companies involved onto a glide path to $0. German solar, wind, and fuel cell technology will be even more advanced by that point, and the US market will be a goldmine for it. New automobiles will be required and German companies will be well placed to meet the demand thank to investments being pursued now. High speed rail will be important and German companies dominate the field, and will be even more technologically powerful in two years time...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361633873966</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 10:37:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361635430124-8</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>sanromanwiliam</Username><Timestamp>1361547275275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:34:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>yaredchrismas</Username><Timestamp>1361635430124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 11:03:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361639061286-9</Id><Title>Who is to blame for American backwardness in Energy? - Reagan &amp; GWB</Title><Msg>Reagan pushed through policies to cancel most of the U.S. government's subsidies for advanced energy technologies after he was elected in 1980. His low tax policies on fuel and his weak environmental agenda allowed the oil, gas, and coal industry to prosper, and the US auto industry to pursue low tech inefficient vehicles to meet American consumer fads. The free market in American glutted itself on cheap energy for a time, at the expense of long run sustainability of prices and enormous environmental damage, damage which has manifested itself in higher American healthcare costs. Low investments, and poor or no coordination of education at the US Federal level, undermined America's scientific and technological ability, and the military buildups Reagan and GWB pursued diverted the resource into largely useless applications. The money squandered on the US military generated nothing either except death, waste, and more burdens for US tax payers in Veterans benefits. For 6 out of 8 of Clinton's years the GOP set the agenda through its control of the US Congress and carried the torch of backwardness and ignorance forward, picking up where Reagan left off. America fell further and further behind. The Reagan and W's free market policies reigned supreme and failed miserably - except to enrich the fossil fuel lobby. In the meantime Europe, and in particular Germany, pursued a systematic government coordinated effort to improve energy efficiency and develop the scientific and technological base to move away from fossil fuels. The lesson of the oil prices of the 1970s was learned and acted on. When GOP obstruction is removed with their removal from office the technologies will be deployed en masse in the USA thanks to free trade between Europe and the USA... The USA will profit from that and Europe will profit too.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361639061286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:04:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361639349008-10</Id><Topic><Title>GE Wind Tops List Of Wind Turbine Manufacturers In Global Market</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360937840348</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 09:17:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>US Based GE Wind topped the list as 2012′s top wind turbine manufacturer, according to a new report. GE will be the company for the 1100 Wind Mill Farm in Rawlins,WY that construction will start June 1st...</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1361639349008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:09:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361641924961-11</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report, thanks</Msg><Username>petersullivan767</Username><Timestamp>1361641924961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:52:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361641937678-12</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report, thanks</Msg><Username>petersullivan767</Username><Timestamp>1361641937678</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:52:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361642218321-13</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361642218321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:56:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361642266577-14</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361642266577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:57:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361644861386-15</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361644861386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 13:41:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361644940153-16</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361644940153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 13:42:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361644979670-17</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361644979670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 13:42:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361646683425-18</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361646683425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 14:11:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361648081268-19</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361648081268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 14:34:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361656655960-20</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361656655960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 16:57:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361656665810-21</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361656665810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 16:57:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361656724831-22</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361656724831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 16:58:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361666722346-23</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>lucianoanderson120</Username><Timestamp>1361666722346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 19:45:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361666735322-24</Id><Topic><Title>Exxon Mobil Corporation Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>christianson.timothy</Username><Timestamp>1361451418447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:56:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>lucianoanderson120</Username><Timestamp>1361666735322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 19:45:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361666741333-25</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking news! Analyst Downgrades Exxon Mobil</Title><Username>lancemiller317</Username><Timestamp>1361447156878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:45:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ████████████ VIRUS ALERT!!!!!!!! ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>nobeer3356</Username><Timestamp>1361666741333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 19:45:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361673033854-26</Id><Topic><Title>Who is to blame for American backwardness in Energy? - Reagan &amp; GWB</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361639061286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:04:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had a Chevrolet Geo that got 40 miles to the gallon in the 80's. I also remember paying 58 cents a gallon for gas. I think Reagan did a good job with energy. I'd rather buy a Bush era car that gets 35 mpg than an obama era electric car (chevy volt) that catches on fire. Oh yeah remeber solyndra who obama sank many millions into which went bankrupt? Quit boring us with your leftist talking points.</Msg><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1361673033854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 21:30:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361675665903-27</Id><Topic><Title>Who is to blame for American backwardness in Energy? - Reagan &amp; GWB</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1361639061286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 12:04:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stanley Meyer was poisoned during the Clinton Administration. You need a high powered microscope to discern the differences in the two parties (really one) when it comes to the oil barons for the last one hundred years.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1361675665903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 22:14:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>