<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373698184004-1</Id><Topic><Title>Has "molded bluecheese" ever gotten a thumbs up ????</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373579593170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 17:53:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither has you moron runt.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1373698184004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 02:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373722187714-2</Id><Topic><Title>Energy prices plummeting in Germany…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368537956602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:25:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mid-July spot power prices down 58% from 5 years ago...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373722187714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 09:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373723481635-3</Id><Title>shape-memory plastics &amp; high efficiency heat engines…</Title><Msg>Another setback for Buggy Whip Energy &amp; Co Better invest in that time machine company I mentioned… C.S.A. Time &amp; Petroleum GmbH Helmholtz-Zentrum Geesthacht: 11-07-2013 Press release First shape-memory plastics able to reverse deformation Biomaterial researchers in Teltow have developed plastics that can repeatedly change from one shape to another and then back again when temperatures fluctuate within a selected range. The material, dubbed “polymer actuators” by its creators, thus overcomes a major limitation that affects similar materials. Up until now, polymers with temperature-controlled shape memory could only change form once. The new material represents a breakthrough that will open up a wide variety of applications – from automatic blinds that function without electricity to new kinds of heat engines. Researchers from the Institute of Biomaterial Science in Teltow, part of the Helmholtz-Zentrum Geesthacht, have now presented the polymer actuators in the online edition of the renowned PNAS journal. “Once the ambient temperature goes above and then below certain threshold values, our actuators can change shape many hundreds of times,” says Professor Andreas Lendlein, director of the Institute of Biomaterial Science. He explains that the programming of the plastics provides a relatively large amount of freedom for choosing the threshold values and the kind of shape change. He can therefore imagine a very diverse range of applications for the new material. Tilman Sauter, a PhD student at the institute, gives an everyday example of where the plastics might end up: “The material could be used to make sun blinds that need no external electricity supply and are able to darken a room purely on the basis of how warm they are.”</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373723481635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 09:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373723503655-4</Id><Topic><Title>shape-memory plastics &amp; high efficiency heat engines…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373723481635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 09:51:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Another possibility is a heat engine, where the actuators would form the basis of a drive element. To demonstrate how the engine would work, researchers at the institute use an experiment that involves heating a plastic, which then opens up and moves a drive unit. When the temperature drops, the plastic returns to its original state. The temperature-memory effect makes it possible to control the rotational speed of the drive unit. At a molecular level, the active polymers are built of structural elements that undergo changes to their mobility within a very wide temperature range. To transform the activity at the nano level to macroscopic movement, some of these structural elements are assigned to an internal scaffold that determines the geometry of the motion and orients the motion. “We can vary the proportion of motion elements to shape-giving elements, and this allows us to control the movement,” explains Dr. Marc Behl, head of the Active Polymers Department at the institute.”</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373723503655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 09:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373733955142-5</Id><Topic><Title>Has "molded bluecheese" ever gotten a thumbs up ????</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1373579593170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 17:53:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blue cheesed is on IGNORE and this board seems better.</Msg><Username>basherbuste_r</Username><Timestamp>1373733955142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373741740816-6</Id><Title>Southern ladies are a powerful influence…</Title><Msg>Hilton Head and Charleston, South Carolina are very interesting. Once I have wrapped up affairs in Hamburg we will take a trip. Germany solar technology is coming to the region and it will be useful to explore the area fully. It will be convenient to have a house in Charleston to aid this effort, and to solve annoying visa issues for Nicole. By fall there will surely be more oil runts to bash. The board is running on empty. Perhaps some had strokes, and can't keep up their usual pace of ranting &amp; raving. I'm sure by fall there will be more. We'll see.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1373741740816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 14:55:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373741934137-7</Id><Title>Wyden: Natural gas proposal coming ‘soon’</Title><Msg>Wyden: Natural gas proposal coming ‘soon’ By Ben Geman - 07/13/13 01:24 PM ET Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee Chairman Ron Wyden (D-Ore.) said lawmakers on the panel will soon unveil proposals on natural gas policy, a topic that has been a top committee focus this year. The committee, in hearings and informal committee “forums” this year, has heard hours of testimony on hydraulic fracturing, natural gas exports, infrastructure and many other topics related to the nation’s gas production boom. “I’d like to say I was a supporter of natural gas before it became cool. Fifty percent cleaner than the other fossil fuels, but some serious environmental challenges. You asked about fracking. The one that’s even more significant is the question of methane gas emissions,” Wyden said in an interview airing this weekend on Bloomberg Government’s Capitol Gains. “So our committee is looking at this. We’re going to look at it in a bipartisan way. Senator [Lisa] Murkowski is the senior Republican on the committee. Always meets me halfway. And we’ll have some ideas to offer soon. I think they’re going to be bipartisan,” he said. But an aide to Murkowski said the senator’s main focus is currently limited to finding ways to improve permitting to enable construction of needed pipeline infrastructure. “We are at the level of looking at whether something could be done legislatively and what that could be,” spokesman Robert Dillon said. Elsewhere in the interview, Wyden reiterates his concerns about the proposed Keystone XL oil sands pipeline, which would bring crude oil from Alberta’s oil sands projects across the border en route to Gulf Coast refineries. The Obama administration is weighing whether to approve a cross-border permit for TransCanada Corp.’s proposed pipeline. Wyden said “evidence sure indicates that a big part of that energy is going to be exported.” “For example, of the refiners in the Gulf Coast area, more than half of them are for</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373741934137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 14:58:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373742781187-8</Id><Title>Reid confident he has votes to trigger nuclear option in Senate</Title><Msg>Reid confident he has votes to trigger nuclear option in Senate By Alexander Bolton - 07/13/13 12:00 PM ET After days of intense lobbying, Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid (D-Nev.) is confident he has enough votes to trigger the nuclear option to change the Senate’s rules. Reid needs 50 votes for the controversial tactic, which Republicans say would forever “change the character of the Senate” but Democrats argue is necessary to fix a broken institution. Reid expects to have at least 51 Democratic votes to prohibit Republicans from filibustering President Obama’s executive-branch nominees. Vice President Joe Biden could provide insurance by presiding over the chamber to break a tie vote. The standing rules of the Senate require a 67-vote majority to change the rules, but Reid would circumvent that by making a point of order that senators should be prohibited from filibustering executive-branch nominees. This would clear the way for the Senate to confirm Obama’s most controversial nominees with simple majority votes, including Richard Cordray, the nominee to serve as director of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, and three picks for the National Labor Relations Board (NLRB). It’s called the nuclear option because it would cause a meltdown in bipartisan relations. Senate Republicans on Thursday threatened to shut the upper chamber down until next year’s election. Republican Leader Mitch McConnell (Ky.) warned Reid would be remembered as the “worst leader of the Senate ever” if he moves forward. Sen. Carl Levin (D-Mich.) will vote against any point of order Reid raises to change the rules. Sens. Mark Pryor (D-Ark.), who is facing a tough election next year, and Max Baucus (D-Mont.) are “leaning no”, according to a senior Democratic aide. Sens. Jack Reed (D-R.I.) and Tom Carper (D-Del.) are two other swing votes, but Democratic leaders expect them to ultimately support Reid. Reed has wavered back and forth in recent meetings with</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373742781187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 15:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373744255664-9</Id><Topic><Title>Reid confident he has votes to trigger nuclear option in Senate</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373742781187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 15:13:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@SenatorReid TWITTER Followers 116,749 I'll be on @MeetThePress with @DavidGregory this Sunday to discuss the important need to #EndGridlock in the Senate.</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1373744255664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 15:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>