<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357979465257-1</Id><Topic><Title>Advancing the collectivist agenda</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357923868010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 12:04:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>orri is another #$%$ sewer rat traitor to america.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357979465257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 03:31:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357979516780-2</Id><Topic><Title>What about all that asbestos in the old Houston Exxon Bldg ???</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1357833613324</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 11:00:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who cares #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357979516780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 03:31:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358001652636-3</Id><Topic><Title>Are You GETTING KILLED?</Title><Username>lisanewhitenack817</Username><Timestamp>1309568753000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-07-01 21:05:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Am Impressed!!!</Msg><Username>j.ivans</Username><Timestamp>1358001652636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:40:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358005976936-4</Id><Topic><Title>Advancing the collectivist agenda</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1357923868010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 12:04:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will go insane running down your "sewer rats" in the years ahead. The transformation of the American economy into something that can grow in a sustainable way will surely impose severe losses on many speculators and parasites. The parasites fall into numerous species of rentier, each species collecting income off of a different type of waste and inefficiency they try to foster. Just a few examples: trucking in lieu of railroads, urban sprawl in lieu of urban planning, automobiles in lieu of metro rail systems, wasteful wood frame construction in lieu of more permanent structures, stock scams and cults of equity in lieu of the real accumulation of savings, mass ignorance in lieu of sound education, a culture of guns and crime in lieu of the cultivation of productive traits. The Cult of Equity (ie the fraudulent theory that investing in stocks produces large outsize returns and is the road riches) promises to be impacted most severely as the requisite taxes are imposed to stabilize the system to say nothing about the obliteration of the waste above, waste which has been capitalized into stock values. If not for the rest of the world lending and enabling the waste the entire speculative scheme would have collapsed long since. The taxes are coming, and the interest charges will never be escaped.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358005976936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:52:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358018054592-5</Id><Title>Big government science</Title><Msg>examples from the past Ernst Abbe (1840-1905)--a product of German government schools and Universities. He created the modern theory of optics and developed Zeiss Werke into the premier supplier of microscopes, spectrometers, lens, and other optical equipment. The scientific approach to optics, possible because of the German government's investment in education, opened up the fields of medicine, biology, chemistry, and the materials sciences. The advances, and instruments that made them possible, increased life expectancy by about 50% and were the foundation for many key industries. Could such a figure have prospered 1850s-1860s America, in a culture of limited government and primitive educational opportunities? It is highly unlikely, unless one happens to be born rich, which is not statistically likely, such outcomes will not occur. The more likely result is he would have ended up a clerk in some entrepreneurs store, or a carnival barker, or in some other menial task achievable without the aid of government. Nikola Tesla--a product of Austrian big government education - Gymnasium and Graz University of Technology. He was key to the entire modern AC power system. He was able to defeat Edison, even with Edison's alliance with JP Morgan, because of the theoretical, scientific power of his approach, pure power realized thanks to government education. Edison, a product of America's limited government, had to self-educate himself using books, many of which were the product of European higher education. That is, at best, a crude and amateurish way of accumulating knowledge. Very few people can do what he did. There are thousands of other examples too. To the extent the United States was able to contribute and advance it did so by rejecting the theories of limited government and copying Europe - copying things like the Gymnasium - "High School" and the Graz University of Technology ~ MIT and hundreds of clones across America. It also benefited from importing human capital from abroad, that is people like Nikola Tesla, or just importing instruments made by Abbe's Zeiss Werke.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358018054592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:14:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358024762407-6</Id><Topic><Title>Big government science</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358018054592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:14:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would love to trade 500 worthless, greedy and self-serving politicians in Washington today......for a few of yesterday's great inventors. With out modern transportation, communication, electricity, machinery and medicine, we all would still be using out-houses and tending chicken coops and filling the graveyards at 45.</Msg><Username>ten_meaux77</Username><Timestamp>1358024762407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:06:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358027086639-7</Id><Topic><Title>Big government science</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358018054592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:14:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean people like Rudolf Hertz (1857-1894) who attended Gymnasium, Dresden Technische Hochschule, University in Munich and the University of Berlin? He worked in several other universities as well, financed by government. Google his name and see which fields sprang from that product of government education. Or what about Friedrich Althoff (1839-1908) who emerged out of the Prussian government's Commissioner's Office for Alsace-Lorraine in Strassburg. He developed the concept of the research university, a system copied by the University of Chicago and Johns Hopkins University. It is not a simple matter of just building a structure either. A systematic approach, and the encouraging of network effects and clustering is key. That is most easily achieved with the resources of a government. Private enterprise will not create such as system because it cannot profit from it directly. Inventors do not just happen. Of course the above examples are the product of a highly advanced and rational system of Ministerial government, something was not very democratic. The United States can achieve similar effects, however, so long as the party in power believes in government. Teddy Roosevelt's government, for example, set up the Kaiser Wilhelm-Theodore Roosevelt Exchange Professorship program which was the work of Althoff. Creating a "network effect" between America and Germany was most important Progressives, who wished reform America's backwardness and move beyond the limitations of limited government.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1358027086639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:44:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358040426155-8</Id><Title>Los Angeles Utility Set To Launch 100MW Solar Feed-in Tariff Program</Title><Msg>Los Angeles Utility Set To Launch 100MW Solar Feed-in Tariff Program January 12, 2013 Mridul Chadha Image Credit: joncallas (some right reserved) The Los Angeles Department of Water and Power is set to launch a solar feed-in tariff program for its customers for the first time ever. Under the program, households, businesses, and warehouses would be able to inject excess electricity generated from solar power projects into the grid and earn up to $0.17 per kilowatt hour (kWh). The program will also be open to third-party solar power generators and renewable energy technologies other than solar power. Los Angeles Mayor Antonio Villaraigosa expressed his happiness on the launch of this program, which can be seen as yet another milestone in the state of California’s target to procure 33% of its energy from renewable energy sources by 2020. “Today we took another major step forward in transitioning to a clean energy future for Los Angeles. I’m proud of the LADWP Board of Water and Power Commissioners for moving Los Angeles forward to become the largest city in the nation to offer a feed-in tariff solar program. The FiT program takes advantage of our abundant sunshine to spur new private sector investment that will create jobs and decrease our city’s reliance on dirty fossil fuels.” The feed-in tariff program will also play a critical role in the transition from fossil fuels to renewable energy sources, which the Los Angeles Department of Water and Power is about to undertake, believes General Manager Ronald O. Nichols. “Expanding local solar power is an important part of the evolution of LADWP’s power supply from one heavily reliant on coal, to one with more energy efficiency and renewable energy balanced with natural gas. LADWP is replacing over 70% of its existing energy supply over the next 15 years. Local solar not only increases the level of renewable energy we provide to customers but also helps maintain power reliability as we transition away from coal power.” The Board of Water and Power Commissioners has so far approved 100 MW of capacity under the program; a decision on increasing the capacity by 50 MW will be taken in March 2013. 20 MW of capacity will be allocated to the generators every quarter between 2013 and 2016. The first 20 MW of capacity will be tied in a 20-year contract with the utility, which will pay $0.17 per unit of electricity supplied to the grid. Los Angeles Tries Catch-Up With Other Californian Cities While the Los Angeles Department of Water and Power may have entered the feed-in tariff game slightly late, the program can surely be expected to gain significant traction and attract several small-scale solar power generators. Recently, the California Solar Initiative crossed the milestone of 1,000 MW of installed solar power capacity under feed-in tariff regime. Cities like San Jose, San Diego, Bakersfield, and Fresno have been the leaders in this initiative, while Pacific Gas and Electric (PG&amp;E), Southern California Edison (SCE), and San Diego Gas &amp; Electric (SDG&amp;E) have been the leading utilities implementing this initiative. sDOTtt/1yl6n</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358040426155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:27:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358042264465-9</Id><Title>Q&amp;A: Can renewables alone (with storage) power the grid?</Title><Msg>Q&amp;A: Can renewables alone (with storage) power the grid? Posted on 01/11/2013 by Dan Ferber Willett Kempton at a wind installation in Denmark. (Photo courtesy University of Delaware) Conventional wisdom among many utilities and analysts says that renewable energy is expensive and unreliable because the wind doesn’t always blow and the sun doesn’t always shine when electricity demand is highest, and because grid-scale storage is expensive and not ready for prime time. As a result, many in the electric power industry believe that to power entire regional electrical grids, we must continue to rely on fossil fuels for much of our baseload power. Last month, Willett Kempton, a renewable energy expert at the University of Delaware, reported a detailed analysis turning conventional wisdom on its head. Writing in the Journal of Power Sources, a peer-reviewed journal, Kempton and his colleagues reported for the first time that by 2030 the grid could be powered almost entirely using a mix of wind (both on- and off-shore), solar and grid-scale energy storage, and that this grid would be both affordable and reliable. This conclusion came from extensive computer modeling that analyzed four years of hour-to hour data on weather and electricity consumption by the PJM Interconnection, the regional transmission organization for a 13-state swath of the mid-Atlantic and Midwest. Midwest Energy News caught up with Kempton to ask him what it will take to move to a grid powered almost entirely by renewables. Midwest Energy News: Earlier studies showed that in theory there’s far more than enough wind and solar power to meet the world’s electricity demands. But many believe that wind and solar are too intermittent to be reliable as a source of baseload power, and our limited ability to store that energy until it’s needed will keep us continually reliant on fossil fuels for baseload power. You found that wasn’t the case. If renewables and storage were adopted as you describe in this study, what would the electrical grid look like in 2030? Kempton: You have a diversity of sources because you’re more likely to have power generated when you need it if you have onshore wind and offshore wind and some solar. A lot of the time you’re generating more power than you need. And when you are doing that you store it, but before long your storage fills up, so most of the time you’ve got excess power. Sometimes, when you don’t have enough power being generated by renewables, you discharge your storage and run on that, plus whatever renewables you’ve got. And a few times per year, you actually have to look to some other source. In our analysis we used fossil, using legacy plants that are already in existence, and just running them much less frequently. So, that’s what the system looks like: Lots of apparently excess renewables, a very small amount of storage, and some older fossil plants that are being kept around for these situations. Earlier computer modeling efforts by renewable energy analysts had tried to match wind, solar and hydro generation to electricity use to see if renewables could provide reliable electricity. Your model instead tested 28 billion combinations of renewables and storage and sought out those that were least expensive. Why did you seek to minimize cost rather than maximize reliability? We did set a reliability limit, so we said you have to enough power to run the system 30 percent of the time, enough for 90 percent of the time, enough for 99.9 percent of the time. For each of these, we ran for minimum cost. The reason we did that is that we really were trying to match two fluctuating things. People talk about renewable energy fluctuating, but load also fluctuates. So, unless you really understand whether the fluctuations are in sync or out of sync, it’s very hard to know how much renewable generation you need to make load. [It’s also hard to know] which types, because wind on land tends to peak in production more in the evening, though that varies with location. Wind offshore tends to be more constant, but tends to peak when you have storm patterns moving through. And solar, of course, peaks at noon. So, what’s the least-cost combination of those three and storage? We couldn’t know that in advance. We really had to try all combinations. Your model found that the most affordable renewable-dominated grid was one with more than twice the generation capacity than would seem to be needed. Does that mean the excess energy would be wasted? If we only had today’s uses of electricity, and didn’t change anything about how we use electricity, than yes it would be wasted. But what we saw when we did this model is that the excess primarily occurs in the cold months. That’s not necessarily something we expected. I mean, we knew there was more wind in the winter. We’re getting lots of excess electricity, especially September, October through May. And lo and behold, that’s when we’re using a lot of fuels for heating. So . . . we asked the question, suppose we displaced natural gas for heating with this excess electricity? And when you calculate the energy value of that excess electricity, it’s pretty close to the same as the amount of energy burned for natural gas. In this study, you sought to minimize all the costs of burning fossil fuels, and you included costs that ratepayers don’t pay for today, such as the damaging health and environmental effects of harvesting and burning coal and natural gas. Given the political power of utilities and fossil fuel companies, that seems like a big assumption. Why do you think it’s justified? We’re not saying this is going to happen. We’re not saying this is a prediction of the future. We’re just saying let’s just look at what the costs are. Because people say, Renewable energy is expensive, or electric cars are expensive. Let’s figure out what the cost actually is. Say I opened up a new business. I want to buy some things, manufacture a product and sell it, but I’m going to take some of the costs and I’m going to put it on somebody else’s ledger. So I’m not going to actually pay for the steel I’m using. I’m going to charge Dan for that. Well, I’m going to be able to offer my product at a lower price. That’s what the fossil fuel industry is doing right now. Especially with health costs, which is an immediate, current cost that actually just goes right over on the ledger of health. We’re not saying that’s going to change, just like I wouldn’t have said in 1960 people are going to stop smoking cigarettes. We’re just saying, what is the actual cost of this? So don’t tell me that cigarettes are cheap, or that electricity from coal is cheap–it is, by market price–but that’s not the total cost. We were trying to calculate total cost. At the same time, we did not subsidize the renewables. We didn’t say, hey, there’s a production tax credit now and that’s a cool policy and you can get the taxpayers to pay for part of your wind turbine. We took away all the subsidies. We just put the actual costs of renewables and the actual cost of fossil, and put them together. To achieve the sort of all-renewable grid that you write about, do we need new or improved generation or storage technologies? We did not assume any technological changes. We took the numbers that were projected for 2030–what the same technologies would cost then, with the kind of minor refinements you get when you manufacture a product over 20 years. And, we took the cost projected for storage. I don’t think that’s realistic. I think that we will have step changes in both storage and in renewable generation, and they’ll probably occur before 2020, much less by 2030. But we didn’t assume that. We just assumed current technologies with refinements, but not new discoveries. What policy changes would have to happen to make the grid you describe a reality? My first answer would be let’s just charge what stuff costs. So, a new technology gets subsidized for 10 or 15 years, but if you’ve got external costs, they ought to be included in the price. So, we can estimate, when you build a coal plant, you don’t know if Jones is going to die of cancer vs. Smith, but you know from epidemiological studies that it will cause approximately this many deaths and lost work days and so forth. So that should be part of the cost of generation. If you do that, then the market will just do this stuff by itself. In the policy area, the other way to do it is what we’re doing now, which is to subsidize renewables until they get to enough volume that they’re actually able to compete without subsidies. But that’s a policy answer. The other way to answer the question is, What would we do to get there? I think I would say we would need some analysis by the energy planners to ask not just what’s cheaper today–onshore wind or offshore wind or solar–but to ask what kind of systems do we want when we build this out to 30 percent or 50 percent of our energy production from renewables. Our study shows you don’t want to keep just picking the cheapest source. You want to pick sources that go together so that one that might be a bit more expensive, but produces power when your cheaper ones are not producing much power–you want to have that as part of the mix. That’s not the way we do planning now. You need another 100 MW? What’s the cheapest way to do it? That [describes] all state energy planning and all [utility] planning. Nobody’s doing this kind of analysis like we have done here. midwestenergynewsDOTcom/2013/01/11/qa-can-renewables-alone-witih-storage-power-the-grid/ ----------------------------------- Writing in the Journal of Power Sources,... sciencedirectDOTcom/science/article/pii/S0378775312014759</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1358042264465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:57:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>