<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359957047752-1</Id><Topic><Title>Chu says big solar soon to be cheaper than coal and gas</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359943981197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 21:13:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes it is sad how big oil/natural gas have held this country in bondage. The politicans since jimmy Carter have had no guts to do the right thing for the whole country. They look only after themselves and the big money flowing to them. Republicans had a chance then to become the peoples party but instead clung to the big oil and country club set. Oil/ng is a natural resource and as such should not be pumped just for wasteful uses. Solar and wind altho more expensive short term can not be held hostage by a foreign nation, hence we would be freer. Govt, knew this yrs. ago. These middle east wars are basically over oil. and they also could be solar independent. With much less carbon pollution, cleaner air and water.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1359957047752</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 00:50:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359963919672-2</Id><Topic><Title>Institute of Combustion Technology - Energy Applications</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359896967143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 08:09:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All well and good, but doubt they find a magic bullet to make big gains. Agree they should continue research, but one should not expect miracle like discovery. Thinking if a break thru comes it might be in the bio-plant area. perhaps something like modification of photosynthesis to make hydrogen from sun lite and water. Think the world is stuck with fossil fuels for the forseeable future.</Msg><Username>upsidetonograph</Username><Timestamp>1359963919672</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 02:45:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359979640359-3</Id><Topic><Title>WAHLEE WAS DEPORTED!</Title><Username>wahleee_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1359766723167</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:58:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wahlee and maxipad r the coward #$%$ c-nts. Someone must have given them an attitude adjustment.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1359979640359</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:07:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359984527183-4</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may end up being the company to follow this month.</Title><Username>van_reynolds</Username><Timestamp>1359981229731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:33:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fantastic info on report</Msg><Username>montytorres</Username><Timestamp>1359984527183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 08:28:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359985175797-5</Id><Topic><Title>Institute of Combustion Technology - Energy Applications</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359896967143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 08:09:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do not understand the research effort at all I will not explain it to you. If you google the Max Planck Society you will get some appreciation of the size and concentration of the effort. It is not aimed at a single "discovery" either, which anyone with any knowledge of German scientific institutions should know. Further keep in mind that computing power is a key input in quantum chemistry and physics, and for a long time held it back. That barrier is gone.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359985175797</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 08:39:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359986412884-6</Id><Title>English real estate...</Title><Msg>Upper middle class houses are ripe for buying across England. I will buy until my sweet angel has enough to satisfy her. lol Upper class properties in places like London are overpriced, being driven by Chinese money and banking money.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359986412884</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:00:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359987056994-7</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may end up being the company to follow this month.</Title><Username>van_reynolds</Username><Timestamp>1359981229731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:33:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lovely</Msg><Username>trent.marschel</Username><Timestamp>1359987056994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 09:10:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359990073384-8</Id><Title>Deutsche und Amerikanische Waffen für die Welt!!!</Title><Msg>*panzers and troop carriers for Saudi Arabia and Qatar. *frigates and troop carriers for Algeria *submarines for Egypt ...rocket launchers, anti missile systems... The globe is well covered. ***and the USA uses German physics (quantum cascade applications, and quantum material's research discoveries) and Germany uses American drone tech... Now if the US would just balance its budget...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359990073384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:01:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359991004556-9</Id><Title>Wind And Solar Competitive With Natural Gas In The Lone Star State</Title><Msg>Wind And Solar Competitive With Natural Gas In The Lone Star State February 4, 2013Andrew Texas is tops among US states when it comes to installed wind power generation capacity, having added 1,826 megawatts (MW) in 2012 to bring its cumulative total to a whopping 12.212 gigawatts (GW), enough to power nearly 3 million average American homes, according to the American Wind Energy Association’s (AWEA) latest industry report. Ongoing improvements in wind turbine technology, manufacturing processes, installation and operations and maintenance, along with investments in transmission infrastructure, bode well for the future. The same is true for solar photovoltaic (PV) power systems, and though solar energy hasn’t caught on nearly as fast as wind power, Texas is no slouch there either, ranking seventh nationwide in terms of installed solar power generation capacity, according to the Solar Energy Industry Association’s third quarter 2012 state rankings. Progress on the clean energy front is happening extraordinarily fast. So much so, in fact, that in its latest biennial Long Term System Assessment report to the Texas legislature, regional grid operator the Electricity Reliability Council of Texas (ERCOT) “found that if you use updated wind and solar power characteristics like cost and actual output to reflect real world conditions, rather than previously used 2006 assumed characteristics, wind and solar are more competitive than natural gas over the next 20 years,” Environmental Defense Fund’s (EDF) Colin Meehan highlights in a January 28 EDF blog post. Texas Alternative Energy Paths Basing the assumptions incorporated into the complex models ERCOT uses to project and forecast conditions on Texas’s electricity grid on actual, historically recent real-world data as opposed to the assumptions used in 2006 made a huge difference in the results reported in ERCOT’s latest Long Term System Assessment. “What they found was astounding: without these real-world data points, ERCOT found that 20,000 MW of natural gas will be built over the next 20 years, along with a little bit of demand response and nothing else.” “Once they updated their assumptions to reflect a real-world scenario (which they call ‘BAU with Updated Wind Shapes’) ERCOT found that about 17,000 MWs of wind units, along with 10,000 MW of solar power, will be built in future years,” Meehan writes. ERCOT’s report authors go on to state that “the added renewable generation in this sensitivity results in lower market prices in many hours [of the year].” “This means that when real-world assumptions are used for our various sources of power, wind and solar are highly competitive with natural gas. In turn, that competition from renewables results in lower power prices and lower water use for Texas,” according to Meehan. The latter point – lower water usage – shouldn’t be lost on Texas legislators responsible for making policy decisions and taking actions to help assure healthy, sustainable living conditions for present and future generation Texans. Better understanding the interrelationships between water supplies and usage and energy production and use — the water-energy nexus — have become increasingly critical in recent years given changing precipitation patterns, a global rise in mean temperature and two years of historic drought — drought that has recalled memories of the Dust Bowl years that affected Texas and Texans so badly. Scientists and policy makers worldwide are working to improve our understanding of water and energy resources and their interrelationship. There’s an urgent need to go beyond and improve upon the overly simplistic, generalized models and metrics still most commonly used, as sister site PlanetSave notes. As Meehan notes, ERCOT’s report lays out two alternative future paths for Texas’ energy system, one dominated by the use of natural gas to produce electricity, and the other based on a diverse mix of energy sources centered on clean, renewable wind and solar-generated power. It’s now incumbent upon Texans’ elected state representatives to fully and openly #$%$ ERCOT’s report and chart the future course for energy production and use across the Lone Star State. In doing so, they can put Texas on the road to a healthier, more sustainable future. sDOTtt/1zl1K</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991004556</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:16:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359991694284-10</Id><Title>4.47 To 1 — Ratio Of U.S. Voters Who Would Prefer Carbon Tax To Cut In Spending</Title><Msg>4.47 To 1 — Ratio Of U.S. Voters Who Would Prefer Carbon Tax To Cut In Spending February 3, 2013Zachary Shahan Power plant pollution via Shutterstock Politically, it seems there are simply too many whack-jobs (aka Tea Partiers) in Congress to get a carbon tax passed… or to get almost anything sensible passed. But that doesn’t mean Americans wouldn’t support the policy. For example, a recent poll found that 93% of Democrats and even 66% of Republicans (like much of the world) support a carbon tax. Furthermore, 67% of voters would rather see the government tax carbon pollution than cut government spending in order to fix budget problems, versus a measly 15% who would prefer the reverse. Here are some more interesting findings from the recent poll (from Friends of the Earth, via climate crock buster Peter Sinclair): “Voters’ strong support for carbon taxes do not differ greatly based on how the revenue would be used: whether to help solve our budget problems (70 percent in favor), or to help solve our budget problems as well as fund climate and clean energy jobs programs (72 percent in favor).” “Survey respondents were very supportive of a carbon tax even when presented with strongly-worded arguments against it, including the contention that ‘with the economy in trouble and too many people struggling to find jobs, this is a wrong time to pass a new tax on every business and consumer in America.’“ And here are more fun stats regarding a potential carbon tax: “Even a modest tax on carbon dioxide pollution, like that proposed by Representative Pete Stark (D-Calif.) in 2009, has the potential to generate substantial revenue: Stark’s tax, for example, could have yielded $80 billion in the first year alone, and $600 billion over 10 years. That is about half the amount that the automatic spending cuts ($1.2 trillion) would save over nine years, less if part of the revenue were refunded to consumers.” Who would’ve thought? Republicans and Democrats alike don’t like the fact that we’re cooking our planet, and have the common sense to see that discouraging that while earning money for the American public is a good idea. First step accomplished. Next step: remove Tea Partiers and their kin from Congress! sDOTtt/1zk8H</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991694284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:28:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359993215589-11</Id><Title>Energy storage costs to halve, market set to boom: study</Title><Msg>Energy storage costs to halve, market set to boom: study By Giles Parkinson on 31 January 2013 A new study released by the Clean Energy Council points to the huge role that energy storage can play in the evolving power markets, but points to the huge barriers – mostly the interests of incumbent utilities – that stand in its way. The report prepared by consulting group MarchMent Hill, entitled Energy Storage in Australia – Commercial Opportunities, Barriers and Policy Options, predicts the market for energy storage technologies could grow to more than 3,300MW by 2030. (See graph at bottom of article). It suggests that the use of storage is inevitable, and that it will have a fundamental impact on the electricity industry – which has been designed on the principal that energy cannot be stored. All that now changes. The report canvasses a range of technologies – from lithium-ion and other types of batteries, to pumped hydro systems, “smart hot water” devices and technologies such as compressed-air and flywheels – that could be used by utilities to balance the grid as the penetration of renewables grows, better meet peak demand, strengthen regional and off-grid areas, and facilitate the growing use of electric vehicles; and used by commercial and residential customers to optimise the output and the economics of their own renewable generation, such as rooftop solar. The cost of storage is predicted to fall sharply, as this graph below suggests. The report estimates that the average cost could drop by more than half by the end of the decade under the most optimistic scenario – possibly to just above $300/kW. Under its baseline scenario, it is expected to fall to $550/kW. This seems a little conservative, given the recent UBS report that noted a 40 per cent reduction in costs in the last two years and predicted a compound reduction of 10 per cent a year in the decade to come. The industry itself has aimed for around $250/kW, although a report from Lux Consulting also predicted around $500/kW – depending on the extent of mass production. The MarchMent Hill report, however, highlighted that the impediments to storage lay not just in the integration of a range of technical issues, but also the threat to the economic models of many of the incumbents. This needs to be addressed by providing different incentives. “The financial incentives of electricity distributors are not necessarily aligned with the interests of their customers, in situations where energy storage could be advantageous,” it notes. “Despite the seeming unsustainability of the historical approach to meeting peak demand network businesses are still more heavily incentivised to continue on this capital expansion trajectory, than to find alternatives. Their income, to a large extent, is determined by the amount of capital they accumulate in their regulated asset base. Their incentive is not necessarily for least-cost alternatives to building their regulated asset base, and there is no retrospective test applied by the regulator to determine whether they could have met the grid’s needs more efficiently. It also says retailers are unlikely to have the incentive to deploy storage, even if it could insulate them from peak prices. “Most retailers are already covered by financial hedges, or physical hedges in the form of a wholly- or partly-owned generation portfolio. These hedges represent a more developed market, and likely a cheaper option, than storage-based hedges.” It suggests a range of policy and technical measures. The most notable of these is the commitment to the renewable energy target, removing diesel fuel subsidies, and encouraging appropriate price signals. And, to address “cultural issues”, it suggests engaging with the AER and ERA to establish a practice of requiring a “burden of proof” from network operators when they are arguing against storage in favour of network expansion. “Australia needs to start planning in earnest now for the integration of large quantities of storage into the electricity market,” it writes.”While the use of storage may not become widespread until towards the end of the decade, the speed of change and reform in the energy system is typically very slow. “ Interestingly though, it suggests that Australia should focus on regulatory rules and technical issues, rather than R&amp;D investment. “Australia is too small a market to enable R&amp;D investment in, and competitive production of these materials,” it says. That will come to a big disappointment to the likes of RedFlow and other battery storage developers. reneweconomyDOTcomDOTau/2013/energy-storage-costs-to-halve-market-set-to-boom-study-52851</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359993215589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:53:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359994145439-12</Id><Title>Big Energy Feels The Heat</Title><Msg>This morning, the leading integrated energy stocks are coming under selling pressure. It is important to note that the energy sector accounts for roughly 17.0 percent of the S&amp;P 500 Index. It is now very easy to see why this industry group is so important for the major stock indexes. The leading energy stock in the sector is Exxon Mobil Corp (NYSE:XOM). Today, XOM stock is declining lower by $1.00 to $89.02 a share. Short term traders should watch for intra-day support around the $88.80, and $88.32 levels. The daily chart is signaling support around the $87.75 area. Traders must remember, XOM has the largest market capitalization in the world around $410.0 billion. Some other leading integrated energy stocks that are declining lower today include Chevron Corp (NYSE:CVX), ConocoPhillips (NYSE:COP), and BP plc (NYSE:BP). All of these leading energy stocks are still signaling further weakness on the daily charts. As long as these stocks remain weak it is very difficult for the major stock indexes to trade higher. Often, the leading energy stocks will trade inverse to the U.S. Dollar. Nicholas Santiago InTheMoneyStocks</Msg><Username>jonnisilver</Username><Timestamp>1359994145439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:09:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359996047657-13</Id><Topic><Title>In Depth XOM Research Report !</Title><Username>beverlybrown584</Username><Timestamp>1359908983786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 11:29:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks !</Msg><Username>susanmiller182</Username><Timestamp>1359996047657</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:40:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359996397274-14</Id><Topic><Title>Wind And Solar Competitive With Natural Gas In The Lone Star State</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991004556</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:16:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The first nail has been put in on solar and wind in Texas as new homes are going on sale for less than $200,000 with NO power lines just Nat gas to fuel cells. No need for wind or sun just clean gas.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1359996397274</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:46:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359996513381-15</Id><Title>German Solar Technology Powering Saudi Arabia...</Title><Msg>A 3.5 megawatt power plant was just completed by German solar companies outside Riyadh. The Saudi government is going to build many more too to eliminate its requirements of natural gas and oil... Germany's solar industry is the biggest and most technologically advanced in the world, and has the power of the German government and its massive array of German scientific institutions behind it. Costs are plummeting and will continue to plummet as Quantum optics and chemistry, powered by the raw power of modern supercomputers, pushes aside irrelevant and obsolete technological concepts...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359996513381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:48:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359996615884-16</Id><Topic><Title>In Depth XOM Research Report !</Title><Username>beverlybrown584</Username><Timestamp>1359908983786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 11:29:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report , thanks !</Msg><Username>victoria.duffy</Username><Timestamp>1359996615884</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:50:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359997233511-17</Id><Title>Energy 2020 -- FINAL ONLINE VERSION Lisa Murkowski</Title><Msg>Energy 2020 -- FINAL ONLINE VERSION Lisa Murkowski 123 pages thehillDOTcom/images/stories/news/2013/02_february/energy-2020.pdf</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359997233511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:00:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359997330934-18</Id><Topic><Title>In Depth XOM Research Report !</Title><Username>beverlybrown584</Username><Timestamp>1359908983786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 11:29:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good one !</Msg><Username>william.koening</Username><Timestamp>1359997330934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:02:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359997709045-19</Id><Title>Ex-dividend date nd to be in by close Wed.</Title><Msg>Just fyi, the ex-div. date can be confusing for new investors. It is .57, and you have to be in position by the close of Wednesday this week.</Msg><Username>brightstocks</Username><Timestamp>1359997709045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:08:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360000240284-20</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may end up being the company to follow this month.</Title><Username>van_reynolds</Username><Timestamp>1359981229731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:33:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh yes it does</Msg><Username>hillschristopher621</Username><Timestamp>1360000240284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:50:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360000641999-21</Id><Topic><Title>Trek back to $80 begins soon</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1359065370898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 17:09:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1360000641999</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:57:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360000780913-22</Id><Topic><Title>Energy 2020 -- FINAL ONLINE VERSION Lisa Murkowski</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359997233511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:00:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>February 4 News: Murkowski Lays Out GOP Energy Policy Devoid Of Serious Climate Action By Jeff Spross on Feb 4, 2013 at 9:39 am Sen. Lisa Murkowski (R-AK) Senator Lisa Murkowski (R-AK), the top GOP member on the Senate’s energy panel, laid out a sweeping blueprint today that includes opening up more federal lands and waters to oil drilling, launching a new green energy “trust fund,” and general revamping of U.S. green energy policy — but no serious climate action. [The Hill] The blueprint – which Murkowski hopes will launch a broad discussion of energy and resource policy direction in coming years – includes some proposals that are extremely unlikely to advance any time soon, such as opening the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge to drilling. But the blueprint also contains an array of other ideas, such as expediting liquefied natural gas exports to U.S. allies; promoting use of small modular nuclear reactors and creating a new quasi-federal agency for nuclear waste management; and bolstering energy storage R&amp;D, to name just a few. It calls for steering some revenues from expanded oil-and-gas development into a new federal “Advanced Energy Trust Fund” to finance programs on renewable power and alternative fuels, energy efficiency and advanced vehicles. Rural communities in Colorado are coming out against the Obama Administration’s decision to open up nearby public lands to oil and gas exploration, while some of the more solidly Republican urban areas in the state are lining up to support the proposal. [NYTimes] The International Energy Agency has a new report out detailing how Europe’s Nordic region could achieve a carbon-neutral energy system by 2050. [IEA] By driving out coal here in the United States, the shale gas boom is driving a big increase in the burning of coal by European utilities, despite EU environmental policies designed to curb the share of polluting fossil fuels in the energy mix. [Financial Times] Bureaucratic fighting between China’s environment ministry and China National Petroleum Corp (CNPC) and Sinopec Group has thwarted stricter emission standards for diesel trucks and buses — a main cause of air pollution blanketing dozens of China’s cities. [Reuters] Two new papers highlight how the hole in the ozone layer, which is beginning to recover because of limits imposed on CFCs, is influencing major wind patterns, ocean circulation, concentrations of carbon in the atmosphere, and even rainfall in the Amazon. [NYTimes] Using climate models, researchers determined that certain areas could enjoy cooler and wetter summers if currently deforested areas are replanted with trees. [Khaleej Times] A battery-powered train capable of traveling 600 miles on a single charge is now possible, if not immediately likely to pull into a local station, according to research commissioned by the British Government. [The Guardian] The Western Australia Greens have unveiled a $68 million plan to install solar panels on all public housing homes, in what could be an interesting test of the ability of solar to gain traction as an election issue. thinkprogressDOTorg/climate/2013/02/04/1535201/february-4-news-murkowski-lays-out-gop-energy-policy-devoid-of-serious-climate-action/?mobile=wt</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360000780913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:59:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360001417698-23</Id><Topic><Title>In Depth XOM Research Report !</Title><Username>beverlybrown584</Username><Timestamp>1359908983786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 11:29:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really helpful report !</Msg><Username>anthony.dunavant</Username><Timestamp>1360001417698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:10:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360001632706-24</Id><Topic><Title>Deutsche und Amerikanische Waffen für die Welt!!!</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359990073384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both Germany and the USA use the Phonecian alphabet and the Sumerian wheel too.Both those countries are freckles on the broad face of history.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1360001632706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:13:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360001726187-25</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may end up being the company to follow this month.</Title><Username>van_reynolds</Username><Timestamp>1359981229731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 07:33:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lot of profits to be made on that one on up and down side</Msg><Username>morrison.erro</Username><Timestamp>1360001726187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:15:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360003336930-26</Id><Topic><Title>Deutsche und Amerikanische Waffen für die Welt!!!</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359990073384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The written Hittite language is Germanic. It took a (Teutonic) Scandinavia Jørgen Alexander Knudtzon discover the key when he found the word for water... It is far older than Phonecian. Hittite metal working technology and weaponry was dominate for ages... We are way past the wheel...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360003336930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:42:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360005803043-27</Id><Topic><Title>In Depth XOM Research Report !</Title><Username>beverlybrown584</Username><Timestamp>1359908983786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 11:29:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks a lot !</Msg><Username>ronald.bailey</Username><Timestamp>1360005803043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:23:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360007716256-28</Id><Topic><Title>$$-LQQK-$ Secret XOM Info REVEALED! $-LQQK-$$</Title><Username>luislee278</Username><Timestamp>1359997105338</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report.</Msg><Username>jalenjonson</Username><Timestamp>1360007716256</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:55:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360009736350-29</Id><Topic><Title>Wind And Solar Competitive With Natural Gas In The Lone Star State</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991004556</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:16:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So do people.</Msg><Username>1molly2</Username><Timestamp>1360009736350</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:28:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360010015099-30</Id><Topic><Title>4.47 To 1 — Ratio Of U.S. Voters Who Would Prefer Carbon Tax To Cut In Spending</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991694284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:28:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did anyone advise these people that THEY would be paying the carbon tax? I bet not. Taxes are not "free income" to the government.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1360010015099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:33:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360012540529-31</Id><Title>Big Oil Lacks Appeal</Title><Msg>The downgrade parade will begin shortly - price target = $80. SAN FRANCISCO (MarketWatch) -- Chevron Corp. CVX -1.11% and Exxon Mobil Corp. XOM -0.99% are among the companies that will be "challenged" over the next 12 months due to their lack of growth and high capital expenses, analysts at Barclays said in a note to clients Monday.</Msg><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1360012540529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:15:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360013543188-32</Id><Topic><Title>$$-LQQK-$ Secret XOM Info REVEALED! $-LQQK-$$</Title><Username>luislee278</Username><Timestamp>1359997105338</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sir_ironia</Msg><Username>albertlee911</Username><Timestamp>1360013543188</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:32:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360020088992-33</Id><Topic><Title>Big Oil Lacks Appeal</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1360012540529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:15:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XOM is one of THE best long term core holdings one could have, IF one wants energy, and yield with long term growth. XOM is a great play on both coal and NG. GLTY. -Frieberg</Msg><Username>frey_guy17</Username><Timestamp>1360020088992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:21:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360020389502-34</Id><Topic><Title>4.47 To 1 — Ratio Of U.S. Voters Who Would Prefer Carbon Tax To Cut In Spending</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991694284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:28:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are completly FOS.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1360020389502</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:26:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360020574251-35</Id><Topic><Title>Wind And Solar Competitive With Natural Gas In The Lone Star State</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991004556</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:16:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again, completly FOS. You are missing a good game here.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1360020574251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:29:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360020684620-36</Id><Topic><Title>Wind And Solar Competitive With Natural Gas In The Lone Star State</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991004556</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:16:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clean? Unlike your shorts.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1360020684620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:31:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360022388774-37</Id><Topic><Title>Big Oil Lacks Appeal</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1360012540529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:15:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XOM is up-to the challenge of the energy stupidity objectives of this administration and the gullibility of the children who believe in the outright fantacy of man-made warming of the earth. If you are a trader: go for it. If you are an investor, you need more education. It is curious to me that people sacrifice long term reality for the sake of short term mis-information. That alone makes you a quart low on objective reality, not to mention common sense.</Msg><Username>rewindstevens</Username><Timestamp>1360022388774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:59:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360025354004-38</Id><Topic><Title>Big Oil Lacks Appeal</Title><Username>nip7890</Username><Timestamp>1360012540529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:15:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love my v8's, take a look at a prius driver, you want to hang out with them? hot rods forever!!!</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1360025354004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 19:49:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360028863824-39</Id><Title>If He's So Patriotic Why Did Ted Nugent Dodge Vietnam?</Title><Msg>anothe fear driven right wing COWARD!</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1360028863824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 20:47:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360028979838-40</Id><Topic><Title>What Has Any Republican EVER Done To Help Middle Class?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1359895848355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 07:50:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual No answers from the brain dead right wing cowards. They can't even defend the insanity they support.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1360028979838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 20:49:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360031663989-41</Id><Title>It is a funny species when left wing peace protesters during the Bush Administration</Title><Msg>Rally and support the of the Obama administration's genocidal wars in Libya, Syria and numerous other African and Middle East countries by liberal left wing Democrats spells certain death of the American Empire. Americans let 25% of their children go to be hungry to support 1000 military bases in 148 nations. The children of satan with thier television propaganda organs in New York City brainwash US taxpayers into going trillions more in debt for Manhattans profiteers in the arms rackets. The userous money changers keep printing money and debasing the middle class in the process. Filth like Chuck Schumer will not vote for Chuck Hagel</Msg><Username>kcannuli</Username><Timestamp>1360031663989</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 21:34:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360033912411-42</Id><Topic><Title>What Has Any Republican EVER Done To Help Middle Class?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1359895848355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 07:50:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Well, their you go again" you forget under Reagen, the country did get trickled down on.</Msg><Username>fss13</Username><Timestamp>1360033912411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 22:11:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360037947538-43</Id><Title>Currency Purchase...</Title><Msg>sold all £ for € @ 1.1675 €/£... £ basis .8581 £/€ (1.1654 €/£)... gain on £ +0.18%... 100% euro deposit (German)...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360037947538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 23:19:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360038049124-44</Id><Title>Has any GOP Senator ever put the USA's interests ahead of Israel?</Title><Msg>It is not possible under our whorish form of govt.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1360038049124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 23:20:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360038445878-45</Id><Title>German real estate...</Title><Msg>a buy... Upper middle class for rentals...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360038445878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 23:27:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360039083967-46</Id><Topic><Title>Has any GOP Senator ever put the USA's interests ahead of Israel?</Title><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1360038049124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 23:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CHUCK HAGEL LOVES AMERICA FIRST--THATS WHY THE GOP HATES HIM--even if he is a republican they hate him</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1360039083967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 23:38:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>