<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-14"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368507451332-1</Id><Title>god bless dndn stockholders! with a 10.00 buyout!</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1368507451332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 00:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368508381908-2</Id><Title>god bless dndn stockholders! with a 10.00 buyout! help us jesus!to the stars!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1368508381908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 01:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368525920503-3</Id><Topic><Title>The Land of the Uneducated</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368365905130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:38:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still kicked your krout #$%$ during the war.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1368525920503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 06:05:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368537874016-4</Id><Title>IEA sees U.S. oil shockwaves ousting OPEC as supply driver</Title><Msg>May 14, 2013 at 7:00 am by Bloomberg The U.S. shale boom will send “shockwaves” through the global oil trade over the next five years, benefiting the nation’s refiners and displacing OPEC as the driver of supply growth, the IEA said. North America will provide 40 percent of new supplies to 2018 through the development of light, tight oil and oil sands, while the contribution from the Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries will slip to 30 percent, according to the International Energy Agency. The IEA trimmed global fuel demand estimates for the next four years, and predicted that consumption in emerging economies may overtake developed nations this year. “The supply shock created by a surge in North American oil production will be as transformative to the market over the next five years as was the rise of Chinese demand over the last 15,” the Paris-based adviser to 28 oil-consuming nations said in its medium-term market report today. The development of U.S. shale resources, enabling the nation’s highest level of energy independence in two decades, is creating a “chain reaction” in the global transportation, processing and storage of oil that may escalate as other countries try to replicate the American oil boom, according to the IEA. Crude futures for settlement in 2018 are trading at a discount to current prices, signaling expectations for increasing supplies and constrained demand. Brent Curve Brent crude for settlement in 2017 is about $12 a barrel cheaper than front-month prices on the ICE Futures Europe exchange. June contracts were near $102.60 today, while futures for December 2017 were at $90.39 a barrel. Global oil demand will increase by 6.1 million barrels a day, or 6.7 percent, to 96.7 million a day by 2018 as the economic recovery gathers pace, the IEA said. Demand estimates for 2017 are about 95,000 barrels a day less than fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/14/iea-sees-u-s-oil-shockwaves-ousting-opec-as-supply-driver/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368537874016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:24:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368537956602-5</Id><Title>Energy prices plummeting in Germany…</Title><Msg>Spot power prices hit close to 0 this past Sunday. The average price for May is down more than 1/3rd from a year ago, and down 50% from 5 years ago. Low marginal cost solar &amp; wind power being sold in increasing volume is why prices are falling so rapidly. Germany’s industry will respond to these power rates over time, increasing its outputs as it sells to foreigners. There’s no reason to expect the pace of power generation from solar &amp; wind to slacken either. In fact it will accelerate as industrial demand for the power builds and more and more funds become available to deploy more and more capacity, harnessing steadily improving technology. Germany could probably double its total industrial output if enough solar &amp; wind power could be brought on stream, something that would not be very helpful to foreign competitors and energy companies that rely on their power demand. Producing products with a low labor input will be emphasized since while capital and energy can be deployed in effectively unlimited quantities labor is limited. As German scientists develop the technology for bio-refiners to turn sawdust and other materials into plastic a whole new area of industry will appear to absorb cheap power. None of these developments are good for the oil &amp; gas industry. Its days are numbered.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368537956602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368539038389-6</Id><Title>Hillary using Obama for election</Title><Msg>Don't worry Hillary using Obama for the election. She would of never been though of being elected if it wasn't for the worst case scenario.</Msg><Username>investing_is_a_game</Username><Timestamp>1368539038389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368539082847-7</Id><Title>"If you leave existing power plants out of the picture, you're being overly optimistic."</Title><Msg>... "Carbon reduction at power plants has to be addressed but in a very sensitive way," said William K. Reilly, EPA administrator under President George H.W. Bush. "If you leave existing power plants out of the picture, you're being overly optimistic." U.S. emissions of greenhouse gases have ...</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368539082847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368545352345-8</Id><Title>WTI oil over $100/barrel very soon. Watch oil ramp now.</Title><Msg>Just in time for peak summer usage.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1368545352345</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368545510808-9</Id><Title>See oil free falling</Title><Msg>There is no real demand any more. Wake up people all been manipulated by markets. Yes Wall Street speculation only. Too many fuel effecient cars/ Other sources of energy out there. I see car prices plunging because of too many energy efficent cars in market place here.Wall Street plays these games aways to the point of collapse with their greed</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368545510808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368549742988-10</Id><Title>wake up people energy prices should crash here</Title><Msg>Prices have all been manipulated as usual by Wall Sgtreet by speculation. Not by supply/demand free market. Energy prices will crash here because there is no real demand. Its all been manipulted with supply control etc. With all the energy savings in the market place with all the new fuel effecient things we have this is ridiculous. Con sumers rtule put your foot down to these games by the market place. We rule the consumer. Use just a little less or dont buy and prices free fall. Time to send a message to Wall Street that the consumer rules.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368549742988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368550714681-11</Id><Title>XOM may well skyrocket tomorrow! This is the key reasons why.</Title><Msg>Has any person looked over the articles being released? Eye opening stuff that will help any investor or trader. gooDOTgl/7BwBS (DOT means .)</Msg><Username>costanzoronald</Username><Timestamp>1368550714681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368552012073-12</Id><Title>When will Exxon up dividend?</Title><Msg>Last year, if my memory is correct, Exxon increased the dividend at the end of the second quarter. Does anyone have an idea on this....What to expect?</Msg><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1368552012073</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368552895904-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Land of the Uneducated</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368365905130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:38:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Das stimmt! LL</Msg><Username>cancel190</Username><Timestamp>1368552895904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368553130988-14</Id><Topic><Title>The Land of the Uneducated</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368365905130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 09:38:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without Jesus Christ as your savior, there is no direction in life that ultimately/eternally means anything, so if you don't know Jesus as savior........TAKE YOUR PICK,...................IT DOESN'T MATTER !</Msg><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1368553130988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368553287796-15</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well skyrocket tomorrow! This is the key reasons why.</Title><Username>costanzoronald</Username><Timestamp>1368550714681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good stuff</Msg><Username>bakerstephen459</Username><Timestamp>1368553287796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368553355459-16</Id><Title>Exxon has runned out of gas!</Title><Msg>No pun intended. XOM is topping out here folks. Time to take profit and wait this game out. Greedy little piggy's get slaughtered. Is That You? oink oink</Msg><Username>high_surf_warnings</Username><Timestamp>1368553355459</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368553624063-17</Id><Topic><Title>WTI oil over $100/barrel very soon. Watch oil ramp now.</Title><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1368545352345</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid or mentality challenged? What has oil prices done the last two years during May &amp; June? Oil supplies are at levels that haven't been seen since 1982 while oil prices are presently at high levels. Keep that day job son, you need it.</Msg><Username>high_surf_warnings</Username><Timestamp>1368553624063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:47:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368553866749-18</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well skyrocket tomorrow! This is the key reasons why.</Title><Username>costanzoronald</Username><Timestamp>1368550714681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks man</Msg><Username>sorensen_matthew</Username><Timestamp>1368553866749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368554290899-19</Id><Title>Hedge You Long Position With SCO</Title><Msg>You may be an rookie in the markets but that doesn't you have to trade like one. Hedge your bet now when the markets/Oil are inflated. SCO reduces your risk and allows you to hold XOM while sleeping well at night. A huge build in oil supply is being seen. Oil is trading at a huge premium.</Msg><Username>high_surf_warnings</Username><Timestamp>1368554290899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368566441861-20</Id><Title>buybacks</Title><Msg>how do buybacks work? does the company offer you, or do you have to approach the company? and how to do that? can someone explain?</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1368566441861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368567834405-21</Id><Topic><Title>buybacks</Title><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1368566441861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:20:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The company buts back XOM stock on the open market. Once the buy it, the stock goes into XOMs treasury . Think of it as a company calling in a bond. By doing this there are less shares . Technically the remaining shares are then worth more , since the profits apply to a smaller share count. Exxon has been buying back shares at 3-5% per year for years now..... By 2018 the stock should get a nice kick.... This I just hold this one and trade everything else .</Msg><Username>ah673000</Username><Timestamp>1368567834405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:43:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368568502831-22</Id><Topic><Title>XOM may well skyrocket tomorrow! This is the key reasons why.</Title><Username>costanzoronald</Username><Timestamp>1368550714681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Key Logger site.....get your computer repaired</Msg><Username>basherbuste_r</Username><Timestamp>1368568502831</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:55:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368569953441-23</Id><Title>Xom in breakout...next stop</Title><Msg>Before any serious resistance is $100 on my chart....dividend, recovering world economy, plans to export natural gas to so. America and china equals huge growth for Exxon!</Msg><Username>pkj100</Username><Timestamp>1368569953441</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368575544503-24</Id><Topic><Title>When will Exxon up dividend?</Title><Username>yrsw05</Username><Timestamp>1368552012073</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:20:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They last declared an increase in dividend on April 24th and payable on June 10th. Increase to 63 cents from 57 cents quarterly.</Msg><Username>_j_t_</Username><Timestamp>1368575544503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368577845953-25</Id><Title>Cedar Lake awards pact for E85 fuel storage tank</Title><Msg>Cedar Lake awards pact for E85 fuel storage tank May 12, 2013 7:45 pm • Mary Wilds Times Correspondent CEDAR LAKE | The Town Council has awarded a contract to build a storage tank for E85 fuel. The project had only one bidder, Grimmer Construction of Highland at $44,000. The town is using federal dollars to build the tank. Because $175,000 had been allocated, the remainder of the monies will go into Cedar Lake’s Cumulative Capital Development Fund. E85 is an abbreviation for an ethanol blend fuel, 85 percent of which is denatured ethanol. U.S. government subsidies encourage the use of E85, which has a high octane rating and is less carbon intensive than petroleum. The storage tank will hold E85 fuel provided free by the federal government for use in police vehicles. nwitimesDOTcom/news/local/lake/cedar-lake/cedar-lake-awards-pact-for-e-fuel-storage-tank/article_2e4a1dc8-8ad9-577f-a47d-5e181c18b641.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368577845953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368585756572-26</Id><Topic><Title>Xom in breakout...next stop</Title><Username>pkj100</Username><Timestamp>1368569953441</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DXY is moving into unfavorable zone to XOM.</Msg><Username>after8before12</Username><Timestamp>1368585756572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 22:42:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>