<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371877667067-1</Id><Title>XO M</Title><Msg>mobile, odamba tax cut, u.s trseury will be selling oil futres to bring fair value of oil 2 cents a bar</Msg><Username>boldchris</Username><Timestamp>1371877667067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 01:07:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371900270821-2</Id><Title>time to sell energy,, buy retail and travel</Title><Msg>pcln 813 looking to bust thru 900 soon</Msg><Username>tagthatstock</Username><Timestamp>1371900270821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371900390445-3</Id><Title>wmt 73</Title><Msg>safe retailer to look at</Msg><Username>tagthatstock</Username><Timestamp>1371900390445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371900529356-4</Id><Title>$usd 82 looks angry to 87-89</Title><Msg>3 currencies are crashing,, i warned them a couple of weeks ago,, they better move to $usd or lose 20% purchasing power in an already deflationary time.</Msg><Username>tagthatstock</Username><Timestamp>1371900529356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371906465850-5</Id><Topic><Title>All the (speculating) world trembles before Germany's high court...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1370961077051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 10:31:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump. I expect the Federal Constitutional Court to rule the ECB's measures and plans illegal as they expose taxpayers to the risk of losses and tax liability to cover them without a vote in the Bundestag. That would amount to an termination of the ECB's policies since they will not be able to get such a vote approving them. The losses will not occur because the ECB's plans will be rendered null and void. It very well could be that the Federal Reserve has been observing these proceedings and has realized that the game is over. The dollar would face utter ruin if Bernanke pursued his poor policies in the face of a true sound money policy dictated by the Bundesbank, something that will be the reality soon. ........... In other news I've increased my real estate allocation in Berlin-Potsdam to as much as possible considering the supply of suitable upper middle class rental properties. By fall there will be a fresh crop of houses to harvest, buy up.... No stock or bond is a buy under the circumstances. Allocations Residential Real Estate: 90% Berlin - 21% Stuttgart - 25% Frankfurt - 20% Munich - 14% Duisburg, Essen - 5% Ludwigshafen - 5%. euros and German t-bills 10%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371906465850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 09:07:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371906652424-6</Id><Topic><Title>Energy prices plummeting in Germany…</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368537956602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:25:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump. Back near 0 again and at low levels all week.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371906652424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 09:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371918533538-7</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla demonstrated 90 second battery swap</Title><Username>gnostocks</Username><Timestamp>1371822504482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gno; I wonder if Tesla copied this battery station concept from Kandi. Kandi makes electric vehicles in China. Paul</Msg><Username>sps14626</Username><Timestamp>1371918533538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 12:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371926601714-8</Id><Title>Australian Renewable Fuels restarts biodiesel exports to US</Title><Msg>Australian Renewable Fuels restarts biodiesel exports to US By Ron Kotrba | June 21, 2013 Australian Renewable Fuels Ltd. announced June 21 that it has recommenced exports of biodiesel. The first shipment of 5.7 million liters (approximately 1.5 million gallons) of biodiesel is now en route to the U.S., to be followed by another shipment of 5 million liters (1.32 million gallons) in August. Customers for the order are Valero Energy Corp. and Gavilon Inc., two of the world’s leading energy companies. Gavilon is a Nebraska-based international grains, food and fuel storage and distribution company whose energy division stores and transports a range of fuels including crude oil and refined products, gas and renewable fuels. Australian Renewable Fuels CEO Andrew White notes the drop in value of the Australian dollar, adding that additional export opportunities are being explored. Relaunching its biodiesel exports means elevated production at the company’s Largs Bay, South Australia, and Picton, Western Australia, plants, and complements its existing long-term supply contract with Shell Australia. Australian Renewable Fuels also announced execution of terms with a new banking partner. The terms provide for a $6 million working capital facility to fund the sales growth and development of the business both in Australia and on export markets. The company said the unnamed partner is one of the world’s foremost top tier banks, which will provide unique resources and transactional support as Australian Renewable Fuels grows its business in the world commodity markets and in the Asia-Pacific region. biodieselmagazine</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371926601714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 14:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371941424011-9</Id><Title>Will you stand with President Obama in the fight against #climate change? Tune in on Tuesday:</Title><Msg>TWITTER Barack Obama Verified account ‏@BarackObama Will you stand with President Obama in the fight against #climate change? Tune in on Tuesday: YouTube... Addressing the threat of Climate Change At 1:35 on Tuesday June 25th President Obama will speak at Georgetown University on the growing threat of climate change. He will lay out his vision of where... 191Retweets 99Favorites 4:34 PM - 22 Jun 13 twitter</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371941424011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 18:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371949807923-10</Id><Topic><Title>Bluecheese: All his posts are "absolutely worthless" !</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371752941651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, just giving 'em all a thumbs down........there's no pertinent info in a single post.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371949807923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 21:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371950157542-11</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese is a walking encyclopedia.....</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370133089920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make that an abridged encyclopedia of totally useless info.</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371950157542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 21:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371950189411-12</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese is a walking encyclopedia.....</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370133089920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you got a single thumbs 'up' yet ? Other than your own ?</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371950189411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 21:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371959531379-13</Id><Title>Forschungszentrum Jülich</Title><Msg>* €500,000,000/year budget *most powerful supercomputer in Europe devoted to the war on fossil fuels. *its website has much useful information on fuel cells, photovoltaics, and other German energy technologies. The Green Wolves of Jülich, and other such German wolf packs are armed with powerful weapons, weapons which render irrelevant previous concepts of what is possible, and what can be achieved with the application of money and manpower. The difference in power is similar to the bow-and-arrow versus modern weaponry, or the difference in potentiality between the native tribes of Africa and the Americas and their Europeans conquerors. Germany’s wolf packs are well funded and well armed, and they are encircling their prey. When the time to strike is right, the alpha males will move in and tear Big Oil to pieces, and the females will consume its carcass at their leisure.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1371959531379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 23:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>