<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368251334645-1</Id><Title>Carbon dioxide levels hit troubling milestone, scientists say</Title><Msg>Brian Vastag and Jason Samenow, Friday, May 10, 3:09 PM Human influence on the Earth’s atmosphere touched what climate scientists called a dire milestone Friday as concentrations of heat-trapping carbon dioxide nudged up to a level unseen in about 3 million to 5 million years — long before modern humans. A monitoring station in Hawaii recorded carbon dioxide concentrations of 400 parts per million Friday, dramatically up from the 316 parts per million recorded when the station made its first measurements in 1958. The monitor, high atop the Mauna Loa volcano, offers the longest-running record of atmospheric carbon dioxide measured directly from the air. Carbon dioxide is a primary greenhouse gas, efficient at trapping heat from the sun. The colorless gas is released from power plants and vehicles as they burn coal, oil and gas. “[The] increase is not a surprise to scientists,” said Pieter Tans, a senior scientist at the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. “The evidence is conclusive that the strong growth of global [carbon dioxide] emissions from the burning of coal, oil and natural gas is driving the acceleration.” Climate scientist Joanna Haigh of Imperial College London said the particular figure reached Friday — 400 parts per million — holds no particular significance except as a milestone. “It gives us the chance to mark the ongoing increase in [carbon dioxide] concentration and talk about why it’s a problem for the climate.” Scientists have firmly linked rising atmospheric carbon dioxide to higher global temperatures, which have increased nearly a degree Fahrenheit, on average, since 1950. Larger temperature increases have occurred in the Arctic. In 2009, an international agreement sought to limit temperature increases to 3.6 degrees Fahrenheit (2 degrees Celsius) by... washingtonpostDOTcom/national/health-science/atmospheric-carbon-dioxide-levels-hit-worrisome-milestone/2013/05/10/7cfe450c-b9a4-11e2-b94c-b684dda07add_story.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368251334645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 01:48:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368251643308-2</Id><Title>Senate panel to try again on EPA nominee</Title><Msg>Zack Colman - 05/10/13 07:48 PM ET Democrats will try to advance Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) nominee Gina McCarthy to the full Senate again next week after a GOP boycott thwarted attempts to do so Thursday. Sen. Frank Lautenberg (D-N.J.), who has been in ill health, will make the trip to the Capitol for the May 16 hearing, Caley Gray, a spokesman for Lautenberg, told The Hill. That would give the Senate Environment Public Works Committee a quorum for a vote. The GOP’s absence and two missing Democrats — Sen. Max Baucus (D-Mont.) also wasn’t present — left the committee two members shy of a quorum Thursday, thwarting a vote on McCarthy, EPA’s top air quality regulator. Republicans are blocking McCarthy’s nomination because they want EPA to hand over more information about the data it uses to design regulations that the GOP and industry oppose. They say McCarthy has not fully answered inquiries about transparency at the agency. Democrats contend McCarthy has answered more than 1,000 questions. They — along with President Obama — say Republicans are being “obstructionist.” Committee Republicans might disagree that Democrats can proceed with a vote, citing committee rules. Ranking member Sen. David Vitter (R-La.) cited committee rules that two members of the minority party must be present for a vote in a Thursday memo to committee Chairwoman Barbara Boxer (D-Calif.). Staff members for committee Democrats maintain that Senate rules trump committee policy for such votes. Senate rules require one more lawmaker than half the total body — in this case, 10 lawmakers. Even if the committee does advance McCarthy to the full Senate, confirming her could be difficult. Republicans have floated the idea of employing a filibuster on her nomination, and it is unclear whether Democrats could escalate the 60-vote threshold. Vitter’s office did not respond to requests... thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/299153-senate-panel-to-try-again-on-epa-nominee</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368251643308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 01:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368251744026-3</Id><Topic><Title>Carbon dioxide levels hit troubling milestone, scientists say</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368251334645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 01:48:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More Bu;; #$%$ from blew cheese......she doesn't know what she's talking about, merely SPEWING Green #$%$. Continually.......and not contributing one good fact to the XOM board. Wouldn't know a Co2 from a hydrogen molecule. She get's her talking points from the penny/post providers who send it to her.</Msg><Username>basherbuste_r</Username><Timestamp>1368251744026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 01:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368264218419-4</Id><Topic><Title>Bi Bush shows Trotskyite Neocon colors with IRS appointee</Title><Username>rockhardchicano</Username><Timestamp>1368241200384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:00:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ u commie POS.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1368264218419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 05:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368277363113-5</Id><Topic><Title>OIl prices will free fall</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1368107007947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-09 09:43:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- means something too, but maybe not to you. You fail to explain what supercomputers have to do with inelastic demand or oil. Sie konnen gar nichts verstehen, das ist shade. Your stupidity is mind blowing. Stick to keeping your money in a bank as that is the only place you won't lose it. Most Germans are smart and wonderful people, evidently you're not one of them. These are my last words as I don't waste them on individuals like you. Spater.</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1368277363113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368281396004-6</Id><Title>Benghazi, corrupt IRS----that's OBUMMER for you</Title><Msg>what a total piece of C R A P</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1368281396004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 10:09:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368282044562-7</Id><Title>polymers to make petrochemicals obsolete</Title><Msg>The focal point of the technological effort is in the Berlin area. Pilot industrial facilities are southwest of Berlin near Leipzig. About a dozen technological/scientific divisions from the Fraunhofer and Max Planck Societies, as well as German industrial companies are involved. Of course the effort is supported by major super-super-computing assets in the Berlin area as well as in Stuttgart funded with state monies. I suppose “combined arms” is a fitting metaphor, and if one wanted to be colorful they could draw symbols for an army group on the map (box with xxxx over Potsdam, Germany) with symbolic arrows for attack objectives. Main field objectives: *biopolymers: using agricultural and forestry raw materials to replace fossil fuel sources feeds *functional polymer systems: energy production, material applications to products *synthesis and polymer technology: bio-plastics, resins, membranes for gas-liquid separation *specialty polymers – polymer/water interaction; solutions; gels; dispersions; surfaces (See Fraunhofer Institute for Applied Polymer Research, and Polymer Surface Alliance websites for particulars)</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1368282044562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 10:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368317268968-8</Id><Title>Maine votes to ban ethanol in gasoline, takes stand against E15</Title><Msg>Maine votes to ban ethanol in gasoline, takes stand against E15 Danny King Posted May 10th 2013 7:14PM Comments102 If it can go in your gas tank, it's potentially controversial up in Maine. A few years ago, out-of-spec gas pumps were a problem. Today, the issue is the corn-based biofuel ethanol, which the state legislature is taking a strong stand against. Citing potential engine and environmental damages, Maine's state legislature has taken another step to potential rid itself of ethanol blends into its gasoline inventory. Legislators have approved a bill by more than a 3-to-1 margin that would ban ethanol blends in Maine – as long as two other nearby states do the same, the Bangor Daily News reports. State leaders also supported a resolution urging the government to ban gasoline with a 15 percent ethanol blend (known as E15), altogether. Most gasoline in the US contains up to 10 percent ethanol blend. Maine regulators started talking about a statewide E15 ban early this year. The state said at the time that at least two other New England states would have to go along so that Maine refiners wouldn't have to make a custom blend for the state only, which would cause the state's fuel prices to jump. On the federal level, the word is that E15 is fine. Last June, the US Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) officially allowed for public sales of E15 as part of an effort to cut foreign-oil dependency. Groups such as AAA have since been critical of the EPA's decision, saying that E15 would cause engine damage as well as food shortages. E15 has been sold in some states since the middle of 2012, starting in Kansas, and there have not been any widespread reports of problems with the biofuel but it's not being sold just like any other fuel. greenDOTautoblogDOTcom/2013/05/10/maine-votes-to-ban-ethanol-in-gasoline-takes-stand-against-e15/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1368317268968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 20:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368321450267-9</Id><Topic><Title>IRS admits to improperly targeting conservative groups</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368219687891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:01:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON Senior Internal Revenue Service officials knew agents were targeting tea party groups as early as 2011, according to a draft of an inspector general's report obtained by The Associated Press that seemingly contradicts public statements by the IRS commissioner. The IRS apologized Friday for what it acknowledged was "inappropriate" targeting of conservative political groups during the 2012 election to see if they were violating their tax-exempt status. The agency blamed low-level employees, saying no high-level officials were aware. But on June 29, 2011, Lois G. Lerner, who heads the IRS division that oversees tax-exempt organizations, learned at a meeting that groups were being targeted, according to the watchdog's report. At the meeting, she was told that groups with "Tea Party," "Patriot" or "9/12 Project" in their names were being flagged for additional and often burdensome scrutiny, the report says.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1368321450267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>