<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-28"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372403237634-1</Id><Title>Abengoa Opens Pilot Plant That Turns Waste Into Biofuels</Title><Msg>Abengoa Opens Pilot Plant That Turns Waste Into Biofuels 27 June 2013 June 27 (Bloomberg) — Abengoa SA, Spain’s largest biofuels producer, inaugurated a demonstration plant that can make bioethanol from municipal solid waste, its first using the technology. The facility in Babilafuente, central Spain, can treat 25,000 tons of municipal solid waste to generate as much as 1.5 million liters (396,000 gallons) of bioethanol, which can be used as an alternative fuel, Seville-based Abengoa said. The plant is the largest globally than can produce biofuels from waste, according to Bloomberg New Energy Finance. Its technology involving enzymes can prevent more than 80 percent of the waste from going into landfills while also being a source of clean energy, Abengoa said in a statement. The developer of solar and water desalination projects is also building a second-generation biofuel plant in Kansas that uses corn stalks and leaves as feedstock. Second-generation biofuels are made from plant waste or organic material rather than food crops. Abengoa also has plans for a $110 million waste-to-energy facility in Arizona that will generate electricity from municipal waste. bnef</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372403237634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 03:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372415683946-2</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jojomaxi the idiot here.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1372415683946</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 06:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372415721850-3</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jojomax the commie rat.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1372415721850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 06:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372416030503-4</Id><Topic><Title>Sen. Feinstein plans power plant carbon bill</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1371773048802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>finestink os a commie coward #$%$ devil and will rot in hell forever.</Msg><Username>raul_10_spain</Username><Timestamp>1372416030503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 06:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372425553634-5</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Banks became much more solvent after the sheep were convinced to pay more for bank shares and gold. If enough briefcases get presented for filling with €500 &amp; €200 euro notes the banking system would have had to sell gold or more bank shares. So the prices needed to be higher. The sheep have complied well and are being thoroughly fleeced. The gold price has been steadily collapsing since the euro crisis of 2011 which indicates the gold sheep must be running out of money. The banks of Europe have by no means run out of gold to sell…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372425553634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372427331824-6</Id><Title>Is there Any news on Royal Dutch offer 4 talisman energy? Is xom interested too?</Title><Msg>I heard rumors rds looking to replace falling production and Bc tlm down from 24 to 11 looking to pounce</Msg><Username>ianwallach</Username><Timestamp>1372427331824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 09:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372429478899-7</Id><Title>Universal Bioenergy Inc. (UBRG).............. Another new contract was announced today</Title><Msg>eom</Msg><Username>ubrg_07</Username><Timestamp>1372429478899</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372429637539-8</Id><Title>Gold &amp; Oil Price...</Title><Msg>Gold @ 300 euros per ounce. Oil @30 euros per barrel. That is where this commodity collapse will end. How much gold do you think Europe might own? Germany ran trade surpluses continuously from the early 1950s until the time the euro was created, and the Netherlands ran huge surpluses too. One of the purposes of the euro was to find a way to sell $ and gold to someone other than a German and receive an asset -- € -- that one could spend and invest in Germany. Without the euro, and considering Germany's trade balance situation, if a German corporation or individual sold dollars or gold bars for Deutsche Marks it would result in another German corporation or individual owning the dollars or gold bars. It was simply mathematically impossible for foreigners to accumulate Deutsche Marks with Germany run trade surpluses year after year - Germany owned the foreigners $, gold, etc. The only way to get rid of the unwanted foreign exchange was to find a way for Frenchmen, Italians, Spaniards, Greeks, etc to buy up the $ and gold Germans owned in exchange for euros. Euros withdraw from BNP Paribas in Paris look the same as euros withdrawn from any bank in Germany.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372429637539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372429908888-9</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't they have message boards in #$%$ Germany ?</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1372429908888</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:31:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372430044852-10</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah but Democrats have them all occupied trying to figure out how to take away everyone else's liberty and freedom...</Msg><Username>jugeard_bastid</Username><Timestamp>1372430044852</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372433615539-11</Id><Topic><Title>hansesteelyard &amp; bluecheese have serious OCD</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1371420582357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where else could I find the imbecility of the n;: e;: g;: r;: o on display &amp; the biggest oil pig on the planet + its acolytes in one place? I consider it good strategy to think like my partner and she dislikes both. In literature the concept is akin to "foil". In politics the concept is enemy. Germany herself has declared war on this industry in every way a Sovereign power can. You get no formal declaration for the same reason the mythical "gods" did not deign to speak to lower creatures - only destroy them if they annoyed them. My role is to consider my woman's views and country's views equal to the Divine. There is nothing better to motivate the mind &amp; body than an arouse fool to take the opposing point of view. I explained this before. You don't like this Maxwizard? Too bad....</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372433615539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:33:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372438392973-12</Id><Topic><Title>Brief cases full of €500 notes disappearing from banks around Europe...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372337023704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 08:43:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Firstly,our American oil companies including XOM are diversified by investing in natural gas which is a green type of energy.The demand for oil is good for another 5 to 10 years.You write off the oil barons too easily. On another subject, I do not understand why some contributors in here characterize you as a liberal since you show a decided leaning toward feudal notions of nobleness and privilege. But then,chacun a son gout. I enjoy your postings as they show an academic streak and are non biblical and scientific.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1372438392973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 12:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372441630768-13</Id><Title>Rather than try and cut CO2, we should build a super spaceship to take a handful of the best humans</Title><Msg>to seed another planet.</Msg><Username>stevemcqueen7890</Username><Timestamp>1372441630768</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 13:47:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372443714935-14</Id><Title>OIL NEXT TO BREAK DOWN</Title><Msg>BUY PUTS</Msg><Username>jjohns8181</Username><Timestamp>1372443714935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 14:21:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372477329703-15</Id><Topic><Title>Brief cases full of €500 notes disappearing from banks around Europe...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372337023704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-27 08:43:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don’t think you appreciate the implications of a 20%/year drop in photovoltaic power prices. It should be obvious who is causing that to happen too, and that there is no limit to how long the campaign can be sustained. OAO Gazprom will be the first Oil &amp; Gas Hog to be taken down by the wolf packs. It’s a big one. They just lost a case with RWE AG over oil-linked gas prices which will cost them billions of euros. Their market is being destroyed by Germany’s relentless buildup of solar &amp; wind capacity. They are basically in the position of begging for customers now. It is better to sell energy at 0 profit instead of lose money on fixed costs with no customer. Gazprom has the back of a government backing too, but not one with as deep of pockets as Germany. We will absorb the fixed costs until they are low enough to wipe competitors in any market. Then the wolf packs will roam freely...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372477329703</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 23:42:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>