<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365672445762-1</Id><Topic><Title>after Texas stab massacre---WE NEED KNIFE CONTROL !!!</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365621144762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 15:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See maxidopey u still cant any thumbs up u fuked up commie sewer rat.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1365672445762</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 05:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365676069758-2</Id><Topic><Title>gun safety= "you don't have guns---we do"---Government.</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365524992560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:29:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'll say it again</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365676069758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 06:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365682157730-3</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very useful:</Msg><Username>clinekate341</Username><Timestamp>1365682157730</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:09:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365683220156-4</Id><Topic><Title>GOOD LUCK TO BLUE STATES---selling municipal bonds after Detroit and Stockton CA</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365676148938</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 06:29:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all lib commie dumbocraps states now going to starve like the commie rats they are.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1365683220156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365684875341-5</Id><Title>Obummer---the Food Stamp King</Title><Msg>GREAT RECORD HUH?</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365684875341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:54:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365686983951-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer---the Food Stamp King</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365684875341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:54:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What relevance does this have to XOM?</Msg><Username>lior_c</Username><Timestamp>1365686983951</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365687192447-7</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good report!</Msg><Username>hargreaves_leo</Username><Timestamp>1365687192447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365687644624-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obummer---the Food Stamp King</Title><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365684875341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:54:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ACTUALLY, QUITE A BIT</Msg><Username>gcoffman008</Username><Timestamp>1365687644624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:40:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365688300745-9</Id><Title>Renewables, Efficiency Take Flight In US Air Force Energy Strategy</Title><Msg>Renewables, Efficiency Take Flight In US Air Force Energy Strategy April 10, 2013 Silvio Marcacci Unstable global energy supplies and greatly reduced federal funding might be the two biggest threats facing the US Air Force – but it looks like clean energy technology is the solution to both. US Air Force jet image via Shutterstock That’s the message from the US Air Force Energy Strategic Plan, which signals a major shift toward energy efficiency, renewables, distributed generation and microgrids, and green buildings to “actively seek solutions to the energy challenges that pose a threat to our operations.” USAF action could have a significant impact on America’s energy consumption and emissions footprint. After all, this one single branch of the military represents 48% of all Department of Defense (DoD) energy consumption, which in turn represents 80% of all energy consumption by the federal government. Massive Reach, Massive Footprint Put simply, the Air Force uses a tremendous amount of resources every year: it burns 2.5 billion gallons of aviation fuel, uses 64 trillion BTUs of energy, and consumes 27 billion gallons of water. That all adds up to a $9 billion annual energy bill (8% of the USAF’s total 2011 budget), a $150 million water bill, and 35 million metric tons of carbon dioxide emissions. Air Force brass are realistic about their resource footprint, admitting the USAF will continue to consume large quantities of energy for the foreseeable future. But, using less energy is a strategic imperative. “Reducing demand for energy is the single, best action the Air Force can take to improve its energy security,” says the report. Less Energy, Stronger Air Force Reducing demand is where the strategic plan truly takes flight with the Air Force’s most ambitious goals. The USAF aims ... cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/04/10/renewables-efficiency-take-off-in-us-air-force-energy-strategic-plan/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365688300745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365689269403-10</Id><Title>Universal Bioenergy Inc. (UBRG) and Elite Pharmaceuticals, Inc. (ELTP) getting ready!!!!!!</Title><Msg>dont miss it.</Msg><Username>eltp_22</Username><Timestamp>1365689269403</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:07:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365690039889-11</Id><Title>House Republicans push to give Keystone pipeline approval authority to Congress</Title><Msg>By Sean Cockerham | McClatchy Newspapers WASHINGTON — Promoters of the Keystone XL pipeline are agitating for its fast approval now that the State Department has downplayed the project’s impact on global warming. Energy leaders in the House of Representatives back a bill to force the government to approve it, and the premier of the Canadian province of Alberta is in Washington lobbying for the project. Some Republican congressmen dismissed concerns at a hearing Wednesday on the Keystone bill that the jumbo pipeline to tap Canada’s greenhouse gas-intensive oil sands would warm the planet. Texas Rep. Joe Barton was skeptical of the linkage that scientists have made between greenhouse gas emissions and climate change. “If you’re a believer in the Bible, one would have to say the great flood is an example of climate change. That’s certainly not because mankind had overdeveloped hydrocarbon energy,” Barton said, It’s up to President Barack Obama to decide whether to allow the 1,700-mile pipeline to bring oil from the Alberta oil sands to U.S. refineries on the Gulf Coast. The bill, sponsored by Nebraska Republican Rep. Lee Terry, seeks to take that authority out of the president’s hands. TransCanada Corp. first applied to build the pipeline in 2008, and Alexander Pourbaix, the company’s president for energy and oil pipelines, called Wednesday for swift approval, saying it still might be “many months” before Obama decides. Alberta Premier Alison Redford also is in Washington lobbying for approval of Keystone, saying in an address at the Brookings Institution research center that denial of the pipeline would be an ongoing thorn in relations between Canada and the United States. A coalition of Keystone opponents suggested that Redford cut short her time in Washington and mcclatchydcDOTcom/2013/04/10/188191/house-republicans-push-to-give.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365690039889</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365690118812-12</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing!</Msg><Username>garner_nicole</Username><Timestamp>1365690118812</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365694017197-13</Id><Topic><Title>XOM Insider Trading Reported !!</Title><Username>rose.lazo</Username><Timestamp>1361977364676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome stuff!</Msg><Username>tommyunknow</Username><Timestamp>1365694017197</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:26:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365697737307-14</Id><Topic><Title>'Teen Mom' star Farrah Abraham: Yes I made a porno</Title><Username>jack_kerouac</Username><Timestamp>1365605136871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 10:45:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Good grief, do you think Obama will blame Bush for this too!" At this point I'm inclined to praise the behavior. The more Americans spend the richer it will make Germans. I'm quite impressed by the ability of a certain American Hausfrau to spend too. I'm enjoying myself quite a bit...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1365697737307</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 12:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365727134502-15</Id><Title>Wind energy grows 28% in a year, delivering more economic benefits to America than ever</Title><Msg>Wind energy grows 28% in a year, delivering more economic benefits to America than ever Washington, DC, April 11--Wind energy grew 28 percent in America last year, setting a new installation record and confirming its status as a mainstream energy source, according to the American Wind Energy Association's U.S. Wind Industry Annual Market Report for 2012, released today on a webinar for association members and reporters. In its best year ever, the U.S. industry topped all energy sources with 42 percent of all new U.S. electric generating capacity. Over 6,700 new wind turbines were erected, which produce enough electricity to power the equivalent of 3.5 million homes. Overall, America finished the year with 45,100 wind turbines that can power 15.2 million homes. The bumper crop of wind energy benefited the U.S. economy across all 50 states, through $25 billion in private investment in new U.S. wind farms, tens of millions of dollars paid to landowners and local communities in lease payments and property taxes, and billions in projected savings for electricity consumers. In fact the impact of wind power development was so strong that an industry analyst said it caused a noticeable uptick in the entire U.S. economy in the fourth quarter. "We had an incredibly productive year in 2012," said Rob Gramlich, Interim CEO of the American Wind Energy Association (AWEA). "It really showed what this industry can do and the impact we can have with a continued national commitment to renewable energy. We're doing what Americans overwhelmingly say they want: making more clean, renewable energy, and creating good jobs in U.S. factories." AWEA's report found that over 550 factories across the country provide parts and services for the wind energy industry, which provided 80,000 American jobs in 2012. Wind power also aweaDOTorg/newsroom/pressreleases/annual-report-2012.cfm</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1365727134502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365730262552-16</Id><Title>MAXIPAD MAXIPAD</Title><Msg>knee pads are on sale at Walmart!!!!!!</Msg><Username>max_suks_coc</Username><Timestamp>1365730262552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>