<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357621892590-1</Id><Title>Alberta lakes show chemical effects of oilsands, study finds</Title><Msg>Alberta lakes show chemical effects of oilsands, study finds Pollutants from 50 years of oilsands production found in lake 90 km from facilities By Margo McDiarmid, Environment Unit, CBC News Posted: Jan 7, 2013 3:14 PM ET Last Updated: Jan 7, 2013 4:54 PM ET Read 606 comments606 A new study released today suggests chemicals from 50 years of oilsands production are showing up in increasing amounts in lakes in northern Alberta. And the effects are being felt much farther away than previously thought. The joint study between scientists at Queen's University in Kingston, Ont., and Environment Canada looked at core samples from five lakes close to the oilsands mining and upgrading operations in Fort McMurray, Alta. They also studied samples from Namur Lake, 90 kilometres northwest. The authors focused on polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons, or PAHs. These are cancer-causing chemicals that are released when things are burned. They can occur naturally — from forest fires, volcanic activity and geological deposits — but burning petroleum in the production of the oilsands leaves a particular fingerprint, so the scientists were able to trace where the PAHs in the core samples came from. A new study released today suggests chemicals from 50 years of oilsands production are showing up in increasing amounts in lakes in northern Alberta. And the effects are being felt much farther away than previously thought. The joint study between scientists at Queen's University in Kingston, Ont., and Environment Canada looked at core samples from five lakes close to the oilsands mining and upgrading operations in Fort McMurray, Alta. They also studied samples from Namur Lake, 90 kilometres northwest. The authors focused on polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons, or PAHs. These are cancer-causing chemicals that are released when things are burned. They can occur naturally — from forest fires, volcanic activity and geological deposits — but burning petroleum in the production of the oilsands leaves a particular fingerprint, so the scientists were able to trace where the PAHs in the core samples came from. A new study has found heightened levels of cancer-causing chemicals traced to Alberta's oilsands developments in lakes surrounding Fort McMurray (lower right in this Google satellite map image), including Lake Namur, marked by the A. (Google Maps) The study found that the levels of PAHs in all six lakes had increased anywhere from 2½ times to 23 times background levels in the early 1960s, before the start of oilsands mining in the region. The PAHs fall into the water from air pollution and are deposited in the mud over time. One of the study's authors, biologist John Smol from Queen's University, says these formerly pristine northern lakes now have the same chemical composition as lakes near urban areas. "This is an early warning indicator of what is happening, he said. "These lakes are not pollution pits by any means, but these wilderness lakes are similar to your typical urban lake." In response to the study, Federal Environment Minister Peter Kent said that the industry has been making an effort to reduce its pollution but he also says that the new federal-provincial monitoring system that was announced last year will play a big part in keeping an eye on contaminants coming from the oilsands. "Certainly oilsands operators in the last 22 years, since 1990, have reduced their [greenhouse gases] for example and their other contaminants by close to 40 per cent. But this report reminds us of the need of continuing cumulative monitoring to be sure we don't get into situations where cumulative levels do get past acceptable levels." Smol says scientists were surprised to see that even Namur Lake, the farthest away, was being affected. "The footprint of the tarsands is much further," he said. "Here we have effects 90 kilometres away." The study warns the chemical deposits will increase as oilsands production in northern Alberta triples in size in the next 25 years. Other studies have warned of problems The effect of the oilsands on the environment is highly controversial. There was little monitoring of the air and water in the region before the production started and there is a polarized debate about what is considered "natural" occurrence of petroleum deposits in lakes and rivers. But other studies have suggested problems. A study in 2010 by University of Alberta scientist David Schindler discovered deformed fish in Lake Athabasca downstream from the oilsands. It caused a huge public outcry and eventually led to a federal-provincial environmental monitoring plan for the Alberta oilsands announced last February. Monday's study concludes there is "little doubt of the unprecedented increases of PAHs" in northeastern Alberta's lakes, and warns of "striking contaminant increases consistent with the prevailing winds blowing across local upgrading facilities and surface-mining areas." The scientists also took a look at how the chemicals from the oilsands are affecting zooplankton, which are sort of the canary in the coal mine in freshwater research. Zooplankton are tiny little organisms the size of a dot that float around in water and are eaten by fish. So far, the study shows the zooplankton are doing fine, with numbers at an increasing level. Scientists think warmer temperatures caused by climate change are actually helping them to survive the effects of the chemicals. But that may only be short-term good news. The study warns of the "unknown" long-term ecological effects of the PAHs, as increasing amounts of the chemicals occur in freshwater lakes and are absorbed by fish, birds and up the food chain to humans. DOCUMENT PAGES Zoom « Page 1 of 6 » cbcDOTca/news/business/story/2013/01/07/pol-oilsands-alberta-lakes-pollution-pah.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357621892590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 00:11:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357643513820-2</Id><Topic><Title>God Choose President Obama to Saved America, AGAIN!!!! Radical Republicans on Suicide Watch......</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1357590559189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ #$%$ #$%$</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357643513820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 06:11:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357655728692-3</Id><Topic><Title>God Choose President Obama to Saved America, AGAIN!!!! Radical Republicans on Suicide Watch......</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1357590559189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG! You're as ignorant as can be!</Msg><Username>yankeeddandy</Username><Timestamp>1357655728692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 09:35:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357660587272-4</Id><Topic><Title>God Choose President Obama to Saved America, AGAIN!!!! Radical Republicans on Suicide Watch......</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1357590559189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Goofy post!</Msg><Username>bobhals</Username><Timestamp>1357660587272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:56:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357661603953-5</Id><Topic><Title>China Increases Overall Renewable Energy Capacity</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357581442639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:57:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>China is finally mastering 7th century technology.</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1357661603953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:13:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357662191185-6</Id><Topic><Title>God Choose President Obama to Saved America, AGAIN!!!! Radical Republicans on Suicide Watch......</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1357590559189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Low information voters choose President Obama not knowing he wants to fundamentally reform America into a European style socialist country.</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1357662191185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:23:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357669594504-7</Id><Title>With decision looming, green groups press Obama to kill Keystone XL pipeline</Title><Msg>With decision looming, green groups press Obama to kill Keystone XL pipeline By Zack Colman - 01/08/13 10:02 AM ET More than 70 green groups urged President Obama in a Monday letter to kill the Keystone XL pipeline to make good on promises to address climate change. Obama has publicly pledged to tackle climate change a handful of times since Hurricane Sandy struck the East Coast, though without detailing specific policy plans. In their letter, the groups said Obama should speak out more often on climate change, impose emissions limits on existing coal-fired power plants and focus on creating clean-energy jobs. They added the president also should shut down the proposed pipeline that would bring Canadian oil sands to Gulf Coast refineries. “Hurricane Sandy made it tragically clear that many communities are extremely vulnerable to climate change. We can and we must build back better — with investment in sustainable infrastructure, not the kind of carbon-intensive development that helped drive this problem in the first place,” the groups wrote in the letter. Green groups have been expecting a final decision on Keystone from the State Department for several weeks. State has final say on the project’s northern leg because it crosses into Canada. The project cleared one of its final hurdles last week by getting a positive review from the Nebraska Department of Environmental Quality. The state determined a revised route for the pipeline posed minimal environmental harm, though opponents disagreed with the assessment. Green groups have expressed optimism that Obama’s pick of Sen. John Kerry (D-Mass.) to replace Secretary of State Hillary Clinton signals a greater administration emphasis on climate change. And with the State Department holding the keys to Keystone, some environmentalists hope Kerry will stop the project. The pipeline, however, has industry approval and support from a swath of the public. And it is unclear whether Obama, who has said he wants to enhance the nation’s energy exporting prowess, would want to pick a fight with the oil-and-gas lobby early in his second term. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/276047-with-decision-looming-green-groups-press-obama-on-keystone-xl</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357669594504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:26:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357670006125-8</Id><Title>EPA fracking study may dodge some tough questions</Title><Msg>EPA fracking study may dodge some tough questions Posted on January 7, 2013 at 7:16 am by Associated Press Comments(0) Range Resources workers stand near the rig that drills into the shale at a well site in Washington, Pa. (AP Photo/Keith Srakocic) PITTSBURGH — An ongoing U.S. Environmental Protection Agency study on natural gas drilling and its potential for groundwater contamination has gotten tentative praise so far from both industry and environmental groups. Glenn Paulson, the EPA’s science adviser, describes the project as “one of the most aggressive public outreach programs in EPA history.” The final report won’t come out until late 2014. But a 275-page progress report was released in December and, for all its details, shows that the EPA doesn’t plan to address one contentious issue — how often drinking water contamination might occur. Congress ordered the EPA to study the potential effects of hydraulic fracturing, or fracking, which entails blasting a mixture of water, sand and hazardous chemicals at underground shale to release the gas or oil captured in the rock. As a gas rush surged in parts of the Marcellus Shale region that underlies Pennsylvania, New York, Ohio and West Virginia concerns arose for the watershed that provides drinking water for 17 million people from Philadelphia to New York City. For the study, the EPA is talking to experts from the industry, the environmental community, and universities. It’s conducting its own research and using federal supercomputers to analyze the possibility of contamination. In the report, the EPA describes what it is and isn’t studying. The agency also indicates its final report won’t provide a measurement of the likelihood of contamination — for example, once every 100,000 wells or once every 1,000. The industry and many federal and state officials say fracking is safe when done properly, but environmental groups and some scientists contend the risk of contamination is too great. Earthworks, an environmental group based in Washington, said it welcomes the EPA study but has concerns with plans not to include some probability of groundwater contamination in the final report. The EPA had planned to do both computer simulations of water contamination and actual field tests at drilling sites. But the agency hasn’t found a drilling company to partner with to test groundwater around a drilling site. That leaves the computer simulations. But the EPA said those won’t be able to address the likelihood of contamination “occurring during actual field operations.” “In its inability to find a single company willing to test water quality before and after drilling and fracking, the EPA is being thwarted in perhaps the most important part of its study of fracking’s impacts,” Earthworks said in a statement. “Computer simulations are not enough,” Alan Septoff, a spokesman for Earthworks, said. He said the EPA study and any future studies should consider the likelihood of water contamination. The EPA did not immediately respond to requests for comment. The progress report says the EPA is studying the possible impact on drinking water at several stages of the fracking process: when water is drawn from reservoirs or underground sources and used for fracking; when a chemical mix is injected into the ground to break up rock; when wastewater from fracking is disposed of; how the drilling wells and wastewater-storage wells are constructed; and the potential for toxic fluids to migrate from deep underground to near-surface drinking water supplies. The American Petroleum Institute, an industry lobby based in Washington, said in a statement that the progress report “is just the first step in a multi-year research study.” “More collaboration, continued transparency and stakeholder involvement are essential elements for any scientifically sound study, and we hope that the rest of this process remains open and any data released has the necessary context,” API policy adviser Stephanie Meadows said. Despite its concerns, Earthworks described the EPA study as a positive step. “It represents a step towards EPA’s first real scientific inquiry into the safety of fracking,” the group said. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/01/07/epa-fracking-study-may-dodge-some-tough-questions/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357670006125</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:33:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357671035072-9</Id><Title>90% Renewable Electricity By 2015 Is Uruguay’s Goal</Title><Msg>90% Renewable Electricity By 2015 Is Uruguay’s Goal January 8, 2013 Jake Richardson In September of 2011, Uruguay announced it could increase its wind power capacity by 800 MW. Not long afterwards, that figure was increased to 1,000 MW. In the beginning of January 2013, a new goal was publicized: 90% of all its electricity from renewables by 2015. Uruguay wind turbines Image Credit: Daniel Stonek, Wiki Commons Though this figure might seem like a pipe dream to some, consider the fact Nicaragua has stated a similar goal, and both countries actually do have a chance to deliver the goods. Uruguay has slightly more than half of Nicaragua’s six million people, but it has 1,500 MW of hydroelectric power already. About 45% of its electricity comes from hydro and 15% from biomass, so the remaining 30% is expected to be generated by wind. One thing in the country’s favor is the increasing renewable energy investment trend in South America. This trend is creating demand for turbine manufacturers like Vestas, which is supplying Chile with 90 MW of turbines soon for a new wind farm there. Extra wind power is required in Uruguay to complement its hydro, which is robust but intermittent. Developing domestic renewable energy is an intelligent choice — especially for countries that rely heavily upon foreign oil. Although the initial outlay of capital may seem shockingly large, the overall amount of money they give away to other nations for oil has a detrimental impact on their economies. These domestic energy projects also employ local people and teach them new technology skills. In August, it was reported that 21 wind farms were under development in 11 parts of Uruguay, so this energy independence movement is definitely under way. Green energy is also a good choice for Uruguay because it helps preserve local natural habitats, and eco-tourism is an important part of its economy. As electric vehicles become more common, the country will have implemented the infrastructure changes it needs in order to accommodate them, and hopefully reduce reliance on gas-powered cars, so there will likely be less air pollution, which can cause health problems and even premature death. sDOTtt/1y7EF</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357671035072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:50:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357673317371-10</Id><Title>Green Bay utility to stop burning coal at two state plants</Title><Msg>Green Bay utility to stop burning coal at two state plants By Thomas Content of the Journal Sentinel Jan. 4, 2013 A Wisconsin utility will stop burning coal in some of its aging boilers at power plants in Green Bay and Wausau, and invest $300 million to upgrade other plants under an agreement reached with the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. Wisconsin Public Service Corp. of Green Bay will pay a $1.2 million civil penalty to settle allegations that it violated the Clean Air Act by making upgrades to the power plants over the years without installing modern pollution controls. It will also spend $6 million on environmental mitigation projects. The agreement announced Friday is similar to settlements the EPA has reached with utilities across the country, including We Energies of Milwaukee and Dairyland Power Cooperative of La Crosse. A settlement is also being negotiated with Wisconsin Power &amp; Light Co. of Madison, which announced it planned to shut down its coal-fired power plant in Cassville, on the Mississippi River in southwest Wisconsin. Under the WPS agreement, the utility will invest $250 million to upgrade environmental controls at its 30-year-old Weston 3 coal-fired power plant, located near Wausau. The additional $50 million would be spent if the utility decides to replace rather than retire the old coal plants. The utility's 437,000 ratepayers in northeastern and north-central Wisconsin would pay for the projects on their monthly electric bills. Exactly how much bills will go up would be determined in coming years. If approved by the state Public Service Commission, the Weston 3 project would take more than three years to complete and create 200 construction jobs. Older boilers at Weston, and two older boilers in downtown Green Bay at the Pulliam power plant, all built in the 1950s or 1960s, would either be shut down, or be converted to burn natural gas, under the settlement. "This settlement will eliminate thousands of tons of harmful air pollution each year, thus improving air quality in Wisconsin and downwind areas," Ignacia Moreno, assistant attorney general for the Justice Department, said in a statement. Under the settlement, filed in federal court, WPS admitted no wrongdoing. "We acted then using what we believed to be the proper process for making the improvements," said Terry Jensky, WPS vice president of generation assets. "Many utilities across the country followed the same procedures and they have or are now facing similar action from the EPA." The EPA said the settlement targets pollutants that are released into the air when coal is burned, and contribute to acid rain, smog and haze. The pollutants cause health problems as they are converted in the air to fine particles that can cause severe respiratory and cardiovascular impacts, the agency says. The settlement could result in an unknown number of staff reductions, the utility said. In many cases, the smaller coal-fired power plant boilers have not been running as much as they used to because of changes in the Midwest energy market and the low price of natural gas, said Kerry Spees, WPS spokesman. WPS also agreed to spend $6 million on a variety of environmental projects, including a program to provide incentives to replace inefficient wood stoves in Brown and Marathon counties, as well as upgrades to the company's wind and hydroelectric power generation. Jennifer Feyerherm, who focuses on energy issues for the Sierra Club in Wisconsin, said Friday the settlement is good because it will shutter "some of the oldest plants in the country" and reduce emissions of sulfur dioxide, a pollutant linked to asthma and increased rates of hospitalization for respiratory illnesses. But she said the Sierra Club wanted the EPA to set more stringent standards for the Green Bay coal plant in particular. "It doesn't go as far as we had hoped," Feyerherm said. "But every step that we take in phasing out older coal plants will improve our health, and as we do that, we're making room for investments in clean energy." jsonlineDOTcom/business/green-bay-utility-to-stop-burning-coal-at-two-state-plants-1a88og6-185720931.html</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357673317371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:28:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357673762861-11</Id><Topic><Title>God Choose President Obama to Saved America, AGAIN!!!! Radical Republicans on Suicide Watch......</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1357590559189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check the stock market "fool" and stop lying Satan's follower.....Radical Republicans still on Suicide Watch......</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1357673762861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:36:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357674050230-12</Id><Title>France launches new offshore wind power tender</Title><Msg>France launches new offshore wind power tender 8 Jan, 2013, 11.10PM IST, Reuters PARIS: The French government on Tuesday launched a second tender to build 1,000 megawatts, the equivalent of a nuclear reactor, in offshore wind capacity as the country seeks to become a leading player in the industry and cut its reliance on nuclear. The tender offer is for a</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357674050230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:40:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357674427180-13</Id><Title>US Energy Initiatives to set up its first Calif. biodiesel plant</Title><Msg>US Energy Initiatives to set up its first Calif. biodiesel plant By U.S. Energy Initiatives Corp. | January 08, 2013 USEI will use Methes process technology at its small-scale plants in California Photo: Methes Energies International Ltd. U.S. Energy Initiatives Corp. announced that is has signed a letter of intent to form a joint venture that will provide the tools, experience and support to build several small-scale biodiesel plants in California featuring Methes Energies Canada Inc.’s Denami 600 technology. “We are excited to be working with companies with such stellar reputations,” said USEI CEO Anthony Miller. “The management of USEI believes that in 2013, [the company] will center on biodiesel first, then later its oil and gas technologies. We have decided to take this green alternative path first because it provides us with the most successful path possible. We have formed joint ventures with two companies that have significant success in this field, and these relationships are those that will fuel our growth. Methes Energies Canada Inc., a wholly-owned subsidiary of Methes Energies International Ltd. … is a biodiesel equipment provider and biodiesel producer. Our second joint venture firm (yet to be named) is a biodiesel producing company located in Riverside County, Calif. Under our joint ventures with these firms, we will develop a biodiesel producing plant in Southern California with a capacity of producing more than 1 MMgy featuring the Methes’ Denami 600 biodiesel processor. The Denami 600, one of Methes main products, has one of the smallest footprints in the industry. The Denami 600 can quickly and easily be set up anywhere to produce 1.3 million gallons of ASTM quality biodiesel per year. The Denami 600 is modular and scalable in 1.3 million gallons per year increments. This plant is our primary focus for the first half of 2013, our goal is to build our initial biodiesel plant in here and build other plants throughout the U.S where strategically possible, based upon the success of our initial operations.” Miller said Methes will be involved in all aspects of the venture and more information, including USEI’s financing plan, will be released in coming weeks. biodieselmagazineDOTcom/articles/8872/us-energy-initiatives-to-set-up-its-first-calif-biodiesel-plant</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357674427180</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:47:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357680730815-14</Id><Title>Obama escalates slaughter of brown children in the third world</Title><Msg>Barak H Obama is drastically increasing drone usage in the Middle East with young soldiers using their joysticks to blow up villages in Afghanistan. Obama is ramping up plans to use drones against peace groups (terrorist sympathizers) on American soil. The medicated patsies in Tucson, Aurora, and Newtown are pretenses for incrimentally disarming US citizens as the two party duopoly under orders from New York central bankers demands more confiscatory taxes to service interest on an inextinguishable debt.</Msg><Username>lyubasha2004</Username><Timestamp>1357680730815</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:32:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357682294149-15</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (XOM)</Title><Username>liza.pugh329f</Username><Timestamp>1357651669041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 08:27:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone should report this #$%$ by hitting "Report Abuse.' It will help get Spammers off the Yahoo Boards.</Msg><Username>basherbuste_r</Username><Timestamp>1357682294149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:58:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357683238029-16</Id><Topic><Title>God Choose President Obama to Saved America, AGAIN!!!! Radical Republicans on Suicide Watch......</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1357590559189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are not an American. You are from the 3rd world so shut up. Obama is taking us to your third world status. Does that make you feel better? My guess is that you are from the Midevil East.</Msg><Username>eagle1776321</Username><Timestamp>1357683238029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:13:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357689424605-17</Id><Topic><Title>God Choose President Obama to Saved America, AGAIN!!!! Radical Republicans on Suicide Watch......</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1357590559189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, is this better? Low information voters choose President Obama knowing he wanted to fundamentally reform America into a European style socialist country.</Msg><Username>kyuzosix</Username><Timestamp>1357689424605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 18:57:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357691833842-18</Id><Title>Interior vows ‘high-level’ Arctic-drilling review after Shell’s mishaps</Title><Msg>Interior vows ‘high-level’ Arctic-drilling review after Shell’s mishaps By Ben Geman - 01/08/13 04:50 PM ET The Interior Department is launching a “high-level,” 60-day review of Shell’s troubled 2012 attempts to look for oil off Alaska’s northern coast after the company experienced a series of mishaps. The review arrives a week after Shell’s Kulluk drillship ran aground en route back from the Arctic region, and as Interior is under pressure from green activists to block 2013 drilling off Alaska’s coast. Interior said the review of 2012 Arctic operations will “help inform future permitting processes in the region.” Interior Secretary Ken Salazar, in a statement, said the Obama administration is committed to energy exploration in “frontier” regions like the Arctic, but also said careful oversight is needed. “Exploration allows us to better comprehend the true scope of our resources in the Arctic and to more fully understand the nature of the risks and benefits of development in this region, but we also recognize that the unique challenges posed by the Arctic environment demand an even higher level of scrutiny,” he said. The grounding of the Kulluk was among a number of woes Shell experienced in seeking to begin long-delayed drilling in the oil-rich Beaufort and Chukchi seas last year. A separate drillship, the Noble Discoverer, slipped its moorings and dragged anchor while heading to the Arctic, almost running aground in Dutch Harbor in July. Separately, a key piece of equipment the company needs on hand to contain a potential subsea blowout was damaged during testing. Ultimately, Shell did not win regulators’ permission to drill into oil-bearing zones, but was allowed to begin preliminary, so-called top-hole drilling last year. Interior said the review, which will include technical assistance from the U.S. Coast Guard, will identify “challenges and lessons learned.” “The review, which is expected to be completed within 60 days, will pay special attention to challenges that Shell encountered in connection with certification of its containment vessel, the Arctic Challenger; the deployment of its containment dome; and operational issues associated with its two drilling rigs, the Noble Discoverer and the Kulluk,” Interior said. The review will examine Shell’s safety management, oversight of contractors and ability to meet federal standards for development in the Arctic climate. The grounding of the Kulluk has created new uncertainties around Shell’s years-long, multibillion-dollar effort to strike oil in Arctic waters off Alaska’s coast. The next drilling window in the Arctic seas begins in the summer, when sea ice recedes. “Inspections are now underway to better understand the Kulluk’s overall condition. Once complete, we will know more about the Kulluk’s immediate future, including its availability for our ongoing exploration program. Before speculating on any impact to our exploration plans, we will first complete our detailed evaluation of the vessel’s condition,” Shell said in a statement Tuesday. The company said it welcomes Interior’s review. “While we completed our drilling operations off the North Slope safely and in accordance with robust permitting and regulatory standards, we nevertheless experienced challenges in supporting the program — especially in moving our rigs to and from the theater of operations,” Shell said. The company said it’s already in “dialogue” with Interior, and that “a high-level review will help strengthen our Alaska exploration program going forward.” Shell’s experiences could influence how much development ultimately takes place in the U.S. Arctic region. Companies including ConocoPhillips and Spanish oil giant Repsol also hold leases in federal waters off Alaska’s coast. Environmentalists bitterly oppose drilling in the rough waters off Alaska’s coast, calling it a threat to whales, polar bears and other endangered and sensitive wildlife that inhabit the Arctic seas. Michael LeVine, senior counsel with the group Oceana, said a broader federal review is needed and that “Shell has proven that it is not prepared to operate in Alaskan waters.” “A full investigation of Shell’s season of mishaps should include not only the Department of the Interior and Coast Guard, but also NOAA, and other agencies. The government must reassess its commitment to exploration in difficult places like the Arctic and how it makes decisions about our ocean resources,” he said Tuesday in response to Interior’s announcement. The U.S. Coast Guard has initiated a separate probe of the “circumstances and contributing factors” in the Dec. 31 grounding of the Kulluk on an island in the Gulf of Alaska. Interior's Bureau of Safety and Environmental Enforcement and the National Transportation Safety Board will provide technical advice in the probe, the Coast Guard said. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/276143-interior-vows-high-level-arctic-review-after-shells-mishaps</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357691833842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:37:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357692541372-19</Id><Title>Hands Off, Oil Industry Warns Government</Title><Msg>Hands Off, Oil Industry Warns Government By JOHN M. BRODER January 8, 2013, 2:59 pm7 Comments Jack Gerard, the often-combative chief executive of the American Petroleum Institute, said Tuesday that the United States was “at the crossroads of a great turning point” in the nation’s energy history. United States Energy Association Jack Gerard, chief executive of the American Petroleum Institute. As long as Congress and the Obama administration don’t mess it up, he warned. In a broad-gauge speech in Washington on the state of the American oil and gas industry, Mr. Gerard said that because of new petroleum finds and new drilling techniques – chiefly directional drilling and hydraulic fracturing in shale formations – the United States could become the world’s leading energy producer. “North America could become self-sufficient in liquid fuels in roughly 12 years,” Mr. Gerard said, citing figures from the International Energy Agency. “And as a potential energy exporter, we can help bring greater stability to the geopolitics of energy, to say nothing of the positive impacts increased U.S. supply would have for U.S. businesses, workers and consumers.” But he cautioned that this rosy future was dependent on the federal government’s not interfering with his industry, by, say, raising taxes on oil companies, or imposing new environmental regulations on fracking operations, or limiting greenhouse gas emissions from refineries. “The most important thing is to do no harm,” Mr. Gerard said in a question-and-answer period after his speech. “Don’t overreact and do anything that would impede or discourage what we see going forward state by state today.” He said that North Dakota, Texas and Pennsylvania had seen a huge boom in job creation and economic activity tied to drilling operations on private lands in recent years, while exploration on federal lands and waters has been stagnant or falling. He attributed the discrepancy to more business-friendly regulatory and tax policies at the state level, and he encouraged Congress and federal regulators to follow the lead of officials in state capitals. He urged the Obama administration to open more federal land and water to drilling, but said that this did not have to include national parks and environmentally sensitive areas. Mr. Gerard bristled at a suggestion that major oil companies benefit from billions of dollars in tax subsidies, saying that the Obama administration’s assertion that the industry enjoys $4 billion in unnecessary tax breaks is a “myth.” “The oil and gas industry gets no subsidies, zero, nothing,” he said. “We get cost-recovery benefits, much like other industries. You can go down the road of allowing economic activity, generating hundreds of billions to the government, or you can take the alternative route by trying to extract new revenue from industry by increasing their cost to do business.” He added, “We not only pay our fair share, we pay more than our fair share.” greenDOTblogsDOTnytimesDOTcom/2013/01/08/hands-off-oil-industry-warns-government/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357692541372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:49:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357695328519-20</Id><Topic><Title>Hands Off, Oil Industry Warns Government</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1357692541372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:49:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would get the #$%$ out of america and tell all the workers to call nobumba.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1357695328519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:35:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>