<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-21"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369130857995-1</Id><Title>maxipad ???</Title><Msg>Where is the commie coward runt #$%$ hiding?</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1369130857995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 06:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369142227045-2</Id><Title>Shell CEO says it’s too early to speculate about oil-price probe</Title><Msg>Shell CEO says it’s too early to speculate about oil-price probe May 21, 2013 at 6:49 am by Bloomberg Royal Dutch Shell Plc (RDSA) Chief Executive Officer Peter Voser said it’s too early to speculate about the European oil-price fixing probe and the company is committed to the “highest standard of corporate behavior.” Shell, BP Plc (BP/) and Statoil ASA (STL) are targets of a European Commission inquiry into whether prices of crude, refined oil products and biofuels were manipulated, potentially harming consumers. Platts, a price assessor owned by McGraw Hill Financial Inc. (MHFI), was also questioned as the probe was announced last week. “Since the investigation has just commenced it would be inappropriate to speculate about the outcome,” Voser told shareholders at the company’s annual general meeting in The Hague today. Shell is committed “to achieve the highest standard of corporate behavior.” The commission is trying to determine whether oil companies colluded to distort prices in the $3.4 trillion global crude market and in markets for fuel products. The probe has highlighted that some energy markets lack the transparency of stocks and bonds. “It’s important to bear in mind at this stage it’s just an investigation into facts and evidence and no adverse finding has been made,” Voser said today. “All Shell companies have fully cooperated with the EU investigation and will continue to do so going forward.” Platts’s North Sea Dated Brent benchmark sets the price of half the world’s crude, from Canada to Australia. Its kerosene assessments are used by the airline industry, where fuel accounts for about a third of operating costs. In the biofuels markets, the company assesses the price of ethanol and biodiesel as well as ethyl tert-butyl ether, an additive that’s used in gasoline production. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/21/shell-ceo-says-its-too-early-to-speculate-about-oil-price-probe/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369142227045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369143607687-3</Id><Topic><Title>German technology aiding Russian military buildup</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369108434086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quite the conclusion that just because the Russians are spending some money on their military that it does not bode well for oil. Obama just keeps printing money in the basement of the White House and U.S. budget deficits keep going higher. Stick to real estate as your conclusions are baseless. By the way, have you seen Xom's stock price lately? Konnen sich mich verstehen? Ich glaube nicht.</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1369143607687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369143745549-4</Id><Topic><Title>Why To Short XOM? OK</Title><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369095553864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You go right ahead and short Xom. And then feel the squeeze.</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1369143745549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369144077243-5</Id><Topic><Title>German technology aiding Russian military buildup</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369108434086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oooopaaalaa, Konnen Sie mich verstehen? Noch nicht.</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1369144077243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369144693921-6</Id><Topic><Title>Will James Inhofe Ask For Federal Assistance?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1369085870867</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>watch Inhofe and Coburn--they both voted NO for sandy funds AND voted NO for ALL FEMA funding (said agency NOT needed) for several years now. Watch the worms turn--or more like snakes they will come running with open arms for federal aid for Oklahoma the gop has become sickening to watch--at least the w bush phony Christian segment</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1369144693921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:58:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369146050361-7</Id><Topic><Title>German technology aiding Russian military buildup</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369108434086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of more interest to me is the steady sell-off in US government bonds the past year despite furious efforts by the Federal Reserve to prop them up. Where would they be without $1 trillion+ in pumping/year? It will be bad. As US credit collapses in the future, the taxes required to service the interest on the debt will crush your economy, and especially the oil industry. Your idiotic Fed has not been printing either, it has been borrowing from banks to pump the bond market and in turn the stock prices you mention. It may well resort to printing though, and then you will really see the interest rate shoot up. I look forward to watching the US attempt to maintain its Imperial military establishment trying to borrow from China and Germany at 8-10% and cover interest payments on $20+ trillion in debt. You will be in perilous shape. As for your idiotic stock: just wait and see what it trades at when $ interest rates hit such levels and US income taxes hit 90% + 20% VAT to cover the interest, and you have wealthy Americans renouncing their citizenship in droves. Further, I have friends who work for one of the defense contractors I mentioned. Their family has been in the industry since the 1930s. It amuses me greatly when weapons find their way to peaceful countries. If rednecks like you disapprove so much the better...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369146050361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369146066099-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why To Short XOM? OK</Title><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369095553864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great rebuttal, ahahahhaa</Msg><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369146066099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369146289216-9</Id><Topic><Title>Will James Inhofe Ask For Federal Assistance?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1369085870867</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those Confederate meridionals like Inhofe, hate big gummint and only love the big corporate greedos who sponsor their little suckholing hearts.Watch the crudball beg for FEMA assistance and kiss Obama's butt. Makes you wonder though about the clods who voted for this piece of nitrogeneous waste.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1369146289216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369147360401-10</Id><Topic><Title>Oil looking bullish. WTI oil soon over $100/barrel. $6/gal gas coming.</Title><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1369066497744</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:14:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A huge glut of oil in the market as oil prices go higher. Has anyone every heard of supply/demand? These markets are so manipulated With full support of yahoo clown on these boards. Bubble continues to build while idiots look the other way. Are you one those idiots "$100/barrel" ?</Msg><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369147360401</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369147401634-11</Id><Topic><Title>Why To Short XOM? OK</Title><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369095553864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Want a better rebuttal? Ever hear 'past performance is not an indicator of future results'? I could discuss such things as return on shareholder's equity, stock buyback program and natural gas prices, but I rather just encourage you to short Xom. Again, go ahead and short Xom. And then feel the squeeze.</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1369147401634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369147800520-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why To Short XOM? OK</Title><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369095553864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intelligence can't will a p I s s I n g Match with a schmuck. "And feel the Squeeze" Only 1% of XOM float is shorted ahahaha Keep that day job, schmuck!</Msg><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369147800520</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:50:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369148026847-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why To Short XOM? OK</Title><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369095553864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"can't win" typo..4:54am in Hawaii..yawn</Msg><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369148026847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:53:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369148283628-14</Id><Topic><Title>German technology aiding Russian military buildup</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369108434086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our idiotic Fed has not been borrowing from banks to pump up the bond market. A central bank implements quantitative easing by buying financial assets from commercial banks and other private institutions, thus increasing the monetary base. This is distinguished from the more usual policy of buying or selling government bonds in order to keep market interest rates at a specified target value. Expansionary monetary policy typically involves the central bank buying short-term government bonds in order to lower short-term market interest rates. Where do you think the Fed is getting the money to buy the assets? It may not literally be printing the money, but it is essentially the same thing. I never voted for Obama, he's a disaster and giving freebies to everyone. He'll try to just wipe out the debt when the interest surp#$%$ tax revenues. As far as defense goes, we can all blow each other up hundreds of times over. Who cares if they keep making bombs, except that it's a waste of money. You're probably happy, because the U.S. protects German #$%$ in exchange for having bombs and military bases on your soil. That's a deal I'd take too. I'll stick with Xom, you stick to real estate. Gruss Gott!</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1369148283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369148713241-15</Id><Topic><Title>Why To Short XOM? OK</Title><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369095553864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So quickly you resort to name calling and vitriolic remarks. You are not worth the powder to blow you up. You are not worth the waste of air you require. What are you going to do all summer during your break from elementary school? Don't bother replying. I don't plan on wasting any more words on you.</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1369148713241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 11:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369149051801-16</Id><Topic><Title>German technology aiding Russian military buildup</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369108434086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WRONG Federal Reserve Flow of funds release z.1 7 March 2013 P. 76, lines {32-45} liabilities of the Federal Reserve monetary authority; line 32 depository institution reserves: Q4 2012 $1.49 trillion up from $20.8 billion in 2007. That items is liability of the Federal Reserve, and asset of the banks they borrowed the money from. By definition it is a loan. What they did with the money is listed under assets: pump US government and mortgage prices buy buying with the $1.5 trillion they borrowed. Lose all your money I don't care. I will enjoy watching your countries tribulations too. You are quite simply a joke.…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369149051801</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 11:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369149433815-17</Id><Topic><Title>German technology aiding Russian military buildup</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369108434086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WRONG. And I am not wasting any more time on you. #$%$ off. What a dumb #$%$.</Msg><Username>stockminder</Username><Timestamp>1369149433815</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 11:17:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369149967417-18</Id><Topic><Title>German technology aiding Russian military buildup</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369108434086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you are accusing the Federal Reserve of falsifying the report? That would be a violation of US federal law. The line item is listed on the next page as an asset too. By definition it is the loan. Anybody educated in monetary economics with real experience in banking understands this too. Further this is why day traders and readers of journalist rags do not work for London banks, and why they should be regulated out of the markets entirely and prohibited from gambling, and especially on margin-- which if you have not done yet you will. LOL A true imbecile. Not even worthy #$%$ 2... It would be nauseating to see it.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1369149967417</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 11:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369150258011-19</Id><Topic><Title>Why To Short XOM? OK</Title><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369095553864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suggest that you take time off these boards to learn what you obviously don't know or understand. Guys like you just follow the heard w/o even knowing why. You posts confirms this. You have no real rebuttal but pretend that you do. 18 years under my belt in these markets, Jr. The only waste is you even being on these boards. You have nothing to offer "feel the squeeze" ahahahha ahahahhahaha I rest my case, rookie.</Msg><Username>high_surf_warning</Username><Timestamp>1369150258011</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 11:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369150563202-20</Id><Topic><Title>maxipad ???</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1369130857995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 06:07:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The commie POS must have gotten his but kicked. Guess he learned he was the most hated commie rat on this board.</Msg><Username>bluemax19</Username><Timestamp>1369150563202</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 11:36:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369152702757-21</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SHOULD BE IMPEACHED !!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>wwwwwwwwwwwppppppppppp</Username><Timestamp>1369151184251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 11:46:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>would be nice. he's shredded our constitution apart</Msg><Username>theinvestor229</Username><Timestamp>1369152702757</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 12:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369152728025-22</Id><Title>Universal Bioenergy Inc. (UBRG)</Title><Msg>watch it</Msg><Username>theinvestor229</Username><Timestamp>1369152728025</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 12:12:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369155980739-23</Id><Title>Can we make it to $100?</Title><Msg>It's been a long, long, long road... but I think we can make it to $100/share before the 'bubble bursts' at the end of this summer. Let's join the party and break out to some new highs!</Msg><Username>mookie771</Username><Timestamp>1369155980739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369158663611-24</Id><Title>Split Effective Date.</Title><Msg>When will they announce a 3 for 1 Splitzzzz?</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1369158663611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:51:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369159535454-25</Id><Title>Senators warned of ‘narrowing’ opportunity to increase gas exports</Title><Msg>Zack Colman - 05/21/13 12:50 PM ET The United States needs to move on natural-gas exports to take advantage of global demand as the number of international competitors grows by the day, experts told the Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee on Tuesday. Panelists warned during a forum convened by the Senate panel that the U.S. faces a "narrowing" window of opportunity to reap the economic benefit of exports. “If we wait too long … we will lose the jobs,” said Octavio Simoes, senior vice president of Sempra International and president of Sempra LNG (liquefied natural gas), in a refrain heard often Tuesday. The discussion on natural-gas exports comes after the Energy Department (DOE) last week green-lighted a second controversial project allowing exports to nations lacking a free-trade agreement with the U.S. Those projects, of which 19 are pending, require more scrutiny from the DOE than deals to nations that have a free-trade pact with America. Under federal law, the DOE must determine such proposals are in the public interest under federal law. That means exports must not significantly raise domestic energy prices or lower U.S. stockpiles too drastically. The applications are the subject of Capitol Hill debate regarding the future of the sudden glut in domestic natural gas supplies. Republicans, industry and some Democrats contend the benefits of shipping natural gas abroad — adding jobs, reducing the trade deficit and helping allies in need of energy — outweigh domestic price jumps, which analysts expect to be modest. “We simply cannot afford to needlessly drag our feet on exports, or we’re going to let real economic development opportunities, and the chance to provide our allies access to an abundant, affordable and clean source of energy, slip through our fingers,” committee ranking member Sen. Lisa Murkowski (R-Alaska thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/300995-experts-tell-senate-panel-opportunities-for-natural-gas-exports-narrowing</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369159535454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369160246956-26</Id><Title>Eos Energy Storage Raises $15 Million, Gets Funding From NRG Energy</Title><Msg>May 21, 2013 Zachary Shahan Eos Energy Storage has released its second big announcement of the month, a funding boost that includes funding from NRG Energy, a major US energy company. I just featured a long post on Eos Energy Storage less than a month ago, followed soon after by a post on its first pilot project (with Con Edison). Click that first one above for all kinds of details on the company’s energy storage technology. The essentials, however, are simply that Eos Energy Storage has developed a grid storage solution that is much cheaper than what has been on the market up until now. Of course, it has just launched its first pilot project, so we have to wait until it actually gets to market, but according to the company, that should be in 2014. The Eos Aurora battery is projected to cost $1,000/kW or $160/kWh. The cycle life is 10,000 full cycles (30 year life). And the storage system has a 75% round-trip eﬃciency. As such, the LCOE is very competitive. (Click to enlarge.) In the press release sent out late yesterday, Eos announced that it had raised $15 million Series B financing “with participation from a syndicate of 21 strategic and financial investors.” One very notable investor this round is NRG Energy. As the release notes, NRG Energy has “the nation’s largest independent power generation portfolio of fossil fuel, nuclear, solar and wind facilities.” Despite having its hands in some not so clean sources, it has been heavily focused on diversifying into clean energy and potentially disruptive technology solutions. This is the first time NRG has invested in an energy storage company. “Eos’s technology is of strategic interest to NRG as we seek to enhance the value of our generation assets and evaluate novel energy storage business opportunities,” said Denise Wilson, NRG Executive Vice President and President, New Businesses. “We have confidence in cleantechnicaDOTcom/2013/05/21/eos-energy-storage-raises-15-million-gets-funding-from-nrg-energy/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369160246956</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369162594652-27</Id><Topic><Title>Will James Inhofe Ask For Federal Assistance?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1369085870867</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the inhofe diaper is alreadystarting to stink--what a spineless jellyfish--all talk big man right until it affects his votes what mighty principals with principles the new gop</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1369162594652</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369162637754-28</Id><Title>IRS's Lerner Had History of Harassment, Inappropriate Religious Inquiries at FEC</Title><Msg>which she brought to the IRS where she decided to target Christians and conservatives. Completely consistent with Obamao's desires. weeklystandardDOTcom/blogs/irss-lerner-had-history-harassment-inappropriate-religious-inquiries-fec_725004.html?page=1</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1369162637754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369163442930-29</Id><Topic><Title>Split Effective Date.</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1369158663611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:51:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>never moron so #$%$ you poor slob.</Msg><Username>bluemax19</Username><Timestamp>1369163442930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 15:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369164022877-30</Id><Title>★★★★HEY DUMMIES...Just KEEP ON BUYING...Bwhahaha! DISASTER LOOMS</Title><Msg>very soon boys.....</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1369164022877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 15:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369167093778-31</Id><Topic><Title>IRS's Lerner Had History of Harassment, Inappropriate Religious Inquiries at FEC</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1369162637754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny you left out shulman--head of the irs--oh thats right--the W put him in place--sure he did a GREAT job for W but just terrible for Obama--yeppers pull this leg it plays jingle bells</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1369167093778</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 16:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369169710546-32</Id><Topic><Title>IRS's Lerner Had History of Harassment, Inappropriate Religious Inquiries at FEC</Title><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1369162637754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how you left out the fact that Lerner was directing the group that targeted conservatives and lied to Congress about it - and plans to take the fifth rather than testify to the Committee tomorrow.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1369169710546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 16:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369170408763-33</Id><Topic><Title>Split Effective Date.</Title><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1369158663611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:51:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>never they are buying up shares as fast as they can over the last 10 years</Msg><Username>chrisofmel</Username><Timestamp>1369170408763</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 17:06:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369170909891-34</Id><Title>Obama opposes GOP bill on Keystone XL oil pipeline</Title><Msg>Obama opposes GOP bill on Keystone XL oil pipeline Posted on May 21, 2013 at 3:57 pm by Associated Press in Keystone XL Crewmen work a site for TransCanada's Keystone XL project in Wood County, Texas. (Cody Duty / Houston Chronicle) WASHINGTON — The White House says President Barack Obama opposes a House bill that would speed approval of the proposed Keystone XL oil pipeline from Canada to Texas. The White House said Tuesday that the bill “seeks to circumvent longstanding and proven processes” by removing a requirement for a presidential permit. The legislation also says no new environmental studies are needed. House Republicans say the bill is needed to ensure the long-delayed pipeline is built. The project, which first was proposed in 2008, would carry oil extracted from tar sands in western Canada to refineries along the Texas Gulf Coast. Opponents say the pipeline would carry “dirty oil” that could trigger global warming, while supporters say it would create jobs and bolster North American energy resources. A House vote is expected Wednesday. fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/05/21/obama-opposes-gop-bill-on-keystone-xl-oil-pipeline/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369170909891</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 17:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369181400853-35</Id><Title>Industry accuses EPA of skirting rules for public review of draft fuel regs</Title><Msg>Ben Goad - 05/21/13 05:31 PM ET The oil and gas industry’s leading trade association accused the Environmental Protection Agency Tuesday of skirting federal law by cutting short public consideration of new regulations meant to curb air pollution. By limiting the comment period for the rule to just 23 days, the EPA is would be violating the Clean Air Act – in the name of clean air, the American Petroleum Institute (API) charged. “EPA is cramming through unnecessary new regulations for gasoline that could drive up costs without providing significant environmental benefits,” said Bob Greco, director of API downstream group Director Bob Greco. “By limiting public comments, EPA is trying to skirt public participation and transparency in the rulemaking process.” A proposed rule intended to cut pollution from automobiles by lowering sulfur content in fuel waspublished Tuesday in the Federal Register, nearly two months the EPA detailed the measure. Interested parties and members of the public have until June 13 to weigh in on the 1572-page proposal.   Firstannounced on March 29, the proposed rule endeavors to reduce smog, soot and toxic pollution. Refiners would be forced to lower sulfur content of gasoline by more than 60 percent to 10 parts per million by 2017. More than 158 million Americans currently experience unhealthy levels of air pollution linked to respiratory and cardiovascular problems, according to the agency. While automakers have backed the rule, the API strongly opposes them and contends the regulations would lead to higher gas prices for consumers.   “There is an onslaught of federal regulations coming out of the EPA that could put upward pressure on gasoline price,” Greco asserted. The EPA maintains the rule would increase pump prices by less than a penny per gallon. thehillDOTcom/blogs/regwatch/energyenvironment/301109--industry-accuses-epa-of-skirting-rules-for-public-review-of-draft-fuel-regs</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369181400853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369181989912-36</Id><Title>EPA Proposes RFS Amendments</Title><Msg>Cindy Zimmerman – May 21st, 2013 The Environmental Protection Agency has announced proposed Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS2) amendments and clarifications, which include new pathway determinations for advanced biofuels such as isobutanol and ethanol from crop residues. The EPA proposal also includes “various changes to the E15 misfueling mitigation regulations (E15 MMR) which are minor technical corrections and amendments to sections dealing with labeling, E15 surveys, product transfer documents, and prohibited acts” as well as changes to the survey requirements associated with the ultra-low sulfur diesel (ULSD) program. EPA is proposing to allow renewable diesel, renewable naphtha, and renewable electricity (used in electric vehicles) produced from landll biogas to generate cellulosic or advanced biofuel RINs. Renewable compressed natural gas (CNG)/liquified natural gas (LNG) produced from landfill biogas are also proposed to generate cellulosic RINs. EPA is also proposing to allow butanol that meets the 50% GHG emission reduction threshold to qualify as advanced biofuel. The rulemaking also proposes a clarication regarding the definition of crop residue to include corn kernel ber and proposes an approach to determining the volume of cellulosic renewable identication numbers (RINs) produced from various cellulosic feedstocks. Further, this proposal discusses and seeks comment on the potential to allow for commingling of compliant products at the retail facility level as long as the environmental perfor­mance of the commingled fuels would not be detrimental. The action also addresses “nameplate capacity” issues for certain production facilities that do not claim ex­emption from the 20% GHG reduction threshold. Several other amendments to the RFS program are included. “This proposed rulemaking package is essentially a collection of ‘housekeeping amendments’ that will address several odds and domesticfuelDOTcom/2013/05/21/epa-proposes-rfs-amendments/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369181989912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369183266799-37</Id><Topic><Title>★★★★HEY DUMMIES...Just KEEP ON BUYING...Bwhahaha! DISASTER LOOMS</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1369164022877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 15:20:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've been saying that for years now.....even a broken clock is right twice a day. Keep wishing !</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1369183266799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369183271331-38</Id><Title>Front &amp; Center: Ethanol critic: End state mandate</Title><Msg>May 22 2013 Florida legislators passed a bill this year to repeal the state law that requires most gasoline sold in the state to include 10 percent ethanol. The bill, awaiting action from Gov. Rick Scott, would be largely symbolic, because federal law still requires that gasoline be mixed with ethanol or other biofuels. Opposition to the mandate has united some unlikely allies in the oil industry and environmental community. Senior editorial writer Paul Owens recently conducted an email interview with Charles Drevna, an ethanol critic and president of the American Fuel &amp; Petrochemical Manufacturers. Q: What is the Renewable Fuel Standard? Is it meeting its objectives? A: The federal Renewable Fuel Standard, established in 2005 and expanded in 2007, requires that increasing volumes of biofuels be blended into U.S. gasoline, with the goals of protecting the environment and reducing dependence on foreign oil. But growing ethanol feedstock to meet the RFS destroys natural habitats and converts wild lands to farmland at an alarming rate. The process of producing ethanol depletes water resources and causes higher greenhouse gas emissions than producing fossil fuels, and is expected to for years to come. And these are not sacrifices that must be made in the name of energy security. Gasoline demand has been declining since 2007, and increased production of North American oil and natural gas is mitigating concerns about imported energy. Q: How does the mandate impact consumers? A: Ethanol contains 33 percent less energy than gasoline, meaning that as more ethanol is forced into fuel, vehicles will cover fewer miles per gallon, and consumers will need to fill up more often.… In boats and other smaller engines — such as those in motorcycles, lawnmowers or generators — ethanol can quickly cause the corrosion of metal parts (including carburetors), degradation of plastic and orlandosentinelDOTcom/news/opinion/os-ed-front-center-ethanol-20130521,0,5203896.story</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1369183271331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:41:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369191155194-39</Id><Topic><Title>★★★★HEY DUMMIES...Just KEEP ON BUYING...Bwhahaha! DISASTER LOOMS</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1369164022877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 15:20:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you poor boy!</Msg><Username>hrant4005</Username><Timestamp>1369191155194</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 22:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>