<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370325604329-1</Id><Title>Billionaire activist to target Obama supporters in anti-Keystone effort</Title><Msg>Zack Colman - 06/03/13 08:08 PM ET Billionaire and climate activist Tom Steyer intends to target voters who supported President Obama’s reelection bid in a new campaign to sharpen opposition to the Keystone XL oil sands pipeline. Steyer said the arguments for building the Canada-to-Texas pipeline have “collapsed.” He said his NextGen Action political action committee would announce its new campaign June 20. “Given that none of the chief arguments being put forth by supporters of the pipeline remain standing, NextGenAction is going to be working with our friends and allies who are opposed to the development of Keystone XL to intensify our efforts in communicating what is the right policy choice to your Administration,” Steyer said in an open letter to Obama that was obtained Monday by The Washington Post. A number of left-leaning and green organizations that oppose Keystone have recently criticized Organizing for Action, a political group with roots in Obama's reelection campaign, for not taking a position on the pipeline. The controversial pipeline is currently under federal review. TransCanada Corp., Keystone’s builder, still requires a cross-border permit from the State Department to complete the project’s northern leg. Steyer said a Friday announcement by British Columbia’s provincial government negated a key argument used by Keystone supporters. British Columbia said Friday that it officially opposes Enbridge's proposed Northern Gateway pipeline, which would haul oil sands across Canada for export to Asia. “[T]he argument that the tar sands oil was going to be delivered across Canada if the U.S. pipeline was not permitted has been demolished,” he wrote. Keystone’s supporters have rejected claims that the pipeline would ramp up greenhouse gas emissions or accelerate oil sands production. They contend demand will force oil thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/303225-billionaire-activist-steyer-to-target-obama-supporters-in-anti-keystone-effort</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370325604329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 02:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370335227089-2</Id><Topic><Title>Is bluechesse just talking to himself ?</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1369874941332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 20:49:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jojo sissy a moron.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1370335227089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 04:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370335350372-3</Id><Topic><Title>maxipad ???</Title><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1369130857995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 06:07:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone finally gave him an attitude adjustment.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1370335350372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 04:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370351217324-4</Id><Title>Illinois must adopt fracturing rules, hire experts</Title><Msg>June 4, 2013 at 6:49 am by Associated Press CHICAGO — High-volume oil and gas extraction probably won’t begin in earnest in Illinois until next year because the state first must adopt rules and hire dozens of new employees to help regulate an industry eagerly pushing into new territory. Gov. Pat Quinn promised a quick signature on a measure the Legislature approved last week that would impose the nation’s strictest regulations on hydraulic fracturing, which he says would create thousands of sorely needed jobs in southern Illinois. But it will take three to six months for the Illinois Department of Natural Resources to adopt rules to mirror the Legislature’s regulations. The agency must hire more than 50 engineers, inspectors, lawyers and other experts for its regulatory program. And companies that want to drill first must register and qualify to frack in the state before applying for a permit. All that will take many months and perhaps as long as a year, industry and environmental groups said. “I think that fracking should not move forward in Illinois until the whole process … is completed,” said Henry Henderson, director of the Natural Resource Defense Council’s Midwest office. His group helped negotiate the regulations, which stemmed from an unusual collaboration between lawmakers, regulators, industry and environmental groups. “There is a significantly serious process before us to ensure the technology to enforce the rules is in place,” he said. DNR Director Marc Miller said the agency must spend about $5 million to get the program off the ground. The Legislature included $6.1 million in the state budget for the next fiscal year, which begins July 1, but Miller said the agency has enough financial flexibility to begin hiring right away. Drillers will pay an $11,000 fee to the DNR for each permit, but it will be a while before the agency collects enough money to make the fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/06/04/illinois-must-adopt-fracking-rules-hire-experts/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370351217324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370351542442-5</Id><Title>MidAmerican decides against Iowa nuclear plant</Title><Msg>MidAmerican Energy says design plan isn't approved; environmentalists celebrate Jun. 3, 2013 MidAmerican Energy has scrapped plans for Iowa’s second nuclear plant and will refund $8.8 million ratepayers paid for a now-finished feasibility study, utility officials said Monday. The utility has decided against building any major power plant. That’s because there is no approved design for the modular nuclear plant it envisioned, and there are too many questions about limits on carbon emissions from a natural gas plant, the company said. “We opted for what was in the best interest of our customers,” MidAmerican vice president for regulatory affairs Dean Crist told The Des Moines Register. The decision ends, for now, a three-year controversy over the future of nuclear energy in Iowa and how to pay for a possible nuclear plant. Iowa has one nuclear power plant, the Duane Arnold plant near Palo. Crist said a feasibility study started in 2010 found that two 700-acre sites near Thurman in southwest Iowa and Wilton in southeast Iowa would work for a modular nuclear plant, which was expected to cost around $1 billion and to be built in phases. The MidAmerican study, finished several months early, also noted that the type of modular nuclear plant envisioned could be cost-effective, would be safer than earlier plants and would be a $135 million annual boon to the Iowa economy for 40 to 60 years. In addition, the 11-year construction would bring another $1.2 billion in spending, a peak of $75 million in payroll, and 1,880 jobs. But MidAmerican said those modular plants have not been designed and approved yet. And carbon regulations continue to make fossil-fuel plants a tougher proposition, Crist said. Muscatine County Supervisor Scott Sauer said he had opposed any power plant at the Wilton-area site, preferring that the utility build on the sites of decommissioned coal... desmoinesregisterDOTcom/article/20130603/NEWS/306030045/0/comm/?odyssey=nav</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370351542442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370355587130-6</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese is a walking encyclopedia.....</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370133089920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump ........................</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370355587130</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370355813302-7</Id><Title>TSLA is THE strongest momentum stock on the market</Title><Msg>Momentum Train gives best tip: Tesla Motors (TSLA) is THE strongest momentum stock on the market currently. It went up 230% in the past year, but it is just at the very beginning of the rally because it released an outstanding quarterly report and Consumer Report rated TSLA car with a score of 99, the highest score ever given to any car in the history. Tesla has the best car of the year and ever. This young company has explosive revenue growth rate of 1700%. Tesla is becoming the best automaker in the world. Get on board the momentum train and load up this explosive growth company Tesla while it is still young.</Msg><Username>momentum_train</Username><Timestamp>1370355813302</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:23:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370369488209-8</Id><Title>Rex is a moron engineer.....</Title><Msg>XOM an intelligent business professional as a leader. Go back to a Rock. Not a Wreck.</Msg><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1370369488209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370370176246-9</Id><Title>United Airlines Executes "Historic" 15 Million Gallon Biofuel Deal; Shares Rise 2%</Title><Msg>United Airlines Executes "Historic" 15 Million Gallon Biofuel Deal; Shares Rise 2% By Midnight Trader, June 04, 2013, 01:07:40 PM EDT Vote up United Airlines (UAL) executed a definitive purchase agreement with AltAir Fuels for cost-competitive, sustainable, advanced biofuels at commercial scale, representing what the company called "a historic milestone for aviation." With United's strategic partnership, AltAir Fuels will retrofit part of an existing petroleum refinery to become a 30-million gallon, advanced biofuel refinery near Los Angeles, Calif. AltAir will produce low-carbon, renewable jet fuel and other renewable products. United has collaborated with AltAir Fuels since 2009 and has agreed to buy 15 million gallons of lower-carbon, renewable jet fuel over a three-year period, with the option to purchase more. The airline is purchasing the advanced biofuel at a price competitive with traditional, petroleum-based jet fuel, and AltAir expects to begin delivering five million gallons of renewable jet fuel per year to United starting in 2014. United will use the biofuel on flights operating out of its Los Angeles hub. UAL is up 2.2% to $32.88. Shares have a day's range of $32.15 - $33.39, within a 52-week range of $17.45 - $35.27. nasdaqDOTcom/article/united-airlines-executes-historic-15-million-gallon-biofuel-deal-shares-rise-2-cm250673</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370370176246</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370371009126-10</Id><Title>Interior Dept. plans for offshore wind leases draw GOP fire</Title><Msg>Zack Colman - 06/04/13 11:42 AM ET GOP lawmakers on Tuesday sharply criticized the Interior Department’s move to hold the nation’s first offshore wind lease sale. Sen. David Vitter (La.), the Environment and Public Works Committee’s top Republican, said it amounted to the Obama administration “picking energy industry winners and losers.” Interior announced on Monday that it would hold an auction on July 31 for 164,750 acres off the coast of Massachusetts and Rhode Island, which has the potential to generate 3,400 megawatts of electricity — enough to power 1 million homes. Interior Secretary Sally Jewell called the pending lease sale — which has drawn interest from nine firms — “history in the making.” She said the July bidding could be a bellwether for future offshore wind lease sales, though she noted it might take time for a commercial industry to develop because the projects are expensive and difficult to finance. Democrats applauded the move as a strong step toward developing alternative energy sources. “Offshore wind is a win for American jobs, for American energy security, and for our environment, and it will start off the coast of New England. With lease sales in federal waters, offshore wind will also be a boon for U.S. taxpayers,” Rep. Edward Markey (Mass.), the top Democrat on the House Natural Resources Committee, said in a Tuesday statement. For Republicans, the milestone is more of a boondoggle. Vitter’s office circulated a letter on Tuesday that the Louisiana lawmaker and Sen. Lamar Alexander (R-Tenn.) sent to former Interior Secretary Ken Salazar last November. The letter presses Republican concerns about President Obama’s offshore energy policies, as the GOP contends he keeps too much of the coast off limits to drillers. Republicans want to open drilling in some parts of the Atlantic and Pacific oceans thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/303321-interior-dept-offshore-wind-plan-draws-partisan-fire</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370371009126</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370371706542-11</Id><Title>North America investment hit record, as oil industry profits dropped</Title><Msg>June 4, 2013 at 12:44 pm by Emily Pickrell Oil and gas companies are continuing to increase their investment into North American exploration, reaching a record $185.6 billion for capital expenditures in 2012, according to a study on oil and gas reserves released Tuesday. Independent energy companies are continuing to chase domestic oil prospects, investing larger and larger shares of their profits in future projects, Ernst &amp; Young said in the report, which analyzed the 2012 reserve estimates of the 50 largest companies in the oil and gas industry. “The increased exploration and development spend we’re seeing in this year’s study speaks to the incredible opportunity unfolding in tight oil from shale formations and the high cost of developing these unconventional resources,” said Marcela Donadio, Americas oil &amp; gas leader for the global Ernst &amp; Young organization, speaking to reporters at the report’s release. “Everyone wants in and they are paying a premium to play,” she said. More than 30 of the 50 companies studied have increased their level of capital spending domestically, investing in more expensive extraction techniques, such as enhanced oil recovery projects, that had been considered too costly in earlier years. Military helicopters: Battlefield engines take on oil field mission The shift is pulling capital towards the US, fueling job growth and the further development of ancillary industries, such as seismic technologies. “A lot of companies are selling international assets to bring cash back into the US,” said John Russell, a partner with Ernst &amp; Young. The investments, however, come even as the industry profits decreased almost 60 percent for these companies, driven by historically low natural gas prices in 2012. Natural gas prices have been hard hit by a flood of new supply, with spot prices falling from an average of $4.12 per million British fuelfixDOTcom/blog/2013/06/04/oil-and-gas-capital-investments-reached-186-billion-in-2012/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370371706542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370372357261-12</Id><Title>Straits of Hormuz Satellite image</Title><Msg>Straits of Hormuz Satellite image talkstockDOTcom/tmDOTasp?m=430276&amp;</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370372357261</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370378041293-13</Id><Topic><Title>Straits of Hormuz Satellite image</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370372357261</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that a hurricane?</Msg><Username>boilerroommanager</Username><Timestamp>1370378041293</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370384735128-14</Id><Title>Oil and gas lobby says State Department considering Keystone hearing</Title><Msg>Zack Colman 06/04/13 02:17 PM ET The State Department is looking to hold a public hearing in Washington, D.C., on the Keystone XL oil sands pipeline this summer, the American Petroleum Institute (API) said Tuesday. The department recently held a Keystone hearing in Nebraska, which covered its draft environmental review of the project. Cindy Schild, the API’s downstream director for refining and oil sands, said she had thought it was the last and said more public hearings would delay a final decision. “They’ve held already probably a dozen hearings, we thought that that was the last public hearing,” Schild said in a Tuesday media call. “But then they discussed having another one, possibly this summer.” A State official told The Hill, “No decision has been made on whether the department will hold an additional public meeting.” The official said it would allow for more public input once Foggy Bottom reaches the phase where it will determine whether the project is in the nation's interest. That would come after it finalizes an environmental impact statement for the Canada-to-Texas pipeline. That phase would determine whether to grant a cross-border permit to TransCanada Corp. so it could finish the pipeline’s northern leg. But Schild said a hearing on that part of the process is unnecessary. "We think this project is in the national interest," Schild told The Hill on Tuesday. She argued that if a hearing is held it should be on concerns other than the environment, saying "that one has been put to bed" by the department's draft environmental analysis. Keystone’s supporters, which include Republicans, centrist Democrats, industry groups and some unions, contend the State Department already has taken too long to render a decision. They say it would provide a burst of short-term construction jobs and strengthen energy security. “The president needs thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/303335-oil-and-gas-lobby-says-state-dept-considering-keystone-hearing</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370384735128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370384838448-15</Id><Topic><Title>Straits of Hormuz Satellite image</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370372357261</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Medium risk of a Tropical Storm or ....</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370384838448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:27:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370385238250-16</Id><Title>Oil and gas industry steps up ethanol fuel fight at Supreme Court</Title><Msg>Ben Goad - 06/04/13 01:47 PM ET The oil and gas industry’s leading trade association renewed its call on Tuesday for the Supreme Court to strike down Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) regulations allowing a high-ethanol fuel blend into the marketplace. The action is the latest salvo in an ongoing legal battle between the Obama administration and the American Petroleum Institute (API), which first urged the high court in February to take up consideration of the EPA’s decision to approve E15 fuel for cars made in 2001 or after. The agency and the biofuels industry say the blend — which contains 15 percent ethanol, rather than the standard 10 percent — is safe for those vehicles. But the oil and gas industry has produced studies finding that the mix would damage vehicle engines, and some automakers have said they would not honor warranties in cases where E15 was used. “E15 could leave millions of consumers with broken down cars and high repair bills,” said Bob Greco, API group downstream director. “It could also put motorists in harm’s way when vehicles break down in the middle of a busy highway. We are asking the Supreme Court to step in and protect consumers by striking down EPA’s dangerous E15 mandate before it’s too late.” Specifically, the group is asking the court to reverse a ruling by the U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia that upheld the EPA’s approval of E15. API supported the request with a brief filed Tuesday that responded to arguments from E15 supporters, who have asked the court to pass on the case. In the brief, API cites the opinion of Judge Brett Kavanaugh, the lone dissenter to January’s appeals court decision, who said, “EPA’s action simply cannot be squared with the statutory text.” Bob Dinneen, president and CEO of the Renewable Fuels Association, said the matter had been settled in the lower court. thehillDOTcom/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/303367--oil-and-gas-industry-takes-ethanol-fuel-fight-to-supreme-court-</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370385238250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370385628778-17</Id><Topic><Title>Rex is a moron engineer.....</Title><Username>binnybeoris</Username><Timestamp>1370369488209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:11:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>English is your second language?</Msg><Username>catfish957</Username><Timestamp>1370385628778</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370393041421-18</Id><Topic><Title>bluecheese is a walking encyclopedia.....</Title><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370133089920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the idiot's posts go on !</Msg><Username>jojomax411</Username><Timestamp>1370393041421</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370396625758-19</Id><Title>Regional Gas Price Spikes Pose New Challenges for Industry, Lawmakers</Title><Msg>Regional Gas Price Spikes Pose New Challenges for Industry, Lawmakers By Lauren Gardner Roll Call Staff June 4, 2013, 1:57 p.m. Memorial Day weekend marks the unofficial start to the summer driving season — and in recent years that has meant steadily rising gas prices. But for the second consecutive year, drivers filling their tanks for holiday road trips paid less at the pump on average than a year earlier. And AAA motor club, which pegged the average retail price for a gallon of gasoline nationally at $3.63 on May 27, projects that prices will continue to drop this summer. Despite this bright picture nationally,not everybody has been enjoying cheap gasoline. Across much of the upper Midwest and the Pacific Coast, price spiked to more than $4 a gallon just before Memorial Day. Ironically, some of the hardest-hit areas — such as North Dakota, Minnesota and Nebraska — are near the sources of booming North American oil production, such as the Bakken shale formations and the Western Canadian tar sands. The regional price spikes pose new challenges for industry and policymakers. In past summers, the primary driver of higher gas prices has been supply shortages and the high cost of crude oil on world markets. But crude oil prices are down from a year earlier, and the Energy Information Administration projects they will fall further in the year ahead. Private sector and government analysts say the regional spikes in gasoline prices can be blamed on a high number of planned and unplanned refinery outages, which affect areas served by the facilities. Earlier this year, malfunctions or breakdowns caused unplanned refinery shutdowns on top of</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1370396625758</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 21:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>