<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-30"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372565184956-1</Id><Title>Valero joint venture Diamond Green commences production from biodiesel plant</Title><Msg>Valero joint venture Diamond Green commences production from biodiesel plant EBR Staff Writer Published 28 June 2013 Diamond Green Diesel, a green joint venture between Valero subsidiary Diamond Alternative Energy and Darling International, has commenced production of bio-diesel at its 9,300 barrel-per-day plant. The plant produces renewable fuel by processing recycled animal fat and used cooking oil as well as corn oil. The fuel can be shipped by pipeline and meets low-carbon fuel standards. Darling International chairman and chief executive officer Randall Stuewe said that the company is delighted with the mechanical completion and startup of Diamond Green Diesel plant. "This joint venture will be a producer of high quality renewable diesel capable of fulfilling the RFS2 biomass-based diesel mandate. Our partnership with Valero will benefit Diamond Green Diesel through multiple operational synergies," added Stuewe. Besides biodiesel plant, Valero also owns 16 refineries, 10 ethanol plants and a 50MW wind farm. biofuelsandbiomass</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372565184956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 00:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372572363579-2</Id><Title>Corn futures for delivery in December tumbled 5.1 percent to close at $5.11 a bushel at 1:15 p.m. on the Chicago Board of Trade,</Title><Msg>Corn futures for delivery in December tumbled 5.1 percent to close at $5.11 a bushel at 1:15 p.m. on the Chicago Board of Trade,</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372572363579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 02:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372575196408-3</Id><Title>☛☛☛☛NOBAMA, Supreme Court, DEMOCRATS...Laughing stock of the world...</Title><Msg>BETTER get em' OUT ASAP...</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1372575196408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 02:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372577613134-4</Id><Title>☛☛☛☛NOBAMA, Supreme Court, DEMOCRATS...Laughing stock of the world...</Title><Msg>The IRS, HOLDER, NOBAMA, CLINTON, etc....thinks that YOU are a pack of worthless "SHEEP"....yeah really !!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1372577613134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 03:33:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372599027995-5</Id><Topic><Title>Methane scrutiny in Obama climate plan may cost drillers</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372564126752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 23:48:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is not equipped to lead the USA or any country. He lacks the genetics to convincingly lead the majority of his people, people who are different than him, and who will reject whatever he says simply because he said it, and will do everything in their power to undermine him. All we see here is another vacillating equivocal policy out of him, one that could have been written by Shell Oil -- perhaps he watched a few of their commercials and formulated his policy based on them. His uselessness is irrelevant though, except that it condemns the USA to a huge economic decline in the future. All the investments in high cost oil &amp; gas will be stranded and a loss to the US economy, and the environmental damage they bring with them will take decades to undo. Angela Merkel, on the other hand, is equipped to lead in every respect. Her education is particularly suitable, in contrast to Obama's education which is particularly useless and unfitting to the task. Germany's scientific &amp; technological establishment will solve the problem, and drive fossil fuels to extinction. Photovoltaic technology, fuel cells, and batteries will destroy the oil, gas, coal, and nuclear industry. The US solar industry has been forced to perform on a treadmill switched to maximum speed by the pressure of the German government. Many of the US solar companies are collapsing in exhaustion, unable to keep up with the pace and drop in prices. China's government has been forced to heavily subsidize theirs to keep them from collapsing under the pressure. If all of them expire it is irrelevant. The treadmill will remain at maximum speed, and whatever they accomplish during their period before exhaustion will aid the scientific effort.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372599027995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372601794682-6</Id><Topic><Title>Methane scrutiny in Obama climate plan may cost drillers</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372564126752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 23:48:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope they are all union workers.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1372601794682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372601990646-7</Id><Topic><Title>☛☛☛☛NOBAMA, Supreme Court, DEMOCRATS...Laughing stock of the world...</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1372575196408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 02:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no the american people are the laughing stock of the world. They voted this POS in.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1372601990646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372602039447-8</Id><Topic><Title>☛☛☛☛NOBAMA, Supreme Court, DEMOCRATS...Laughing stock of the world...</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1372577613134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 03:33:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep the whole dumbo party needs to be jailed or deported.</Msg><Username>ref_steve_blairstown</Username><Timestamp>1372602039447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372603867649-9</Id><Title>Major Oil sectors may go up 2nd half 2013.</Title><Msg>The major oil sectors did not go up (participate) during the 1st 1/2 of 2013, thus investment firms are rotating into them for the 2nd half of 2013. Hope this allows Exxon to move up some. Exxon did not trade weak as the rest of the market did on Friday.</Msg><Username>dvoowner</Username><Timestamp>1372603867649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372616374078-10</Id><Title>Complexity Of US Carbon Emissions Cuts, &amp; The 3rd Oil Crisis?</Title><Msg>Complexity Of US Carbon Emissions Cuts, &amp; The 3rd Oil Crisis? June 30, 2013 Zachary Shahan We’ve covered the intricacies of US carbon emissions cuts a few times here on CleanTechnica. I think this reader post was my favorite on the topic, but I also think this post of my own and this repost are worth a read. Shrink That Footprint has offered up another great repost on the topic that is very well done. It also gets into the possible existence of a 3rd oil crisis. Check it out below or click on over to the Shrink That Footprint website to read it. US carbon emissions are down 12% since 2005. According to many an editorial the reason is simple. The fracking boom has driven out coal. But that isn’t what the data says. The data says that oil emissions are down more than electricity emissions. That natural gas is at best responsible for half of emissions cuts. And that electricity generation tell us only half the story. If we want to really understand what happened to US emissions we also need to ask why oil emissions have tanked. America’s Carbon Cliff Using the charts from our recent report ‘America’s Carbon Cliff: Dissecting the Decline in US Carbon Emissions‘ this post is going to try to explain what happened to US carbon emissions between 2005 and 2012. We’ll start with a macro overview of what happened at the national level, then take a closer look at the changes in each sector and finish with a discussion of oil consumption. For a more detailed explanation of each chart check the full report. Four ways to dissect the decline Energy related carbon emissions in the US declined about 12% from 2005 to 2012, or roughly 700 Mt CO2. The decline in total emissions has been widely documented. In the context of the last fifty years it looks like this: US Carbon Emissions Decline The drop in carbon emissions in the last seven years has been even greater than occurred from 1979 to 1983. URL at talkstock</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1372616374078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 14:19:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372646121272-11</Id><Title>tar..tar...</Title><Msg>alot of oil spills in the de seret...arba....du they called it tar..s..and... try...ing...to unload.... x..o...m beg...us cause...i just filled my tank... 40....cents...a gall...on</Msg><Username>boldchris</Username><Timestamp>1372646121272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372648713676-12</Id><Topic><Title>☛☛☛☛NOBAMA, Supreme Court, DEMOCRATS...Laughing stock of the world...</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1372575196408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 02:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the american people are the laughing stock of the world. They voted this POS in." That is true, but I don’t mind. My house is graced by more American femininity now thanks to Obama. After 4 years of his Presidency one of my wife’s friends from college is in need of some help. So she’s staying with us at our new house in Steglitz-Zehlendorf borough, Berlin. Germany sends her thanks if she is successful in catching a husband. She's very ready for a husband and children. One can never tell about such things but I think the attraction between lonely male scientist (one of my renters) and pretty, friendly female holds much promise.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1372648713676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 23:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>