<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360041386145-1</Id><Title>OXF - Best Value of 2013</Title><Msg>Energy Boom Major Breakout Trade!</Msg><Username>soundenergypartners</Username><Timestamp>1360041386145</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 00:16:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360050177776-2</Id><Title>Iowa Senate Approves 5% Biodiesel Mandate</Title><Msg>Iowa Senate Approves 5% Biodiesel Mandate Micah Walter/Bloomberg News 4/20/2009 12:00:00 PM The Iowa Senate approved a bill last week that would require that diesel fuel sold in the state contain 5% biofuel, the Des Moines Register reported. Retailers would earn a tax credit if their diesel contained 10% biofuel or higher, the paper reported. If approved, the measure would add Iowa to a list of seven other states that require biodiesel to be blended with diesel, the National Biodiesel Board said in a statement. State Sen. Jack Kibbie told the Register that the mandate, which would go into effect July 1 if the House and governor approve it, would save 1 million barrels of foreign oil per year. Truckers have objected to biodiesel mandates, reporting that the blended fuel gels in cold weather, clogging fuel lines in diesel engines. ttnewsDOTcom/articles/basetemplateDOTaspx?storyid=21743&amp;t=Iowa-Senate-Approves-5%25-Biodiesel-Mandate</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360050177776</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 02:42:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360050330246-3</Id><Title>Canada Sets 2% Biodiesel Mandate</Title><Msg>Canada Sets 2% Biodiesel Mandate Micah Walter/Bloomberg News 2/14/2011 11:30:00 Diesel fuel and home heating oil will be required to contain at least 2% biofuel content beginning July 1, the Canadian Broadcasting Corp. reported. Federal Environment Minister Peter Kent made the announcement Thursday in Ontario, the CBC said on its website. Kent said the rule will cut greenhouse gas emissions from transportation and heating fuel. Beginning last December, gasoline in Canada was required to contain 5% biofuel. The move was applauded by the Canadian Renewable Fuels Association, which called it “good news for consumers, farmers and energy diversity.” “Biodiesel is a better way to drive and an innovative way to fuel our economy,” said CRFA President Gordon Quaiattini, “Biodiesel is a cleaner alternative to conventional diesel. It will help moderate price by adding to our fuel supply, create new jobs, and benefit farmers and drivers alike,” he said in a statement. ttnewsDOTcom/articles/basetemplateDOTaspx?storyid=26114&amp;t=Canada-Sets-2%25-Biodiesel-Mandate</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360050330246</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 02:45:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360075161030-4</Id><Topic><Title>Currency Purchase...</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360037947538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 23:19:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sold all € for £ @ 0.8605 £/€ € basis .8565 £/€ (1.1675 €/£)... gain on € +0.46% 100% £...LIBOR rate...0.50%</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360075161030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:39:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360076296296-5</Id><Topic><Title>4.47 To 1 — Ratio Of U.S. Voters Who Would Prefer Carbon Tax To Cut In Spending</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991694284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:28:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A carbon tax, a fuel tax, and a value added tax should be imposed to balance the US Budget... Borrowed money is not free "income" to the government...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360076296296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 09:58:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360077494352-6</Id><Topic><Title>4.47 To 1 — Ratio Of U.S. Voters Who Would Prefer Carbon Tax To Cut In Spending</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991694284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:28:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to worry hans, it is coming, the savior has promised more taxes -- the only promise he keeps. bring taxes on! the more the merrier! let the obamabots pay the piper they voted for!</Msg><Username>geezee003</Username><Timestamp>1360077494352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:18:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360077712834-7</Id><Topic><Title>XOM will probably become the stock to see this year.</Title><Username>michaeltorres948</Username><Timestamp>1360070173924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:16:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hits you guys</Msg><Username>hillschristopher621</Username><Timestamp>1360077712834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:21:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360077814284-8</Id><Topic><Title>Deutsche und Amerikanische Waffen für die Welt!!!</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359990073384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be unscientific to say that the Hittite language outdates the Punic one. Furthermore, the hittites spoke an aryan language, so do and did the Armenians and Kurds and it is doubtful if they plied the waves on viking ships and ate pickled herring and raw bacon.. By the way, your love of war weapons and death is a bit sick don't you think? I like to think of Duetschland as the Heimat of Beethoven, Schiller and not of Mengele and Himmler.Geld?</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1360077814284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:23:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360077958674-9</Id><Topic><Title>It's a funny species that cares more about watching a leather pigskin move around a field than it does</Title><Username>snthsnth1</Username><Timestamp>1359997194684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:59:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Natural resources are not the source of a civilization's wealth and strength. Human intellect is the source and it is developed through education, and the most efficient model is state supported and directed education and science. It takes less than 1/1000th the energy to make a tonne of steel as it took before the advent of modern chemistry. Now we can make light with next to no energy, and from materials that use very little energy either. Fiber optics reduce the energy and resource requirement of communications many times over. There's what is possible with pure ignorance, then there what is possible with classical chemistry and mechanics, then there is what is possible quantum chemistry and mechanics, then there is what is possible with quantum chemistry and mechanics matched with supercomputers.... Ancient civilizations offer no useful clues, except that free market provision of education and small government is a bad policy. State directed education, science, and technology is the best model...Centralization of intellectual power into networks is key and magnifies the returns many times over.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360077958674</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:25:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360078357360-10</Id><Topic><Title>Deutsche und Amerikanische Waffen für die Welt!!!</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359990073384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Hittites were around from 1700 BC to 1200 BC. The Phonecians from 1200 BC to 500 BC. You must have difficulty with basic math. I suppose you think modern American came before the Puritans landed in Massachusetts, and that the computer language developed in modern times was in fact created by the Puritans... Totally ignorant...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360078357360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:32:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360079158373-11</Id><Title>OXF - Best Value of 2013</Title><Msg>Energy Boom Major Breakout Trade!</Msg><Username>soundenergypartners</Username><Timestamp>1360079158373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:45:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360079640291-12</Id><Topic><Title>4.47 To 1 — Ratio Of U.S. Voters Who Would Prefer Carbon Tax To Cut In Spending</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991694284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:28:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It works well for Germany and England. I don't see the problem... You need to do something about your school system too. It is atrocious... The taxes should help pay for improvements.</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360079640291</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 10:54:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360080920760-13</Id><Title>Dividend Hikez Slated For Spring?</Title><Msg>What about a 3 for 1 Splitz also?</Msg><Username>stenchcloud</Username><Timestamp>1360080920760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:15:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360080962778-14</Id><Topic><Title>What Has Any Republican EVER Done To Help Middle Class?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1359895848355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 07:50:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something tells me you are a peter puffer. You most certainly are an assehole</Msg><Username>iitriumvirate</Username><Timestamp>1360080962778</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:16:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360081042130-15</Id><Topic><Title>If He's So Patriotic Why Did Ted Nugent Dodge Vietnam?</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1360028863824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 20:47:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where did Clinton or Obama serve? Clinton ran to Europe. Obama never held a private sector job. You are truly just stupid.</Msg><Username>iitriumvirate</Username><Timestamp>1360081042130</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:17:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360081711664-16</Id><Topic><Title>4.47 To 1 — Ratio Of U.S. Voters Who Would Prefer Carbon Tax To Cut In Spending</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991694284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:28:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forcing others to provide you a military is not free "income" to the Germans... Oh wait, maybe it is... That's right, we're doing it because YOU can't be trusted with guns... I guess it is free "income" to the Germans, never mind.</Msg><Username>x1ikng</Username><Timestamp>1360081711664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:28:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360082143300-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ex-dividend date nd to be in by close Wed.</Title><Username>brightstocks</Username><Timestamp>1359997709045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:08:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next quarter should be interesting, I wounder what the line is on XOM issuing another 20% dividend bump. Anyone have any thoughts?</Msg><Username>mwds06</Username><Timestamp>1360082143300</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 11:35:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360085309754-18</Id><Topic><Title>4.47 To 1 — Ratio Of U.S. Voters Who Would Prefer Carbon Tax To Cut In Spending</Title><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1359991694284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:28:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound very unstable and insane. So now you are saying that Germany's military potential is so formidable that it forces others to defend it? LOL... I would agree Germany does have the technological ability to project vast power, and with drones and quantum technologies that power will only grow. When you have quite exhausted yourself smashing ants in the desert we will see who needs whom... My wife has just about finished her hair and makeup, so I must be going...</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360085309754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 12:28:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360087366298-19</Id><Title>First Wind Projects 50% Portfolio Growth In Coming Years</Title><Msg>First Wind Projects 50% Portfolio Growth In Coming Years February 5, 2013 Zachary Shahan First Wind, which is focused on the development, financing, construction, ownership, and operation of utility-scale renewable energy projects in the United States (primarily wind power projects), is one of the top wind power companies that will benefit from the recent decision of the U.S. Congress to keep supporting this nascent but fast-growing energy sector. Following the decision to extend the wind power production tax credit (PTC), First Wind announced that it now “hopes to increase its operating portfolio of wind projects by 50 percent or more.” “The ambitious effort could mean that thousands of people will be employed building new First Wind projects over the next few years along with millions of dollars in investment and new revenue generated for host communities and others, while delivering cost-competitive clean energy to more homes across the country,” First Wind adds. The company currently operates 980 megawatts (MW) of wind projects in 6 U.S. states. I’m sure this is just one of many stories about the benefits of extending the wind power PTC, and I’m sure the PTC is still creating a net benefit for the American public. Furthermore, as we’ve noted plenty of times before, historical subsidies for wind power don’t compare to historical subsidies for competing energy industries (all of which continue to receive subsidies even though many of those subsidies no longer benefit society, but actually harms it). So, I think the wind industry very well deserves these this support, and we should all make it very clear to our friends and relatives that this simple wind power subsidy is creating jobs and benefiting our economy! sDOTtt/1zof4</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360087366298</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:02:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360089407304-20</Id><Topic><Title>Deutsche und Amerikanische Waffen für die Welt!!!</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359990073384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The native Americans did come here before the Puritans and the alphabet was definitely a Phoenician invention. Do you get your history from the neo Nazis? All humanity is involved in today's cultural advances and to say that it is just a teutonic thing is very gauche. Few Germans would agree with you.Furthermore, you have no idea what others know or believe.Get rid of your belilgerent arrogance as it makes you look irrational.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1360089407304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:36:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360089542119-21</Id><Topic><Title>XOM will probably become the stock to see this year.</Title><Username>michaeltorres948</Username><Timestamp>1360070173924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 08:16:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they all are</Msg><Username>bleroy70</Username><Timestamp>1360089542119</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 13:39:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360095238072-22</Id><Topic><Title>Deutsche und Amerikanische Waffen für die Welt!!!</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359990073384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“The alphabet was definitely a Phoenician invention.” -wrong. The Phoenicians did not invent writing or the first alphabet. The Phoenicians “alphabet” has no vowels and is not a true alphabet. The Hittite and Egyptian Empires signed the world’s first peace treaty in 1258 BCE dividing the world the Phoenicians would one day control parts of between them. Both could write and neither used Phoenician. The first true alphabet is the Greek alphabet, and the “Greeks” who invented it were the post-Dorian invasion Greeks. Those “Dorians” who conquered Greece and eventually produced the world’s first true alphabet –with vowels and consonants were from the North – in the lands ruled by the Germanic Kings of Eastern Europe for eons, of the same stock that produced the Hittites... As for the “Indians” who lived in America before they were conquered and annihilated. The methods that were used to achieve that do not concern me. The end justified the means. The USA was a useful creation, and still has much potential. The USA’s methods were quite acceptable by European standards (which is to say Germanic standards) and I have no comment. Presenting falsehoods and innuendo in the place of fact and rational thought is perhaps socially acceptable to people like you, but for educated elites it is considered quite “gauche” and obnoxious. It certainly is not convincing except as means of controlling the thought of people like you – rather like children’s tales or propaganda. Most Germans do not reach the pinnacle of the system and you most certainly have not reached the pinnacle of whatever system you come from. They have little real say over policy or the direction society takes. I consider them irrelevant, as I do you. The sooner you learn your place in your system the better. Your kind is seriously damaging its prospects for success…</Msg><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1360095238072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:13:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360101675971-23</Id><Topic><Title>Deutsche und Amerikanische Waffen für die Welt!!!</Title><Username>hansesteelyard</Username><Timestamp>1359990073384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your manipulation is very puerile and unscientific. You would have been great in the Munich Braukeller. I fear that you are out of step with the current civilization push and belong to Berlin back in 1933. Those days are over, kamerad, and the world is becoming internationalized whether you or I like it or not.Reality has passed you by and you live in a war world of pain and death.Too bad.</Msg><Username>aeskylosa</Username><Timestamp>1360101675971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 17:01:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360105338812-24</Id><Topic><Title>$$-LQQK-$ Secret XOM Info REVEALED! $-LQQK-$$</Title><Username>luislee278</Username><Timestamp>1359997105338</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>helpful report.</Msg><Username>johnreed295</Username><Timestamp>1360105338812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 18:02:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360106562321-25</Id><Title>ERIC CANTOR YOUR NOT FOOLING ANYBODY GOP WELL NEVER CHANGE PERIOD!!</Title><Msg>Oh yeah GOP feel your pain !!!! ALL BS REPTARDS !!!</Msg><Username>pra11pra11</Username><Timestamp>1360106562321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 18:22:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360107608524-26</Id><Title>Chris Kyle Death Inside Firing Range Reveals The NRA LIE!</Title><Msg>That good guys with guns are the answer to bad guys with guns.. This Chris Kyle was the best trained, most well armed man on the planet and he was shot dead in a shooting range no less. So much for the more arms saves lives boloney. Now I got no beef with this guy Kyle but the argument all you gun nuts make about having arms being the answer to protection is bogus.</Msg><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1360107608524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 18:40:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360108570772-27</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Kyle Death Inside Firing Range Reveals The NRA LIE!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1360107608524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 18:40:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing "real" about you, wahleee boy, is the fact that you are brain dead. And you continue to demonstrate that.</Msg><Username>infernalequinex</Username><Timestamp>1360108570772</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 18:56:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360113436908-28</Id><Title>With Egypt oil will break the highs</Title><Msg>New highs are on their way.</Msg><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1360113436908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:17:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360114047270-29</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Kyle Death Inside Firing Range Reveals The NRA LIE!</Title><Username>walhieeeeeee</Username><Timestamp>1360107608524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 18:40:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Columbine pretty much debunked the "security guard" at schools horse kaka</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1360114047270</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:27:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360114115215-30</Id><Topic><Title>With Egypt oil will break the highs</Title><Username>yainvestor2</Username><Timestamp>1360113436908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:17:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what Egypt oil ??</Msg><Username>mrsuerte</Username><Timestamp>1360114115215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 20:28:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360121442237-31</Id><Title>Solar PV Installations Hit 32 GW In 2012, 35 GW Projected For 2013, According To IHS</Title><Msg>Solar PV Installations Hit 32 GW In 2012, 35 GW Projected For 2013, According To IHS February 5, 2013Zachary Shahan IHS, a “global information company,” has reported that global solar PV installations totalled about 32 gigawatts (GW) in 2012, a new record that beats 2011′s 28 GW and 2010′s 20 GW. Global solar PV annual installations and projections. Click to enlarge. As could be expected, 2013 is projected to best 2012, as is every year after that for many years to come. IHS projects that the annual installation capacity will reach 61 GW by 2017, triple 2010′s total and nearly double 2012′s. (See the chart on the right.) Meanwhile, the price of solar modules is projected to keep falling. The net effect is that solar PV suppliers will see their annual revenues drop, according to IHS, resulting in a continued “solar shakeout” as weaker companies fall out of the market. This is a natural process in the maturation of nearly every industry. “According to IHS, industry revenue—measured as the system price multiplied by total gigawatts installed is expected will decline to an estimated US$75 billion in 2013, down from US$77 billion in 2012,” PV-Tech writes. “PV industry revenue was said to have peaked in 2011 at US$94 billion.” However, IHS calculates that solar PV revenue will rise above $100 billion between 2014 and 2016, and will reach as much as $115 by 2016. With the market tightening, but still growing fast, suppliers are under pressure to reduce their own costs however they can — through technology innovation, manufacturing innovation, waste reduction, or other measures. The bottom line: solar PV prices will continue to drop, installations will continue to increase, and solar PV suppliers will continue to go out of business as the industry consolidates. The Changing Market It’s no secret that Europe has led the solar installation race, with Germany clear at the head. But other regions have been getting into the game to a much greater degree in recent years, and that’s expected to continue. “IHS noted that a major regional shift in PV demand was occurring and that the industry was becoming truly global. Europe was said to have accounted for more than 80 percent of solar demand in 2010, declining to 53% in 2012, and forecast to slide further this year to only 39% of the global market. Not surprisingly, Asia and in particular China is on track to replace Europe as the world’s largest source of solar installations in the coming years.” A Solarbuzz report recently found that 33% of global solar PV shipments ended up in China. With China’s rapidly growing economy and astounding energy use growth, this is no surprise. However, these aren’t the only factors affecting its solar installation growth. 7 out of the top 10 leading solar PV suppliers are based in China, but they are being squeezed hard by anti-dumping legislation in the US, Europe, and India, as well as by the shrinking profits mentioned above. As a result, the Chinese government has started to shift its focus onto stimulating solar demand (rather than solar panel production). “IHS expects Germany to fall to third place in 2013, behind China and the United States. Japan and Italy follow in fourth and fifth, respectively,” PV-Tech writes. “Geographic fragmentation is also expected to escalate this year. The market research firm noted that the top 5 countries by installations accounted for nearly 75% of total solar demand in 2012, but is expected to decline to 65% in 2013.“ In a phrase: solar power is becoming global. sDOTtt/1zqqR</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360121442237</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:30:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360121481267-32</Id><Title>BYE BYE OIL</Title><Msg>From Cold Fusion Times [visit]…. “April 19, 2012 – Massachusetts Senate Minority Leader Bruce E. Tarr (R), and his staff, visited the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Cambridge, MA) on April 17, 2012 to learn more about the developments in cold fusion (LANR, lattice assisted nuclear reactions). This cold fusion update was in Prof. Peter Hagelstein‘s Quantum Electronics and Energy Production and Conversion laboratory where the JET Energy cold fusion NANOR desktop demonstration unit was operating. Dr. Mitchell Swartz and Prof. Hagelstein led the discussion and reviewed the development of nanomaterial cold fusion devices for over more than two decades, and this particular R&amp;D breakthrough and some of the components which allow its function. The group contributing to the discussion on ways to help push the technology forward included Dr. Brian Ahern, Keith Owens (who initiated the visit), A.J. Paglia, and Stephen Mulloney. Sen. Tarr’s excellent questions, and his continued interest to investigate this ultra-efficient and ultraclean energy production technology, herald his awareness of the importance of this alternative energy to the security and energy interests of the Commonwealth.“</Msg><Username>altrade65</Username><Timestamp>1360121481267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:31:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360123106839-33</Id><Title>Can Congress ever agree on climate change? An interview with Henry Waxman</Title><Msg>Can Congress ever agree on climate change? An interview with Henry Waxman Posted by Brad Plumer on February 5, 2013 at 9:06 am Four years ago, Rep. Henry Waxman (D-Calif.) was trying to craft a climate-change policy for the entire country. But he only got halfway there: His massive bill to cap U.S. greenhouse-gas emissions passed through the House, but eventually died in the Senate. Rep. Henry Waxman (D-Calif.). Now he’s trying again. Although Republicans have since retaken the House, and Waxman is no longer chair of the energy committee, he’s still trying to call attention to the issue. Recently, Waxman formed a new Bicameral Task Force on Climate Change with Sen. Sheldon Whitehouse (D-R.I.) — an effort to raise awareness about global warming among legislators and to look for policy solutions. Waxman and I spoke Monday about the new climate task force, the prospects of a carbon tax, and what President Obama is’s planning on climate change. A lightly edited transcript follows: Brad Plumer: Right now the conventional wisdom is that no climate policies can pass Congress — House Republicans aren’t going to vote for a cap on carbon emissions or anything of that sort. So what can a climate task force actually do? Henry Waxman: We have three main goals for this task force. First, we’re trying to raise awareness among our colleagues and the public about the dangers of climate change. We’re trying to provide a forum to develop effective policies to address it. And we’re working to develop measures to reduce carbon emissions to adapt to the harm that climate change is already causing and is expected to cause in the future. There’s a lot that Congress can do here, but the president can also take some important steps on his own without Congress. He’s already made important moves in the right direction—there have been significant investments in solar and wind energy, we’ve already doubled the development of solar and wind in this country. There are new tailpipe standards for automobiles that will double fuel economy and lead to major carbon-dioxide reductions. And the Environmental Protection Agency has proposed new carbon standards for power plants. BP: Now when you say you’re trying to raise awareness among colleagues — do you think there are lawmakers who can actually be swayed on this issue? HW: I believe that it’s important for Congress to hear from scientists and other sources about the concerns they’ve expressed with regards to climate change. Over the last two years, House energy subcommittee ranking member Bobby Rush and I have written to [Republican Chairman of the Energy and Commerce Committee] Fred Upton and [Republican Chairman of the Subcommittee on Energy and Power] Ed Whitfield 21 times requesting hearings on new scientific findings and other important developments related to climate. They ignored every one of those hearing requests. Whether it’s from the National Academies of Sciences or the International Energy Agency or the World Bank or PriceWaterhouseCoopers. This was all new reported data. They’ve ignored our requests to hear from researchers about climate change effects on agriculture, on marine ecosystems, on communities impacted by extreme weather. BP: But would any of these scientific reports actually change anyone’s minds? It seems like many politicians have already firmly made up their minds about climate change. HW: I think that many lawmakers still don’t realize that there’s a shrinking window for action. They think we can put this issue off indefinitely, and that’s not scientifically accurate. But yes, a lot of members are engaged in willful ignorance — and I’m talking about the committee that has jurisdiction over this issue. BP: Now you mentioned that the Obama administration could, in theory, do a lot to tackle climate change on its own. What, realistically, would this will look like? HW: The president has substantial authority to reduce carbon pollution. As the Supreme Court affirmed back in 2007, the Clean Air Act authorizes the Environmental Protection Agency to control carbon pollution from a wide range of sources. It can set limits for new and existing power plants and get substantial reductions. The EPA has proposed regulations for new power plants but hasn’t yet finalized them. The president could also make sure that other agencies besides the EPA and the Department of Energy include a strong focus on climate change as they carry out their various missions. There’s no silver bullet on climate change. It will take wide action across the board. Sen. Whitehouse and I wrote a letter to the president urging him to develop a plan of action for the administration to take. He can use his existing authority to reduce carbon pollution 17 percent below 2005 levels by 2020. I think he can do that on his own. BP: Did you get a response to that letter? HW: We haven’t heard a response yet. But the president did make a strong point in his inaugural address that climate change is something that we will have to respond to. BP: Do you think the White House has to tread carefully here? Are they worried about a backlash from Congress if they try to do too much on carbon emissions unilaterally? HW: The president has a very good record in dealing with this issue. But in the past, there was a lot of concern about the president’s reelection in parts of the country where he might suffer if he was out front on policies that couldn’t pass Congress. But now there’s a groundswell for action. And the president is not going to run for re-election again. I think he’s committed, as he said in his inaugural address. BP: So he won’t be quite as timid on the issue in his second term? HW: Look, I don’t want to criticize him for what he didn’t do because he did so much more than his predecessors. He did support our legislation in 2009, but even though it passed the House and had majority support in the Senate, it couldn’t get 60 votes and get past the filibuster. Then once Republicans took control of the House in 2010, obviously we couldn’t get legislation of that magnitude through. And the president I think took important steps. But there’s more that he can now do in his second term. BP: A lot of the unilateral actions that President Obama could take are mainly focused on short-term emissions cuts through 2020. But what about the larger goal of an 80 percent cut by 2050. Is that something only Congress can do? HW: In my view, Congress needs to act. The task force hasn’t taken any positions yet, but Sen. Whitehouse and I both believe that we ultimately need to put a price on carbon to drive technology and give full incentives for market forces to achieve a transition to a low-carbon economy. That would benefit the country not just by reducing greenhouse gases, but also making us the leader in a key economic area. In my view a price on carbon makes sense because without it we are essentially subsidizing oil and coal — those fuels are not paying the full cost of the external damages they cause to the environment and public health. A carbon price would put all of these things on a level playing field. BP: Your cap-and-trade bill in 2009 was one way to do that. Could cap-and-trade ever return? Or is that idea dead? HW: A price on carbon can take a number of forms. One is cap-and-trade. Many people have argued for a carbon tax. Some Republican economists have urged that we put a carbon tax in place and use the money to lower other taxes. Other economists have said that a price on carbon can help us not just solve an intractable problem in climate change but also help reduce the deficit. And others have suggested a carbon tax where the money is recycled back to consumers. The essential point here is that any carbon price would have a strong impact on decision-making throughout the economy. BP: So what are the prospects for a carbon tax getting through Congress? HW: Certainly it’s something Congress can look at. I think there will be pressure for new revenue when the debt ceiling comes back later this year. And this is a source of revenue that will look awfully attractive compared to other alternatives Congress will have to face, whether it’s other taxes or cuts in entitlements. BP: Now are there any climate-policy areas where Democrats and Republicans could conceivably work together? HW: I think there are actions Congress could take that would help alleviate the problem of climate change short of a price on carbon or a carbon tax. Energy efficiency standards. We could increase our investments in research and development. Here’s an example of a proposal I thought should have passed Congress. [Back in 2009], Congressman Upton (R-Mich.) had co-sponsored a bill with former Rep. Rick Boucher (D-Va.) that would have put a tax on electricity generated by coal power plants, and the money would have been used for research into how to sequester the carbon. That would have been helpful. Yet when I asked Rep. Upton over the last two years to consider moving the bill he had sponsored earlier, I got no response. BP: Now, you also mention climate adaptation. Even if we passed a carbon tax tomorrow, we’re still likely to see some effects of climate change in the decades ahead. Is this something the government isn’t ready for? HW: I think we need to approach this issue with a great deal of timeliness. Agencies should be developing adaptation plans — and this is something the administration can do without Congress. But Congress can also pass laws or appropriate money for different strategies. In 2011 we experienced 14 weather and climate disasters that each caused more than a billion dollars in damages. They cost $60 billion in all. In 2012, total damages will be even higher. We’ve just passed legislation to compensate victims of Hurricane Sandy. We’re still reacting after the fact. We need to figure out how to prevent some of these things from happening, and accepting that we’re now seeing a regular pattern of extraordinary events. BP: Are you seeing any interest in climate-adaptation measures from members of Congress who might be otherwise skeptical of, say, capping emissions? HW: I think even Republicans have to acknowledge that climate change is taking place. They may not think it’s man-made, but they can acknowledge that it’s happening, and that we’re seeing more and more extreme examples of it. And I think a lot of representatives have constituents who understand that we need to do more about this problem. Farmers in the Midwest who are suffering from drought. Urban areas affected by hurricanes. I think they understand that there’s a problem and we need leadership. BP: Now you’re going to call for the House Energy and Commerce Committee to hold hearings on this subject. What happens if those requests get turned down? HW: The Energy and Commerce Committee will have votes this Wednesday — Rep. Rush and I will propose amendments to their plan for the coming Congress to require hearings on these issues. We may be defeated, but to vote against even having hearings? Imagine having that on your record. washingtonpostDOTcom/blogs/wonkblog/wp/2013/02/05/can-congress-ever-agree-on-climate-change-an-interview-with-henry-waxman/</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360123106839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:58:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360123639291-34</Id><Title>California Adopts Low-Carbon Fuel Standard</Title><Msg>California Adopts Low-Carbon Fuel Standard Measure Will Boost Biofuels Usage, State Agency Says 4/27/2009 12:05:00 PM Write a Letter to the Editor The California Air Resources Board has adopted a low-carbon fuel regulation that targets cutting greenhouse gas emissions from the state’s transportation fuels by 10% by the year 2020. The new regulation will boost biofuels production and usage and is aimed at diversifying the variety of fuels used for transportation, CARB said in a statement Thursday. CARB said that to produce the more than 1.5 billion gallons of biofuels that will be needed, more than 25 new biofuel facilities will have to be built, creating more than 3,000 new jobs, mostly in the state’s rural areas. Production of fuels within the state will also keep consumer dollars local by reducing the need to make fuel purchases from beyond its borders, the agency said. Seeking to enhance private sector and federal investment into alternative fuel production and distribution, California is also providing funding to assist in the early development and deployment of the most promising low-carbon fuels. ttnewsDOTcom/articles/basetemplate.aspx?storyid=21806&amp;t=California-Adopts-Low-Carbon-Fuel-Standard</Msg><Username>bluecheese4u</Username><Timestamp>1360123639291</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 23:07:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>